n
[Music]
he
n
[Music]
one we balling we ball we Bing don't
touch my balls go away go
away my balls children children my balls
my balls stop the ball play no more
balls are being tugged now enough balls
have been tugged off
I will swing my balls I will smack you
in the face go
away
stop why are you fighting about balls
for 15 minutes help Mom Mom her balls
are so big they hurting me you're
jealous huh yeah biggest balls here yeah
you're
jealous grow some freaking ball don't
hurt me don't hurt me the shy guy we
have shot we have we've scared the shy
guy
guy I don't talk to
girls take off that Mas baby let me see
that face let me kiss that
face
no Shy
Guy gosh you're the cutest shy guy I've
ever
seen o oh you
oo wow okay welcome everybody sorry it's
uh taken a little while my PC and my is
PR are acting up but seems fine now
we're playing on release day Mario Party
jambourine
y y and now I would like to hear
everybody's introductions let's start
with
SH I I I'm I'm Shi and
and my arch for H life mama told me not
to talk to girls cuz
they yeah what we are so
safe
no who's who's next Who's chasing me
what about me I'm a mole yeah the mole
yeah the mole you're not a girl I'm not
scared I'm a mole you're still you're
still digging are you digging some girls
up digging D dig dig dig trying to find
your dream wife I
see I already found it right my dream
wife I'm looking her right in in the
eyes what that our
mom the
dad the M are cuz you have to listen to
me now no my college flies they're all
going to go into
dirt I needed to start my Mining Company
no don't worry B you don't have to go to
college you can just be a
streamer oh yeah oh
yeah so yeah is Monty still digging to
this day she will never stop
digging Mo Marvin actually Marvin the
mole Marvin the mole oh yeah wait is it
not Monty it was Monty it's Monty but it
looks like a Marvin to me at this point
oh okay okay okay then bioo you're so
cute you got balls he I am tocky
people just like toad I
SP like down of May party oh oh oh
smoking are you going to talk like that
for the whole stream how long have you
been
smoking oh good toad
voice thank you my toad voice sounds
like
this that's a really good toad voice I
know I know I had a lot of practice with
Lu
Mansion there's a lot of talented Lu's
Mansion I hate them I hate them so
much they're really annoying in Luigi's
[Music]
Mansion but yeah that's crying that's
the group yeah we're going to play Mario
Party JY
yippe
yipp so where do we start is it over
here and where we originally were the
balloon the balloon
okay I'm ready for take off let's
go I'm excited maybe I should have
played
toad maybe all right we got to choose
like a map party party Shield is in
control uh does it say the levels or is
it uh are these the worlds my opponent
will be friends oh friends is the
world y roll Di
uh-huh three types of
spaces H mini games yeah
yeah wow the the typical I'm not reading
[Music]
this they got buddies and tomatoes and
that's it oh sounds
good easy all right you wanted like
medium difficulty right yeah which is
the M is so
cute oh this this green looking world oh
it's a Mario no handicap right oh no
handicap
yeah uh any party settings uh yeah
number of turns 10 so I think it was was
it usually very accurate minutes is is
about 2 hours so that's good yeah I
wonder how accurate that is okay all
right wing it let's
go y
they said 15 is
better oh 15 oh we we can do 15 we'll
see I think it's too late but we'll drag
it out the
room no no it's okay we'll drag it out
yeah yeah yeah yeah we can always we can
always play the mini games at the end
to as a filler right now this is our our
warmup yeah and they say it's really too
short
I mean we can we can always
restart we just start shut up can we
without closing the room I
wonder I don't know hold up can I say no
say no yeah just say
no I am not reading wo a 10 W 10 wait
can we just keep
playing it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter it's not Monopoly where you got
to be fast we're in cars
that's so cute
cute
a
a I've never been in cars before in a
Mario Party game I think that's cute
have you been in a car at all yeah not
driving though I'm
ready oh guess
ready
but can we now we can speed run this and
do two
things so
you know how to
drive I don't see an option to leave
maybe in sh's
like yeah somewhere okay we'll go back
to the
uh oh yeah okay
okay 15 will be better reach quitting
G clap over that was fun good thanks for
the party thanks for watching
that was good and I hit yeah hit the new
data hit new data
yeah oh good God he's going
over stop explaining we know it we know
it
already I'm surprised they did it
again okay this one 15 turns correct
yeah I think we can start with
opponent
yeah okay 15 start no motion just in
case anyone gets
sick all right start for real for real
let's
go yipp yipp Yi
yipp who gets to be the first
now can you get 10 Again Last this time
dang
it we restarted on
purpose to sabotage
yeah roll and
Raceway give us those
cars yappa yappa skippa ski no
oh the
same let's go my sh
balls
oh chase after me I don't get the pink
card ha yeah looks like it he's smack
first let's go I'm going to go to the
star purple so we got to watch this
every
time I guess so my
goodness so many animations all right
looks like we're going first here we go
here we go here we
go my turn I'm Daisy cuz I'm orange as
always I love playing daisy come on
don't disappoint me me today I always
lose in Mario Party so place your bets
now chat oh six good that's not
bad oh my God we're
zooming oh but a really normal feels
boring okay all won once okay my turn I
will talk like this on my turn oh oh
good luck let's go let's go
oh no oh but
it's wait wait oh look that's not to bad
could be
good yeah get it get
it oh
so you can afford the star now
yeah yeah Shy Guy you going the star
what the heck I'm going to be shy I'm
going to go find a
girl I hope find a girl out there you're
passing all the
girls come back what is this uhoh
huh
camera where are you going is that where
the ladies are oh I
guess you're so far going to find me a
away my turn I'm Monty mole I'm
ready bye wait I think that's the that's
the red
squid why am I so poor Monty you're not
going to get any girls with that amount
of
[Music]
money I'm sure there's some nice Mo who
be into
Monte what is wrong with
Monty blame it on the
Monty we got to win we got to destroy
her it on the crane crane game cran game
a crane game a fun we're trying to avoid
it yeah yeah okay ready there's not
really much to do here just just rolling
away got toid yeah I hope you're bad got
he but this seems I got a guy this seems
easy for you to
win I don't know you got to press you
got to press uh plus or minus oh I have
to press it oh we all we all let's go we
all press it
oh good God I wish I was the yellow shy
guy right
now run run run run run I just got a
regular Shy Guy everyone that's good run
won't you be satisfied with shy nice job
just take a shy guy a different Shy Guy
run run run run run come back come back
you getting regular
sh there's so many regular sh R run run
R I love how bad you
are don't run run don't
run are you color blind are you color
blind back to
[Music]
me here it's
over y let's go we got nothing out of
that y we did it I thought this would be
easier for you now it's so
hard you have to anticipate it yay sorry
Monty looks like we'll be getting the
[\h__\h] no Please Please The
[Music]
Woman My
Wife you're you're the you're the
underdog the under mole right now don't
worry yeah yeah you they'll never expect
me to start
digging okay where where are we going
going oh the
shop
shopping shop is always
good
ooh I think I'll go I don't want to buy
too much I don't want to spend too much
money but maybe a triple dice to get
further ahead
I'm anyway at
20 oh so now I can't afford it but it's
okay I probably won't get the first star
oh you got lucky oh there you go
yeah creepy
dice give
me what's a creepy
dice find the star
again go further
please okay I love
four wait is that
we're
together time to flirt like giggy do
your
best um she's right next to
you oh okay I see youall no no no s
you're not related by blood don't
worry oh okay nice big balls you have no
don't touch my balls D I'm going to
touch
never mind never mind wow don't leave
leave like
go bye bye I'm going to purchase I'm
going to spend all my money oh that's
very smart of course yes I love
RNG can't wait what did you buy what the
pie the pie oh the pie oh yeah who knows
where go random it's a hole in the
ground you love holes in the ground
don't you I love digging
mini mini game mini
game oh
sorry okay orange Purple
Gang produce who are we producing oh is
this who's producing
who what's this the sort the fruit pick
up work together to send
ban that oh I get it banana thank you
all right let's go game now but what if
an apple Falls in are they sorting out
the apples on their own oh yeah the
apples go on the middle apples go in the
middle oh I didn't see that oh God this
is stressful no she puts it the ping the
oh
sorry okay
okay so you got to grab the
watermelon yeah yeah yeah okay and then
apples in the middle I got the bananas I
am red those bananas Queen let's do this
I'm probably going to give me that
banana Queen too badly oh yeah I I get
bananas thank you banana in the middle
banana in the middle
sorry it's okay I wasn't ready for it we
got the banana here I got it oh okay
watermelon watermelon good good good
apple no why is she put it back
noon watermelon watermelon
banana in the middle banana coming for
you that was so
short that was so
short why didn't we get a full minute
yeah I wanted more time I was just
getting into
it oh again again
nice oh man
okay moving up moving on up but I like
how they they read the room and put us
into to the teams that I was hoping for
oh yeah oh
yi
yi oh we got to make an
[Music]
extinct copy item it you pass uh you get
to do all kinds of things twice
oh when when we have how do we get
him think he has to run him
over oh we got to get
Yi is he all the way over there
he'll be mine he'll be mine he's the
kind of guy I like he's so far the last
of his
kind no no I need to get your it'll be
yours eventually they they'll teleport
yeah
two no it's the other it's the other
one that's where you left I see
yeah that's fine I'll take you slowly
not bad woo now we're together again oh
no not
again let's see uh
mushroom two dce three dyce four
dce custom o custom's useful
yeah which one which
one I want to take
I want to take four dice to move fast
four
di got to go fast huh Sonic
Speed we'll only stop for Crossroads
not hi Dad oh no welcome to my
Square let me know if you need
HR H HR don't call HR we I'm not
harassing anyone we need family
counseling
uh um wait what is the
exclamation Oh I don't know what it
means an event
Advent oh oh oh oh do I have
to oh no I'm going to get run over a
monster
truck oh that's a good thing me
actually you stop but closer to
Yoshi you can get Yoshi yeah not bad I
mean I guess I'll have
[Laughter]
to would you have had the money anyway
yeah if it's 20 coins anyway oh well the
first star doesn't
count I can't afford the star I'm going
for
luck give me something cool and I need
them bag oh nice just one you just get
one item no no enough oh oh I a
two oh no they're going to be a thief oh
so many
TR oh my go they're helping you be
careful with where you're putting that
get double the coins oh Now's the
Time m
M hot cross FL what's that oh hot cross
the floor is lava oh the floor is
lava build the you chose the same block
as someone else no one gets it oh it's
like gambling how do we how
what oh I see all so you pick you pick
which path you want but if you pick this
same path as somebody else then you
don't neither you get it oh and then you
don't move on okay I like this it's
interesting
oh how do you ose a path you use a
joystick oh yeah on the right side you
you choose the uh button that's the one
that you want like up is the first
pattern oh the right button I see oh
okay okay okay I guess I get it okay it
works with the x a I end with the d-pad
I
guess oh I think it only works for my
right
side all right all
right everyone go for the three go for
the 3
one nice nice nice
nice
o
huh I made my
de G no why are you sabotaging me I'm
not I'm
not come on I'm going for I'm going I'm
going no you stop why is so orange why
so orange stop being so orange okay I'm
going for it again I'm going for the
same one no no no don't don't don't
please
don't
stop okay okay okay what are you going
for I I think I know which one you're
going for I'm I'm going for the to I'm
going for
the why
did I I every time know Mind Games man I
don't have time to pay attention to your
needy
child I don't have I'm trying to pick
the same one Ki was
picking I was trying to pick the ones
that I thought would be unpopular but oh
well it was unfortunately popular with
the GG
I'm kind of happy about it really oh
crap he's only there for two turns you
should got get there fast we failed
together all right um actually wait how
far you're 13 what's the board looking
the board the board looking like
[Music]
a well with a triple dice I think I
could get to 13
right probably be able to
unless you roll really
bad that's the story of my life it's
highly likely come on let's let's
see that's oh there you go another nine
oh okay I'm going to make it two then
she'll get in a high number you made
there barely barely
though okay wa wait wa we're going up
right I'm going
up oh a this doesn't mean anything girls
don't worry I will lose so fast no
you're going to win today m- yeah mm but
I'm happy to have this one you guys will
probably steal it from me won't you no I
I don't know I think only gii can do
that please don't steal I will I will
never steal she has she has a star
stealing item I think yeah it's a trap
right it's a trap so if you land on it I
think oh the star is moving
oh where are we
going oh up there okay wait I think I
can make it if I use the four maybe
probably M many stars to be had many
stars to be
had 12 okay I'm going to use oh the
turbo D turbo D two two two let's
go one oh wow Hot Wheels
Hot
Wheels uhhuh all 10 okay you're doing it
let's
go I made it I made it I made it 19
let's go let's go look like we are
starless right this yeah this
way wo wait
I wait wait wait what what to land
perfectly on it no no no what you don't
have to wait what oh where is the star
then what maybe maybe it's there maybe
we miscalculate it yeah maybe it's at
the other side yeah yeah look at the
board I too need to figure it out stop
anything oh I even read that Al loud but
I didn't understand oh I can't go
actually oh that wasn't as good as we
thought it was maybe I can at least get
maybe oh
no oh dang hey I am an itemless shy guy
I need my help oh po please don't
believe me I love
po wait wait wait why can't I second one
because you don't have 50 coins with 50
coins you could steal a star now you can
only steal money s more oh yeah dang it
I'm poor all right uh I love you Bab
[Applause]
she's so
richo hello liy licky licky your oh
spicy only 10 yeah it's only 10 you were
lick for the service you were licking
her her her I provided a good service
today hi
be have to face the shame that I just
felt
where do I place
this place it in front of kiaha what
okay oh I can't I can only place it oh
within your area yeah my
area okay I'm randomly tossing it right
here oh we we will we know okay I wonder
do we have to land on it or do it is it
it's not going to happen when we just
pass by right yeah okay oh my God that's
scary
Oh
yay
item yo you have no money though I
I'm Min
game we going to have teams or what
[Applause]
oh don't do the crank please cookie C
you love cookie cter don't you oh yeah
cookie oh they were they replied to you
I saw that before so cute they love you
I love you Cookie Run Kingdom H wait we
have to choose the AHA yeah oh okay
everybody so shy has to cut and then I
have to cut and then has to cut oh God
yeah yeah so we got to be fast order a
yeah it's good to remember your
shape yeah just think about only your
shape okay I all all right
okay we're good we're good please give
me the same shape as
before good luck GG you have to manage
all of it oh God you can do it you can
do it all right I'm star I'm star okay
I'm toad or
mushroom you were too fast okay okay
okay okay smooth smooth
smooth
smoo oh I'm so glad I don't have much
work let's go
no are we fast yeah yeah I think
so can we get
faster oh go
go we did it do we do it how
many so cute I want to
eat who who won
[Applause]
y I'm stealing her cookies
congratulations professional cookie
cutter yeah it's
experience cookie R kingom you deserve
it rich enough for it you deserve it you
need four more coins at least just don't
roll for the just don't get to the star
now yeah yeah yeah yeah just try to roll
low I have to roll low roll low
H where am I and where is everything
else uhhuh uh you're the top player I
don't think you get the star cuz it's
sort of yeah I know I I just want to
make sure I'm not like anywhere
dangerous all right here we go but the
Trap is very far away CH oh dang here we
go I'm in a hurry in a hurry but just a
normal field come on
[Music]
okay I just go Qui get Yosi oh
nice you're almost there
Yosi you sto right in front of him right
in front of him give me an idem what's
that creepy use it on a player to
something something I can use on someone
[Music]
M what I got no hope anywhere
so whatever I got four I'm a four shy
guy oh
God goodbye
Shi alone what's going on I'm
guys oh no maybe he'll take
P oh I want Bowser
revolution
revolution come on come on
oh that's the wor I got I got to Le you
guys
[Applause]
welcome why did you do
this you want us all to sh name no no G
has even less coins for the
star now I can get all the [\h__\h] at
least financially
but he didn't give them to you right no
no
yeah is this everywhere possibly the
first the worst outcome might as well
maybe Bowser Revolution would have been
worse oh what you're going to replace
the lucky one what if I land on it cross
your own thing won't you I hope you land
on it no I can't afford the star
everywhere I can't afford it I'm
broke I don't think you could afford it
either before
could don't worry that'll be a big
comeback for you oh
yeah is the guys on the CR oh oh youly
flying
object oh it's like the crane game again
but not really oh
oh oh I'm
scared hey let me practice more and jump
move and jump okay as long as one of us
survives then we shall be good survive
we have to survive cuz she took 10 coins
from
us let's
go Lu sh in your uh uh in your purple EO
no no wait ah
I was pressing B
to please should
be uhoh oh
man
uh-oh I was trying to jump but I got
other side we have to split
it's time
[Laughter]
look how proud Daisy is of herself to
kill
[Music]
you oh you get your 10 coins back yay y
my 10 coins I win by doing nothing
y yeah you want your teamw
work thanks team oh wait oh you can get
him
still did you go
what is he gone is he just yeah yeah
he's gone for now
what that's fun he's only there for
three turns I think amazing left where
are we going I know he saw be about to
come like see what's up yeah sure let's
get some money
um sorry sorry you have yeah okay I I
got this i got this i got this i got
this i got this
Li them good oh yummy yummy tastes
mushroom still
10 thank you why do everybody want to
lick me so bad you guys want me so bad
yeah a little bit we want those Sports
kind of
wants I'm feeling funny right
now what is this feeling what's this use
on play to make it so the dice can only
oh I see
I'll wait I'll wait
for at the last moment right really if
only there was
Yoshi
Yoshi Yoshi
Yosi Yoshi Yi I'm just a shy guy got no
items and no
[\h__\h] no pictures
please I'm so shy a shy or
I go this way see oh see you oh oh
what's that what is that there another
shop it's is not red
M your turn Monty
mole your teeth are so be oh your one
tooth is so beautiful thank you I want
to rip it out of your face let me look
at the board maybe you can use it as a
xylophone Monty has been through a lot
let's not rip out his
teeth he has been through so much triple
dice where will I
[Music]
go you're so far
oh bad where did you think you're going
You're so far anywh
oh oh it's time
more who is getting lit I think even
though she has the most bu you should
lick people again
I I think
[Applause]
Ian art of us licking
beo so you're the you're the only edible
thing among
us no you're a you're a chicken I'm
Daisy no she's a human girl it would be
inappropriate are edible M are edible
everything is
edible maybe the mole but light wave
okay four
player ground
P oh God hey hey
oh oh well great oh no I'm not going to
I see I'm not going to win hey but so
when you're in the when you're jumping
normally when you're in the air you
press it again to ground pound yeah but
I did it and I think I landed on the on
one of those brain waves and then I fell
out of it okay we everyone ground pound
as much as possible yeah nothing beat a
ground pound to pretend it's your
mom yeah for
um I'm dying I'm dying oh because
there's it
oh oh
hi hello I guess I The timate Ground
Pounder for now the ultimate Ground
Pounder yes thank you for sacrificing
your
mothers it's very fitting that it's you
I
think cuz I'm a shy guy I have to Grand
p a mask on cuz I'm so shy oh new you
people always underestimate the shy
guy yeah they shouldn't
cuz he's so shy that's the
underdog oh was just a c all along where
are we going
Daisy somewhere good
free I'm going oh you can get a mushroom
if you go yeah yeah wait could I afford
30 to start nah
whatever I don't need it unless it
inreased oh okay I
mhm okay okay okay more curses to get
creepy M spooky month creepy
month W
10 10 oh
wow thank you you for that lap
bonus even more
coins more coins to lick off of her no
for me to be shy just a shy
guy I wonder what you're passing oh
shoot I hate myself I hate yeah what is
this let's fill up your tank oh why do
we have to fill up our tank items you
get three items for 10 no way I
guess that's
amazing Amazon welcome
oh W wao that's so worth it wow I feel
likey oh like got so
cute what a deal I want that deal thank
you I feel like a new man hey is it you
don't even have to land on it oh my God
you just it oh that's so worth it wow
I'm aiming for it my turn Monty the
mole oh Monty
just get all the girls I got to go this
way too
now you going to copy me oh but I
already I have an item already it's fine
two items is worth it yeah I think so
too see what you get Triple D
trip don't forget is is scary dangerous
it will not stop dangerous
oh luy oh coins coins coins coin
yes now the under dog is coming y
yeah the character Arc is there double
double let's go what four
player Oh money money give me money
that's like so much money
har uhhuh ahuh
oh cross the collect the coins oh ow
what
oh it's just like maple story oh it's a
jumping puzzle is it like maple story I
don't really know if it's yeah maple
story
to Okay jump jump just like map story
The Second
One camera move faster oh bye no no come
on sorry no wonder I always lose my
it's the pig it's the
pig I'm only good at getting money
anything
else we still get the money jump ping
the jump ping Monty D El gigy what
happened the jump ping it was the
P you experienced it too as she fell
down yeah could have been worse totally
yeah yeah the the the Ping
new see my parkour thing was accurate
she a parkour Mario Mario what Mario
what are you doing here oh my god oh
okay it's right next to you Shori oh
yeah you can get it
Shi yeah oh yeah I guess I could unless
it's your turn first no it's your turn
Face Where's My Luigi I'm Da I need my
Luigi get get rid of Mario I don't care
about
him let's see oh you're into the the
vacuum power I see no no I'm so over it
honestly oh okay everybody's pretty far
from the Star
huh I like how Mario's just standing
there asserting dominance down
there U should I curse someone is it
worth it I don't think it's worth it cuz
someone's going to get Mario no matter
what oh oh yeah items I was more like
thinking about the star but bib you
don't have a like a like a triple dice
or right there yeah but yeah you're not
going to I think you're not going to
make it I'm not going to make it cuz I
don't have any special dice or anything
yeah all right let's see let's play cool
cuz I've been licked enough thank you oh
you could be licked a little
more why won't it shoot
me I'm for
I'm not going to make it this
round it's a case go oh what's this uh
go
shopping oh they have a better they have
a
trap oh I do have trap yeah for you Star
Steel uh what's the that's too risky
though it's the it's the star stealing
one oh but I think it's too risky I'd
rather have
but I'd rather have the triple
dice
[Laughter]
yeah that nervous
laugh oh you passed it so
barely but you still got
punished oh at least Y get Mario now
Mario uh I don't want to I don't want to
risk it so I'm just going to
be I just feel like I'm going to get
really bad luck with my
rolles nah I just know it I just know
it oh I'm just a shy guy please let me
have a
GL Mario Mario Double the girl 16 girls
how long will he stay
with give you five he points too what a
man oh
what mini game to get so you don't
actually get
him
everyone you don't even get him
Advantage what the
heck why you suck
I
betrayal absolute
betrayal wow that we Mario carting or
what disgust me
Mayo what
what how cute we just having a good time
the much are we doing here your your
belly is so wobbly
G you want to touch it you want to rub
it it's good luck oh we
have oh please don't be
platform oh a this game wait what's this
game is this ah wait what why race
flag what is RA
[Music]
flag uh maybe if we're at the
top oh wait wait what why race FL play
it with a why do we flag oh flag you're
just racing to the top yeah does shiy
have an advantage because cuz it says
something about get three points from
the start play with
Advantage what do
yeah flag shoot freak more bumper balls
all right I'm familiar with all of these
do we have to push off Mario is this all
of it I feel like there could be a third
game yeah I think so repeat yeah
exactly oh oh maybe the race flag was
for a different
game cuz it's still the same controls
okay this is like the only one that we
can pump him with
uh ah wait the last game is shy guy
says so shei says I am not ready ah come
on is that the one is that the one with
st Advantage probably I think so come on
we want to see the last game can we all
just fall off it's just practice it's
just practice okay okay
see aha mat oh okay it will we know are
we guessing I have no idea oh how do I
how do I show it okay you got to press
left or right wrong right will be from
from our perspective what's on the right
so the white flag is right and the red
flag is
left yeah okay I think oh okay I killed
wait I don't get it what yeah I I
couldn't press the flag the flag yeah
you have to react pretty fast uh L and
R oh L and R okay okay free games in a
row is it is it is it reversed or is it
the same no it's just what do you mean
reverse it's um it's the same isn't it
if you press L it will be red and oh
okay yeah it's like what we see not not
from their perspective it's from our
perspective do you know what I mean well
yeah it's the yeah left is red and right
is white as far as I remember I'm to
fall off
one
our oh one more time
okay you want one okay I just really
wanted to beat his
balls but you got to react fast I guess
I don't know how much time we have to
react okay okay I see maybe he shoots
the one who who last put it up or the
one who only the ones who failed I
wasn't paying attention to the last one
actually oops
I actually thought I was the yellow shy
guy for some reason what was the jumper
ah you do have an advantage you get
three points from the start oh points
doesn't mean anything though oh I guess
be some point stuff okay okay okay let's
go I used to be good at this but not
good enough why are we going against
Mario
too it's cuz he hates everyone
true how cringe of Mario
I messed
up there
yeah everyone's so locked
in you really want
Mario
yeah I only failed once
yes come
on I play my leg oh we do get over
points okay okay okay okay all right all
right there there's a
chance let's go next one the bounce ball
bble is the ball girl we must
get still higher than me she still
higher than she oh but I don't have the
gamer Lu stop bullying
me don't worry I don't think anyone's
bullying you right now why are you being
Mario up it makes no sense we're balling
we're Bing to like Pi part in the event
let's bully
Mario Mario this is your stupid thing
yeah let's get rid of Mario first come
on yeah let's get rid of him I hate him
get out Mario get him out of here Peach
and Peach and Bowser instead yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we almost had
Himes peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches peaches peaches peaches are we
still going for Mario you get him get
him I'm scared him we got him okay how
do you know like if you get the points
you just live I think you just live yeah
what if we just like stop rolling no no
no no I can't trust you guys I can't you
guys best
anxiety I'll get
youy to kill me that was really not
intentional trust issues guys no
no
wow so many points
why she is going to get
Mario no no I'm not no I'm not oh God
okay you will you will left is red right
is your believe uh red is L yeah which
one's L again uh
red bye
[Music]
R so how long does this go
for I don't know someone I guess
infinitely
what's wrong with him what I didn't know
I thought you both of them yeah I pr I
press I did I pressed both but he
registered red thank God what wrong that
is so mean what's wrong with guys good
Lu Mario I hate
him what up now we know he'll pull a
fast one on us I know Mario byebye screw
you Mario I hope you get [\h__\h] I don't
trust him anymore I
I are you sure I oh no I was waiting for
him because the trust
isue I to change
it okay wow what am I am I I think you
might have a chance you might get like
13 to win
because yeah my my advantage really you
Mario I
hate oh she only left my room see she
was so shy she just I was so mad I was
so mad she's like now you may want to be
with me now but I'm out of here mm-
[Music]
fall mine if an opponent passes you your
ally will go with
de not even loal why Mario has some not
even loal what the heck he has some
serious commitment issues oh oh wait
wait wait I know but that's so
stupid after fighting so hard for him he
still won't commit to you he's a FAL
commitment what's the
point oh my God like he's better than
mon at
least I thank God I'm committed to
Luigi well it's committed to you is the
question of course he
is oh you can buy too cuz you have Mario
wow oh but yeah you have your wait does
he does it give you
two I already took it it's fine shote
are you going to try re-entering the
room later when you're done with your
turn uh sure yeah
okay oh that's weird I think my my uh
body app actually closed
ah yeah it's okay you'll come back I
have to get rid of an item you don't
have you can pass can't you maybe not I
think I have too many items I think
that's the issue oh you have to get rid
of one get rid of the curse it's not
that good I think uh yeah I'll get rid
of it actually I don't really need
it I think I almost landed at your trap
cucumber I'm going to get
push okay okay I'll join
soon Mony time
turbo Turbo die
goori
Mario you unloyal you already have so
they have no stars I don't think Mario
was ever loyal to Monty you won't get
him now
wait wait if you if you go too fast will
you pass yeah I'll pass the star wait do
I well Mario doesn't want to come with
me I
guess I wonder if you have to land on
the same
space I don't know rules
unclear rules were unclear I I think you
don't have to land on the same space but
the turbo just passes everything except
Crossing passes everything
crazy when will we learn I'm trying to
see where I'm going she is so big here
cute if I go this way where do I land
okay everyone watch me do the sick drive
by what was the
point okay but wasn't it really
cool it was really
I love how you're just failing it's
hot thank you it makes me it makes me
really excited for your comeback oh oh
oh okay be boo all
alone said are we shooting are we
shooting let me shoot them look in the
wild oh yeah move oh we have to hit you
uh steering up to try to hit them we
have if any of the
on the team five rounds they all win
we're not supposed to hit them all right
good luck
GG
okay oh I see I mean easy
enough okay hope we stay alive I think
it will be more difficult for people
once there's less people on the
field in the beginning it's you can
still hit more of us good luck
I like the strategy very
bold moov
time all right sh you got this Mind
Games m
game it's really too far
break those ankles don't leave it to the
shy guy I'm too shy that was funny oh my
God good job you got more cash good
job good good mind games I like how only
one of us has a star up until
all it will change I think later in the
game the stars get easier don't they and
the items in item shop get better and
stuff so you get stars and three stars
okay board check
again uh oh
oh oh is that someone
nearby I think
beibs oh you going to use it on
me you're the closest and you have money
do you have to use it on
[Music]
me
okay ladies this is this is actually
good because I kind of want to pass me
oh to see what happens wait I thought it
had to be the other way around it's an
experiment I have to pass you oh ah
finally if you're not careful shiori can
buy the star twice oh why can't I buy
this
oh cuz of Mario oh
oh oh no how do you even land on the
star it has to be a perfect land right
no just pass no you just pass
oh oh but you just can't turbo pass I
assume wait no way she can buy twice no
way no way think I can if I end up bu
car oh I can't it's in a yeah they said
that you can buy it if you have an ally
no way no way I should have stopped
her no way no way well I yeah you should
have stopped St it's okay I'm going to
are you gonna stop her
okaying this star no way wow oh my God
on the shy guy huh I don't even know
where I am on the
map oh that's crazy an ally is
crazy yeah well this is how in the late
game you get more stars get an allyy
wow 50 memberships thank you so much
everybody's getting
memberships yipp oh boy all the Pebbles
all the no lights giggy what are your
fans called
again GRS y all getting memberships
today I was getting a membership yay
cute so so
wholesome what are you going to do I
have no
idea uh I I don't know how the creepy
block works I assume like each roll is
stuck essentially yes each roll
is you can't negate it with uh you can't
negate it no o even with the mushroom
thingy even with the mushroom you can't
guess I'll try
it wait but you if you you're you're
going to pass the it can wait I thought
I I don't know how I don't know how to
Game Works can it cancels it but you've
got to I don't know how this game
workso not again she turo she's turboing
out of there but if he turbo you can't
like have the star though right yeah you
can't have the star that makes no sense
this game sucks
that what oh I know he's going to add a
few what what oh he go so
far W okay uh I guess I'm going to pass
the
star we can I get out of this actually I
know I know what to do then I guess
maybe you'll be close to the next
star I can't believe
it we already had a couple of good
examples of how this works this happen
three times
already how do we not learn from this
I am
starless where am I on the
board I see all right guys watch this
where my head there's no telling where
I'll
go oh there's just no telling dig dig
dig
oh wait where is this where is this
where am I I have no idea the top no the
Middle Lane top left F St four the star
star
[Laughter]
star where is it me you got your first
star oh no welcome back to
the why are you so
cursed I I was hoping you would be the
underdog and now would be your comeback
no
no I I have a I have a chance you have
so many tur have a chance I
believe oh what what is this match the
correct key to the correct gate does
mean what does it mean why what
what you choose
the so we just guess oh I guess you
guess oh WR what you die
ah and then since you already tried I
know that it's not this one so I could
try that
one
okay oh but there's three different
Gates so the one you chose might work on
a different gate
M okay this takes a while to figure out
or you got to get lucky yeah just get
lucky hurts my
brain too much guess you're winging it
yeah yes RNG and
memory that's not even boo that's like
discount boo who is this what is that
ghost Emoji looking I want to go
last okay I go what if I get really
lucky yeah Diamond that would be crazy
Diamond middle Diamond
middle okay dang it wasn't it
diamond
midle oh diamond
diamond right
right we're still get to play okay oh
you still get to
play
triangle
Middle
come what why are you so lucky
oh you didn't want to go
last I thought that would
help B was going to make it it goes in
the square hole the square the square
hole I wonder I wonder which one it
could be wonder what it could be is it
this one no
[Music]
way finish that's crazy Square Hall you
get locked out you lock the cemetery mom
let me in I know how it's night time yay
should have chosen the right
[Laughter]
King what a game can't even afford the
real
boo lame new turn new turn oh my God
only five rounds left oh I think so far
you're
winning you land on trap it's definitely
going to change she got sent magically
onto it oh so it doesn't affect me oh
yeah I think she has to land directly on
it not Dam I haven't had an item in a
million years oh my
god oh okay no problem we near to start
I think okay I going to you I going to
use the item because I'm
scared scared of what this everybody
everybody six to Star b gets her star oh
I got it okay you'll definitely get easy
thank God it's not a turbo or look at
that you're
y y is oh let's go finally another star
owner another star
another
GG it's okay we'll get our turn we'll
get a star too up us with a star where
is it going star rush time it's up there
OHA can get it I could but you girls are
going to stop me aren't you uhoh uh damn
it Mario
wait who do I steal you can only steal a
star from
someone well it's just 10 coins that you
can
steal you can't get anyone from
yeah got to save those 50 coins and you
can steal a
star well K is close to the star right
yeah but even if you steal my money I I
still have enough money yeah that's true
what if Mario takes it too
oh yeah let's try it
Mario Mario this lying cheat
what
oh I didn't realize I could mash the
button to get rid of him oh cuz I didn't
Mash
enough okay then
Mario that's fine Mario
oh I can do someone
else waa Mario does get another turn oh
I
see you're going
[Music]
twice yum
yum oh I messed really hard oh she
messed so hard she's still had enough
for the
[Laughter]
St what a cheater so disloyal oh give me
the luck
one I see I see I see there's so much
competition feeling going
on I know the last out
here no more friendship no more
ball interactions oh I get a
second Mario's crazy I
know oh Mario
Mario Mario I'm sick of you Mario loyal
man don't you already win enough in life
you get so many games just for yourself
give some games to Luigi or or or Daisy
or I don't know shy guy give Shy Guy a
game or Monty yeah give me some
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] Luigi has some games give valigi
some
games or Donkey Kong needs a Donkey Kong
needs a new game
poor Donkey Kong completely forgotten by
Nintendo oh you can cancel out her star
you can cancel out her star if you if
you I'm going
for
she someone has to win it has to be
Kiara y
yes wi never betrays me
here what is going
on has to be shy
sometimes and you are shy of
winning damn Legendary Legendary move I
thought I was
doomed I might still be
doomed take everyone
down come on let's go m
[Music]
poal Oh yay yummy
coins yay
no I can't have
[Music]
anything I think you you were just too
happy and too blessed in seven days to
die oh we're together again I don't want
to be with
SH have to suck it up can I lose on
purpose I'm going to lose on purpose oh
they're they're fighting orange team
strong what is this what is oh I see I
don't actually see it honestly well gy
our strategy will be you'll always try
to get the top part
okay uh wait let me oh you have to get
the bottom part
sorry wait or maybe maybe we can match
this one overlap I over I have to put do
overlab oh is it a different one how
about you stay still if you want the
thing no wait move to the ah we have
have
too no no no no you have to we have to
make the shape in the middle sori the
make the shape in the middle see and you
over sexy very sexy what is that a
hexagon you want uh should I stay still
in your match if you're faster with like
noticing things well you you have to you
have to
ready I'm still really slow on
this I don't know what's going on wait
we already no this is still practice
okay uh you can do it you make this shap
I the the open circle
yeah like this
oh that's a difficult
one okay sh are you are you ready uhoh I
can we can Wing It bio wants to lose
anyway no no she's a
she's going to suck it up she's the
gamer yeah yeah you're gaming we're all
gaming right
now okay I forgive
you she already forgives you for giving
the
star I'm going to do the the that one
okay here we
go good thing we learned how to make
that I the bottom uh wait oh God wa you
you were there yay he go sorry sorry
sorrys and I'm going to do that okay
where's the top where's the top oh let's
go let's go let's go let's go okay oh
uhoh bro I'm really really stupid can
you find the bottom
oh almost
pman [\h__\h] I don't understand
[Music]
[\h__\h] orange girls let's go orange
forever winning beams what are you going
to
do
[Music]
cry oh no I'm getting bullied so hard I
don't even know what I did to
everybody there
there home stretch home stretch the home
stretch uh uh everything's going to get
harder now make it very obvious Toad
thank you
M we're fired up oh yeah oh okay coin oh
less
coin an event special
event
oh oh
oh more even
more wait you can lose so much
[Applause]
money wait what did what did he say
about Star Steel traps are they going to
be double two I think they're going to
be double two I think so uhoh byebye
by by Mario you had enough luck with me
he
says well really he was messing with
you well I can't make it cuz well
obviously it won't be enough and I don't
have
enough
11 ah you mean money I I I mean yeah I I
would have enough money but where should
I go
doesn't matter I'll go
here o the coins ooh so many coin is
that the opposite way of the star
I let's
go wow you're rich wow well I mean I
think we're all going to get rich now
bad feeling either we're going to get
rich or really
broke don't land on the okay
don't land on the red one oh items oh
there you you got items yes so many
items yeah I moved away from the because
I thought I wouldn't I guess I could
have made it next
round oops stay there oh a turbo dice
turbo dice I'm cooking I'm totally
[Music]
cooking I don't want to be a Target chat
I just don't want to be a
Target all set oh coin give me coin
thank
you
go okay let me look at the board
sh all right sh far
away sh
shella oh girls terrify me
Oh yay oh
nice yeah not
bad yeah it's
decent you get items too yeah get items
that's lose coins though oh I want them
too never have enough for the a star are
point you have enough right now well if
I lose it's going to be no you're going
to win from the mini game mhm no no
you're going to win you're going to come
out at the top T I believe in you the
underdog there's still a chance for the
underdog you know who's not going to
win's not going to
win you're winning against Jeep for
now no offense Jeep no we're tied we're
tied
yeah
cool yay
it you got
money let's buy
something it makes
sense but I think this is the funner
way chaos
uhoh now I have so many places to put
this
ooh yeah it looks like
it
yay what do I get oh and you get items
again and oh just coins the best thing
would that you get a star soon uh gy and
then next round you land on your own
Star Steel trap that would be so funny
do it for the
entertainment do it no Lumber tumble
lumber l tumble Lumber ooh
tum Lumber you love trees oh we just run
away oh trees trees trees okay
yeah there's uh can we jump what we what
hey whoo whoa
okay we just shouldn't get pushed into
the water okay but we can't get stomped
or
anything why they chasing us
around they want tired of so mean oh
that's so pretty though they're here to
TU on your balls
no shy you're kind the shy guys they're
kind of mean to us
are you are you a secret spy sorry are
they all shyy maybe I'm spy guy spy guy
spy guy it was a typo all what if I was
a Fall
Guy cuz I'm falling for
you
okay wow that was quite a good
line thank
you oh it's so it's crowded in here I
need less people here
I'm scared what what are they going to
[Music]
do all the way off he's so fast what are
they going to do oh God
crap
[\h__\h] wait I think you did it you
survived last yay look you can do it
Monty Monty is doing his best wow yay
y a little a bit of coins a wow I got
two
coins B boo you good yeah oh yeah I'm
good turns left you're still doing great
you're doing great I'm not sleepy I'm
playing with handheld
okay um myato there is lag I wish I just
could go back in time and make a
different Choice cuz now I'm 57 away I
could have gotten the star if I went up
you could have had two stars I thought
you girls would be like right behind me
and catch up and and go up there anyway
no that's my expectations I told you
we're going to
die a at least I get an
item okay coins coin steel
coins maybe with most coins you get a
star too turo turo turo
tur it's going to kill
me don't roll that high turbo rolls yeah
you get really low turbo rolls yeah yeah
yeah you'll hit you hit these L I don't
like the I don't like the peer
pressure there there turbo not peer
pressure I give it toer pressure cuz I'm
very impressionable no way you're
bullying
yourself now we just going to get low
turbor roll
I'm so impress this might be
good honestly I think you have yeah yeah
you yeah that's not too bad oh
[Music]
oh see
see
yeah is it up is it up it's up I think
follow W yeah I passed
it see follow the footsteps up your
wow being impressionable is your help
yay yeah as long as it's a good crowd a
good CR yeah good
crowd thank God you didn't uh you didn't
follow my Impressions or
whatever wow it's it's 12 out of 15 oh
my God oo oh
no bad and they're even capturing you in
4k when you're losing your money there
was a camera right there capturing your
face they saw the tears fall from my shy
guy mask uhoh where's uhoh oh it's a
trap well put here I don't even remember
where the old one was you you put one
before right yeah it's right in front of
me it's right in front of me oh wait so
it is visible still that's not a good
trap if I can still see it oh bonus wait
is it going to be everyone against
again I I guess oh
no let's win jump the gun jump the gun
what are we jumping we can't let them
have
weing what's this what the heck is
[Music]
this uh one fire to create a path
oh oh I see oh oh that's fun you have to
wait for me yeah oh you don't have to
make you can make a parkour pad you want
to be parkour good at parkour are you
good I I'll try my best oh it looks good
par parkour Park
no I was liveing to early I am the
parkour
Champion I see I see I see oh I like
this this is fun I will be the parkour
champion
can you make
that
almost this is oh and there's an
end
help there
Legend I'm going to
make for you okay civilization my life
though okay wait why am I oh okay we can
do it I'm glad I'm not
shooting why why did I
and I fell okay I'm going to keep going
okay yeah yeah can you make that that no
no I can I can I can make it make that
okay I can I can't make it you we're
going we're going we're going we're
going you going are you a parkour Pro
I'm going I'm going we're
going okay oh no okay okay keep going
keep going keep
going you can make it you can make it
you can make it you can make
it oh they did it oh
man Park hard we were chilling too much
yeah it's okay you did great though you
did really great you too you too thank
you we don't have star but we'll have
all the coins yeah we'll have all the
coins in our civilization all the
economy so messed
up we got to fix
this we we have to have most stars and
most money in this economy that's that's
just how it is we have to win one for
now I'll probably be for soon no no no
no no no you have to believe shii
believe in your sucess believe in the
Jeep believe in the beams no don't
believe it me that would not be a very
good
je what was the one in front of me I
just an oh battle oh
I I just want wait am I doing this alone
oh I guess you are I always I'm okay
Casino
[Music]
Casino this is mean oh it's a path
you're making a path to the item you
want ah oh God wait what am I which one
oh no I I didn't I didn't realiz I
thought I thought I was choosing the Big
Blocks not the in
between
whatever okay now you
know I guess now you know how that game
works go we paid
money wasn't explained well yeah those
games making her comeback give me double
oh I should have used the money one oh
well hey not a lot of
money oh 10 10 10 okay 10 10 right here
10 right here
it oh 10 coins I'm I'm always there
lucky you're right about
there event is it going to move me oh no
it's going to move you
[Music]
no no oh my God wait can I just can you
just do I I it
no they do have scared
me people people are you okay I'm
okay oh no it's just how be it's it's a
d dog world out here yeah it's a it's a
hardcore
yeah this game party life this game is
just meant to destroy my unfortunate
mild party life you can still get maybe
like a star or two actually yeah yeah I
I there's also the the the the extra
star
rewards for most mini games one and so
on yeah yeah no I'm just happy to be
here yay yeah there you go positivity
giggy are you eating
I'm eating my nerd gummy
cluster did you know that that the red
dye in your nerd gummy cluster is made
from uh dried up crushed bug carcasses
oh yes y we
bugs yes you're eating bugs yeah yes I
have eaten a bug once and
I bugs that are that are very very
commonly used red dyee cuz they do it's
a really red pigment when they get
crushed up so
youg
it's I look it up hold on I hope then
bugs or save oh dang this is your first
star Could It Be I'm not going to make
it oh no you you might have a chance
it's a c c oh you can get a SM Ora coin
okay I'm going to get a star right here
oh man yeah are you getting the oh wait
wait one of those is oh no no no I don't
want to be no I don't want to be on my
own no cage in C cage I get in the cage
in that cage kitten we're going to be in
the cage oh no what's this swim you got
up down what oh okay you you're catching
me oh you're catching me okay I'm glad
I'm not the one
catching what what happens if I touch
the chip chip oh okay aha oh no I'm
ready oh this is a little hard with all
of us oh okay so gz is is pressing the
button I'm up and down your left leg CER
CER the fish saved me okay let's let's
do this let's do this oh this is hot no
more practice I know that's what I was
think let's do this let's do this come
ones really slowly locking in no locking
in is bad maybe I shouldn't lock in
maybe I'm worse than I lock in lock in
lock in lock in no not lock like that
H faster
faster wow you caught two fish two fish
no oh
God come here come
here the [\h__\h] fish the fish the
fish no I could have done it face you
didn't really
[Laughter]
it that that had so much potential
potential it was the evil
fish still first that'll change I've
been first for this whole game in the
last two rounds I will I will fall down
oh
don't get out of
here
W Nintendo didn't forget about you move
to
[Laughter]
great that's so
useful donkey K but but with Donkey Kong
do you still get like things twice
though at least yeah oh wait you do no
you you you do you always get two things
with a buy I don't like
though two traps next to each other give
me money if you ever reach this
please I think we're all pretty far from
Donkey Kong kind of oh I think I pass
him
already oh you might be kind of close
he's on that side don't
don't no no I don't want to I don't want
to people I don't want to give your I'm
scared
ofs how many co All In All In
don't F the problem is if I lose too
much money then shii will be first oh
yeah that's right well no no I think I
think you guys could actually steal from
me pretty soon so oh the
licking I'm scared she'll destroy
me
help oh god oh slapping game oh ground
pound slap and ground pound oh
oh oh oh
okay you're so
silly
what you just like getting slapped right
now
huh owie yeah like
that oh I see okay we can jump over it
too okay oh
interesting what of games reminds me of
akb48 ow
oh come
[Laughter]
on this is
tense oh no last last one it's the last
one I'm W make the
move's going to go
[Laughter]
I felt that one at the end when we were
waiting just do it do
it than 60 coins
wa wa so rich I
know I'm I'm exhausted got pity
coins I was playing for OBS I will say
now you might also get Donkey Kong I
think what is the oh Donkey Kong's
pretty oh I
see doco Donkey Kong Doo oh I see
okay why I don't know because come here
to see everything in one window I like
OBS also cuz I was too lazy to open it
up
separately yeah yeah you get Donkey Kong
I think he'll get Donkey Kong yay he'll
bring you to random it's a it's a mini
game Donkey Kong remember oh you can
take your star back yeah that's what I
was
thinking no she'll take it from me cuz
she hates it me no no because because if
uh what is it if Kiara comes here she's
coming here next so she's going to take
it back so I'm taking for shiori yeah I
figured give me my star you know she
doesn't have enough money at least get
right now I don't have but if she gets
it from the mini game then she could
steal it back from me so a
[Music]
true but there's no one else with a star
I
will
probably
yay a oh not
[Applause]
oh right everybody get a chance at
Donkey Kong oh yeah
yeah
I I don't want
Toom it's okay there's only one more
round or or two I don't know one one one
conga line k
conine cute what's this my God so cute
oh is this a rhythm game oh no I that'll
be fun it's a fun mini game but I don't
really want this
guy he can still steal Stars can or like
take two stars if you have the money if
he warps us correctly money uh how do
you even oh I see I hate mini I hate
rhym games I got pain issues
though yeah oh God
what no why not go I'm not winning this
I don't even wait can I do you have the
option of when to use
them uh otherwise it's just like oh
you're almost near a star you have to
this is a baby rhythm game I see still
too difficult for
me oh it doesn't always send it to the
same people yeah
a maybe I shouldn't be playing for
OBS yeah OBS and then ping
easy
oh oh it's slightly easier
okay oh it's bigger a bigger
ball
[Music]
interesting nothing
I hope I get
coins
[Music]
bro hi
oh yeah people's getting
it she's so far
[Music]
ahead
boaa okay good
oh I hate the pressure
oh clap clap clap yeah clap clap clap
clap
Kong wow she's got the
rainbow hey hey hey hey hey
hey the Rhythm I don't have a rhythm to
follow I you're too small hey hey hey
he yeah where is it
going more oh there's more there's more
oh no yes so
[Music]
over 100 at
least
[Music]
time oh no Donkey Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong R where is he sending
you send me how start give us some coins
at least for all that effort
oh he's probably gonna send you on the
last turn oh yeah
maybe uh give me
item always
happens it's okay he still has a turn
yeah he's still he's still he W he's
just send me somewhere send me
somewhere I guess it's next round for
you
you have 10 you 10 to to the start I
don't think I can I can get this
actually I would have to get 10 it's
just very
unlikely well you have a double you have
a double you hit you hit these you could
get there you could I guess I can try I
don't think I'll get it all right easy
10 I will I will go for easy easy
[Music]
J easy
time I see you're doing it
sh hey
y a shy guys I oh it's 20 okay the Spy I
guess so yeah ceiling is 50 and then
normal star is
yay you got a
star yayy you need a star too come on
all right don't worry I'm gambling for
mine is moving where is it going to move
oh uh I think you can get to
it where is it I went up where is it
it's over that was on the bridge
oh no no no no no I don't want to I
don't want
to it's okay I I'm not going to gamble
much I'm poor there's literally nothing
to gamble have my one
coin have my one coin
okay there's nothing to win nothing to
lose there's there's nothing to gamble
here yeah just a fun
time yeah yeah exactly they're there but
it still will count to the
game yeah I guess so oh you just got a
oh you can punch them by the way you can
punch them each other oh you can punch
each other come here B me a sandwich
I see how it is
push P
out here we go I love
marles they're so
pretty should we just stay here and
endlessly punch each other hey we're
only getting one coin out of this it
really does not matter no it matters
you're
PR coin how much do one coin matter to
you
let's go two
Co it's over I'm so insulted it's be
over good job I I will enjoy your two
coins you worked very hard for this may
you enjoy your new found
wealth I feel so much so much more
poor yeah all right this is where I get
my star watch this yeah oh you got this
you got this okay okay okay okay okay
okay I'm want to hit a star I going to
hit a star right here right here right
right now right now right now right okay
it's over it's
overed over I wonder if it's a
[Music]
5050 how could you lose with a 50/50
GG a 50/50 that 99 to one yeah who
knows oh they say it is 50/50 it's
over I
just yay money it was a really one6
really we'll never know we'll never
know all right bring it on granite
getaway Granite
getaway don't say it for Gran it oh oh
you why would we okay I was just going
to ask why why would we jump I guess how
do you jump uh
jump it did not work for me I am
dead here we go let's
go let's
go run
run oh I'm just a shy guy is this the
hold
ayg run I'm scared I'm
scared stop
pushing stop ping I so scared I'm so
scared it's so
scary it is
scary it's trying to kill
[Applause]
us let's go let's go help help no help
for you you oh
what stairs I hate stair there's
bat I'm scared of the bat we're too
good oh we're going to die now you
jinxed it no no why can't I jum I told
you I told you I can't j y did
it I'm happy to lose together with you
gy
we're together it was a 2v2 just like a
thumbnail
yeah oh oh see how far I've fallen Chad
all this time I was first the final
final turn all right all right I haven't
had an item this whole game except one
time I wish I had an item got to change
that huh well wait can I go to the item
shop now over there no where oh she
can't
Ste
no I could have won if I had three more
coins
sh we should
have you wouldn't have made anyway you
needed two more coins you should have
just donated three coins to
me you only gamble two coins wow you can
steal coins she does have a lot of money
I'll just take the
money Lick
[Music]
Lick time to Li the mushroom again 10
coins all
right I'm happy I'm happy to share you
can have some thank you oh and maybe
you'll get a boost from this
69 nice
yeah will you be teleported will I be
teleported is he going to bring me
somewhere got to he looks like he wants
to oh you can
Sho launch me oh somewhere
fun I thought he was going to punch you
out of the map you're going to get
rewarded for that I
feel where am I you of the
star oh W you get the star did
it it's a win and you get you get double
Stars I think you can have two stars
[\h__\h]
yeah it's do
story you get everyone stole from her
and now she's a
winner wait can donkey also buy or was
it al already no no he already counted I
think
okay oh oh my God don't I don't know
who's near there I think G I'm kind of
far still I
see I think I'm past it actually yeah
I'm right past the
start jump pad jump pad and never got to
jump with those
either I'm not experiencing this game to
its fullest I
feel seems like I need to play it again
sometime
soon yeah good that I already have
another have lined
up get more Mario party
again Shi what are you seeing with your
eyes your aming
eyes
oh I need to take my shrooms without
look
time I'm hungry you want one of my stars
sure I'll give you one
oh shoot I'm not going to get
it okay cool I actually was going to
take your star
though take my star you deserve I will I
will type of stars star in my eyes but
money I I get three times with one go
she licked me so much I hope look like
husband and wife I hope you will get uh
uh extra star for being the most licked
person in the
game please give me a licking star yeah
I got to go fight someone
now here we go oh for money is that the
last game thing depend on how I we we're
at the last match I don't think the
coins matter at this point well you if
be loses all of her coins you can win
yeah yeah oh it's a random block 40
coins yeah oh there's Granite getaway
again but they're doing snag the flags
snag the flags ooh I hate
Flags why what did they ever run around
and gra oh that's it oh okay oh can I
take one back I am I am kind of no you
can't take it back
okay oh okay this is pretty simple you
just move okay got it
[Music]
oh
wa hello any more flly
where are they all what are they oh man
I'm so bad at flag hunting remaining
five remaining two
now
oh remaining one oh I don't see it where
is it we're TI giggy we're
TI look like we're matching hi we're
matching again
it's a 2v2 it's a
dou
a what a fierce battle my poor we don't
have to share do
we oh we're
sharing good though very good very
wholesome very in sync give me my coins
had a good run look at the star that's
right behind
me the star is right
the story of your
life going oh you got a mushroom
mushroom it didn't even give me it was
the last
turn if only that was a backwards uh
like block thing yeah where's the
backwards block divers more money you
just get money yippe
yippe okay oh theyve the diver
how to open what are we bring it back up
spaming a wait how do you get the I
think you bring it back
up oh my God oh my God oh see
okay I wish I could steal your treasure
sh treasure
SPID they're bullying only free okay I
think we can start yeah you don't get
that many coins for this this mhm I mean
we're also on the final level
so let's go your butt's so
heavy yes
oh don't take my
coin please leave me alone I'm was just
a shy guy come on faster faster faster
F pick it up pick it up pick
it that's mine that's mine
I stop
you we still get the amount of coins
though yeah good yeah it's only six good
game that's such a little amount of
coins not worth our time that's not
worth it they should scale it is it over
it's over I guess so oh man that was
fun crazy stuff with Donkey Kong and
Mario I hate I hate them so much I love
Donkey Kong he was so helpful that's
that's not oh yeah yeah now look at my
look at me failing it's hard to tell
based on the graph alone but here shy
guy asked bu to steal a star from
Toadette
oh oh
oh to tell but so got two star two whole
Stars yeah now present the bonus Stars
bonus Stars B oh there's only one only
one who landed on it wa sh can
win I
think where's the lick star we need a
licking star
yeah sightseer B oh maybe a GG who
traveled the most I don't
know not TR so far oh I was I zoom I did
turbo twice yeah it was worth it in
hand that's it that's all that bonuses
give us more
bonuses the
bonuses wait are you still tied you two
on Stars I think so but on money maybe
not wait how did that
happen the underdog
story so
much what do you call an underdog who
who never ended up like getting out of
the underdog
status well at least shei has coins to
invest in business yeah I have so much
coins for my mining business yeah I use
so many I use So Many Items what do you
mean balance because I stayed the same
all the
time oh sides your oh uh-huh
what oh actually do I control this I
don't know who controls this right now
oh I'm I we can all control it we can
all control we can all see it oh I don't
know what these items mean so oh oh most
coins in total orange also B
boo most mini games won B
boo uh no yeah Showdown mini games
number of items
bought number reactions used great I'm a
winner let's go
winner you're so
reactive yeah I'm the winner the winner
the
winner okay wait I can't get out of this
menu can you
press we all
fam we did it what get party points
party points party points does only sh
get it cuz we're in her her party no I
think we all get it cuz you got it too
yeah oh oh achievements add insult to
injury why why would you do that who did
that
o oh oh unlockable oh is it a battle
pass do they have battle pass
oh
oh wao what are you getting oh new
inventory in stock what do we buy Pro
rules rules ah yay we got it to a safe
data what a PR the party Plaza can we
buy stuff
now it's over it's so
over we all
fil where are we going what are we
checking out I don't know can we buy
some where is the shop I guess we can't
do it in the
lobby to be in our
own I want to know what we get
H well okay then let's gather in the
middle okay the middle the the balloon
the balloon well we'll find you we'll
find you okay there y
y that was fun everybody y yeah than for
hosting congratulations on winning
people you did it after all the bullying
after all
the I so much maybe that's the the
secret you have to be
to win yes luy I guess let's tug on your
hair oh no my balls my balls give us
your balls BS we don't want your stars
we want your balls lucky balls we want
give me give me no to have a piece you
have like four pieces to share
some yeah well that was that was fun I
will play this again in the near future
Chad so keep an eye out on it for some
now you have now you have experience yes
which will not it will not help me trust
me you'll be a winner maybe H geky is in
the next collab too for some reason so
maybe think I'll L St no you will win
that time that's that's when the
Underdog Story finally Finds Its finale
this is not the end I didn't get a star
cuz I'm going to get a bunch of stars
next time yeah exactly it's the story
line you saved up the money for it yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah only to realize it
doesn't transfer to the next
game no I was saving it for Mario Party
[Music]
2 too bad oh well thank you girls for
joining me on this even
though it was all kind of scuffed behind
the scenes before we got started but
everything was smooth during it yipp
yipp yeah y y y thank you ispk you
ISP I appreciate it yeah I I I I feel
like we're all winners of course yeah
because we had a fun time together so I
won I won cuz I got licked by everything
not because of the stars but because I
got licked by everyone I friendship yes
I could agree with that I I want that
Yum Yum Yum to happen to me too now
suddenly I feel like that's how you get
lucky right gigy why you staying into
the into the abyss I'm going to jump no
don't
jump sorry sorry I just saw so much
water that I I want to be in
there the beaver what is Monty is Monty
a beaver yeah a am am yeah Bieber's
tails look different I guess yeah Bieber
would have a big ta yeah I think they
also have more teeth instead of just one
teeth oh yeah for the trees singular one
yeah all right then I I got to go make
dinner ladies and gentlemen
So yeah thank you so much that
was oh oh yeah wait gig birthday talk
about it talk about
my birthday is tomorrow we are having a
birthday party it's a very terrible
times for kiawa so
unfortunately I I I'm sorry that it's
not such a bad time no no no we had a
party right now a Mario
partyio this is the pre lost but it was
a birthday
party wait so when is it say it it is at
um 6:00 p.m. PST 9 p.m. EST 1000 p.m.
CST I don't know the rest of the time
zones 10 a.m. JS 10m jst hm is wait is
it tonight or tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow
oh okay well you guys more than 12 hours
make sure to be there for gig's first
birthday thank you it's going to be 1
year old I'm going to be one year
old okay happy birthday in advance happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
Sho happy birthday can I have a kiss
kiawa can that be my birthday gift can
you give me a kiss in front of
everyone of course I would do that any
time sorry sorry I I need to avert my
eyes let me get behind you sry I don't
want see get behind me I don't trust you
got to get behind you behind you I want
I can't see here hide hide okay I'm
hiding behind you okay now you can do it
okay I'm watching okay here I I I'll
bend down in your it won't show up but
I'm really bending
down I feel
it and for you
too kisses for
everybody I hide I hide
beibs why why you already got a kiss
it's too latey guys I thought you were
shy don't be so
shy woman
watchery so you're shielding me from the
kisses yeah I'm the shielding guy Shield
guy okay in German we say Al
in say it
[Music]
girls byebye
w
[Music]
he a