[Music]
this
who wrote that i don't know
wait i forgot where's the tree i was um
where's the trail was punching
oh my god
[Music]
wait where's my rock
where's my beloved trusted rock
there's my beloved trusted rock is it
here is this one
yes
okay
you
yeah i got wood
yeah
where's my okay here we go do we just
punch with rock or is it better to um
is it better to
okay it's eight
we're getting eight wood
yeah
i think x is good right because i read
of a little
okay nice
hit the x i'm hitting the x right i'm
getting like eight wood so i think i'm
doing good
i think i'm doing good
oh
oh my god how
how
how guys
i'm doing
yeah
oh there we go
oh nice okay
nice
okay one nice nice nice nice nice nice
okay okay okay okay
so they're saying like uh you know i
read up some survival guides on the
internet and they're saying
if i want to play rust i need to make a
lot of uh you know i need to harvest a
lot of wood you know
ah
guys oh my god so hard
math
oh my god
oh okay we need to be a little down okay
so it's not
okay
okay i know it i know where center is in
this game
i have to like do it like a little bit
lower
instead of like
instead of like aiming straight here for
example like the x is here i i can't do
this i need to like aim a little bit
down
i need to aim a little bit down
oh yes yes yes
yes yes yes nice
oh yes nice
pro
x
punch
puncher or i don't know with the rocks
yeah guys this is the quality rust
experience you guys are saying
[Music]
oh my god okay nice nice nice nice
are you so close so close
yes
go go
[Music]
so is this so is this the only thing we
do in this game what what i see i see my
gem mates they're like super i don't
know yeah they're they're they're really
they're really advanced you know they
have guns and stuff like that
why do i not have them why do i have a
rock you know what do i gotta do to
trade stuff with uh
what am i gonna do to like uh have guns
and have houses and have stuff
and then you can make an axe now
an axe wait no but but i was just
getting the hang of this
when i was just getting the hang of this
do i not need this anymore if i'm doing
the axe
oh come on
i need to work my way up to technology
what do you mean
guys
but your gen mate is judy addiction
i do star fingers
starving
if we're starving what do we do eat the
tree
eat mushrooms
but this is fun
oh that is broken yeah like my soul
with yeah
wait wait guys wait i will unbroke i
will unbreak chat
i will unbreak chat don't worry guys
don't worry you guys will be unbroken
soon
[Music]
the previous waiting room had like a a
really really pretty url it has omaye in
the url
oh yes
okay guys if we're starving what do we
eat mushroom
eat
[Music]
how do we eat the mushroom is this not
food
eat
eat ah do we torch the mushroom
oh my gosh
three to eat
oh
oh my god school okay let's let's uh
let's let's let's let's
um
cue to craft okay okay okay
common common common we make
x x x
uh tools tools
hammer
what's hammer
ha
hammer
but i want the axe
oiney
wooden spear for what
ah
maybe you need some stone for the axe
okay okay okay
yeah let's make hammer first
let's make hammers because obviously we
will need this
craft
we need 40 14 seconds
should we like make a house can we like
sleep
can we like sleep i don't know
like what happens when nighttime comes
what happens when nighttime comes guys
[Music]
nice
it becomes dark but other than that
nothing much okay okay okay
nice
this is so satisfying it's okay i'm
stuck in this prehistoric era
annoying
okay where's
where's my rock
where is it
oh
oh no
it's gone
where
where is it
can we just like take rocks that are why
am i starving
nice
nice hunger
[Music]
bye i guess no more rock
you can craft a new rock to mine with
really
listen learn to not throw the rock i
wish like they would give you uh you
know
come on
like where where did it fly to
so sad
okay um
oops
crafting
stone hatchet
ah we don't need
hatchet harvesting wood
we need stones
we need stones guys
stones where
did i soft fluff myself am i no longer
able to harvest
stuff
oh no
make a new stone what is this push
oh
it finds stones around what is this rock
or i don't have stones
in my area
where where's your house
[Music]
is always an option what do you do what
happens when you sudoku this is where i
first appeared
so we can try sudoku yes
oh my god so sad
it's at e10 your face is at e10
oh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
p8 is kiwama okay
now i have a new rock i gotta go towards
my corpse
there's no animals around here right
there's no wild animals like dangerous
wild animals that can attack me in the
night right
all right
i'm used to the darkness
it's good
you want
there's a bear i don't think there's
bears in beaches
p8 is kiwama let's see
huh wait
[Music]
where's where's where's p
oh it's so dark
okay
we're so close
we're so close to our dead body
so close to a dead body no i'm not gonna
use my torch because i am you know
don't you have a torch yes i do
but i'd rather
stay undetected if i can't see the wild
animals they can't see me
either right
html
and moomin
cool
okay
also how do you like chat how do you
like chat with people
oh look the moon's so beautiful today
um oh we're so close to our mount oh
this is the boat
where i first appeared
my dead body is so close
you have global chat enabled um i saw
kyla and zetta chatting earlier
so maybe
where's my dead body
oh
what is that a house
also where's my dead body
i don't see it
oh hi
oh sorry i mean uh loot
what do you press oh here
nice
okay
loot
nice
bye
okay um now we can uh grab some rocks
push to talk is beat like for example
hello ah nice nice nice nice nice
okay
that's great
oh no meat
sag
did you harvest your corpses who what is
that whose place is that
why is there like an established place
over there
hit your body what for
don't go to that house why
okay
okay i'm gonna
try to get some stone
to make
a hatchet or something
oh
[Music]
but these are metal oars not stones
where are the regular stones
i feel like i'm too advanced for this
i'm too advanced for my horse
[Music]
hey
wait one on the ground
all right
[Music]
oh let's try crouching
doesn't work either
i think
you know what
too stubby
there's somebody's house over there
[Music]
seems civilized
i don't know if i want to approach them
scared
um
[Music]
stones we don't have stones
hello
[Music]
you cannot gather anything here
huh
no not this one
hmm why is there scary music i don't
know
oh pick up
no
can't really pick it up
don't think so fine shiny stone okay
okay
okay there's civilization and i'm scared
so i'm oh what was that
that's a metal ore
i don't want a medal or i just want
i just want
um
i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm
hello
stone
are you here
hello
no not you
i need to know what they look like first
i'm like spamming e right now
in case i can like pick them up no i
can't pick any of these up i'm starving
already
it's okay
man living is tough
does your in-game vc work it should work
it should work uh but i'm on push to
talk right now
so um
yeah
it should work because um
i said it
no
these are sulfur oars
[Music]
no i want regular stones are these no
these are not stones either
these are
where
the quest for the stone
oh
stones what is this what is this
oh yes yes finally finally
oh my god
oh no
thank you
thank you stones
oh come on
there we go
these angles are
very
wait
oh thank you
i'm gonna gather all these stones
because stones are really hard to gather
[Music]
oh my god
okay there we go
[Laughter]
i'm going crazy
um this is for harvesting wood right
this is for what still a metal ore and
sulfur ore
okay i'm gonna craft this
okay and while we wait we should keep
harvesting this
okay
oh no okay
wow oh my gosh that feels so satisfying
cool
[Music]
no
oh
so cute
okay
nice
i'm starving oh my god i don't care i
can just like eat stones or something
ah
wow so
so difficult
nice oh my gosh i need to find mushrooms
or else i will die
you know you guys you guys please it's
difficult you guys are like it's the
singing but no it's not the center guys
sometimes it's like you know it leaves a
little bit of um
concentration
to hit it
and what's this
and this excuse me hemp fibers
are you food or your clothing
should we be dressed
or is it not important i don't think
shirts are important
but what is important is mushroom
[Music]
let's like eat oh my god
oh god okay okay
listen we are okay okay come on we oh we
are here in peace we just want food
it's like the mushrooms thank you
okay i don't know i don't have my
headphones like um the other way
but
here steps
no it's not the other way i'm i'm
starving still my goodness
why don't your footsteps
yo leave me alone
leave me alone i'm just i just wanna
gather wood
nice
oh okay
oh
okay
ah i'm starving though
oh sulfur orb this looks kind of
disgusting
okay eat eat
eat
um what do we do
we just like
punch trees until we die
see i'm getting better at this
and it's also it's way easier to aim
with this
[Music]
it's way easier to aim with
this oops
let's go
find resources then build your base um
kimono was telling me to build at
p where's p
so far
p-8
[Music]
the heck
ah
oh who are you
oh my god
hello
[Music]
can you hear me hi
yeah
okay nice nice nice
lead me to your house
it's so far it took me like 10 minutes
to come here well i'm 15.
i'm looking for you and you never showed
a map on your screen
i want to surprise you oh okay okay okay
oh well i am certainly surprised
but first uh
you need food let me give you food uh
here oh my god
okay can you hear my cats
should i turn on i'm on push to talk
right now should i just like release it
or i don't know
[Music]
i hear your cat how are you how are you
yeah
i think you gave me away
okay i think
options so audio maybe
on it
yeah i don't know
i don't know how to turn on how to turn
off push-to-talk
[Music]
it's like
it's in uh options controls
and then auto transmit voice
auto
transmit voice
doco
oh my god
doko is the auto transmit voice
[Music]
oh there you go
hello
hi
[Music]
oh my god i brought my cat outside
because she was just looking at the desk
ready to like climb up and i'm like no
[Music]
okay okay um you got you ate the food
did you eat the food yes
one
somewhere in i hear
an echo
of myself
[Music]
yeah you should turn off the stream
probably from you
i turned it off
test test
oh
do you hear maybe it's the
maybe it's my steam mic settings or
something
because i hear you but i also hear
myself coming from you i think
really weird
i mean hmm
i can i can um i can i can try to um
check the settings for
um for chat
yeah but that's apparently that's steam
settings because there's you can't
choose a microphone
in the settings of rest voice input
device should be
and then voice output device should be
okay i'll try default is it better now
try talking do you still hear me
yes this to her
i still uh
i still hear myself
okay what about now but like a second
a half a second delay or like i'm
half a half a second
that is so weird
do you hear me now
uh yeah i hear you i hear you
okay it probably doesn't change until
you restart it's okay i'll i'll try to
ignore my my self
oh
that's so annoying though let's uh let
me just like turn off
okay should we um
is it can we are we allowed to like use
discord or
no
oh hell yeah i did that yes yesterday
the day before yesterday with um because
i don't like the voice chat in here but
everybody uses it yeah i just can't
really figure out like how to make
the
yeah because over here it's like as
it's correct over here it's correct
oh
we can do this card yeah let's do it i'm
gonna go
mike picks up the speakers no i don't
care so
hmm
oh
oh oh never mind okay
wait i'm gonna turn off
moshimos wait i'm gonna turn off um auto
d this this thing
yes
okay um okay
oh my god
oh [\h__\h]
wait i missed
okay right away let's go scared okay
[Laughter]
okay it's a long way but uh follow me
and also i only played this game on
stream one
okay it's not like i know everything
about going super hard
[Music]
you can hit me once you can hit me once
to make it even you don't no no you
don't hear me double anymore right i
turn myself off in the game nope
okay okay
see it's a long way because i'm on full
screen so when i like switch back like
my character like swings yeah yeah yeah
i should just follow me now all right
it's a long way all right it could be
dangerous she'll hide behind me when
something happens okay
i will bring you to
the
horotoni area i guess you could smell a
lot of
foreign sorry area why are you so fast
not that
not the life oh oh you can uh if if you
press shift while running you are faster
okay nice nice nice
one dangerous thing if you ever hear
like a helicopter sound uh run for your
life
why
um or like take cover somewhere oh i see
because the helicopter once it sees you
even if you're under a tree or something
or if you stand in front of a window
even it's gonna shoot you down
no okay okay okay okay
uh and if you're like in an area that's
a safe zone the game will tell you
but if you're in that kind of area you
have to
take off your weapon
like just scroll up to a different item
that you have oh and then the warning
will go away are you following me yes
yes yes yes you're just really fast
pression yeah i am holding shift
no i really oh yeah i dropped weapons
didn't i told me i don't know if you
told you but yeah you weren't on the
weapon i guess uh-huh i'm holding the
stake this is a safe zone
inside here is a safe zone there's like
npcs
um giralis i don't know much about the
game i'm not the best person to like
answer your questions i still have
questions too i'll tweak some settings
because yeah um a little bit messed up
hold on
[Music]
chat
thank you sounds better now
okay
yeah i said i'm not the best person to
be asked questions about the game
because i don't know [\h__\h] it's okay
either we can um we can uh gamba do our
best
yeah
let's go for the safe zone i guess okay
it's so far it's like we're on the other
side of the map i went there because in
in my stream when i did rush first time
stream like two days ago
uh it was ahmed who showed me around a
bit so i moved to where she
lives
so far away
i'm probably gonna run through some snow
areas where it's gonna tell you that
you're cold but oh well you know what
[Music]
you can destroy certain uh eyes like
this
i need to wear heavier clothing
oh yeah i don't know how how important
that really is
i think at some point it does damage oh
wait there's a i just found a baseball
cap at least that could help oh okay you
take this
oh thank you put this on this will save
you from being cold even with my clothes
it told me i'm cold oh okay um where's
my where's the where's the baseball cap
huh okay
yeah nice
yeah
nice
okay
and i hope you won't die in the cold
yeah i mean if i die it's um
i don't know
we'll try to get through it fast yeah
six degrees when a bear follows you um
run
okay i'm already running here
yeah it's kind of like uh the bears are
as fast as you when you're running
but you
you can escape
just run the front or kill it
i'm killing my butt
i can throw rocks
oh
uh you can i mean at the moment looking
at your inventory um
i think
i don't know you could you could try
using the rock i guess so the the fire
or
even though
the stone acts that you'll make a
mushroom okay i don't think i should be
distracted
hi
who
chunkers just jumped off my my lap and
then jumped down again she keeps on
meowing
oh my god she's so talkative
yeah i recently talked so much when i
sit on my computer
i want your attention
oh [\h__\h] i'm sorry
[Music]
i'm uh
it's not like i don't give her attention
i'd give her so much attention
throughout the day
oh my god oh minus eight degrees i will
die in the no like real me will put that
uh
yeah we'll get you something to wear
okay um hem fibers that you picked up
those are used to make clothes i only
think they can also find clothes in like
right oh you can do ice skating here no
no okay
maybe
yeah um
i always destroy those because they have
scraps in them usually maybe you heard
of scraps
uh-huh yes scraps the thing that
everybody wants and then the things that
everybody uses because they're gambling
all the time yeah
oh in the distance i see um
i see something flying
[Music]
so uh the thing is that this weekend i
guess the server will be white yesterday
are you sending me a chat i don't know
how to chat oh my god
oh
let's just enter like in minecraft
i'm on my way to p8 was it
real that area
[Music]
p a p for p file
oh
okay
yeah but it's still far like even when
it sounds super close it's still usually
pretty far but
you have to once you hear it you have to
think about taking cover but you can see
it on the map moving oh really it's
currently going a different opposite
way than we are
[Music]
yeah i was like in my house at some
point
and it was like flying
quite a distance away but like also
higher than my house but still saw me
through my windows and then it shot down
my house and dropped like a bomb on my
house
[Music]
it was [\h__\h] terrifying
robotic kamala yeah kiara's a little bit
robotic here i think it's just i can
still hear you don't worry
yeah i am your body you are robot
chicken robo chicken
now look it's okay
uh yeah just like slightly it's not so
much that you're like i can't hear you
or nobody can hear you
just a little bit it's as if like chat
what's the what's the stall park quarry
is that a safe place to be at
oh my god there's a bear
yeah that's number's fine okay really
what what's this
what's that
oh
is it is it abandoned
looks abandoned no
where are we
i don't know where we are now even
it's dangerous follow me let's go to the
safe zone first okay okay i thought the
area was safe the the area before
oh
[Music]
safe but uh
you should come to where we live oh okay
ah did you eat the food that i gave you
you have to press the button on which uh
it's position yeah okay good because i
saw you're
very hungry yes it's okay taking care of
my people i'm no longer hungry thank you
for the meal
someone's like randy you're freezing and
i'm like and
i don't have clothes oh you can't go
through there
oh yeah
that's okay
is there fall damage in this game
yeah i think i felt it before but it's
um
i don't know how high it is to to get
how you have to be to get damaged
[Music]
okay we can try
i guess i can recycle that so what i
currently
do all the time or like did until you
started your stream
is i kept on going back and forth
between like an abandoned convenience
store
and my house and kept on like collecting
materials because um like every like
five minutes or so
they drop um
like automatically generated uh
items oh that's not convenience stores
and like other places i guess
yeah so keep on going there take some
stuff recycle some stuff get the scraps
go back to my place learn some recipes
man i already got it all figured out
sometimes you see these kind of
uh thingies
[Music]
and then there's some cool stuff inside
sometimes and sometimes not so cool
stuff but even if there's something in
there that you can't really use then you
can often just recycle it and then the
recycling will give you scraps and you
need the scraps oh anya's fp8 already
where are we
i am i'm coming we're almost there and
the helicopter is uh currently circling
close by so
fast
go fast go fastest going to the
supermarket
okay okay
yeah
it's not coming yet okay okay
i
gosh uh i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
chat uh coming
oh i see my house i think almost
yeah
we have arrived
we have a wife let's go
oh
it's not well i'll show you my house too
because i'm proud of it but let's first
say hi to anya
where's anya i see her
is that her
maybe it did i think that's a
hey
where's she going
is that that's her yeah yeah ah
i'm naked with uh
ho ho ho wait let me turn on here
hello
[Music]
i couldn't figure out the voice chat
because i keep hearing you know other
people can hear themselves from me even
though i somehow said it correctly
so i'm just using this chord so sad
i can't hear you though
he got a senpai but when you're talking
i think
i i think i'm the one echoing
because i heard myself from here too
from there too yeah
yeah i can't hear my own voice yeah i
don't know how to say it it feel good
because i i have no space in my house
wait wow i'm going to give you an smg
oh
spicy
here you could go
can i help you maybe two three two
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you thank you
minutes box
what what box but again we have 15
minutes box together but the thing is
usually there might be people and so you
will you have to be ready to like shoot
people who wants to get the box
oh
where where is the ball where where is
the ball i don't see it on the map yet
do you think it's dropping soon
yet but it should be dropped in a bit by
the helicopter can you see the
helicopter it should be going down
yeah yeah
i don't know if i'm ready
for that
no i think i'll just take care of reyna
for now so she can build a house
thank you
thank you thank you
thank
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't shoot at us she shoots you
crazy
i'm gonna eat i'm not gone where are you
oh i'm i'm taking cover i'm eating
oh yeah yeah eating helps um where are
you taking cover i don't see you oh i
see you i see you
ah wait okay yeah i'm down here this
house i'm standing by is i think
northern senpai's house
and then
over there where you're coming from
right now somewhere there is mummy and
lame house
and my house is over
here
i'm thirsty
i can give you something to train yeah
kfp
in front of my house this blue thing you
open it up
and then um
oh yeah you need to con
i think i know you push the icon that's
a drinking cup
yeah can you open that button more
options are available with e
ah
drink water
am i drinking
oh nice
it works it works nice you can drink
more okay i'll drink more
a little bit
nicer
okay good so let me show you my house
okay
because i put a lock on my door uh you
wouldn't be able to enter and let me
turn on the lights really quickly
[Laughter]
i'm going to drink
my thirsts
one's the second place you keep on
drinking if you want okay i'll i'll
drink as i wait
is this like unlimited water
no it's not unlimited i collected it
okay sorry sorry sorry i'll stop
drinking no it's relatively easy to get
water
okay
oh i hate it i see the helicopter
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is my place um what's kind of a
pain in the ass built uh
there's my sleeping bag there you need
to make a sleeping bag later because
it's uh it's like a
um
kind of like a save point when you die
you can respond where you put your
sleeping bag okay okay okay okay okay
mm-hmm and this is something that's
called a
a
thing
a thing i forgot
but you put like for example if you make
a hazard of wood you put wood inside and
then it tells you how long your house
will be protected for oh
it's a two cupboard yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh okay i've heard of that i've heard of
that
wait i need to i need to i need to add
some fuel to one of my lamps okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah i did this all in pretty much just
one day okay but today i added some more
lamps yeah here i have some boxes and a
shelf
and then um here i have a fridge and a
chair nice and another box and i have
this thing here which i placed here
thinking that something could grow but
no chat was wrong it has to be outside
to the second floor
oh my gosh a bear rug
yeah i can turn on a romantic fire here
yes
and by the door is she telling me that
senpai i always leave my door open but
people will always tell you are you
close to do it ah it's close okay she
doesn't mean me yeah okay
okay wait come up again
okay
so in general you may have noticed you
can craft things from your inventory but
at some point if you want to craft
specific things you will have to get one
of these crafting tables and there's
different the workbench there's
different levels of them so this is a
level one workbench and here i made a
repair bench today because i repaired my
own axe
yeah i don't have much stuff though i'm
like new to this game oh
what's your housekeeping nice i like
that thank you yeah
i think it's actually turned out pretty
cozy
and you can look if you look outside the
window oh what's that you see something
sparkling in the distance the stars that
you know now that those are stars but
also
there's also you see that the bright
tower in the distance that's fubuki
senpai's farm
uh i don't know if i see it but
okay
i only see the one
you see something that's a bit bright on
the water on the water oh yeah yeah yeah
the sparkly thing
yeah that's kobuki's fish farm
[Music]
romantic sunrise sunrise
spicy
[Laughter]
c4 is now on sale
wow
amazing oh let me give you some clothes
nice thank you
i think i have something that could fit
you um
oh this one's pretty fashionable let me
look how that looks on me oh oh let me
keep that done
oh
i'll give you this and it's my old
gloves they still smell like me oh it's
okay
bone
helmet and bone armor
oh i'm no longer naked
oh yay
if you wear that bone armor uh
wait i think you dropped it yeah you
dropped it yeah i think i dropped it on
the floor if you wear that you can't
wear pants apparently um it doesn't come
by oh my god i'm so stupid okay
nevermind
oh okay
nice i like the baseball cap though
yeah amazing you can keep that stylish
mm-hmm
yeah
[Music]
no no this is not the one that anna gave
me i'm gonna give me just something made
out of wood this is a bow number yeah i
i killed some animals and made this
myself
nice yeah
so you want to build a house yes but i i
only i don't have much i only have like
500 wood
that's pretty good to start with
um
i think
we can
start now it's bright outside
again so i close the questions where do
you want to build it
how do i close the door can only you
close the door oh yeah i think so i
guess so
let me close it
[Music]
you can look for a spot when you want to
build your house okay what's a good one
remember the server will be wiped at the
end of the week
yeah yeah
listen you can also live with me if you
want i can give you a key
true but you know i think it would be
also nice for me to like learn how to
make something server's going to be
wiped though like at the end of the
month right or like somewhere i don't
know
yeah yeah that's apparently the end of
the week already yeah that's why i just
want to study a little bit
okay
well look for a spot outside that you
like but you need a little bit of space
you can't build too close to other uh
homes apparently
okay
yours is very cozy it's like at a you
know like as a slope so it's like hidden
at first glance
yeah it's cute
i'm here i'm a little bit proud of it
who's next to you let me see the one ah
that's true luna senpai i nothing fine
oh nice nice nice nice
cute drawing oh okay yeah you can draw
on the wooden panels oh exciting
hmm okay
what's a good place who is this house i
can be neighbors with whoever this is uh
originally here i thought it would be
nice so i started building here but then
it didn't work something didn't work i
guess because it was too close to that
house oh
so here i guess there's a cursed place
um first place okay let's let's let's
see
from there
you don't have to be by the cliff you
can go a little bit more inside
like close to the road also if you want
i'm shy i mean not shy but like what if
like i'm alone like in the middle
what about oh that's also a cursed place
that looks like
yeah
yeah this looks like
maybe like
here for example
oh there's a lot of good space in this
grass
oh maybe you
you can still you're still super close
to everybody else
maybe yeah maybe maybe maybe
oh
okay
nice
i have a pickaxe just like in minecraft
okay whose house is this people's houses
are so cute
oh that one the other one that one is
the ahmed the one you're looking at
what shop 3 000.
cool
okay if you're ready to build yes okay
i'll build anywhere server's going to be
wiped anyways right
yeah
um so if you go
into
uh
the crafting menu
and go to construction
yeah
you see the the blue building planning
plan i craft it
yeah
take that okay dad like crap crap thing
and then it takes a few seconds why is
there a helicopter sound no it's far
it's far
holy [\h__\h] it's bringing free loot crates
ah that's what anja was aiming for right
helicopter that's the that's the ship
i'm gonna go there
this ship
i can probably build like by the water
but that's too low to for comfort i
think
oh you can go there if you want
i like being
i like having the high ground
oh
helicopter is
circling the power plant hopefully it
does come here
and where where do you want to build if
you have the the blue plan
uh put it in put the blue plant in your
in your hot
thingy yes yeah and then press the
button yeah yeah and then uh how does it
work again uh
you have to
hold
uh
like this build here you know
yeah first you're building the the
ground anyway the one that you have
selected right now
oh that should have been probably a bit
higher
oh how do you make it high
uh just with the mouse just aim higher
oh with the mouse oh something like that
like this
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay
i'll be here yeah get one of those plans
and then i'll check out books
uh
okay helicopter is going somewhere else
yay
okay and then
maybe you should make it a bit bigger
big bit wider
yeah some items take a lot of space
okay
oh
line of sight blocked oh there we go
hmm
i'm trying to uh
i'm trying to build i don't know i don't
have
what kind of house should i build i
don't know
it doesn't matter it's your first house
this is my first house i guess
oh
line of sight blocked
so building here is kind of complicated
okay and then for example okay i have
this for example okay
yeah
oh and i'm coming
what
maybe i should like get rid of this
how do i get rid of this uh
use the hammer i'm not sure if you can
get rid of this but if we can just
destroy it you uh
yeah just just bonk it
i i can't reach it there you go okay
okay i think your house is a good sign
now
okay yeah
um so now you have to build walls uh-huh
uh
how do you do this again oh yeah uh when
you have the blue print selected yeah
right click and then
around the bottom there there's walls
but also you have to build window walls
too they're separate oh okay okay so
keep that in mind and then there's also
a doorway as well a doorway maybe we
start with the doorway
where the doorway
ah too close to the power lines oh [\h__\h]
yeah right above oh your roof will have
a problem because
oh
oh [\h__\h] didn't look at that
should we just like build this way at
least one floor should work
i can place walls
or should we should we make like the
door here and then we expand here
instead
so at least like this level can have
like two story
yeah
you really need such a big house for one
week no it will take a lot of wood okay
never mind just keep it this size for
now okay
okay
is this a doorway
no this is where's the doorway
okay where do you think the doorway
should be
uh
so why do you feel like it's easiest to
enter
i would say over here that makes sense
here
yeah okay
boy
oh there we go
hello
why is it so difficult to build
i'm able to build it oh there we go
there we go
okay building it from here is easier
um and then
a wall
oh [\h__\h] here here
i can't place a wall
oh
here again but not here
okay then maybe we should build
here
towards here
let's destroy this door or something
yeah or maybe we can have the door it
doesn't matter
yeah
yeah it's fancy having a doorway you
know like a partition or something
yeah
um
okay foundation
foundation okay
yeah we're we're kind of building it
like this okay it's okay
it's like a
okay
you can have two separate small houses
yeah there's a cap in between
how about that yeah this this will be
the tap in between
and then you have one house here
exactly exactly in one house that's the
living house
exactly
look at that so cool
[Music]
amazing amazing amazing right now some
walls this is too big it's stupid you
know it will cost woods too to keep this
from decaying oh that doesn't fall apart
i mean it's only one week i think
famous last words yeah phil yeah i could
get a wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
wah
i'll build you some walls too
but i don't know where you want the
windows
maybe in the middle
one wall
should be okay looks nice looks okay
do we need uh do we need windows here no
we don't need too many windows i don't
think
oh
need some privacy yeah we need some
privacy if um we cannot build in this
area oh my god yeah yeah that's because
here on top there's the the cable
yeah
so that's why i was saying only a path
in between and this is the
like yeah two houses connected by one
path okay
[Laughter]
okay nice
oh
oh my god so does that mean we need a
wall here
if you want to or you make another door
here and you keep that open oh you
already put one there yeah
oh what is this anything is fine
you're the architect okay okay okay yeah
let's let's concentrate maybe on this
part of the house maybe
hello
oh she's taking care of the baby i think
uh yeah it's the you know the noises
very common
i picked her up so she stops meowing at
me oh
a ramp for you a step steps
and then what do we need to make
i need to make a roof
there's a roof option too
there's a roof option but most people
just put a flat roof aka just a floor
because roofing is kind of difficult i
[\h__\h] it up too
yeah so just the floor option would be
the smartest i think okay so foundation
uh no not foundation uh there's a floor
on the right somewhere oh floor yeah i
see it yeah
just as a ceiling yeah
oh my gosh so low ceiling
yeah
oh it's okay i guess
okay nice
oh do we need stairs nah maybe no
i just want a two-story home but i think
it would be hard to maintain
what are you even gonna put into that
house huh that big house
i don't know we just um for if we want
to have slumber parties
we can have that in my house oh true
at least i have like somewhere to go
home for example like or like to put my
stuff you know
right here helicopter it's fire
but that's what you believe
coming towards us okay my last wall
yeah already i mean not wall floor
and then
what how is there a door you can also
make a uh when
you can make a door but that's in the in
the normal crafting menu uh-huh i think
we should uh go and take cover
uh oh like my house won't do
oh yeah no because of the windows and
all that uh yeah bye let's go to mine oh
my god it's coming
oh hi
it's okay oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] so fast it's so nice
[Laughter]
okay it's flying away thank god i got
hit did you get hit uh no
i'm bleeding
oh no it's shooting at me
oh no where should i go then
oh no
oh no what should i do
uh no it's flying away it's okay oh no
somebody's house is burning
oh god did it hit someone's house yeah
it did it did
it did hit someone's house can i like
use water to like
no that doesn't work i think i tried it
on my house before
it just goes off after a while but um uh
no senpai house crispy
ah it will go off it it's just
disappeared on its own when my house was
burning oh okay um should i wait for you
somewhere
no i'm not i respawned in my in my house
on my sleeping bag
okay
it happens that's
you see i don't know if you saw on the
map how far away it was at first but it
comes so fast so you really have to run
and take cover and once it sees you
it
kind of doesn't give up for a while
uh-huh
oh is that you walking
yeah i'm looking at the fire you know i
like fire
oh it's gone it's pretty much gone
nice okay we can continue building your
house okay okay okay okay
do i need a sleeve
you need to make a sleeping bag oh that
was actually really dangerous uh
when you look in crafting menu and then
type in sleeping bag
uh it needs 30 cloves do you have that
what what what is that
type in sleeping bag
or just sleep into the search menu cloth
i don't have cloth
oh i have like fibers
too
okay
[Music]
okay okay
well well it's good practice it's a good
practice
yeah
i'm gonna
i'm gonna make
i'm gonna construct items
i'm gonna make um the helicopter only
shoots you when you carry a weapon in
your hot bar ah an armor on your body
oh
put armor i mean taking all of that off
yeah
hmm
oh well
[Music]
yeah i'm reading the chats
reading it in a chat i see
always learning from the comments
yes
wait do you need more do you need more
cloth yes i need like 20 more
okay you won't get them from the stone
i just like it the noise is so
satisfying
i'll bring you some
some cloth okay have some
so i already
picked them up somewhere
oh
i have 10 with me
mm-hmm
splitting
there we go okay okay
here's 20 is that enough where is oh yes
20 is enough
and then so i will craft sleeping
sleeping
there we go now i can craft it
30 seconds to craft okay
and then and then you place it in your
house on the ground i think it's the
best
okay
at least it seemed like neutral
somebody's house had no damage
yeah strong house
wow strong houses looks fine
over there is that my house why is my
house so ugly
yeah you can um improve the the walls
and all that you can make it more sturdy
but you will need more wood or
eventually other materials i guess but
for now
just make a wood house yeah i can spy on
people's houses from here
but they can also spin you
left click
somewhere by the window so people can
watch me sleep
yeah you can name your sleeping bag oh i
wanna rename sleeping bag
gift rename sleeping bag
um
rainy
[Music]
rain is
okay nice
okay
do you want to use the
foundation over there or no
um i don't know i i mean what can i use
it for
well
you can make another hospital i don't
think you'll need it yeah i mean just
leave it and
you'll just need more and more resources
here i'll give you a mailbox as a gift
what's that welcome gift
mailbox wow should i people can leave
notes
in your mailbox
wait so i don't even have a door
yeah we'll make that that's also in the
crafting menu if you type in door
and there's a two wide door and a one
white door and there's a key lock as
well that you can also put on your i'll
just do the one wooden door
and then i'll do keylock
i'll get rid of
uh your foundation i guess uh
sure i'll just grab a hammer
um if you if you use your normal hammer
i think there's um an option uh to
demolish it
oh really
um maybe not i saw that sometimes but it
doesn't always work i'm not sure how you
need a tool covered that you're saying
ah oh yeah right okay well
okay let's look this is how do i
a lot
ah
this oh [\h__\h] that i'll craft one i'll
craft the tool cupboard yeah you need it
anyway you have to get it
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
okay
waiting
waiting waiting
yeah so like when it's morning i
instantly know because the windows
shining the sun directly to my sleeping
bag yeah
so nice right okay
[Music]
i feel like i should have made like the
door the other way but okay fine
i think it is what it is it is what it
is
okay my my two cupboard is
is it done
yes
[Music]
noise
and then i'll put it
here
i think
um here
anywhere but yeah it has to be inside
and then in the inside there you can put
extra wood and the more you put inside
the longer your house will be kept alive
it for three days okay yeah
okay okay okay
just for one day is okay
okay and then i need to demolish this
maybe
i can't
i can't demolish
uh
you i guess you can just funk it
what a waste of wood
[Music]
what about my door i'm gonna make the
door
should i just like move the door
here maybe i should move the door here
ah
so annoying
i'm probably going to uh go to recycle
something soon you can come with me
okay when we do that
okay okay
let me just um
make a doorway
i wanna make a doorway
i'm gonna make a door
where's the door here it is
oh my god where do i put the door let's
make i'm gonna build something cool i
finally have to ride why can't i foot
door
oh
placings oh oh never mind okay now it
works there we go nice and then i put
the lock here
oh yeah
nice
if i put the lock then what
it you have to put it so that
other people can't go in and steal
things
oh but then so there's no passcode or
anything just like
yeah no it will just recognize that
you're the one who lives here oh
apparently okay okay okay
wow
wait whoa whoa wait wait wait woah
okay so this is my real home
oh my god
it's a home it's an actual home let's go
it looks so glamorous thank you
thank you it's so glamorous
wait i want to build like you know the
the staircase like thing
the people are like
a step
a step yeah you can do that it didn't
work for my place for some reason it's
kind of weird
yeah it should work not into rain it
doesn't work here
yeah it's
it weird
huh
that's weird
then what should i do
just open door
just just just open door
hello
[Laughter]
yeah do sports every time
or does it need a foundation below could
it be
could it be that it needs a foundation
below
and i don't think so
let's try let's try
let's try
i
made two planters outside now i can
plant stuff yeah
okay it works it works it needs a
foundation turn nice
yay
thank you that was from chat oh my god i
haven't put floor floor on this
so i'm gonna put floor
where is my floor
hey come to my house yes this is the
system
i want to show something off yes yes yes
yes
i'm on my way
on my way
hello
look
oh what's that
i built a rain catching
thingy so i can collect water and then
we drink it because the other thing i
have is just a tank where i kept on
stealing other people's water and
putting it into my building
now i can collect it myself i have a
rain catcher
so if you ever need water you can always
take it from here because it fills up
pretty fast i guess oh okay okay okay
nice like oh i'm so thirsty i'm gonna go
to kiara's house
yes and whenever whenever they just
first see she comes to me
spicy spicy hmm
yeah i need to okay okay okay
are you gonna realize how's it going
with your building oh my building is
fine with like chat what if chad says
the walls are like the wrong way around
and i'm like at this point
and whatever yeah
it's okay
time
you wanna inspect my house and then we
can go i don't know recycle parts like
yes
i have to recycle some things uh
just
one momento
i'm coming in a second
no no no
eat some food there's no lamb it's okay
no one needs lamb
okay i need to i'll just put real wood
here protect it for two days
okay
for two days after i have to grill oh
yeah but
i'm on fire i have to grill some food
some some meat
i'll put the mailbox stuff on my mailbox
like around here
yes
nice
did you put some wood into the yes
thingy okay
good good good good
you don't put the case when you're
offline so make sure before you go
offline to put enough in there so that
you know
um you have enough until the next time
you log in okay okay
okay i think i'm uh i'm done i don't
think we need light just yet
do i need to
touch the bed or something
no no it works just like that but when
you die you have to select the sleeping
bag oh
okay to respond there specifically nice
okay
it's night time do we sleep to pass
no you have to wait it's like two
minutes all right all right i'm i'm on
my way to your house
oh okay i think the door is open yeah it
is
[Music]
i'm gonna turn on the lights uh while
you come to the second floor i have the
fireplace on spicy
just the two of us with the oh my god
i'm burnt
by the spicy i was gonna save the two of
us with the bear supervision
i'm making dinner okay
are you hungry
oh comfort 75 uh am i hungry uh
um i'm one i could see something can you
open the the fireplace um uh i guess
there's an option
open and extinguish
open no okay okay yeah open the storage
container does that work yeah you can
eat that one cooked meat that's in there
okay
the cooked one
what meat is this
mystery meat
oh
it's a
pork sorry it's okay
it's okay as long as it's not human meat
it's delicious it takes so long to cook
this what the hell
i thought
another one we can eat as much pork as
we want
it takes like a minute
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh party mama is she always watching you
that's so cute
cute
oh oh no i need more put in more wood oh
no oh okay i have more than enough just
to turn the bus in the dark for a split
second
do you want to lie on the on the bear
rug
cozy cozy
cozy
romantic
i can read you
this
[Music]
yes
very nice
you know including the helicopter
don't i look cool with my wolf hat yeah
actually i was gonna say
we killed the wolf and it dropped a
skull and with the skull i could make a
wolf hat oh that's cool yeah i was like
thinking like why is she a dog like a
wolf i guess what hey i'm a bird a
phoenix yeah yeah i know yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
go ahead
yeah
you're
i don't know what kind of dish is this
barbecue rust barbecue
i wish i had some sauce
yeah
kind of boring just like this it's the i
mean you can make sauce from fruits or
something
but we can't do that in this game i
don't think
probably not
it's so dark downstairs
yeah i could turn on the lights no no
need no need no need it'll it'll consume
fuel i want to save energy you know
save energy
yeah i'll turn on this one
but i also need to put in wood hell okay
i want to say i never turned it on again
i made this one today as well
just the two of us in the dark oh look
at the sunrise
wow so oh oh yeah
we're back
oh helicopter is coming oh really but
we're safe right
probably look
wow
can i cook meat in here too it says what
is this for though ah
maybe
should be able to wait let me see
where's the helicopter
i like the animation when the when my
character brings out the hammers like oh
so so much style
me my
a few and put it in there
that doesn't work it's only for smelting
or yeah i thought so i read that in the
description i was wondering though
shouldn't i be able to make a pizza in
there isn't that the perfect pizza
like a meaty pizza
yeah that would be amazing
you like italian right let's make our
italian restaurants
yeah i don't know what kind of food you
can make like we can make the barbecue
but we can we make something else maybe
like something
well i mean there's different kinds of
meats depending on what animal you kill
and then there's like
all kinds of canned foods like beans and
tuna you can't get those in like the
abandoned convenience oh oh the
abandoned convenience markets stores
um but you can't really do
like you can't cook the tuna and make it
into a proper meal i think they're all
just simple meals
but what you can do if you have a tuna
can and you ate the inside it leaves you
with the
the can itself and then you can either
recycle it or if the tuna can
specifically you can make tuna can lamps
that's the the lamps i have downstairs
those are made out of tuna cans
[Music]
yeah but you wouldn't know because they
look just fine
let me turn them on let me turn them on
yeah see it looks it looks like a
beautiful lamp
wow
yeah no one would know yeah no one would
know
is there like a picture on there okay
it's morning
good morning
[Music]
okay i think
i think
oh no i overcooked one no
oh you can't eat the overcooked one
oh you can
ah
that was fine i ate it
okay i'll let the rest just turn off
okay let's go to the convenience store
then haven't been in a while
oh
putting the food
in here in my fridge that doesn't really
work by the way it's just decoration no
really
yes okay
so much warms
um
let's
go i need something else
okay
apple is your inventory
um no not really full
okay good
because you're gonna get some stuff from
the convenience store probably but
um
you should probably make a chest a box
for your
home and then store things in there that
you don't need at the moment okay
and we can make that before we leave
okay if you type in box into the
crafting menu
it should be
a little box and a big box okay okay
[Music]
my house is so far
oh my god who is who the hell is running
around there you and me
i'm so fast
my door is open for you
oh
um shoot oh my god okay i should build
uh no in the crafting normal crafting
menu in the inventory yeah a box large
wood box
um
is this large wood box or just a wood
storage box
uh you can do either
for the small one for now i guess is
good enough but you don't have enough
wood maybe take a little bit from you i
forgot
yeah storage because
i take a little bit
yeah um um splitting
okay
i don't know how to split it oh my gosh
i don't know how to split oh there we go
ah click on the item once and then uh
there's a splitting thing yeah and then
drag it up yeah you're doing it
nice
[Music]
what's yeah people are asking if i have
a gun yeah a gun from anya melfissa
and then i'll make a box i'll make a
small box
craft just a box
[Music]
this bgm is very um
survivally
[Music]
i got an smg from anya spicy machine gun
nice
okay i have a box
there yeah put it down
and put some stuff in that you don't
need right now
um do i need the gun
you can put all the stones in
okay
okay i put oh
wood do i need wood no
yeah you can put always the rest of the
wood whatever you have into the other
storage oh the tc okay okay uh-huh cause
that one only stores wood you can't put
other stuff inside
there okay
nice okay
[Music]
um
let's go and close the door
[Music]
what was that someone's shooting
i don't know why
aggressive aggressive
oh hey let me try i was shooting
[Music]
it's too fast whatever can i shoot it
uh i don't know if you want to waste
your time no i don't want to waste ammo
i just want to use i want to use that
for i'm killing more important following
wow oh shoot i'm lost too
i'm uh
i'm jumping i'm jumping um
no you're like more up on the map
i am 07 in the middle
uh
he
run towards the abandoned supermarket
it's next to o7
uh
what store
no abandoned supermarket it's on n7 oh
n7 ah okay n7 okay
if you do right click on a specific
location on the map then you will have a
marker there and then
you can see the marker on the top of
your screen oh there we go yeah yeah
yeah yeah
i'm such a good teacher you are
wow
people tell me i'm a pretty fast learner
so
i will absorb all the knowledge that you
give me
so the building you see is uh the
abandoned supermarket people come here
like all the time to check
what new stuff there is oh there's a
wolf running oh
oh my god oh [\h__\h] okay
i got some nice hits there nice
okay and so
well it takes ages
[Music]
you're gonna get some leather and some
cloth and some meat bonk and maybe even
ahead
i killed the chicken
well this is already dead i have to
honor it
so the body won't be a waste you know
you want to make sure it's useful
oh my baby
jimmy
okay oh my baby
okay so certain certain types of boxes
these ones for example you can open holy
[\h__\h] i just built it and it comes with a
small water canter this shitty box i
just built one myself you take that for
yourself what's this stop sign
and those you can recycle and there's
some scraps
it's gotta be fascinating and these ones
now this is for grilling some food
and then uh this one this one here too
this one also responds after you
uh destroy it
try try breaking it this one
with what you just missed it
yeah and then usually it comes
out with two items
yes oh yeah did you pick it up that's
good
um now we run around the supermarket to
see what else there they dropped it's
always in different locations and
there's always different stuff inside
here this
this one for example
wait where
uh inside run around the
market i'm outside
outside outside i'm running around
oh hey
huh
this one
you can take what's inside
okay
oops and then the spring
this one you can break too
take what it dropped and then there's
another one
okay
oh sewing kit what's a sewing yeah
okay ah there's one up here
oh up here
oh my god for real what the [\h__\h]
please be nice please be nice
okay and then inside you'll see these
types of boxes if you open them there's
always some kind of food inside
but they're also always in different
locations
okay
so these like just respawn every single
day or something
uh
every five minutes or so every five
minutes all right then um
yeah look around what you can find give
us some food so you can bring it back
home when you need food
okay okay okay okay
nice
what's this
anymore yes
chocolate
can we like auto sort our inventory i
don't think so huh
ah
i guess not
okay okay i think i took everything i
could take at least
from what i noticed
okay now wait there's um
there's one more here
oh okay
apple and
and one more here
oh
apple and beans
and an oh
in here
uh-huh
there's uh this crate
like that okay
and then here is maybe some yeah some
sometimes in this room
next doors they also have something in
here
this time no but keep an eye open next
time okay okay
and now
outside
uh
oh
no not there
hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah there's a ladder that leads to
the rooftop
on some
edge of the
of the oh no that one you can't break
oh yeah look at the where the stairs oh
there the lid i'm here
mm-hmm just press arrow up
hey okay
there's another crate here and
there's another crate up here spicy
crates
inventory is full by the way i'll take
the rest yes okay
okay now follow me
what you do after you looted everything
you go to this machine
it's a recycled machine
and it's occupied now okay so you put
inside everything that you don't need i
know it will take a few tries to
understand
what you want to recycle and what you
want to keep
uh but for example on your first time
uh at the stop signs and then the first
row second item
i can see is recyclable
second row
second item
uh
probably also the nails
nail third row third item
or the one next to it two probably
and uh the
bottom row the
the fourth item this one
i think and i'll recycle that for now
turn on
yeah
it'll take a while and then we'll give
you out some scraps and some other stuff
and that's the stuff you keep
okay okay okay okay okay okay
i always recycle the blade i don't use
that i don't know you could keep it i
guess some things you can keep something
i don't know i think in the beginning
scraps are important actually there's a
question i wanted to ask my viewers can
i ask your viewers
because i'm not streaming
sure
um like there's a monthly wife but does
it also wipe all the recipes you learned
for crafting
question mark or does that stay
because with the scraps you have you can
like learn new recipes for crafting oh
don't stay okay good good good because i
already learned a lot of things i don't
want to lose those okay so i think and
especially in the beginning uh you
should maybe prioritize getting them as
long as many straps as possible because
then you can get a lot of what is this
new recipes at the workbench quality
pistons
oh uh i think those you can for now
recycle
okay let's recycle i don't think you're
gonna build anything like that
besides that
yeah yeah put that in i always put that
in
and the cans like if you eat the can of
beans now you can put in the can itself
[Music]
okay i'm gonna eat the beans
i'm gonna eat
oh
[Music]
yummy kind of beans
yeah baked beans
um and then i put
maybe what else do i put what's the
sewing kit for okay i don't know
i
don't know yet i think that's i think
this is enough i don't know okay then
recycle that and then i'll also recycle
something okay
and then you already got some nice
scraps yay
what are what are scraps for by the way
yeah as i said um
the only use that i know at the moment
is that
when you get a workbench
then there's like a a tree of recipes
that you can learn
um to craft more things like you can
craft weapons you can craft stuff for
your house you can craft clothes and all
that
but i guess you can also gamble with
them
okay
did you
did it what did you take what's uh there
and what what what it dropped here no
i don't know
take it okay
it's valuable
okay now i'll uh you can you can run
around you can run back to your house
because i gotta recycle some stuff okay
um
[Music]
where is my house
he ate
he is somewhere there okay
[Music]
what if i die
in the middle i'm gonna be fine
you can save crafts by building a
research table for blueprints
okay okay okay okay okay
that's useful
that's useful knowledge you can make a
blueprint from the smg and then you can
make it yourself they're saying
exactly how do i make a blueprint
well you already have the the blueprint
thingy but um what they mean is probably
when you make the workbench
there's many many many recipes you can
learn but in order to unlock them you
need scraps lots of scraps a lot of
scrubs so that's what we gotta make
first research table
yeah workbench level one workbench
that's what you should make next you can
look up what you need to craft the
the level 1 workbench
[Music]
do i put the you know the water thingy
like outside
uh yeah place it in front of your house
maybe
this terrain is really um something
hmm
no you don't have to even steal water
for me
yeah
damn it
it's okay
occasionally i'll steal water
yeah but i could help you but
well at least okay have something the
quinoa water is uh
you know
you know how like water from like
different households or different
countries they taste different something
like that yeah yeah yeah that's kind of
like that
see maybe a little maybe i'm in the mood
for some kimono water today or something
oh my gosh if you oh my gosh if you feel
sick you can throw up you know i put my
rain water thingy like outside the
window
it looks so
nice view
yeah can i move it
once
the thing is with moving things in this
game so far i've noticed that you can't
move anything
you always have to destroy it and then
most of the time you don't even get
something back so always think um
yeah where you want to have it before
you place it oh well that's okay
um
some things you can pick up but
apparently only when you're faster so i
don't know it's weird
it's weird um what can i make
research
uh yeah type in workbench
work
bench
workbench level one
yeah what what does that need what are
you missing uh i'm missing wood but i
can just take take it back from the tc
yeah yeah and then build that and place
it that would be a good good step
guys
also i'm back in the area okay i can
open my door for you if you want
all right i'll go to my house first okay
okay i'll i'll keep it open anyways
i have to grind wood yeah where do i
grind because there's the starting area
or something
grind what do you want to grind oh like
wood
oh you can you choose any any tree out
there there's a million trees out there
oh
oh your building is decaying yeah you
got to put some in there oh my god
don't wanna lose this beautiful mansion
um how do i
indeed meow
that's what i'm saying chunkers 100.
oh
only protected for
so few hours
okay then i'm gonna make a workbench
yeah
do it do it just do it
q
brick bench level one
i'm going to craft it
takes 30 seconds
make a research table too my gosh i
don't have enough resources
i can you know
i can chop down that
tree
yeah do it
get some stuff while you're waiting
oh [\h__\h] oh my god i can't see
oh
okay
i can barely see you but it's okay
yeah
okay
[Music]
oh my gosh this tree
so difficult to see
nice
probably gonna leave you soon because i
feel like you gotta figure it out for
now the most important thing
okay yeah no problem thank you so much
for teaching me so many yeah thank you
okay
yeah i don't think i'm gonna stream for
like too long anyways i need to
just remember like you can always go
back to the convenience you should
always go back when you have nothing to
do to get some stuff for now that's the
one thing i can
tell you what you can do
and chop trees and always close your
door when you hear a helicopter
run
and
yeah
yeah try to oh yeah wait did you look at
the skill tree the tech tree though did
you look at the workbench oh uh no wait
if you open the workbench
there is it says open tech tree
and then you see what you can unlock you
have to start from the top and then it
goes to the bottom and you see how many
scraps you need to first unlock the
recipe
and then you can build it on your own oh
okay okay okay okay okay
unlocked and then i uh oh okay that's
that's great okay
yeah and then what else have fun with
that
yeah thank you
also it's your choice what do you want
to what do you want to prioritize but
if you want i would recommend
uh
weapons first and clothes maybe
weapons and clothes would be good
yeah yeah okay then
bye bye have fun
[Music]
wow
so nice
quinoa teaching me so many things so
cute so spicy and then you guys told me
uh i need to build a research table
what's that for
metal fragments i don't have enough
is that the one from the um
from the oars or something
so the one metal fragments from like the
big stones
uh we fight we
we
bonk the wood so that
where's my stone i need to i need to get
my stone
so that
we need to we need to bunk the tree so
our base maybe maybe for a week or
something it would be nice we could have
something like that
okay there we go
what's this
i have no idea what this is
sulfur ore what is this
oh metal ore never mind i think i can
make one
oh
what's metal fragments what's the
difference between metal fragments and
metal ore they're both made out of metal
it's just the same thing
do you like the game so far uh yeah i do
actually
this is um
i like it i feel like i just need to be
careful because it's like a pvp thingy
and like some people are very very like
trigger happy for some reason
i don't know or maybe they're not people
i have no idea
but you know
sorry sorry
i need a smelter it's the smelter the
one that looks like a pizza machine
leave some resources behind before
leaving oh so that if i die
i won't lose everything that kind of
thing
okay then
okay i don't actually know how to like
split
what do i have to keep pressing see
sometimes it works sometimes it doesn't
bro what
okay you know what i don't know guys
okay guys i'm gonna spend the rest of
the maybe i'll stream for half an hour
more and then i will um
i'll go
put this crap in the teeth
it's okay
will you make a pizza yes
okay i'm gonna go to the jungle and then
i'm gonna chop some trees
oh my god it's a deer
deers don't attack me right
they should be fine
dangerous
i thought i had it down but apparently
no
i hear like footsteps of animals
oh
nice ooh
yeah let's just chop down trees and make
sure like our baby can survive like
maybe like three days or something
and then i'll be able to sleep in peace
okay
timber
so yeah guys
i was like this was supposed to be my
off-shape and your active item was
broken oh my god
then i should make a new one
i know i can repair it but i feel like
it's faster to make a newer one
yes okay waiting waiting six five four
you're off the edges really
no because the thing is you know uh you
guys probably know the reason why i am
you know saying oh it's my off day
because
i don't know first this is my off day
second i'm not feeling too well but it's
like
you know the thing is if you don't feel
too well
you think like okay i don't know like
maybe
things might go not according to plan
for example like oh allah
okay for example
you think you can stream on wednesday
but it turns out that on wednesday you
can't stream because your body is not
delicious you know so i thought like
yeah if i can stream let's just stream
you know
tomorrow morning is supposed to be
donation reading but i might put it on
like
more on the afternoon i guess thank you
super or
yes yes yes bloody not delicious okay
right
what's wrong oh i'm just not feeling
well
it's not often that i don't feel too
well these days a lot
but i'm just not feeling
very okay
um in fact i was actually supposed to uh
go to
uh go visit
an id member
tomorrow but because i'm not feeling
well
i'm uh
i'm just gonna postpone it to next week
i've enter winded exactly
before it gets dark
oh it's so dark let's make this the last
tree that we
chose
let's make this the last tree that we
chopped because it's so dark
honestly
[Music]
okay nice nice nice nice nice
yeah my inventory is full so i need to
uh
i don't know
store stuff
i guess
tinder
oh what do i throw away
maybe stone
i still have a lot anyways
okay
let's go home
where's my house
that i think that's my house the one
with the small window thing
i think that's my house
the shape is pretty distinct i think
drink water
um damn i'll need to go to kiara's house
for that
when thirsty quinoa go
keeps don't eat the apple yeah you know
what i'm kind of dumb like that
um i don't have
i don't have any lighting
god it's so dark
see okay enough for nine days
enough for nine days or i mean you know
what i'll just like
put everything here
why are there animals
okay i wanna
eat this
huh
not recommended from people for people
who are scared of the darkness
um
where's my exit
is this it
oh my god guys
what
why is it horror music
i'm lost in my own house guys
oh my water catcher
this is my water catcher so my exit
should be here
[Music]
weird
this is my water catcher
so this is
okay
[Music]
there we go
whoa
[Music]
oh
i'm outside
nice oh the mute the moon is so
beautiful
exploring in the night
oh yeah can i feel like oh it's morning
look guys we survived the night
[Applause]
good morning
we spent the whole the whole night
trying to find a way out
[Music]
we survived the night on our own
okay
can we like put
construct like lighting here
like a lamp
[Music]
tuna can oh we don't have an empty tuna
can and we don't have fuel
oh
where do we get fuel guys
i guess we're gonna continue to live in
the darkness until we ever get fuel
campfire okay campfire
okay
[Music]
and put it in the middle of the room or
something i guess
[Music]
from animal you can make fuel okay
this music is pretty intense you know
it's scaring me
[Music]
um oh campfire
okay
maybe when it's uh
maybe we can i don't know i feel like
we're done here
i'm not not not done obviously
i want to go to the supermarket again
let's go to the supermarket
uh here abandoned supermarket right
okay yes
you still need that rock probably not
my inventory is
hmm
[Music]
my inventory is not full i don't think
this bgm is scaring me for some reason
yeah me too
well why do i hear
oh the helicopter is far away it's
heading somewhere else oh i'm the wrong
way
oh
is this the correct way
why is it going towards the okay
who is it
i come in peace
i think we um i think it's here the
abandoned supermarket
is there
okay
hmm
oh
why is it close by
there it is i was going to be like um
that's far but apparently no
no it's coming away
huh
wait
okay
[Music]
right hello
is this dirty water what is this
i don't know what this is
small water bottle
oh
okay
pickles
eat at your own risk wait what
container does not accept clear items
what okay
whatever you say
okay let's um
look
around it can't be more dirty than rain
water wait i thought that i thought the
rain water gets filtered you know look
at the machine i thought it gets
filtered it doesn't
okay
then hmm
okay okay okay okay okay
let's um check
nothing here oh something here
hmm
maybe
maybe i can't do anything else oh
there's a
piggy oh bear maybe
let's go home
oh guitar
campfire
burnt bear meat
this nothing
can i
recycle anything
bear meat what is this
what's this
a door controller
wait
huh
oh
cute
can of tuna shouldn't i make this into
lamb like tuna can lamp like what kiwamo
did
[Music]
whose house is this
okay uh let's go home
us go home
[Music]
and we have our trusty guitar here
so we're not lonely
first day we already got a guitar
musician oh my god animal
oh my god animal
oh my god animal animal sounds no
[Music]
scared of the animals
whose house is this
hello oh my god somebody has a car
that's so cool
mummy
man i want to make one of those like the
um
so cute
i'm home
let's go
yes
okay um
my precious guitar should be
here
[Music]
what is this for
or maybe i should okay this is cool
20 fun person
okay
baseball cap
um protected for 17 days i think the
server will reset
um
what do we build like do i make like
another box
i think i should make another box
let's just i don't know let's just play
the guitar
[Music]
upgrade my house to wood
i mean i could
how do i um how do i upgrade
ah
that
like that upgrade to wood
oh spicy
like that
oh it looks pretty decent too
hey by the way how do people have like
fancier looking doors and my door is
like trash
[Music]
how come my doors trash and people's
stuff are good
from swing too long
oh my
[Music]
my house my window isn't barred though
how do i make them bored
[Music]
you can
make better door now we don't need
how much wood do we even have
we don't have enough for everything no
we yes we do we we we we only have this
yeah enough enough enough guys
have enough don't worry
because
we don't need our house guarded for like
we don't need our house like protected
for 13 days no we don't
we don't need our house
okay
with blueprint craft window bar wait
ah not enough
okay
look it looks it looks somewhat better
now
like a hut
like a hot hot hot hut
so nice
okay um uh
six days that's more than enough
four days that's more than enough
let's upgrade everything first
salah okay
okay
i'm gonna do it
nicer
look at that from the outside it's gonna
look good
did you fit guys
do floor two yeah yeah yeah yeah later
guys
look guys it looks decent on the outside
somewhat
like a like a vacation hut or something
some of the walls are backwards dude how
do we even know
how do we know it's backwards and how do
we know it's not backwards
oh yeah
yo let's see
okay um okay let's upgrade this
wooden floor
ah what do you mean i can upgrade huh
oh nice guys
i asked help and just
agreed to would
wait why is it
why is the placement like this like some
of them facing this way some of them
facing that way can we change that
can we change that
i see we upgraded
oh my god guys look oh my gosh full
wooden house guys civilization let's go
right click the walls that are oh okay
okay india this is the offside
oh
oh nice so nice so nice
look at that so cool
okay okay
right click the wall
okay
oh my god
nice
yeah the floor can stay this way it's
it's to add texture
your roof please upgrade to
yeah
okay and then rotate this one too
and then this one also rotate nice and
this one also rotate
so cool
now we have an actual wooden house
vacation cabin so fancy
wow
[Applause]
and the floor is kind of um
i can't rotate the floor
[Laughter]
okay uh and then what do you make guys
the bar
the the how do i make the bar something
oh this
wooden window bars
craft like
three
wow so cool
[Music]
research better accent pickaxe okay okay
okay i'll do it i'll do it
[Music]
large chest and furnace okay
wow so exciting
house building
not let's see
okay and then
um and then i do have this
so i'm gonna
put this here
hi
oh my god there's a helicopter
hi where is big fish
i need to craft again
i'm scared guys
there we go
and then one more
if my windows are barred i'm safe right
undress if you're scared of helicopters
okay time to undress
stay away from the windows damn that
windows are bad i should have built
windows
i shouldn't have built windows
wait what it's far
wait
i need to build one more
oh i don't have enough
oh i dropped it
well um
um
i'll drop meat
and i'll build
i'll build a wooden window bar
well if i'm wearing clothes it's fine
right
if i'm wearing clothes it's fine there's
no weapons or nothing
[Music]
borrow someone else's chainsaw for
faster wood grind oh my gosh i built one
too many by accident
i guess that's okay
for um
no error what do you mean no error
ah okay and before i log off what do i
oh wait no no no no no this one i
haven't put
that's what i haven't put
it's the right amount after all
there we go oh my god our house looking
pretty decent huh
huh interesting
nice
so cool
more than two clothes or gear heli will
attack well this is two so it's okay
okay okay okay
look out far from windows here
here is the logout place
man why are you guys punishing window
lovers sunlight is good
and what are you guys saying research
table i have to make research table i
will do so now
oh
i need metal fragments
i can't make them because i don't have
enough metal oh oh ceiling you guys want
me to upgrade the ceiling why well why
why
what's wrong with the ceiling maybe this
one first
okay a little bit more
i lost a little bit more
my base is decaying no
protected for one hour
okay there
okay
i think this is okay
open open
okay protect it for one day
well i guess
let's go outside
what's this
clothing
water bottle
uh
i don't know
well what are these i have no idea what
these are
burnt meat
okay then um
what about
what if my tool breaks if my tool breaks
i'm gonna go home
okay i'm gonna like uh
last batch of trees until whatever this
is breaks
destroy the foundations you aren't using
outside wait why
um
make a furnace i will i will i will i
just don't have enough materials uh i
don't think i can go online for like
much
longer because um
i need
yes yes it is a lessons cost of upkeep
oh okay then i'll destroy it uh right
after i
put this a sign for other whole maps i
don't know how to make a sign
how do i make a sign
my aim
oh the sun the sun
there we go
oh okay let's let's let's punch the tree
from here
oh where's the i hear helicopter
where is it
oh it's far
we will
insane
pretty loud but it's okay right
[Music]
it's fine right
oh yeah it looks kind of ugly huh
i might upgrade
let's upgrade
um
uh how do i upgrade again
yeah i agree it's ugly
so yeah i guess we can upgrade
okay
nice
look at that
oh my gosh the helicopter is like so
close
like shoot
23 hours
two days
there you go
there you go three days is enough
okay well um i think our house is
looking pretty good my god
i think our house is looking pretty good
right
hmm make a sign how do i make a sign
give a sign
are you friendly
okay okay oh kill extra foundation i
almost forgot to do that
but first let me see where the
helicopter is
the culture doesn't sound far i mean
near so i guess
i can
oh can i use the rock
oh okay yeah and this is not working
um okay it's so hard to destroy this
okay
you gotta hit the sweet spot
i'm gonna hit the sweet spot
my active item was broken
a hammer can remove it
no
hammer
how
not the hammer
i'll just
use the rock
yeah like you can demolish it but only
if you have just built it right
okay
just kill the two connected to your
house okay cool
and this one the last one
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
oh and the rock is destroyed too just in
time
[Music]
what sound is that weird okay
just drop that
oh great to what
this one no need
okay
okay this is nice
wooden sun can be crafted with 300 wood
okay
we do have the wood
it sucks if when you don't feel safe in
your own house
because you have windows
that's dumb why do you punish people who
like windows
okay the rest will dk of course um okay
sign
medium wooden sign and small wooden sign
large wooden sign is locked but why
why is it locked
why is it locked guys
[Music]
need to research it first
yeah
is this it research no
this is the workbench right
huh my research
research
openstack tree
oh you need a research table so not the
workbench uh we'll just make the medium
one then
okay 30 seconds
and can i like make a drawing or
something just to tell like people like
yo it's raining house
okay
like here
like yo welcome to wayne house you know
yeah might need paint
really i mean i'll look for it later
can i draw in game or what
or do i have to like use an external
thing
place it near your door
[Music]
so here or here because
or here
i don't know
it's possible to draw in game that's
cool
okay here
or here
maybe near the door so like
here but i feel like people who come
from this side they will be like oh you
know
next to the door
why not make two true
welcome to rainy home
near the door is
near the door is here but nobody's gonna
look at it
so um here maybe
then
then a paint sign
oh
oh yes
okay oh my god
how do i rotate
hmm
can i rotate
oh there we go
hmm
okay
mouse drawing let's go
[Music]
can we erase
maybe no
rainy home
okay um
are the colors limited to only this
or
maybe
maybe the colors are limited to only
this
akiwawa is here
thank you i'm making a sign for my house
i'll redo the
stuff later
[Music]
okay
yeah i'll like fix the fix the
uh fix the black parts later
[Music]
um i hope i'm safe here
should have probably started drawing at
home huh inside the house
or maybe it's impossible to do so so um
all right then
um what about the colors
what about the colors though hmm
the colors are limited i would think
maybe
[Music]
no one would hurt an artist of course i
will make you cute signs
uh only for more the sum of um
uh 500 scraps or something i could make
this uh you know a living you know
[Music]
no one would hurt an artist except for
bears
now that you mentioned it
gosh oh my god okay
okay
okay okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
they don't appreciate fine arts
so sad
okay oh my gosh i hear birds
chirping
who could it be
could it be
how should i color these
light purple for highlights maybe
let me just uh do this oh my god okay
hey let me just do this first
hmm oh i need blue
what about blue yeah there's no dark
blue
or maybe there is got to be creative
hmm
[Music]
okay
okay maybe maybe it's okay maybe this is
okay yeah
maybe
maybe maybe maybe
what about
the tongue though i kind of don't know
what color is good
or i could like erase it if i think like
it's ugly later on
yeah
because um honestly like i think like
this white is too bright for like the
overall like color balance
but
we already have like a limited set of
colors anyway so it's kind of difficult
i guess
[Music]
yeah
there's there's like a better color for
um the hair
there's probably no
better color for yeah because like the
whole color balance is kind of off
dang our color choices are really
limited
our choices are
is there an opacity setting that's a
very good question
there is there is but it's like
nah
should i
do this instead
no
um
i don't know
oops
[Music]
uh this is so difficult
join the
hmm
purple plus white
we can try
it's for um
nope
um
[Music]
kind of difficult
difficult
very very difficult
maybe white on low opacity would work
hmm
white on low opacity
what's is this all over fascinating no
no it works doesn't work no it doesn't
work
ah
does raw still have hidden color
palettes in in between colors i don't
know
i need to research like rust arts you
know like what i can do what i cannot do
or something
[Music]
super low opacity
this
oh god
no
this is tough
or i think i shouldn't color it
maybe i shouldn't color it is there like
an eraser
there's no eraser huh trash
let's trash it and redraw
if there's no color then let's just make
a black and white sign
just make a black and white sign
uh-huh
okay
oh
[Music]
what today
rainy house
wayne house don joke
yes
nice rides
[Laughter]
okay
oops
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
nice
let's make a black and white sign that's
all right black and uh wooden i guess
and
[Music]
oops
just make white as the highlights
yes
[Music]
house
and i think we should keep this one at
least
this color
i think we should um keep this color
just to like let people know that it's
raining
hey
it's raining let's go okay nice
[Music]
okay
there's animal sounds it's okay
okay i think this is okay
rainy house don joke
okay
okay i think this is enough
[Laughter]
rain is
okay let's let's draw another sign and
then call it a day okay
but i don't know what to draw so maybe
never mind let's just call it a day
yeah
there's people who come from here like
they don't know but maybe if they watch
from here oh rainy house okay look at
that so cool
[Laughter]
i'm gonna take a screenshot let's go
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes
i'll make one more join the royalty
i like one more join the royalty
okay
let's make a new one medium wooden sign
craft
spicy
join the
okay
rainy house
join the royalty
nice nice nice nice nice
okay
rainy house rain house
now
to make another one
okay paint
paint
okay i need to jump to paint the side
are you serious okay um
join the royalty
let's make another black and white
joined uh
oh i'll draw like a small arena here
yes
yes yes yes yes yes
join the royalty
[Music]
yes so cool
nice
join the
[Music]
royalty
okay i would love like a large sign you
know what i'll just be an artist in rust
honestly
rainy the artists
okay
and then
i'll do this
joy
oh my god the the footsteps of the deer
is scaring me
let's add some depth to it
royal
tea
rainy the starting artist yeah
[Music]
okay
first let's color the background
oh my god hold on i can't see okay
color the
background color the background
color it
yes yes yes yes
[Music]
join the royalty
let's go what are you waiting for oh my
gosh okay
[Music]
rust fantastic art space
should i color this
should i color this so like it's more um
it's more eye-catching
maybe i could i could color this
whoo
raw
[Music]
yellow
royal
tea
and we can add yellow
or something
nice
or maybe instead of yellow white is
better
i don't know what do you guys think
maybe maybe maybe white
join the royalty
okay and then i'll fix this
[Music]
i'll fix it don't worry i'll fix it
okay join the
join the royalty okay guys
should we should we turn it to green or
something i think red is pretty nice
i think red's a pretty nice color
the design is very id of course because
we're holo life id
wow
[Music]
okay
mm-hmm should i color
this
or too much
not too much
join the royalty let's go
[Music]
okay
animal near yes
okay such a pro artist thank you this is
the only thing i can do
in this game
i don't have enough survival skills so i
can all i can do is draw
join the royalty
[Music]
okay
join the royalty
and then rainy house
so cute right
can i edit
oh i can i can edit it anytime
yeah
whoa
[Music]
okay
yes yes yes yes survival business cool i
like this one okay i'm gonna take this
one okay i actually don't really like
this one can i change it
to something else because i think
there's just too many colors
okay let's um let's nuke this
oh
maybe just like a
s
maybe just this
joined uh
yes
no wtf i'm sorry i just it didn't felt
it didn't feel right
you can't believe this bird i'm sorry
okay okay i'm just i'm not gonna take
long with this one okay
joined uh
okay
join them
joined uh
royalty
but i want to draw like wayne here
or join the welcome to rainy house
welcome to
rainy house
something like that
oh
suspicious bgm
maybe this one is just like text or
something
ah
like this joined
welcome to rainy house
[Music]
of approval okay um
it's getting dark maybe
yes
maybe something like this
maybe text only
yeah this one's like text only
and then
oh oh maybe make a teacup
uh make a teacup
oh no
did i break it did i break the undo
well when you break the undo then you
know you gotta do what you gotta do
you gotta do what you gotta do
[Music]
okay
okay something like this
[Music]
yeah maybe
yeah
this is uh trying my best to rescue this
[Music]
piece
oops
yeah make it look like we can see like a
coffee house or something
nice
make it seem like it's on purpose
okay
nice
can you sell coffee here i don't know
it's supposed to be tea
i guess it's all right
um
i need to
oops
welcome to rainy house
see it's um it's pretty cozy right it's
pretty nice i think
it's pretty nice you guys think so
whoa
yeah
i think it looks okay
welcome to rainy house it's not really
it's not really readable but
[Music]
yeah welcome to rainy house
and then
rainy house
are you using mouse yes
now let's um take a picture of this one
as well
okay
welcome to rainy house and then
this one is raining house so nice oh my
gosh okay fine guys i think it's time to
uh
i think it's time to stop playing
oh but that was a really good
introduction to rust
yeah i'm gonna put the wood here
protect it for three days nine hours
that's good enough i could always like
log back in if i'm like feeling free and
um
just do stuff okay um you guys should
you guys are saying i should log off in
like a
safe place
oh i love this one so much okay i'm
gonna take a picture like a like a
better picture like this
nice
oh
nice nice
[Music]
okay then
okay
we're gonna do a little talk uh but
we're gonna log off here okay
thank you gonna decorate all the walls
later um maybe if i can like inside
like maybe inside like at least like
here and here like in the in this room i
wanna put paintings
god i'm going to stream rust and all of
it is just going to be like
i'm going to draw you know
just like i'm drawing or something
drawing and rust
you guys are going to be so sick of it
like no survival just draw
you know
i think um you know with the limited
color palette i need to learn like how
to efficiently like make stuff it's like
limited colors i feel like as soon as i
learn how to do it it's gonna be great
oh you know
oh i'm so proud okay um these are not
decaying anytime soon huh
but it's okay it'll eventually decay
but okay
yep that is it guys
thank you gotta bring the diversity to
the whole auras right
[Laughter]
an artist among looters and raiders
okay
wait uh give me a second because i wanna
um
because i wanna actually um
oh there we go
shoot
okay okay guys thank you uh today's rust
is over and then we're just gonna
uh we're gonna
uh chat a little bit before we end the
stream okay
let's go
okay i think i'm too big for this maybe
i'm gonna
[Music]
shoot maybe this oh maybe this big oh
nice nice sorry guys i still haven't
changed it i still haven't changed
i still haven't changed the thing
uh but i will soon i will soon how do i
log out quit maybe exit the game yes
an artist can dream to not be you know
kind of hard for us drawing streams i
mean we gotta have something different
right like everybody plays for us
everybody does different things in russ
and me i wanna
i wanna draw and maybe you know i just
wanna make my house look nice you know
rainy drawings season one you know the
server's gonna be live soon so um i
already have like my best
my my my i don't know
my my my the basics i probably know and
you guys will teach me anyways right
thank you for the nice and comfy stream
though thank you
i guess um i have found so far like what
i like doing in russ like of course i
need i like the hunting and everything
and maybe if i get weapons and stuff i
can do all sorts of fun things
but yeah i kind of like peace and you
know just like chilling in my heart
yes yes yes yes yes yes
and then
okay
um tomorrow there will be a donation uh
reading stream uh i still haven't set
the time the original time is supposed
to be like 11
but i think i'm gonna move it to maybe
a little bit more in the afternoon
yes yes yes yes yes yes
i hope you guys are looking forward to
it and there might be guerrilla rust
for the week i haven't uploaded the
schedule anyway so even if i got
everything down you guys probably don't
know what's coming right
but yeah uh if you guys are asking me do
i like rust the answer is yes i do like
it a lot
i do like it a lot
an artist can dream yes yes yes yes
afternoon without time is really hard
for an a yeah i know it's like your
sleeping time right sadly i think it's
gonna be the time where you guys are
sleeping because lately i think i've
been waking up pretty late
yeah pretty late especially i'm still up
at this hour so i think i might need
some more time to sleep
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes miko had a fishing
hut you could use really
okay okay okay okay
thank you for the fun stream though
thank you um this baby's first rust
ended up really well anya gave me a
spicy machine gun smg kiyama um taught
me all sorts of things she even told me
that i could steal her water you know
very nice
might as well learn what you can before
the reset yeah i feel like because i'm
not going to be ambitious because the
reset is coming soon i'm just going to
use this moment to just like you know
learn as many things as possible you
know
[Music]
yes yes are you gonna prepare yourself
before apex dream collab depends on how
i'm feeling i just tell them like you
know yo i'm actually kind of sick but
hopefully i'll be well and am i gonna
prepare uh no
no i just wanna be there to have fun i
know i'm gonna be like super rusty and
i'm gonna play bad and stuff but you
know i hope
i hope
i hope it'll all be fine yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes
all right yeah thank you um i hope i can
get better soon
yes i guess so i feel like honestly uh
you know when
when kyle was showing me around i was
fine but i feel like when i was in the
um
at the abandoned supermarket i was
already like feeling kind of like queasy
but then pio is like oh like i gotta go
and it's like okay
you know that's good
well such good timing but um drawing
doesn't make me feel sick i guess it's
better
yes yes rusty and apex but will you be a
taxi and rust yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes
and the helicopter sounds yes
okay um that's it uh donations will be
red tomorrow anyways
um yeah i'm actually feeling a little
bit of a
tiny headache but um i'll just go
straight to bed and i guess it'll all be
fine thank you guys for accompanying me
today um you know i really really
thought we wouldn't be able to play
arrested and i was really really
actually very sad like if you guys are
like if you guys are feeling bummed like
imagine how i feel you know but thank
goodness like um
thank goodness the m-chan is coming in
clutch i don't know uh i don't know
because actually i uh a lot of the
you know like some of the members were
like really surprised about it too like
wait what there's such there's there's
such a thing and i'm like yeah i guess
you know but um anyways thank goodness
it all worked out yeah
thank goodness
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes
but yeah i was really upset about it
actually but you know
and i was like okay fine you know what i
i even like bought a new game to play
you know
but um
yeah uh thank you so much for m chance
for the staff for the clutch
yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
yeah it's like really weird i guess oh
well
oh my room with naked rainy will be
missed oh well
uh that was funny oh my room it wasn't
meant to be but it's okay
see you guys tomorrow we'll have a
chill donation reading hopefully
yes yes yes yes
okay then um
thank you very much for your attention
i'll post the screenshots later on
twitter bye-bye
[Music]
you