oh oops hello i think
eggs
do
[Music]
um
hello
wait does the music disappear
yeah
okay
all right there we go
hi everybody welcome
to our
of what i say on twitter i love hotel
yeah yeah
okay
i'm here too yeah i think they could
tell based off the little pod that
you're in
yeah
they're like spaceship pods or something
they're so cool
closing you background from amelia
watson oh no i didn't yeah we're on pc
thank you yeah
it's the first time you reveal it right
oh yeah yeah yeah first time
what the what
the wild west music kind of became more
like rock music oh wow badass kiara's
the only one who can hear the music well
except for you guys i think you guys can
hear the music do you hear the music
yeah it's begging
oh
i mean this is not much of a hotel
though but i don't know nowadays i guess
you call anything a hotel yeah i mean
that's true you could probably run to
like a tent like this at an airbnb or
something hey when's the last time you
actually went tenting
no camping oh oh
it's been a few years like maybe six or
seven years wow yeah for me also i don't
even remember
i was definitely a child so
two years ago
yeah very young
did you have to go to the bathroom
outside or you had like a
like a
toilet or something
um i'm not even sure it depends there
was like one time when i went to uh like
a children's
camp thingy they probably had a toilet
but then when i went camping with my
family we probably didn't have a toilet
but
i mean i don't need a toilet because i'm
an idol and um yeah yeah yeah
oh well that by the way is uh are we are
we lagging or anything is it okay it's
not youtube it's it's our connection but
yeah you guys should still be able to
hear us
it should fix itself because earlier it
was doing something hold up we're going
to switch oh youtube is buffering
oh youtube you little [\h__\h]
move us like this since when we look at
each other it's like
come on
come on it's me oh yeah right it's
sounds like we're buffering
ah
did you is it joined
oh yeah do it because it did not pop up
it should hopefully fix it
come on
oh everyone back okay
oh sure enjoy are you
i think wait one more time
sorry guys
all right png time bingy dumb yeah let's
just do it in front
you have one
no
[Music]
somewhere in some
on my twitter
ah okay i've uploaded some pngs recently
like actually transparent yeah
shut the wait everybody
like i would like
if we're gonna do that then i'll just
switch on the laptop so it'll go offline
for a second
oh yeah we're not we're completely gone
probably been like this for a while
it was buffering so it was online
um
[Music]
so
um um
[Music]
hello we're back
we're now frozen yes
little pots better than nothing
yeah
i'm a caterpillar
me too i do love caterpillars they're so
cute
one day we'll turn to a beautiful
butterfly where we'll be able to move
around yeah yeah well yes um probably at
least me on my birthday when i can move
in 3d i'll be a beautiful butterfly
hey thanks to you um thanks to you
yeah i already i
i saw a little bit of a preview of it uh
today
oh yeah on last night and it looked
amazing already even just a few seconds
that i saw
yeah as well thanks to you
[Music]
it was fun so i mean it's like a good
opportunity it's something i was
planning to do anyway so i think it was
a good opportunity to
push forward and finally take the leap
to do it because
quite a bit of the hell yeah
and that's what yeah yeah
have fun putting everything down again
um yeah it's okay we're gonna prep and
you know who knows what you guys will be
able to see soon yeah
all right what are we doing today
uh well
i suppose we'll be taking some
personality quizzes do you have a beep
on there oh uh
[Laughter]
feed quizzes yeah
they're saying feet feet now
yeah
if maybe you guys remember if you
actually watch our streams you maybe
remember a long time ago nine months ago
people told me it was nine months ago we
streamed you know uh that that
we were here together again oh yeah yeah
we took quizzes yeah and then at the end
i was like i think we did one quiz or so
and we were like oh we should make a
whole stream about this
so that's what we're doing let's start
with the first one and maybe we can put
the links in the chat so you guys can do
it together and look at it because some
of the quizzes have like some pictures
you guys might want to look at it yeah
some visual aids so you guys can see
what we're talking about yeah we'll
describe it though if you can't do it at
the same time so don't worry is that a
little okay for you
wait
oh
a little [\h__\h]
i saw that
all right all right uh
uh which one should we start with
uh the top one maybe the first one that
i said first one i don't know what that
one was we have a couple i have a couple
ones that you guys recommended
and when we're done with those too early
then we'll just go through
bee feed randomly beep beep beep
beep okay so
we're gonna we're gonna do we know which
country you truly belong in based on
your a to z c
food
preferences is that what it is yeah it
yeah
every letter of the alphabet
that's it might be a long question
every little yeah we can link it i can
link it right oh yeah i think i can i
know i linked it i just i'm just asking
okay
is there even
is there even food for zed
but let it set
zucchini it's okay
hold on i haven't started taking it yet
okay okay i'm ready
okay
uh
shoot now while we're doing it we're
gonna both be doing it on separate
devices but we're gonna say what we're
going for so you guys can note it down
unfortunately we think we shouldn't be
showing the quizzes on the screen so
just listen to what we're saying and
then you know so the first question is
choose a food standing with the letter a
would you like to tell me the options
that we have i don't know usually i
think of those oh the options okay yeah
apple crumbs almonds
avocado
apples okay you can
can you eat almonds is that does it have
gluten no no no
okay well apple crumble does apple cream
will have gluten probably yeah
all right um actually that sounds
delicious i'll go for apple crumble what
are you going for uh i don't know i'm
torn between almonds and avocado because
i like i eat avocado like kind of ever
well like every other day oh for
breakfast oh really but i eat a lot of
um i'll go with avocado because it's
nice and creamy choose a food starting
with the letter b please tell me the
options oh my god do we have to do 24 of
these yes
okay
wait how many letters oh wait okay
i don't know how many is it 26
i don't know it's 24 it was actually
incredibly sake so you said 24 i guess
it was wrong
i was close well then we got a zoom for
this tell me the options bananas beans
burgers blueberries
yummy
i do like both bananas and blueberries a
lot oh [\h__\h] should i be choosing burger
because fast food it's my it's my
whole theme
i mean not all burgers are fast food so
you don't have to
but now i'm feeling blueberries right
now i'm going for blueberries what about
you
uh
okay i was just picking no okay
this [\h__\h] bananas b and a and i assume
you know that song yeah yeah he went to
funny that's a good one choose a food
starting with the letter c
carrots cashews cereal cherries
carrots
carrots are good
very good
i'll go for cherries i'm really feeling
fruit right now oh
yummy choose a food starting to let a d
doughnut dragon food dumpling dates
donut i still want to get krispy kreme
hot doughnuts that people have been
recommending to me they're tasty
[Music]
we'll find some out here
choose the food starting with the letter
e egg salad elbow macaroni enchiladas
english muffins oh
what are you choosing uh i don't know
maybe enchiladas because i can eat that
i mean i put the egg salad too
elbow macaroon
i think it's just it's just the shape of
it's like pasta but ah cause it's around
like that yeah yeah
someone cut some elbows in there
um
i do like egg salad but not just like
that does anyone like eat egg salad just
like that
some people do yeah you're supposed to
eat it with like bread huh yeah in a
sandwich i love eggs sandwiches
i would say
just like this like if i had to eat it
exactly the way it is i would go for the
macaroni
okay
uh little letter f fish and chips fox
grapes french toast french green green
did they have not enough words with f
why is it fox grapes i think because
they want to include like one fruit or
vegetable and then like other options
but hell yeah french toast i actually i
make a really good french toast i know
i've heard it i'm gonna try well if you
can make it have you
made it oh yeah
you need to use gluten-free bread
that's so sad
[Music]
what did you go for the green beans
green beans was healthy
she's a food that's with the letter g
uh granola gingerbread garlic bread
grapefruit
100 times scully bird let's go
eh
gluten free coffee
they have that oh yummy uh h
uh ham sandwich hazelnuts honeydew melon
ooh hakka noodles hakka noodles what is
that
never heard of that i guess it's some
sort of
it's
it looks like ramen in the picture
though it does
oh they look thick actually the noodles
look really thick it's like other things
[Music]
oh it's noodles for hackers uh-huh i'll
go for honeydew melon i love it i love
it i like it way more than the orange
melon
cantaloupe oh yeah yeah me too i think
honeydew is the best melon yes yes yes
let's go
oh actually i can i remember
like so many times
in europe my friends are work colleagues
and all that whenever there was like
a
cantaloupe or honeydew melon they would
always say no i don't want this take it
away i want it without
what it's good at least for you too
okay start
starting with the letter i ice cream
iceberg lettuce italian wedding soup i
know that an indian spiced peas italian
wedding soup it like has little
meatballs
veggies and noodles the meat the balls
uh an iceberg lettuce just like that
yeah wait pick the lettuce i like
lettuce very much but just like that i
mean
we can put the dressing on there right
no
no you eat it like that you just bite
into it yeah if it's soaked because
otherwise it's bitter but sometimes i'll
just get a bag of like the iceberg
lettuce and i'll just sit and eat it
like chips i'm good with ice cream
though i'm choosing a lot of sweet foods
uh letter j
jam jalapenos jackfruit and jelly beans
i've never had jackfruit before i think
maybe like any of these things really i
guess jelly beans are the best for me
out of all of these i'll choose
jam it's pretty grab some pretty damn
good jam
in australia uh-huh damn good jam okay
like kiara
but your choices are kiwi kitkat kale is
that some sort of salad kale it's like a
like a lettuce yeah sort of it's like a
really healthy superfood lettuce oh wow
never ate done
[Music]
kentucky jam cake i've not heard of that
before
what is
that kentucky jam cake it's just that
you jam to that cake
actually i love kiwis and kitkats ah
her choice which one did you do kiwi
okay
okay um l foods lasagna lemon bars leeks
slimes mmm i like lemon breakfast but
i'm thinking
[Music]
it's today monday
today's a monday right yes it is it's
mondays for lasagnas hello uh speaking
of monday's the next letters m mmm true
meatballs mac and cheese melon macarons
oh this one's tough yeah meatballs
mac and cheese i think i'll go for melon
because melons the watermelons the
normal ones in the summer are the best
thing in a hot summer eating the juicy
cold watermelon slice yeah
that is really good i don't know which
one to put
all right i'll pick them out yeah i need
more melon than mac and cheese
and letter m
we have
nuggets nuts naan bread nachos
[Music]
chimken nuggets
oh i can't really well if i could eat
them probably nuggets yeah
[Music]
and you do seem to like chicken a lot
because from all the like every time we
ordered food
you would always order something with
chicken yeah and then sometimes it was a
food that came with something and
chicken and you would eat only the
chicken
you get you got everything with chicken
too
is that so
maybe i did
yes i did was the best though that was
with chicken yeah the thai curry was
with chicken uh-huh and the yakisoba
that i guess was what you couldn't move
okay yeah well chicken is good very good
reliable reliable meat you like chicken
all right next is oh
i like
oatmeal olive ew
omelet oranges i love oranges
i'm going for oranges i really like
olives but i'll go for oranges too and
which ones do you prefer the brown one
green ones or the
black ones yeah i like the black olives
what i didn't move from me all right
okay oranges oh it's just okay
choose a food sandwich a little pee
[Music]
like pizza pee plums pears and peas
ah i may cut up some really yummy pears
for us on the first day and they snacked
on them i was like it's like a on a film
set or something where you have craft
services and
you have like some snacks like i cut up
some fruit
yeah yeah yeah i love plums too though
yeah damn man pizza damn what is this
what are you choosing i'm thinking i'm
gonna pick pears because lately the
pears have been really juicy and tasty
ah but i think i'm i'm going for pizza
this time all right
a food a cute there is cute oh there's
quite a bunch of cute food quinoa
quesadilla quince quinoa and queso queso
like friends correctly you know yeah
yeah yeah is queso not just cheese yeah
it's just cheese
and quesadilla is
what can you
pronounce that one quesadilla quesadilla
yeah the elzar silence amelia quesadilla
and what's inside the quesadilla again
uh
it's usually cheese chicken sometimes
but you can have any type of meat pretty
much anything with cheese because quesa
is like queso oh yeah
oh and i think it's it's like tortilla
it's like yeah
what are you going for uh so what the
[\h__\h] is a quince
yeah it looks like a type of pear
keys yeah twins
pins guys have you eaten that before
what does it taste like
it looks like a mix of a lemon and a
pear
this
prince is a fruit very woody
oh
like maybe it's because sometimes people
do savory pears that you put in dishes
maybe it's that type of pear
it's like a lemon a bit really good with
cheese okay i've never eaten it before
so i guess i can't choose
all of these foods make me feel
uncertain because i'm i don't know what
they like cheese right
i
i i i like it
but i'm not like as much as a cheese
lover as many others are
i think
i'll go for the quesadilla though cause
she only proper food in here quesadilla
i picked the quinoa because quinoa is
pretty tasty with like rice yeah quinoa
salad too
my [\h__\h] side doesn't move
it's gross
sometimes it's um
[Music]
ew raisins ravioli radish raisins and
raspberries and more raspberry fan big
raspberry phone yeah ravioli is tasty
but i think it's very strong hell yeah
and choose the food side with the letter
s
samoa says salad sandwich sashimi oh
well i'm interested
um i mean sandwich has you know bread
but
what about samosas do samosas have
gluten i think so because it's it's kind
of like a more crispy dumpling almost
like it's
or like it's i guess it's closer to an
egg roll but in triangle form and with
more like
spices
i think i'll go for a nice salad i love
salads
i'd probably pick a sandwich because i
still make sandwiches good
too a team
what do we have on that tiramisu tomato
salad toasty what the tofu salad wait
what's the toast it looks like a
sandwich on the picture it's just a
sandwich i toasted a sandwich it sounds
like a british way to or maybe like
australia that's ketchup yeah it's just
it's just a toasted grilled cheese scent
you want my toasty a towel stay
would you like a toaster with some ham
and cheese
quesa queso
queso
yes speaking of spanish food and all
that before
mexicans it's mexican food right yeah
yeah
yeah emma told me that when she eats a
lot this yes she like kind of scratches
off escapes scrapes off everything right
yeah
explain yourself yes yes i like the corn
on the cob but i never had it until like
a few years ago i didn't even know that
it was a thing and then i had it
randomly at the beach one time
and i just scrape off all of the
parmesan and the red stuff yeah it looks
like it's a little bit too much yeah but
i like the taste of it but it's just i
like it when it's in between all the
crevices so i kind of like squish it
into the corn and also scrape it
but that's just corn no no no no
seasoned yeah you can still taste it
yeah
also corn is amazing i love corn me too
so uh yeah we have tiramisu tomato salad
toasty tofu soda i
tiramisu
let me take that one
i like tiramisu when it doesn't taste
like coffee there's really rarely
there's like tiramisu that doesn't have
coffee flavor oh yeah you just like
drinking it or tasting it yeah i don't
like the coffee flavor i'll go for
tomato salad i guess whatever
you
it's tasty it's a got a nice texture
yeah i like it when it's like unagi
don't like grilled and rice that's
really yummy the only thing that weirds
me out about it is like the skin is it
looks really yeah yeah yeah it looks
ugly you should look at it from the
other side
a little bit wait a second
that sounds so familiar to me
oh yeah and now i know
hold on and upside down cake which could
be any cake so i'm going for the cake
i'm gonna pick udon i can't eat it but
it's so good
yummy yummy i feel you we're getting
closer to the end of the alphabet yeah
almost uh v vanilla ice cream vino
vienna sausages and victoria plums
i never had veal before but i probably
wouldn't eat it anyways
is that like a baby
lamb i guess i would say child
not baby oh i see i see because it's
like a little okay
yeah and then the meat is called veal
not the baby cow itself yeah i think i
think but
yeah the thing is like uh in austria no
our
most famous dish called schnitzel
you can make it in with different meats
like pork and
even chicken and so on but the most high
quality and most popular and most
expensive one we make with veal
and it's so good
i would try maybe i try just a special
occasion like whatever you see or
something
have you noticed they're kind of pushing
for ice cream and plants because we had
plums before but not victoria plums and
we had ice cream but not vanilla ice
cream specifically i think they ran out
of ideas yeah in that case i'll go for
the plums because um i wouldn't mind ice
cream because i haven't picked that one
then the next one is watermelon again
no it wasn't it was a melon
watermelon but the picture was a lot of
melon though
obviously okay so we have w with
watermelon walnuts wasabi doritos
very specific
and waffles i want to go for waffles me
too
that's the only regret i have um
during my time at ama's place oh you
guys were now in the hotel but my regret
was not getting those
self-made
almond pancakes that she has offered me
yeah it was like two days in a row or
three days it's just because so we ran
out of time yeah we were so busy like at
one point we were like okay yeah maybe a
little bit later because i'm not so
hungry now and then we were going to eat
it like for lunch but then 10 hours
later it was like 10 p.m so i was like
okay
it's too sweet to eat that late night
i mean i wouldn't i
wouldn't even mind eating pancakes for
dinner
but i thought you know we might as well
order some proper food for anybody
lunch break um
one day i'll get your pancakes one day
i'll make them and then i'll make french
toast in exchange for you okay we'll
have a big breakfast buffet yeah maybe
we still can't
i guess we can
i think
we should have a yeah yeah
all right next up is why yogurt yams
yellow tail yellow squash oh i actually
really like squash
i think i'll pick that one
none of these are foods that i crave for
you don't like yams like uh you know but
yeah
uh i think i do it's like a sweet it's
just a yellow or orange sweet potato
okay i'll go for that okay
where it's at yay the last letter we'll
finally know which country we belong in
according to
a zucchini
which looks like a cake uh an italian
one according to his name
and ziti which looks like a lasagna oh
that's really good and so oh you had it
before uh-huh where's it from it's oh i
don't know
and zucchini bread zucchini it's mini
bread
i think
i'll go for the cake it looks yummy
i already have my country i don't know
which one to pick well then um
i'll go with zucchini okay
oh
okay i have friends
with the eiffel tower as a picture it
says you should visit france make sure
to eat some pastry pastries and visit
the beautiful i already have
i want to
oh
i got
thailand
that's a good place for vacation really
i've never yet it's very cheap
really yeah very cheap and really
beautiful
they probably look they uh eat rice
noodles there right that's gluten-free
yeah yeah
oh yeah so you should visit thailand
relax on the beach on the beautiful
beaches and check out the cool modern
city wow cool no i take that as a
challenge so you shall go to thailand
sometime soon i'd like to until the end
of 2023 i'm giving you a deadline
will you go with me yeah of course
actually quite a popular destination for
europeans yeah this is really cheap it's
well known for that i've never been like
too
well yeah i've never been to like
another continent though well what did
you get a chat what country did you get
you better did it with us
did you
what did you get
francis ah as a friend you're good
friend you friends oh lots of friends
what so many friends in uk oh
how many options are there i want maybe
i should have picked beans that would be
put in the uk maybe
it it's like 50 50 you came france
pretty much oh a few italies oh maybe
there's only the four options
[Music]
scotland indonesia oh okay poland okay
well okay okay there's a few different
ones but it seems like the majority we
have similar tastes then yeah all right
next one
and the next one is
no let's not do that one that's
something okay i'm gonna take so much
time already yeah how about build five
dishes to reveal what percentage picky
eater you are okay interesting i am a
very picky eater but i was i wonder what
bus
beep feed says
[Laughter]
tell me tell me
you guys can
take this quiz too
and let's see how picky we all are would
you consider yourself a picky eater
ramen a little bit yeah like i don't i
don't like well i guess this is pretty
common but i don't like fatty stuff on
meat
yeah same thing just spit it out or
something okay
all right so we have to choose toppings
for our ramen noodles assuming they're
gluten free for you
yeah i don't want to put too much stuff
on it but oh definitely cheese egg
and yeah no uh green onions i'll always
need green and green onions on there i
put mixed vegetables because i like
bamboo shoots
but i don't see it
okay i'll actually only keep getting
eggs and green onions here did you
finish choosing i guess charlie uh what
do you have in your ramen
uh green onions and eggs uh i guess i
should have added pork maybe
ah
can i still edit no okay that's fine i'm
fine with them i put chicken mixed
veggies eggs and green onions for the
ramen yeah okay okay sounds good
next we have a grilled cheese sandwich
okay
i don't really ever eat grilled cheese
sandwiches yeah i don't eat them too
often either
but if i if i do i usually do it with
american cheese because you can pick
different type of cheese apparently oh
yeah
oh
yummy i put tomato and i guess if i just
have to pick out of these ingredients
i'd probably pick spinach bacon tomato
spinach
of lettuce that's just a regular
sandwich okay i'm going for
uh lettuce tomatoes mozzarella cheese
ranch and diced oh can i just it says
diced ham but i will have it sliced ham
that's cheating it's just a sandwich
then but
yeah
that's better lettuce makes everything
better in my mind yeah
okay done choosing
pasta pasta pick it your favorite
you can pick your noodles oh mama mia
spaghetti
[Music]
i will do
i picked the bow tie looking noodles how
cute
and what about the sauce
there it is turkey beef no meat
turkey's healthier i think
i picked turkey i like turkey and pasta
actually i want to see like it what
sauces does it offer afterwards oh
tomato mozzarella parmesan mushroom
sugar parsley ranch sausage uh salt and
pepper okay
i'll go for beer i guess they don't have
alfredo yeah and no yeah no best oh
where's the best don't you put ranch in
the pasta what the disgust
although it i think i've done that no
not ranch
something like some creamy stuff i've
put into my pasta before according to
the recipe though okay
i guess we're just making meat sauce
pasta tomato sauce mozzarella
no parmesan parsley
i basically just made
bolognese oh
yeah i
me too pretty much it but i put
mushrooms i see chat posting there
results a lot of people already
sixty-four percent ninety-eight percent
i think there's only two options
so many 64's what
okay choose the lettuce for your salad
iceberg
yes iceberg good i take it too
toppings ooh chicken
toppings for salad croutons
cheese parmesan cheese tomatoes
[Music]
tomatoes yes
i think that's it for me
yeah simple salad okay
oh
nachos yeah choose a chips for nachos
doritos
you can make nachos with normal potato
chips i guess yeah i mean why not okay i
don't ever eat nachos though
yeah i don't really eat them too often
either
happens for the nachos guess i'll do the
corn
chicken beef turkey nacho cheese queso
black olives lettuce tomato guacamole
salsa jalapeno pepper ranch sour cream
black beans hot sauce queso actually
sounds similar to the german word for
cheese which is kazan quesad
oh that is really similar
what do you normally put on nachos uh
cheese molly salsa
sour cream nacho cheese and tomatoes
jalapeno please
i don't know what to put on there
oh wait i'm trying to keep my dishes
simple but everything i'm not choosing
it's considering me to be picky huh
oh wait i mean i can eat more but
yeah you would eat it but it's not your
preference like if you had to know
how you like it i don't want to put a
million things on all of this
okay
i finished i got mine how much percent
uh oh
i got 64
oh i got 98
you are the ultimate pickiest eater shut
up i mean i kind of
misunderstood doug
you can't say i'm picky then
if you if you try to figure out how
picky someone is this is not the right
quest to do in my opinion yeah well i
think there's only the two well okay
apparently there's 32 64 and then
that's not very accurate how is this
all right
get out of here
beep quiz feet
so next one this one should be nice uh
create your own terrarium and we'll
reveal a deep truth oh
speaking of terrariums you guys i
haven't forgot about the hashtag
ahmedcraft i was gonna make a twitter
post i'll do it later today but we're
still gonna look at your terrarium so
now you guys just have more time to make
them because it did a custom terrarium
if you guys are so nice you're making
them do so yes like they have to are
they drawing them or are they making
real ones real ones oh nice hashtag
armycraft on twitter yeah i saw almonds
terrariums they're so cool
you just reminded me oh i was going to
wrap up
[Music]
i was going to wrap up rakadachi for ina
but i i forgot because i was so busy you
can send it per post yeah that's true
well i'll get into her i'm gonna it's
not that far anyways but they were so
pretty and it inspires me to make some
terrariums too maybe the quiz can help
me to decide what kind of terrarium i
want to make and but you told me you
made one one time before or you have one
ah i made one uh a small tiny tiny baby
terrarium yeah it was like a
and some kind of
event thingy um
taking this quiz
go nice good job amen
thank you thank you
which one it do you have like out of
doterra i would see terrariums you made
do you have a favorite one that you made
my favorite one wait were you so like
especially proud of
i guess the elden run the elden ring one
was really cool yeah that one was cool
but uh some of the plants that i use
have died already so i need to replace
them with like plants that are because
it's because of the shape of the kitchen
yeah yeah indeed but then we said that
it kind of fits the atmosphere of
eldering when the plants are dead
looking
yeah it's on purpose i mean not all of
them are dead but some of them are like
browning a little bit because they're
not getting enough moisture because of
the container tarnished plants
all right so uh you guys have it open
let's start
we start with picking a container
do you have any advice here element is
like certain type of container easy to
work with
um not really i mean i see some of these
are open which means that you can only
pick plants that don't need too high of
humidity i like the ones that are open
in the front it's kind of cool
okay i'll do the the second row left one
i'm gonna pick the last one because i i
like that it has a top oh yeah that's
the cute one the corkscrew top
okay it's all about the layers pick your
first one first layer
that's that must be important all right
yeah
i'm gonna pick charcoal because charcoal
is pretty good for filtering the water
oh that makes sense yeah okay then i'll
i'll actually just follow your advice
i'm cheating
did i choose it i think it's lagging
there we go
pick your pick yeah
no i picked like wait let me redo i
can't redo it right charcoal charcoal
charcoal i can okay second layer now the
first layer i picked charcoal now we're
at the second layer see this depends
well usually you put pebbles because it
helps with the drainage of the water so
you oh
or you could be big or small
well then i'll go for small pebbles
me too and then on top i put white sand
because color wise it makes sense okay i
want it to be bright
your planes aren't going to grow unless
moss doesn't need like soil so you could
grow moss on sand maybe [\h__\h] do i need
soil no
damn
i'm not going back
i pick yellowstone
yellow sand oh
it grows in there
whoa
yeah moss moss like grows on rocks and
stuff because it doesn't most moss don't
have roots so it just pulls moisture so
sand holds the moisture pretty well
actually but the next couple of options
for pick-up plants are there's no moss
here is there anything that works with
my stones
i don't think so maybe a cacti
uh i think they have roots too actually
but
okay i gotta fix it i'm choosing um
yellow sand and see
that doesn't change anything it ain't
really but you chose a tone yeah i
changed its soil okay me too
i'm gonna pick the fern looking one oh
okay apple
i
the first one is is this one
this one oh that one i like that one too
but you know what i don't want to make
the same one so i'm going to go with
the cute succulent on the top right hmm
it's cute
this one at the bottom is shrek ears oh
it looks really fancy cool
it the flowers is does that even work in
the terrarium those flowers the colorful
ones i don't know it depends because
usually flowers yeah they go they'll go
bad pretty fast and
high moisture
uh
i
but i feel like that isn't that one
really big the one the on the top bottom
left it doesn't get i mean it does grow
big over time but yours is like an open
container so it's just still out that's
kind of looking well
interesting okay so try it although are
you choosing the same no i'm picking
flowers okay
go on pick one last plant
i'm gonna pick the big leaf one on the
right
hey i want that too too bad
okay i'll take i don't think the the
foreign one
and then finally pick a decoration frog
oh cute
bonsai tree that one is fake right yeah
the treasure chest i like that one
though just pick a turtle
oh i'll take the frog and then make
everything around the frog like beam
down to the frog it's a
world get something different
okay read yours
you feel the need to please everyone
trauma and direct confrontation is not
your scene you much prefer it when there
is peace between your friends and family
meaning that you feel this overwhelming
need to keep everyone happy and content
this can often lead to you bottling up
your emotions and not taking care of
yourself because you're afraid of
disappointing your loved one but if you
just talk to them and be honest about
how you're feeling you may be surprised
at the positive outcome that could
follow would you say that's
accurate
i don't know if i really want to say it
chad would you say that's true about her
does she want to please everybody that's
not true i don't i sometimes don't even
please chat
i deny them
oh
what they say yes so
but maybe you don't want to place a chat
but maybe you're trying to in a positive
way please like the people you work with
by like helping them a lot
are you referring to
something and and putting yourself in
and what's the word in the in the back
so that the others can shine
that's that is it the same kind of thing
i guess yeah
mine says you tend to over
things you're someone who is constantly
worrying whether it's about the plans
you've just made is that start time too
early or delayed oh yeah even about
streams
well the way your best friend just
replied to your text message you're
always stuck thinking about the finer
details and while it's okay to be
cautious and receptive to the people
around you and something that shouldn't
consume your life and stop you doing the
things you love try not to sweat the
small stuff and you'll find yourself
enjoying life just a little bit more oh
that is
probably where we accurate because i can
think of a big
worry that i have all the time
that is how did i know that from the
terrarium i was mostly even copying you
the terrariums they're powerful you know
oh wow
wow okay
very insightful that is inside full like
okay let's do one more one more i don't
think we have much time but oh
which one should we do we should do two
more let's do two quick ones um should
we do that let's see if your taste buds
are british australian or american okay
what about what about your fans why the
[\h__\h] is a british australian american
what okay
i think they're in like different
sections of the world
i guess so
ah i'm gonna drink some ice cream that
ammo sadly did not make um she said she
had one for me but
i guess she drank it and she forgot
it's not exactly like that
okay
um you have it open
oh uh hold on
chad you participate okay
tell us if your american brit or aussie
and obviously ahmed would be british yes
so well i don't know because the
picture's already here no i do like iced
tea
all right choose a breakfast item well
this is i'll go for cereal
i pick eggs eggs okay choose a drink to
go with that
tea
oh
i don't like any of these i guess if i
had to pick up just pick tea iced tea
you could think it's iced tea yeah yeah
choose a mid-morning snack
fruit
yummy cookies
morning snack cookies yeah okay i'll go
for fruit i do like eating fruit in the
morning just like today i eat pineapples
yeah they were tasty yeah all right time
for lunch
hamburger's saying what's your barbecue
on the on the barbie i'll
go for
hamburglar i'm just big sandwich
what the [\h__\h] oopsie
a drank okay a drag
lemonade juice coke juice lemonade wait
yeah lemonade okay and i clicked on
something too dinner fish and chips
pasta or pizza
pasta
the important one
not my choice of typical desserts but
okay cupcake
difficult choice between donut and
cupcake but
i'll go for a donut then
choose some candy ew
hershey's a licorice when i'm going for
cream egg yeah cream egg is too it's too
much i've never had that before but out
of these choices
isn't that me yeah well it's really like
rich because it's i don't know too
creamy but then this must be the british
choice because yeah this is that's
that's australian that's american so
yeah i don't like licorice i guess it's
just is that licorice inside
liquor like licorice liqueur yeah it's
like it's just really bitter licorice
it's like it's kind of yeah
but it depends there's actually yummy
there is yummy licorice because uh we
had to talk in my uh
swedish snack box
review i think
where i got some licorice that wasn't
yummy and everybody was like but there's
good licorice too like the colorful ones
do you believe that it's true it's true
i think i've had good licorice this is
licorice i don't know how to say it is
it licorice look i i hear it i mean i
say licorice but maybe
i don't know wait now it sounds wrong i
don't know
liquor or ice licorice
it but the cream add that what's inside
that just a cream right
uh yeah it's like chocolate
and then on the inside it's creamy i'll
go for that i'll just pick her keep on
picking some
avocado fruit
uh
we have to pick a fruit pineapple apple
or avocado is it fruit i thought it was
a vegetable no because i think fruit is
classified based on the seed being
inside right chat
i'm going for pineapple
yummy oh come on
i'm british
australian
it's definitely your go-to meal while
you're made to play in a watching cookie
each day is a pool in your garden a warm
sun and staples here live from many
other countries would dream of this
surprise i'm australian too hey mate i'm
british though uh you're deaf you're
definitely a steroid stereotypical you
hear that ted you're stereotypical brick
you probably start your day with a cup
of cup of tea and lunch is always a fish
on chips now no thank you i'll say you
may love football and are always
complaining about a weather when will it
stop raining
i mean it is the closest closest to
where i am so yeah welcome to the club
you said
you're not british anymore you're
australian now mythical australian
congratulations
sorry guys we don't have so much time
but let's do one more one more one more
one last one maybe there is
the whole live which whole live english
girl are you oh yeah yeah although kiara
are you taking this one i said it wasn't
no let me take the one with all the
members or no i took this one of the
five members i wondered if they maybe
updated it for all the members that
would be nice
uh
well
i'm wrong
apparently i have um promoted this quiz
before which is why on the first page it
says definitely didn't expect us to blow
up thanks kiara
so maybe some of you guys took it before
let's see what hell live english girl
you are oh i wonder
what i am
oh my god oh my god okay start quizzes
oh what's your mmo roll
wait it says enter your name do i have
to just ride in bloom
dps damage per second the main attacker
healer keeps the other players alive and
the tank takes hits for the team
epic tank because usually well at least
it oh but it says mmo
[Music]
i used to always play healer
but i feel like nowadays i might want to
play dps but back then i always i loved
playing mmos i was so addicted i played
so many i played like at least
15 different mmos
i was always the healer did you play
mmos before yeah well i only really got
into like one mmo
fist
i know it yeah oh that has really like
really
really what's the word
special unique character designs yeah
yeah it's cute i usually play tank in
that game too so yeah i guess i'll pick
tank you're tank wow sorry it's so cool
you have a character where you just put
all the points into vitality because it
has a health steel so it's kind of like
thank you it that's so cool i want to
play mmo with you you'll be the tank
i'll be the healer we'll get some dps to
join us
yeah
yeah okay i'm going for a healer pick a
quote that sounds like it's from epic
glitcher literature but are actually
just memes you want to read them oh sure
bury me shallow i'll be back
i've been through hell and come out
singing that's callie
violence for violence is the rule of
beasts he says that i don't know baby me
this is hell's territory and i'm
beholden to no gods wait this all sounds
like kelly
to become god is the loneliest
achievement of the world what maybe i
could see ina like lore wise saying
ah bury michelle i'll be back i guess
it's me yeah because i revive
yeah but what would i say this is also
genevieve it's so edgy oh maybe violence
for violence is rule the beast is like
good at maybe oh
it's way too cool we wouldn't say
something like this
we don't talk like this but
okay eh
i'm gonna pick the last one i like that
one the best to become god is the
longest
wow that's so deep okay i don't know
actually i picked the second to last one
this hell's territory and i'm beholden
to no gas wow
all right what trait do you value the
most diligence perseverance compassion
positivity or humor
perseverance is like holding like like
going through something yeah i think
well i don't know i think you could say
it another way but usually it's like
perseverance but ah it could know could
be like some people with different
accents say it differently oh what's
diligence again diligence it's like a
hard work
like you show up to work every day
you're diligent
what am i you're pretty diligent what
are you saying what would you say
um yeah pretty good perseverance i'd say
two
okay
oh okay what do you think you're going
for um
but is it value about yourself or about
others what training in general i guess
okay
if it's in general i might go for
compassion
me too wait i don't know because i like
compassion and humor oh people are too
fast you got inaudible
[Music]
a lot of innas and amez oh good
wow okay wait they're so fast we gotta
go faster okay
um what's your relationship status
single hopelessly binding single not
looking for anything take him hopelessly
according to my new outfit i don't know
if you heard about this but um when
you're up it is a diandal which is a
german austrian like um
traditional dress but the thing is uh
depending on where you tie the ribbon
it has a meaning if you take it or if
you're single or if you're like a maiden
or whatever
and
there was like some miscommunication
with hookah papa my artist so he put it
on the wrong side which means i'm taken
now i'm not
okay i know what i'm choosing
how do you procrastinate on doing that
one thing
i do literally anything else i have to
do except for the one thing i play video
games and vibe until i pass out or i
bond with other people who have not done
the thing
nothing here says
i just do the thing because i guess it's
always procrastinating
yeah
i just do literally everything else i'll
pick that one me too
pick a fear read them failure loneliness
everyone hated me losing someone i love
embarrassing myself
okay
ah
it it's kind of embarrassing to say out
loud though
maybe they could get it from you know
the the last who we get yeah
uh okay okay describe yourself in one
word mischievous humble kind-hearted
charismatic and pathetic i guess i'm
charismatic maybe oh yeah i'd say i'm
i'm pretty humble yeah
[Laughter]
you're i think you are humble you are
all of these things
mischievous i'll pick that one you are
yeah
but that's probably the good answer
for the baby
are you an introvert or an extrovert i'm
ambiver
me too people think i'm an extrovert but
i like being alone so much i actually
don't want to be with people most of the
time yeah
all right your friend trips in front of
a crowd of people what do you do
what
distract everyone by embarrassing
yourself try to get them to laugh it off
it's no big deal fight everyone anyone
who laughs uh take them away from the
scene as soon as possible
why does it feel like a deja vu to me
because you've taken this before no i
feel like this recently somebody tripped
or i tripped oh i chose recently
that was me
i wonder what i'm thinking of oh well so
um
ah yeah i would just laugh it up and no
big deal you know like that try to make
them not feel embarrassed about it i
probably i don't know this is something
i've done before kind of like distract
everyone by doing something else
that's very nice of you
uh oh pick a color
[Music]
are you gonna pick your color
oh you're gonna pick okay i like both of
these colors very much orange and purple
yeah i like i like all these colors too
it depends
it depends on what it's for i guess just
pick any color i guess i'll pick my
color oh
what's the flaw of yours i think too
little of myself i'm a bit airheaded i
can unintentionally hurt people with my
words i don't think i work hard enough
no matter how much i work
uh or people take advantage of me
because of my kindness
i'm going to take the second to last one
i don't think i work hard enough
[Music]
you work so hard for others yeah but uh
i should i'm gonna stream more what you
know after after all of this i'll get
back to streaming
okay i'm i think
everybody including me will be very
happy about that
i probably
unintentionally
hurt people with my words because i'm so
direct
but nobody nobody ever tells me though
but i am assuming that it happens
so not with me though because i feel
like i know yeah
it's just not how you are but it's just
how you speak sometimes i mean other
people like that too
okay i'm gonna cry now
wait in a bad way no i'm a happy way
who's your favorite hall of myth girl
when we have to pick
it up
that's a surprise
oh that last one emma gave it away my
oshie no now i'm stuck i have to pick
one yeah just i'm not looking you know
if i just pick it like i can speak
honestly
i don't but yeah but i actually don't
know
it's okay
it's okay don't worry about pick
yourself when you're in doubt
pick yourself
i feel like it's selfish i'm gonna get
you too yeah
oh
huh
you can't
okay mine still was kiana but yours is
cali that's interesting
it says you're mature for your age i
guess
yeah
and you i guess you could beat a mom
friend
you are extremely hard working
sometimes
and now i wonder what mine says yeah
what the heck i guess i'm the fake
amelia watson oh someone who got ammo
should send the screenshot to ahmed so
she knows what it says about her yeah dm
me and indiana
oh open the ends yeah
[Music]
yeah we should
okay guys um
sorry that we only could do so yeah but
actually oh it's been an hour i guess
yeah we're kind of on a time crunch at
the moment but we might see you guys
later tonight maybe yeah don't take that
you know uh it's a maybe we don't know
it's a possibility maybe otherwise by
the latest probably tomorrow i think
kelly wants to do the
i think she said she wanted to do a
ttrpg
she told her
she said it on stream i'm pretty sure
so yeah
keep an eye open for anything but we do
have
we need to do this one more stream that
uh we thought off with oh um
with the hands oh yeah yeah
it's fine to say it yeah whether or not
we do it yeah hopefully we'll do it in
the next few days at arm wrestling
competition yeah uh you know maybe with
some 3ds something else only the hands
because i thought it was i really really
loved your stream idea when i saw you
right after the link your wish concert
you're trying to kind of ease in into
using your 3d i think that was what you
used to do i mean i still don't want to
use it too much but yeah when i i did my
twitch debut i guess and i used uh just
the arms yeah i love that i think it was
so funny so cute
yeah and somebody i i posted a twitter
post asking for ideas and somebody i
think said arm wrestling contest and i
was like yeah oh my god this is genius
this could work if we use only the arms
but i think we're all weak as [\h__\h] wow
maybe except you i think that's true no
because yeah i was trying to lift some
my bag earlier
i like dropped it and it was
embarrassing
okay but i mean
maybe compared to you guys i mean callie
says doesn't she like callie might be
one of the stronger ones out of us yeah
yeah
me inaudible
oh
well there's actually something there
well touch
wait you're flexing
okay it's very soft i can't even i can't
even carry my grocery bags
so oh yeah you're carrying your laptop
bag because she gave it to me she's like
i can't carry it i'm gonna try it i was
like i'ma try to see it's so heavy and
she's like
yeah i lifted it like a few feet in the
air i'm like what
no when you hold it longer it gets
really healthy yeah that's true it's
true over time yeah
okay so we gotta go yeah um
look forward to more of collabs guys yes
coming very very soon
yay thank you guys for watching oh yeah
amelia buffson we'll make an appearance
in them no armor
not actually but you know maybe
yeah i think we still have inna's ending
screen
wow
wow beautiful
okay bye everybody thank you for
watching
[Music]
you