[Music]
do
so
[Music]
all already in the game i thought we
wanted to show like the characters yeah
no not in the game
out of the game just showing us
the characters it's like the character
selection
not even i'm outside the gate no hold on
i want to get out of this
chaos if you stay by the gate you'll be
safe okay let me get out of this world
uh
do it okay okay
all right i'm gonna show you guys the
characters now we played this game
before a while ago but back then we
played it with
normal characters however one of the kfp
members called
zero duke shout out to zero luke has
made
mods for all of us as you can see we're
using them
um each of our characters are now modded
into the game and each character has
like
not only these two outfits but also
like special like skills and
and and i don't know funny powers
interactions they can do
yeah powers yeah i mean doesn't have
much power
oh yeah because you already picked your
character you already picked your
character
it's okay it's okay well let's see what
else the stream goes
[Laughter]
every character also has a little
variation for example here i can take
off my hats and it says i agree but i
also don't understand a famous quote by
takana
yeah if you click on your character
the taking off the hats or whatever and
changes the skills but
anyway i'm going to go with the regular
house
without my sword i'm class
a halo or no halo cute yeah let's use
the halo in my onion ring
oh this is not just my onion ring
deep fried halo
this is
like yeah why why is it when i take your
hat off all it says is onion
what does that mean because we have
noticed that when i take off my hats
um i look like an orange onion you know
that is true i could see that
[Laughter]
delicious oh by the way the
announcements will be um at the end of
the stream but we won't play for too
long so don't worry guys
just playing around with the characters
yeah
okay yeah okay
okay let's go kelly's side oh i got it
now i'm fine i'm alive all right
i love you kelly right here this is my
watch don't pick it up
is
okay
[Music]
you guys want to dance with me you can
you can do it if you press
press y and and type forward slash dance
a little smaller morning there we go
i don't know how to ground i don't know
okay so when you pick up whoever is low
on brain juice you got to pick up
flowers and that'll help your brain
juice get bigger
can you eat brain juice
adorable you can eat seeds and berries
but
uh if you build a crock pot it's like
better because you make
full meals yeah i got bubba and he's
been
[Music]
turkey
i can't catch up with them
turkey legs
[Music]
wait wait no i died no it's okay you
can't die you're dead
died but she's sleeping nelly
i think she's immortal i don't think she
can die i love me somebody revived me
i don't think i did anything right now
i'm really working
that turkey down okay listen
okay killed my
wait i didn't i get a double point
wait there's a frog wait i want to try
i'm really not doing great what's the
frog looks y'all
is it is this because i'm good i am like
let's
what
[Music]
with the frogs they're easy to kill if
you make a rabbit trap
but i think you might need gold to make
a science machine
i love the rabbit truck uh
i can have a crimson feather
another tree
[Music]
here i am here let me look at you oh
that's so cute everyone has their own
like individual little picture
girl's got a floaty too that's so cute
what about me what do i have i think
oh wait are you girls i want to show you
my ghost form
where are you where are you can you say
you like it
yeah i can do the soul strike i need to
read more to do that
i don't know how to use my ground pound
see the watson group
oh
yeah you can like possess like if you
try to possess this grass you'll set it
on fire i think
[Music]
wow that's cool it's getting a little
bit late so i'm gonna head back
here oh does anybody have wood it's okay
i can make a small um
chocolate yes that's not helpful here
[Laughter]
i have some tips we made a really
awesome pot before oh i'm kind of i'm
thinking about it again it was like a
crock pot
yeah yeah yeah we have to burn um trees
we have to burn stuff so we get
chocolate
control if you set a tree on fire just
rev normally oh
i guess i can do that it's been killed
how do i get tentacles and squats
i have the lowest health out of
everybody so with great power comes
great responsibility
[Music]
um you could try on the gate maybe
it depends on what game like i picked ah
whoa i want to get some wood look at
your own wood
because i want to try next to cali some
more
no stop there's some oh i found a mold
you're gonna make it so
i can't actually hit this with my scythe
that's unfortunate it's very accurate
you can't do something
does anyone have six rocks how do i gain
health back
uh i have a an injection i can give you
if you'd like some health but it's just
production i have plenty of health okay
all right go to the go to the gate i'll
be right there
okay i'm coming it's gonna be dark so
you guys can make a torch
don't touch my concoctions hold on here
you go
what's it good
eat this carrot oh my okay whoa
oh what is that you don't
above your head oh you're puffed
easy life
oh can i have it yes here you go ina
drop switch you're welcome
[Music]
wait was that supposed to be town uh the
watch concoction i think so
yeah did it not work i just sent me on a
really cool
oh no okay trying to eat oh that's so
cute
there we go
oh okay okay it was really dark
[Music]
all right so let me see i can probably
look at it you can make a
a rabbit trap you can make a rabbit trap
and you can lead the frog into the
rabbit trap and it'll die
nice idea uh i want to make rabbit traps
because
i was getting pretty good at that before
actually yeah you just need grass and
twigs
fishing around you need um you need
spider web
spider webs if you find good it would be
good with that
like fishing
are you okay do that good i'm gonna make
i'm gonna make
the crock pot so i can make a living
life on the end
good idea we need to find gold so if
anybody has gold
or finds gold minecraft
[Music]
hunting is my specialty wait you can't
come back alive
i did it once but now i
died again and now i have a super long
cooldown so i'm just waiting
but then everyone has to come to lunch
so you see how i revive you have to see
it yeah
okay tell me baby yeah tell us when
you're ready
60 seconds i'm coming over
i'm on my way i want to see christopher
revive i would like to also see you
but you know you have the same distance
because everything around me can we get
blue okay
got it just like that one side of
minecraft
oh
[Music]
i think it might make you sick
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah
three two i'm it i'll go
holy [\h__\h] okay
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm i'm sorry my dog your assistant
can send you to another place wait are
you dead forever
you guys i have to guide you
okay we'll either have to find a
touchstone
so you have to explore or you'll have to
build a
resurrection heart which you need reeds
for in the swamp habitat
are there monsters in the water uh it
depends
in some areas there's like the ocean i
think there's monsters in the ocean but
not in the rivers
i don't think so can i hurt them
oh is this a category i mean you drop
something when you die
oh no is it my time i'm getting stupider
i've got you know crystals when you die
i dropped
crystals crystals
[Music]
i didn't get salty what is that oh
there's a drumstick
yeah that's from cali she killed the
turkey
i was really proud of that
that turkey all huh you guys have to be
on quest rez almonds
because you're 12 you got only 12 hp are
you scared oh i found spiders
oh wow you gotta say that man holy
there's a lot of spiders over here
and a gold if you guys want to come over
here oh and there's a wormhole
yeah you can get spider webs and fish
i'm gonna go lazy mushroom okay i'm i'm
to the west
from from the west okay i'll meet you at
the saturday
dropping quite a bit okay i'm hungry
oh wait the same oh i got lots of
options
okay
but we need some stone i dropped like
six stone i think but with six more
stone we can make more
quickly i'm just gonna eat them
oh i dropped some food if you guys need
to eat it i dropped carrots and berries
yes thanks because i'm really not
feeling great where's where am i
you i'll be harry potter okay follow me
oh it's gonna be late soon yeah if you
guys have enough stone
or wood
[Music]
i think you need flint and logs
i i only find nice i'm picking this
up okay oh never mind i didn't need to
do that
my body can i eat
skills
[Music]
although you can see me right bye-bye
i can see you rock like
i can see i can't use my meat
you guys don't believe me i'll stop
existing
but i got some food for you i'm gonna
stay away from you guys
because uh you guys i'm gonna give you
yeah
you guys stay over there now kelly stay
over there i don't want to lower your
sanity because if there's a ghost nearby
it'll like lower your sanity i'll just
go oh wait
killed me
how did you think i died what do you
mean feel yourself i don't know but i
told you
right here
[Laughter]
oh nice nice thank you oh my goodness
guys killed me she didn't
[Laughter]
i guess my skeleton on the floor looks
fine
all right cali follow me yeah this way
okay
i'll lead you to the spiders um i think
i know where they are
let's go if you find what you're not
doing fine
right here so yeah if you have uh we
need some gold
here so we also can get that and then
uh you can set up rabbit traps for the
spiders and then
yeah you could kill them like that
there's a bunch of rocks
on the spider we web need to
build a bunch of stuff well yeah
there's gold here if you guys want to
come
oh it'll start chasing you it's not
chasing
[Music]
i killed it and then you you oh nice
uh so with the spider glen you can make
a house you can make health cells if you
burn like small stuff and make ash and
you can mix it with the spider glands to
make like a booster shot
i think so oh my god get in here
the ultimate dummies
[Applause]
there's so much good [\h__\h] here oh my god
why does it keep making it
you guys can set up rabbit traps and run
into the rabbit traps and
you can lead them into the rabbit traps
and get chapped they won't kill you
anymore
bring them here what is that i went into
a wormhole
[Music]
i don't know i just leaned down to a new
area no wait don't pick it up
put it down
[Music]
i'm sleepy oh wait can i not actually
die yeah you're immortal
yeah you're just sleeping
i want to attack you while the while
you're sleeping and he's working the
ghost
too okay
oh can i eat this food or not
i would not recommend eating mushrooms
[Music]
we won't get any of the spider web from
it lighter blend
i don't know does it set stuff on fire
or does it damage stuff
[Music]
they're gonna figure it out
i need to wake up and eat first it needs
to be the first thing i don't know
okay make sure you pick up the spider
webs these are really good
oh no there's more sliders i'm gonna go
to loop to be honest
okay pick up the stuff that i left
please scoot out it's gonna be
dark soon so if you guys have some uh
stones or something
who died
i need to go back to yeah maybe we
should all go back
how about we leave the spiders for now
just pick up the spider webs if you see
any those are useful
yeah i got a lunchbox for your bag buddy
if you have i think you need 12 stone to
make a permanent fire
i'm trying to pick this up oh no his
name is
oh i can make an axe oh i can make a pic
ooh i can make a
camera i'm scared um
are you scared of guns this morsel wait
you being near me is lowering my sanity
go away
i thought she just lowered calories
i ate the monster me it's okay your
brain juice will just go along
i mean if you cook it it's okay no it'll
still drain your sanity
oh wow there's a really big oh my gosh
attack the crawler
can i hit it with my soul scythe
[Music]
i think it's me lowering your sanity if
you see it going down
oh yeah any ghosts will lower your
sanity
look here i think it's both of us
[Music]
[Laughter]
anniversary come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
i think we're all going to die probably
oh very
and then have some announcements so it's
okay we don't it's
you guys have torches i'm gonna die oh
no my campfire
oh i'm dead
i mean i'm still here but that's because
i have to be
[Laughter]
like five minutes
maybe we should start together
[Music]
i want to go hunting should i come to
you to help you
make the crock pot uh
i don't think i can be saved anymore i'm
a little uh
i'm a little uh dead why can't i
it's dark here we wanna we want to do
this thing
well it makes sense maybe we should have
like uh
like a ghost meeting um i can't wait an
echo
i might talk really far
alone in this universe because i can't
die yeah
can i harm the taco just wait for me no
don't stay away from your mom
please tell me they can't sleep
[Music]
cute yeah it is really cute it mines
sure is the game
it knows how to mine please
no i want my name
oh my gosh it's got this jar cat on top
of you that one's fast
hold on yes do i mean to swim
yes it can swim
[Music]
careful the girl's tried it
all right i say we go to another
timeline we can we can try again
can we respond oh no
the only way we can respond is if we
find a thing in the map called the
touchstone
or we have to make um these revive
potions thingies but it's oh yeah it's
kind of difficult it's gonna be hard
with me
because i continue to kind of go to
sleep over and over again which is the
which is actually kind of worse than not
being able to die
right next to you it's like that's me oh
yeah and you're also right next to me
away with you
ancient one
i'm having a really bad time
i don't think he does anything now yes i
am dead
yeah all done we're all dead
give me the seeds i'm just trying i'm
just living off of seeds to be honest at
this point
i'll tell you something with me
thank you hi oh my god please
[Music]
oh my god you okay you okay
running like not a problem in the world
look at you
[Music]
i lost my sense of direction
with my sword you also lost my respect
when you killed me bye
[Music]
hold on i need to set a trap oh are you
scared
uh you start going crazy and start
seeing monsters and they start attacking
you and then you die
oh okay cool this is like among us
i'm gonna lure a spider here what how is
this like among us my
because most of the game i stand in bed
like a ghost
yeah hi come here
[Music]
yeah i know you want something show me
the lights please
oh yeah it does look like that must be
there hey there's a lot of flowers over
here but there's a lot of also deadly
bees if anyone wants sanity
yeah go
[Music]
are there like caves and stuff in this
game um i think there are caves in
single player but because of the way
caves work
it's not easy to do with multiplayer so
he's not a multi-player
uh-huh but we can make a boat there's
like an ocean
and you can go and get it so i'm gonna
head back but i got a bunch of stuff
where i am now oh no no no no a hat
maybe we can find a touchstone we should
do that try to look for a touchstone it
looks like a coffin
uh surrounded by a sticks with pig heads
on it
oh and if we find one we can resurrect
are they nearby or uh it's like random
got it oh you found it
took my trident that's all right wait
don't don't use it all up though
i'm not using it at all don't worry i'm
just kidding okay because the
ual ghost how do you even recharge it
you can recharge it yeah i think you can
recharge it but i think you need like
some electric doodad or something
oh i found a swamp area this is good
because
okay oh this is really good i have some
room yeah yeah yeah
what we did are you like at the bottom
of the top
where the [\h__\h] i'm in
you keep going straight past that water
and you keep going
you'll see the swamp will be there okay
i'm gonna google it
the heck is that
[Music]
we can resurrect all we need oh okay
it's really easy
wait but do you need demons always
available oh
okay okay it's really easy all right
cali okay
all right allie i need you i need your
help cali
you're the only one who can do this
you're the only one who can say that
what should i do what we need is um
spider glands do you have any of those
yeah i killed a bunch of [\h__\h] spiders
okay um okay
okay if you have spider glands we need
three grass and if you go into like the
tabs on the left side
you should see a heart and you might
it's called a telltale heart and you
should be able to make one it's gonna
take some hp and you'll die
but then you can resurrect one of us
with the heart oh yeah sure thing
i got your bag demon show yourself
is this what's this payback is that why
you followed me the whole time
you're hungry no no no no no no
where's the goddamn fence all right i'm
gonna sleep again i'll i'll do it it's
just i can't find my way back so
that's okay
yeah just just hold on we'll protect you
where are your souls
he goes down when seeing ghosts
considering who i am
[Laughter]
just a little oversight yeah that's true
i love that the souls should
uh ghosts should boost your sanity
instead
since you like collect souls yeah
exactly i love seeing those people like
sanity from other people
oh yeah wait no i'm hungry
you should get sanity monster
just relax just take a nap no brush i
need to build a fire
really quick if i cook the meat then
it'll be fine
i can definitely make those things
though
[Music]
what's grass without the g in the yard
oh my god
[Laughter]
have no grass that's the problem you
know it's really hard to think of jokes
like that in english because it's not my
main language
it was a really good joke i'm so proud
of you i'm so proud of you
hey guys
uh one spider gland close to the gate
really close to the gate because i died
there and i dropped it so there's a
there's another land there
hey guys i have a little problem so i'm
gonna help you
but when i open the tab i don't see any
heart or anything like that
uh it should be under survival the news
oh it's under survival okay
[Laughter]
okay it's not a news it's just like the
survival knot i don't know
let's survive because survival survival
is
good i need ashes
that's the problem is that i need ashes
and actually okay
make a torch and you could burn this
stuff here you could burn this grass you
could burn this grass but pick up the
rabbit traps because that'll burn
yeah okay we're in the trees yeah if you
burn the trees you get charcoal though
okay all right let me go grab it i will
revive
all right carol you need a spider gland
and three grams i'm gonna be cali cam
all right no don't pick up the grass i'm
gonna take this don't burn it this one
pick up
okay i had a bunch of grass where did
some of us should have a ton of grass
because i picked up a bunch
there should be some here by the gate
yeah grass
if you can't see it you can rotate with
q and e yeah there's grass right here
there's four grass hang on there's a
turkey
there's a turkey i'm gonna kill it right
here
oh there's 16 grass right here oh
right here what am i making uh oops
okay okay this tree is cookie i bet it
likes halloween
[Laughter]
cookies yeah it's gone
uh we need one spider glam per person so
there's another spider going by the
spiders too all right and so three grass
i'm gonna go beat up spiders i need to
get back to the gate first i think we
have enough spider glands
uh yes i do but it's not marked on there
oh wait i can see where everyone is
though yeah
yeah okay that's us industry
[Music]
how do i make one potion is it in
survival yeah it's in survival it's
called telltale heart and it's going to
take 40 hp so it's probably going to
kill you
[Music]
oh my god now one of us can can rest you
can ride one of us if you use it on us
you know you want to go first
okay you can go first you're you're more
knowledgeable so
what is this i'll revive you because i'm
phoenix yeah because you killed me and
you should make up for it
[Applause]
i'm back baby let me pick up all this
stuff okay
one and i'll die for that okay
[Music]
okay okay i'll give it to you
i don't know
need another spider gland but that's
your stuff okay i'll hold on to the wall
because it's really important
because i would die oh there's so much
good around here okay
that's okay because we have spiderweb
and twigs now
it's almost nighttime i'll give you
something you can make it
here you make it here you go
okay so you want who wants to come back
first you know
he's gonna be more
[Music]
there is a gland in the spider nest
already it's going to be dark soon
though so
oh yeah does anybody have two stones
i have four rocks yeah sorry
are you sure thank you there you go
you have that one and then she's vibing
okay fine i'll go pick about um
and once kuda is back alive i want to do
a group picture with everyone
there's no cheating too close there's no
such thing as being too close
this is lucy get away
[Music]
sorry oh my god no wait no it's going
off wait it's going up
oh backstage that goes for the fire oh
okay
oh yeah right okay garbo right here
barbara give us a sign
mary david
how old are you [\h__\h] mary davis
[Music]
okay okay okay we can go
kiara if you want to get that one i'll
get it how you doing this one
oh okay i'm just gonna oh over there i
see it
oh i'm coming here no i'm here no
it's okay it's okay for the trap
[Music]
okay i'll set it again okay
all right does anybody have over 40 hp
i do okay if we have two glands then we
can rest chiara with the heart
and then we can all be alive before we
do announcements
oh my goodness there is a daughter after
me
yeah yeah we can if we pick up that
other spider gland in the nest can
anybody get it that one that was there
yeah nice
i got one oh okay nice okay we have two
yeah and i have enough grass
yeah and i have i have ashes as well
don't
do any dashes uh well if we were to keep
playing we would need them because then
we could use it to heal to make like
heal stuff oh i see
oh that's right you have the healing one
okay never mind then all right i'm gonna
drop my [\h__\h] here
okay okay okay okay okay let's see
here's the gland
all right oh put traps down for the
frogs put
okay
okay i'll drop it i'll drop it on the
ground for you so here you go all right
yeah
do you have grass
can resurrect and then we still have two
glands yes survival
cannon and three seconds i think okay
don't do it over here go somewhere else
okay so you know we're as good and then
good i will raise me
oh nice sounds good
careful careful don't leave the frog
what no oh my goodness no i lost hp
yeah yeah keep running eat that run come
on don't get hit by the frog it won't
chase you that far so just go
oh there it got trapped okay it's fine
yeah it takes hp now rez is good enough
i need to heal i'm at 4hp now it's fine
it's fine nothing's going to attack you
give the heart to good up i'll kill the
people
i can't feel the heart yes wait why'd
you lose all your i don't have acp
oh frog maybe um
okay kiara's alive so she can do it how
much hp do you have kiara
oh wait i do have a heart okay okay
glands and grass and you can res me too
here and then gland and grass
right there and then go into survival
survival telltale heart careful there's
a frog here again so ow okay
it went back in all my hp almost
[Music]
i have an idea we can do um we can do
well let me build a fire here too okay
everybody press y
and then when in the typing box you can
type forward slash dance and we can all
line up and we can all dance at the same
time
forward slash dance slide
ready for the photo yes
i don't know i think it's a little bit
covered up from the sky
am i flossing sorry what is this
all right are we letting us pee
i'll go on this side i'll go here okay
right like this
we can do that oh we can't
[Music]
is it sad okay what was that
dude
yay
[Music]
thank you and that's
okay
[Music]
everyone it is the whole live english
myth half year anniversary unbelievable
but it's been six months can you believe
it guys oh my god this is crazy
[Applause]
yay exciting so of course we prepared uh
some things for you many things actually
and yeah
yeah and we will start off
with the second slide everyone move on
to the second side
[Music]
acrylic stains merchandise
english myth penta keychain
[Music]
[Applause]
absolute standing standing perfect okay
so with these stands
um you can buy them separately or you
can buy them together
i say buy them together so that way we
can all be together and we won't get
lonely and we won't miss one another
you can put these on your table you can
put this on your desk above your bed
you can get creative and then send us i
guess send those pictures about how you
plan on displaying them that would be
really fun yeah that would be cool
and yeah stands yay yeah really cute
little stands too they're like different
shapes
it was really cool i don't know how big
they are but yeah hopefully
you think they'll be life size
[Laughter]
[Music]
slide everyone and uh it's being
introduced
this is our second wedge it's gonna be
our mascot penta
the five in one key chain you get all
five of those charms at once yeah
and it's gonna be um put on a leather
strap
i think and it's gonna the leather strap
is gonna have the hollow life english
logo
uh yes very cute five in one what a deal
adorable who's um
the key chains it's possible that we
won't have like a second
um like a second wave of orders so
only one wave of orders
yes yeah yeah if you
[Music]
yeah so the page to buy these will show
up at
booth at uh 5 pm
pst 30 minutes p.m est yeah
soon wait a minute 30 minutes from now
on yes
it will be on geekback and on booth both
and just follow check the official
twitter for the links and
uh the announcements erase yeah
you would faint
however
oh it's my turn okay well i guess
um um it's it i'm supposed to
introduce this one but we uh have a
little
it's actually more of um sorry big
stretch
it's actually uh we're gonna let it do
uh the talking itself and then talk
about it afterwards yeah
indeed um so anyway i guess we'll go
ahead and kind of count it down
but uh you guys um you guys will all get
to
see in real time with us yes
something real special coming extra soon
okay
so everyone shut up i'm going to mute
you guys really quick
all right everyone i'm going all right
i'm going
from four and then click on go okay it's
very important
okay
no
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
yes indeed let's go let's move right
along to the next one
this is an image soundtrack
for a whole live english myth
[Applause]
[Music]
very special our own very special uh i
guess
image uh bgm made for us it's
instrumental
um i think we'll actually probably be
using them in streams i know i will at
least
cause vgm that was kind of the intention
but you guys can also get it for
yourselves as well
releasing everywhere march 14th local
time
for you wherever you are 2021 so uh get
it or
be be square be circled yeah
and a lot of people ask but yeah there's
no vocals there's a bgm
but maybe yes i could totally hear cali
rapping to hers
oh yeah i would love to hear it like oh
man am i going to rap to this like oh
okay
it's bgm but still ahead of it
and all tracks are made by camellia
incredible yeah every track really uh
suits each person so i think
maybe we want to get a little comment
what do you think about your song callie
freaking dope when i heard it for the
first time i was like wow this is like a
combination of um everything that i
think makes up me it's got
like this kind of regal and like um
almost like a
gothic tone to it i guess dark
mysterious oh
it's also [\h__\h] dope i don't know it's
uh gangster there's a little bit of
hip-hop in there yeah
i like i can bob my head to it which is
why the title is really good
um that's not good
it's perfect for me what about you guys
and my
second track is mine yeah and it's
i love how the title uh actually um is
like for it stands for kfp it's kiara
fry
um
you can also say like at a party you can
be like oh i get i get all the
other popular kids and the clubs are
like i can't i can't
raise raise the raise the volume yeah
raise the roof
yeah and uh my
my thing is pretty energetic pretty
happy pretty kawaii cute
boppy poppy puppy style so i'm really
excited
to um have that being played in the kfp
stores all over the world worldwide
franchise obviously so it's going to be
played in every store
for until we all die yes
the first track is the enos track yes
uh i really like mine because it has
like kind of like the oriental feel and
it's like really chill
and i can listen to it like forever and
loop i probably will
i really really really like it
[Music]
thank you thank you either too i was
bopping to it while i was playing while
i was playing i was like
this is so good yeah
and the fourth track is i think good ass
track right adventure
shark adventure delicious absolutely
delicious finger looking good baseline i
get the i get the snake face every time
i hear it
the first time i heard that i was
a rhythm gamer senses
you gotta play it very loud get that
baseline to full potential
it's so funky and it's got the i think
it's the shamasan maybe
also it's got my favorite instrument
and the baseline and i melt when i hear
it and then i dance to the beat i'm just
i'm in love with it i'm over the heels
over the moon
yeah the last one is mine and it sounds
like a pop
yeah it sounds i don't know it kind of
sounds like a nostalgic like it almost
sounds like a song from like an older
game
it's really nice and it's called miss t
this like mischievous you guys got it
yeah i thought it was a typhoon
like i'm gonna be having it on loop for
like five
months all of them in my playlist
immediately
i think it's the first time that like
some like whole life members like
release
like just like background oh ost like
kind of music just a soundtrack
and normally everyone releases songs
with their singing in it but we
we're going to do things a little bit
different right i mean it would be cool
if
one day we also have songs together
where we're actually singing
is that what image soundtrack means like
image soundtrack just means like
that i think yeah like like
uh yeah it's like concept art but like
yeah
like music exactly your life's
if you your life had a bgm
[Music]
one of my goals was actually to make bgm
for all of you guys but it looks like
[Music]
i still like the album cover i'm just
looking at it now it's like a shield and
then it has his scythe and like the
tentacles and tried it yeah
my shield is like in the middle
protecting you from danger yeah
yeah it's got like the nether portal on
the back
oh god
[Laughter]
this is the portal that leads you into
the darkness that the rabbit hole of her
life with that being said i know we're
all
uh very excited but there is actually
one more thing but wait wait one more
without chilling yet okay after my drum
roll then you guys can show it okay
[Music]
mascot plushies
we have kiara's bird what is the name
again i forgot yeah
recently we renamed it very recently
actually the reason
uh why i asked my viewers like two weeks
ago or three weeks ago for a name is for
this
and we named it here
my last name normally is read as koto
ni so it has two
ways to read it so actually we write it
differently for this one but
actually my takanashi can be right is
kotori too funny
funny thing that's cute and it looks a
little feather at the top too it's got a
hat like
yeah and then we have bubba
it's like the it's like an anime scene
like a battle scene where it's like
and it's jose's eyes the bubble is
really cute and brown
and then we have a cali's death sensei
oh
hey you guys get to me
and then we have good as bloop they're
all so cute
who looks like he's about to commit very
very very very
illegal crimes
comes blue eyes are right
[Laughter]
i'm so excited please coming soon
tm
[Music]
let's do a balancing contest you can
balance them on top of each other
no cheating no cheating you have to
there can't be any support around them
you just need to be on top of each other
winner again
i don't know my endless love and
affection maybe
did we mention that these are designed
by ina
oh yeah you know designed these yeah
designed all of them
i'm looking forward to my thick fat ass
burp
um i'm excited to grill it grill yeah
you know i think if you burn it i don't
think it'll come back
yeah probably not maybe don't do that
i'm going to put all of them on my bed
well yeah so that is
uh key chains that then the acrylic
stands
and then the album and uh the plushies
look forward to it i guess we'll be
posted
on twitter and i think uh if you're not
on twitter then maybe we'll do community
posts or i don't know probably also
going to be on the under hello live
um maybe i don't know but if you if
you're on twitter i'll probably put a
link in my description in the future
streams maybe the other girls will do
that too yes
yay
i had so much fun drawing them also
please look forward to it
yay thank you very nice
well then that was pretty much it thank
you everyone uh for joining in on the
streams today for celebrating together
with us
does anyone here have some individual
announcements that have nothing to do
with the merchandise then do it now
yeah um okay so basically
first i just want to say to everyone uh
thanks so much for your support in the
chat
super chats will be read next time next
time okay
so look forward to that uh at the in the
just chatting and also um
my my new ep is coming out very soon
my birthday yes that's right it's coming
out on my birthday uh so please
anticipate it um i'm working really hard
on it
and you can actually pre-order it um as
well
uh you can check my twitter for the link
i'm gonna go ahead and retweet it again
after this you can pre-order a physical
copy get special stickers
it does ship overseas um
and uh yeah if you don't want to get a
physical copy
because overseas shipping is uh kind of
scary i understand that
um you can just go ahead and stream it
as well
it'll be coming to all streaming
platforms um on the same day
exactly so so you guys can check it out
there um
please check it it would really it would
really make my day and make my birthday
really happy if you could at least
uh get give it a shot give it a little
listen just a little listen you know
uh whatever yes
so yeah look forward to it that's the
only announcement that i have for now
and this time
announcements everyone can also just say
a nice message so
move on with ame yeah uh
yeah i wanted to like talk a little bit
like about how
six months have been for us and stuff
like that uh for me
i don't know how life has been like kind
of life-changing and
i know a lot of you guys too it's like
so much work
and i don't know i'm really grateful to
be with you guys too because i think
everybody like we just contribute so
much to
the group in general and
everybody also who worked on hololens
like behind the scenes and stuff all
this stuff too
everybody puts in so much work so i want
to thank you guys for six months
and more months to come and we'll do it
again on the one year anniversary
we'll have more stuff yeah thank you
guys so much for the past six months i
really appreciate it i don't have any
announcements other than that though
thank you
i would like to announce that i love you
all
[Laughter]
ceiling's about to leak
yeah thank you let's do our best from
now on
yeah love you all
thank you for everyone's hard work
that's it
that's all i would like to also say
oh my god say
thank you to this absolutely incredible
team of the most lovely people my gen
mates that have changed my life for the
better
um
i'm really lucky to be surrounded by
such really great people
did you write something did you write a
letter no no
i don't
[Laughter]
thank you to you guys each one of you
you've been so incredible this past
month and i want to say thank you to all
of you that are watching no matter where
you come from thank you oh my god you're
crying good afternoon
you're making me cry
[Laughter]
well okay i think that's all okay
okay okay yeah don't be sorry it's tears
of happiness
no territory
yes well uh from my side uh um i'm
celebrating the half year anniversary in
a
few hours when i don't know 15 10 i
don't know how many hours
uh with a whole life original songs
only kind of okay i've been learning a
lot of songs
uh from our senpais to uh show them to
you guys tomorrow
or today oh i heard a kitty cat is that
oh that's my channel
that's my cat uh yeah and um i also
just uh i'll probably get more into deep
detail about how i feel
about uh this half year in that stream
but generally i just want to say
i hope that uh when when we do our one
year anniversary
that we can all be together in one room
and just hug each other
and yeah you know that would be really
nice because now i hear gouda
crying i mean you're sad i want to hug
her i wish i could hunger
[Music]
so let's work towards that making that a
reality making for dear reality making
new outfits our reality and making a
long long
uh future together with us and there's
some kohi's as well
and a reality and making whole live
english even bigger than it already
is yeah yeah let's do it
wait a minute i want to give a sappy
message too
um actually i'm really bad at the sappy
stuff but i just want to say
i just want to say um i really wanted to
do
um creative stuff full-time when i was
just a reaper
um and because of everyone's really kind
support
i was able to get um the chance to do
that uh but i wouldn't have been able to
continue on uh like this if it weren't
for you guys i definitely couldn't have
done it alone so
um thank you guys before we start back
for being great gem mates i don't i
think that um
i mean i can't even imagine a world
where anyone else um
where anyone is not here or or different
or anything like that
i don't want to uh because everything
just kind of fell into place
exactly i feel like how it how it should
have been
um and i'm just really grateful thank
you so much
i'm glad that it's fine i'm so glad to
have the exactly these members hey
yeah you look so badly here
i do want to give one last thanks to to
the viewers yeah like good like gooda
said yeah
it's really yeah the support you guys
all show all of us
is crazy so many people from all around
the world to me that's like the most
mind-boggling thing that's just from
everywhere people are watching and uh i
really appreciate it i know
everybody else does too thank you guys
for your support
we wouldn't be here without you guys
yeah first thing you wouldn't be able to
do this at all actually
thank you the deadbeats teammates
takodachi's
kfb
many many fun memories from now on as
well together yes
all right then i think that's
it yeah we're gonna have a look after
party privately right on discord
so thank you everyone for watching thank
you bye
thank you thank you so much on the flip
side everybody
[Music]
bye
do
see you guys soon but
i want to say thank you for six months