[Music]
Hello
hi sorry I'm
late as
usual Hello
[Music]
everyone I'm at the beach Crazy it's
really cool
Wow it's
so beautiful wearing this Summer dress,
you guys look at
this Come on, wait a minute, the microphone will
move aside
[Music]
Here
we are now, our theme  The theme is we're going to
the beach, guys, are you late? No, you're
not late. The
theme is that we're going to
party at the beach now, okay?
[Music]
Okay, today's plan is we're going to do karaoke,
but short karaoke.
Okay, short karaoke only, not
[Music]
G
but the gu  yes this is some gu unfortunately
can't come So like
eh we
make we make we make fun happy happy
together with the guest who is there okay okay
e what do you sing okay First song First
song First song First song What do you want
War B no okay
already already war  -war Tokopedia singing
is
okay, let's sing something relaxed
first, okay? Okay, let's sing a Chill song
first.
Okay, where is my mic. Okay, I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Hahahaha. Okay, we
eh eh tib.  eh
suddenly in the park E oh sorry sorry
sorry okay
okay I'll be right [Music]
here夏き
[Music]
Riri [
Music] [Music]
kacangan瞬
[Music] [Music] [Music
]
も君将来
[Music]  ] [
Music] [
Music]
Oh, come on, let's sing
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [  [
Music]
将希望 How do you sing
[Music]
Yes, that's the appearance of this, why did
I become like this? Thank you
k
thank My m is like I don't know
why My m is
like wait wait Okay I will recalibrating
myselfit
[Music]
okay that's the performance from Koba with
R Ar
Okay wait
Yao give me the
title title So the first one is
Ririka
singing the song
wisheng
Secret
B Secret
Base
[Music]
bye
Z I'll make it clear let
me
[Music]
That's our first gu wait let
me the and the super chat
not
Al next gu Who is it Who is it
Ririka is already here let's call
her friend maybe
let's call her  Maybe his friend is
wait let me
[Music]
okay I wanted to cry but I didn't. There were
some parts where Rik should have sung.
We sang together but instead
he just kept quiet. Okay, just sing it by yourself.
Okay, the next person is
Let Me Let Me Move here
First.
How about it?  Siho
okay
[Music]
[Music] It's
okay to be here
[Music]
う
[
Music] [
Music]
[Applause]
レス守こで
[Music] [
Music]
首
[Music]
の靴
unas
[Music]
te
別
[Music]
ぎ
k
[Music]
k is having a
hard time again, right? What's wrong with
jumping around, jumping around, jumping around? It's
probably best not to
jump around at all.
Okay, I think it's  better If not jumping
jumping yes wait
Okay I'm done I'm done calibrating again
So I think it's it's song I need to
recalibrate
for song
yes anjoy
okay there was a
and we sang Romeo and
Cinderella by dorico
[Music]
every time
I sing
guik not to his guest  funny I also
understand the name
too I
think I don't want a song that's
too funny
okay I think this one is a cute song cute
song
okay
yes wait where is it Okay I don't want to
jump around Okay I want to be jumping
jumping Okay let's
go bury
spai  Happy birthday thank
[Applause]
[Music]
give me give
me
[Music]
て
bab
[Music]
love
B [
Music]
love
[Music]
me [Music
]
胸
[Music] [Music
]
[Applause]
[Music]
bab baby
baby
[Music]
set happy
birthday
[Music]
I like
that song sweet
Berry baby love what's the title of it baby
baby it's me
Gaga baby gugu  gaga baby sweet
Berry
[Music]
by in
Okay, the reverb can't be turned on,
the reverb can't be heard, okay, wait
a minute
[Music]
ahik, there should be more reverb now,
it should be more solid, it
should be
yeah the sound is a bit small oh yeah Here I'll
increase the calibration
bo yeah Wait a minute for each song we
calibrate our gaming guys Later yeah sorry
[Music]
Sorry
Okay, that's right again guys I'm
back to normal
Okay next next gu is hmm This is it this is
it  oh okay okay okay okay his friend
now
his friend's friend Okay let's go Next song
who suddenly appeared from
below Anjay let's go Mommy yeah yeah
yeah This is my favorite song
[Music] here he is
right
[Music]
yeah
jikaak
[Music]
I'm
sorry
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] t yo yo
kor
Ah
[Music]
yes [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
wait  is it my
[Applause]
[Music]
part
worry just playing games I know that's
plastic and the plastic be
another morning
[Music]
comes just playing games I know that's
plastic
[Music]
to the to
another I'm just playing games I know
that's
plastic dance the PL be
another morning
come
ya klik the mouse
baby wait the rivb the wait Let Me Let
Me hear my own
reverb let me hear my own reverb ah
check now the reverb  is It's OK It's not
that much it's not that
less the reverb is
here the reverb listen
the damn That's a reverb Right
There Yeah it's okay it's
okay it's good like this I don't
like big reverb
because
Leave it I don't'  t really like big reverb is
ok
[Music]
Mar Yes that was the song we
with no
n PL
[Music]
Okay
next there's Bang Akim I swear where's
Bangim Oh yeah War maybe
bang eh is it okay if I  Karaoke
War here haven't asked for Tokpet
ih haven't asked for Tokpet
ih
Sis, you can sing
Warad bangety
the song is
available every 2
pm, my
hands are calibrating
again, wow
[Music]
bye
bye I'm ready for the next song
yes okay Next song
is let's
see let's
[Music]
see I've grown up Mik I'm
now let's see
M Wow, not this one, later, this is the
last one  trk-terak this is the last one
okay Next song is from the [ __ ] board
let's
go
I
[Music]
Black
I don't want to shake much
let's go
[Music]
hak
崩
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
to That's our bir
ha let's
go your way take your way
[
Music] yo [
Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
SH
rocker
Man he
[Music]
crazy
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
Black
Haj
maruno
Mat
[  [Music]
Monat
[Music]
That song is very tiring, I don't want to jump too much,
guys, that song is very
very tiring to sing but very very fun to
sing
[Music]
okay ha
K Black Rock Shooter by
R Okay let's go next gu We
Sing Aduh this time
this time Oh Next gu
okay this one first So that we don't get
too tired, let's just laugh
because this is really making people laugh
this is
really funny let's
[Music]
go
だだ不世界
[Music] なで
見え ない
の中先 だだ ない
[Music]
one two
世
[Music]
let隣 let's go h
の 町 から景 は
[
Music]
[Music]
One Two
3 [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Oh Gama  don't send l2d so
just chicken yeah guys
yeah Kim
[Music]
kimケ僕
[
Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
let let's
go
yeay ko
Salamat Iya mantap thank
[Music]
youamp
amato Hai aligato
Mina dah  Oh, the kobon is gone
too, wait, I'm also gone.
Okay, I'm back. The
four of them are hilarious when put together.
What's the name of this gaming joke
?  what group what Citayam what at that time Yeah
we forgot basically huh
Okay wait
Okay from pok
one one
[Music]
su
uppr one
two first opening
for for pokéon journeys
after the rain this is it
Yeah next Okay Ouch my
throat hurts my th
is a b but
wait  let me
[Music]
myali
Okay I'm back Next song
[Music]
Okay ah Next song yes okay This is it
this is it okay this is it Let's go Let's go
Let's go Let's go
[Music]  ]
Brother PP
ap
[Music]
I have a Pan I have an
[Music] apple apple pan I have a Pan I have Pineapple Pineapple Pan apple pan Pineapple Pan Pineapple apple pan joget apaan sih Gus Anjir ple [Music] yo [Music]
I  have a Uh I don't know ah I have I
don't know I have an Apple I have
Pineapple Apple Pineapple I have I don't
know Apple
[Music]
pineappleen Pineapple
Apple
pen Pineapple apple
[Music]
pan
ngapain
ragus wes
Jan
[Music]
joget with
me with
me no hazing
hak
anjing anjing si
[Music]
hakagus
bagus
PP
PP from
pikaro
pikaro I have Ah oke oke oke
oke I will sing it again
l l no no Wor no The L
Ok
[Music]
Sor
P
[Music]
ap I have a Pan I have an Apple uh apple
pan I have a Pan I have
Pineapple Oh Pineapple Pan apple pan
Pineapple
pan pan Pineapple apple
[Music]
pan P  Pineapple apple pan dance
Time
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
I have a pen I have a pen uh long
pen I have an Apple I have
Pineapple Apple Pineapple long p Apple
[Music]  ]
Pineapple Pineapple apple
pan pen Pineapple Apple
[Music]
p
Now I have the lyrics right
Thank you
okay okay steady hesitate Thank you hesitate
steady BR set
invite invite  sing karaoke or
martial arts ah later this won't be
good Huh
Okay continue
Eh this is it,
this is not it
Hmm
maate mate maate
maate
[Music]
maateate Where is it Where is
it Where where is it wa wa wait wait
ah wait
wait
Okay I want to sing this  with with with
this my lovely person senai but I need
to eh I need to censor her clothes
because
of I don't know my Manager told me so so
I need
to I need to be right
need
Yes
Yes I'm sorry guys my Manager  told me so
so
yes complicated rbet Emang
ya complicated
Emang
tommate
nah this this is what i
want this is what i mean okay okay
okay let's
go
all sorts of things
I think this ok this fine Okay
sorry because it's on my
channel Yes let's
[Music]
go
u nak
[Music]
ehaini
bagus
[Music] [
Music]
め
[Music]
gone Where my hand Why It's like
that
[Music]
ya
Okay I'm back Okay Okay Okay next oh wait
wait wait before that
eh that was ha
camaama ha cama
[Music]
from Where there is I'm jealous funny ma'am not jealous
later I'm afraid YouTube will take it down
tahahak I understand anyway if I'm
told I
obey next
Okay  let's go this song is very
l let's
go
wait looking for the
lyris there's no
lyrics Oh oke Here We
Go
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
indonesiasahayar
Dun masal datang pergi sudah
biasa sendiri
lagi untuk
[Music]
daydreaming of various dreams will not
solve the
problem of trying to
break through all the
dreams the dreams never stop there is
still
your love here Without dimensions come and the
light shines on
your days Remove all the doubts
that cover your
heart and emotions of your eyes bring
light to new things
it's your thank you  you for coming to my
[Music]
birthday ye ye ye
po love you love you
[Music]
to you're not  gna say anything to your
son ​​It's your is my
birthday
No not even a
word
Bro are you [ __ ] serious
What whatever Bro lame
lame What the heck
Man bye bye that next time I want to come
to your birthday
bye bro
oke the
was the  rain spell
the the
family
bobo
Yara rain spell
[Music]
Bob thank you
okay we're already ah at the end of the event
so This is the last song Yes this is this is
this will be the last song
Why l song yes You guys just listen to it
you hear this song like what
okay I'm not ready I'm not ready
forong
ready not ready
[Music]
ready really ugly dog ​​repeat ah
repeat
[Music]
lah what is
it
[Music]
lah
[Music] [
Music]
serada
[Music]
se  You're not so scary Hey
I'm even scarier
[Music]
dong
low blood pressure
[Music] wait
a minute
[Music]
goto
parad Dark
[Music]
paradтова
y
bir Thank you for
and I already told you even though Si Mel Mel
later we will sing this song, okay Then you
have to sing it, the one who rocks, the one who rocks,
it's really calm, eh,
yes, that was the last song, okay, t song,
d t song, D UN
Revel  crazy is called groll
Mang
grow UN
rvel
from
by
e kitaajim
okay
[ __ ] fuing
tired yes
Okay take note Okay screenshot
Okay Okay then I'm
done Eh but I want to sing
this
[Music]
jam
Sodi Thank you Welcome To The
Stream  Welcome To The Stream Thank you
for the Happy [
Music]
birthday No don't even don't
even you don't even say happy birth when
BR
pe
whatever whatever
[Music]
tut maat [
Music]
ya Ng yuk yuk
we're happy  -happy war war
war W War W War Kobo made the lyrics
and Bangakim also made the melody
ee Kobo made it Yes We Made It
together
[Music] wait a
minute
Wah let's go  Come on, come on,
come on, don't forget, guys
[Music]
Topet
Tokopedia every 2 pm check Tokopedia
on Tokopedia any goods also check
Tokopedia Tokopedia is ready every
2 pm disk disk all goods are available
[Music]
disk every 2 pm check
Tokopedia, be satisfied  scrolling search for goods
mandil check Tokopedia eh War Tokopedia
121 don't
forget War Tokopedia 121 come on come on once
again come on for the closing
come on
Yes so that you are reminded of
the song and keep checking Tokopedia war
war Tokopedia every 2 pm check
Tokopedia Tokopedia any goods also
check
Tokopedia W Tokopedia is ready every
hour at 2 pm discounts discounts on all items
there are discounts kag check
[Music]
out
a every hour at 2 pm check Tokopedia at war
war Tokopedia any items also check
Tokopedia
eh
where is
this kokopedia every hour at 2 pm
tokia tokia goods  whatever in
tokia Tokopedia is ready every 2
pm Dis all the goods are there  kag
[Music]
out Come on, what are you waiting for, check out
kanjangwopia
I'm
satisfied scrolling looking for stuff,
check Tokopedia
[Music]
Eh nah