[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
he
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
he
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
he
hello wow
hello
[Music]
wow
k k
[Music]
we're in the game wo why am I so
framy right I thought it was I'm kind of
lagging a little bit wait what happened
both
lagging wait it wasn't it wasn't this
before eh oh it was fine before it was
fine before wait what happened it do be
like that sometimes I think I had that
with other games before yeah I'm not
sure why you tapped into the game or out
of the game I'm tapped into the game but
like before stream started our models
was moving fine um maybe cap the frame
rate I don't know if they can cap the
frame rate in this game usually the
model lags it's the graphics car going
oh my God graic there's a lot of stuff
going on yeah the the frame the frame is
is
C maybe maybe it's just for of us
together vyncs on that's usually what if
I turn it off turn it off turn it off
vsync is evil really VN usually helps it
depends yeah sometimes it's better to
turn it off sometimes it's better to
turn it on I've made both experiences
well the game the game itself isn't
lagging it's just
us it's time for p maybe maybe it's time
for p but it was we before stream start
was working fine it's really laggy fora
too um for me the game is a little bit
laggy but the model is fine oh I'm the
opposite the the game is fine the models
are laggy oh oh I mean that's better you
don't want to see a laggy
game um I probably
PNG should be find in yeah yeah it might
be it might be the the room together
that could be
it you can do the Discord light up thing
if you have it ready oh wait I tabed it
wait what ahuh it's the tabbing that
changes things often oh I depending on
where you're tabing into we're fine I T
if I tab into I can't our thing it's
fine but if I tap into the game it's not
fine
[Music]
mhm uh I instead of
tapping like uh I don't know if it works
cuz sometimes I don't tab I just click
off of the screen and it's fine I don't
know if that helps okay let me see I
thought I mine is fine now after all
tabing back and forth okay maybe I
should rapidly all tab back and for
[Laughter]
what if you do you have a window mode
right now or full screen what um input
capture are you using
for game
capture try full screening the game oh
yeah maybe I can un full screen the game
uh where is
that oh it's already border
Rel m is window okay mine is window now
maybe if
I maybe if I try full screen let's try
full
screen if I can become PNG that's
totally fine
too I have this with some games too but
it's been a while so I don't really
remember any
solution but while we're fixing this
maybe we can talk about our character
choices which who has
which what was my character called again
uh
uh she called again fairy Fair the furry
yeah um the furry the furry she's the
furry yeah for most of the game I think
I used a different character but then
later in the game I switched to fairy so
that we have more variety as well and I
don't remember how to play here but I'll
I'll support you with my ghosts I think
my Whip and my ghost you can watch me
Whip and you can watch me nigh neigh
yay I want to change the color so it
looks a little bit more orange thank you
bio for teaching me how to
do is her is this her original skin is
it is is she pink no she's blue she's
original yeah oh okay H actually I just
realized
bio you are you like the ideal version
of yourself like like small but big
boobies yes this is n is what I aspire
to become one day that's why I play her
totally cool on Nan with katana yes this
is she is everything I want to be or or
is this just what you see when you look
into the mirror yeah even has the evil
bang
yeah I'm sure it'll happen evil I'm sure
thank you thank you for believing of
me one day I can totally see it like the
hair color totally sells it
yeah the hairstyle is like um the the
the infamous anime Mom
oh isn't that isn't that like the one
the one ponytail over the shoulder
that's normally the one ponytail but I
guess the hair covering one eye is also
covering one eye
kind okay then what's Zeta playing not
Zeta what the hell is
not but didn't you want to switch the
character um maybe after this after we
figure out what kind of team comp we
want but um my team is full blonde team
oh I go with Zeta kostro and Char
Char I mean I mean charot but sometimes
I would play kago but not Zeta I don't
know Zeta Zeta is not Zing for me I see
she's not enough a little bit too
complicated okay and then Ena is tiny as
hell Ina potato pot y cute
[Music]
my M your crown your crown is like as
tall as your shoes from your default
[Laughter]
outfit okay my default outfits shoes are
dad
big it feels like
that but I'm potato but to balance the
power level of the party I won't be
playing potato today oh no
potato no PO potato we get to high level
oh you're you're a cool dude now who is
this who's that play a uh aista aista a
aista aista aista yeah can I get a a
frappucino
vanilla
aista wait his name is actually a bista
sand phone sandone sand phone Sandy
Sandy oh s
sand
Al sand alen alen is his name is it
alphan sand Mr alphan sand he looks so
edgy he's wearing high
heels he is
Edy to be why'd you call him a barista
what's the
[Music]
lore it's a long story oh
oh he doesn't look like he would be a
barista to be honest like two days ago
so I was like you
know oh nice
sword all
flexing okay nice hey what level is that
character uh 76 oh so we're about the
same
level
oh oh yeah no 76 oh I heard 36 yeah 76
yeah we have a little bit of a power Gap
uh Zeta and me are like around 40 and
biu and Ena are like 70 but does it
matter does it get adjusted like when we
play together I don't know how it works
but when I when I played with randoms
before they kill things in like 2
seconds but I don't think I have the
gear to like kill things in 2 seconds so
I think it's
fine well G we be strong yeah we'll be
fine it's it's fair right we got like
two four tiers and then two 7 car yeah
I'll do my best I don't remember how to
play I have no idea how to play
me NE I don't know the buttons anymore
oh but uh me and Zeta have not played
the epilogue yet but so it seems like
we're starting with the epilogue group
quests or so yeah yeah okay okay that we
you guys accept the
quests
uh undertake
quest uh wait no okay I think I might
actually have to revert to PNG let me
just just check real fast fine
okay is there right quest uh uh can I
click this oh I can make a
request ah
um uh how do I know I have a lot of
quests how do I know which one is the
right one um there should be ones where
it has like a mark well if you want to
progress the story you can do anything
with the Mark or okay yeah so any Quest
that you haven't
done it's definitely the four people cuz
me alone is fine so I'm going to have to
revert you guys to
pngs okay okay I'm sorry no
problem and are G is there a sign to see
whether the quests are Solo or group
quests everything is a group Quest I
think or can be done in group okay it's
only when there's like a
story um what call it well actually you
I don't think you'll see the story
Quest it could it be that some of these
quests are from before I finished the
game so it's like as long as I think you
hit like the highest level difficulty
should
be okay should be
fine uh cuz I have like 10 quests or so
yeah you'll get a lot of new quests just
go through one by one okay okay you can
will will you guys will help me do my
homework I
suppose then I'll just start from the
top okay okay it's a a normal survival
quest it says spare the rod spoil the
valley defeat as many foes as
possible uh in some snowy regions
uh undertake Quest We Are The
Undertaker mat part for Quest of current
party
okay okay let me
press I'm going to play Ki for the he
okay thank you for your
service let's go I will not be support
at all only Dam
I'm playing so just for this just for
this time oh I I think I have a heal too
if you guys need need it yay double
heels oh on the controller which buttons
are the attack buttons like top or left
square square is attack Square okay
yeah okay it's been a while yeah is
there a focus on on a the is there focus
on one character
okay I'm doing fine
even
oh what's this
grab you can throw
that oh the B there's
money money money
money we got to sh we got to put it into
a shared account cuz we're playing
together is that how it
works do we have to share the do we yeah
do we have to share I mean okay if
you're asking seriously I don't
know yeah that's question who gets the
reward maybe all of us yeah everyone but
like not Shar just like everybody gets
the th amount am
like
this yeah you can just look
Prett all right I remember
to okay I'm starting to slowly remember
how to
play wasn't there always like a ranking
at the end of the game that tells you
who did the most D all
that uhoh I don't want to see I like
bom this is really a lot of
[Music]
En wait are we done
no oh I got to turn the game down sound
protect me protect me
I don't even I don't know it's so CH I
don't know where you
are it's so it's so it's so shiny I
don't know where everyone
is okay I'm back in
Action welcome back these ones they're
so cute I like
them oh I just now remembered that with
fairy you don't button mess but you PR
continue press the same
button like you press it down for
several seconds I just
remembered where are the bad guys here
they are oh that's actually why I don't
play Zeta that much she has like she
needs like order and like structure and
and I'm like no I just want a button
Mas I get it
level
up let's go I feel like I you guys you
guys are so strong there's no chance for
me to heal yeah these wave CLE quests
are really good for
oh wow I'm
grinding I feel like we're playing an
mmpg together right now I love this
feeling I'm in the bubble bubble where
where I'm I'm out of the bubble
take this bom stupid
eyeballs 10 seconds remaining oh I
forgot
skills I found the skills
nice time up time's up nice nice too
late I would have wanted to see
everyone's what is it called the the old
the sky oh we got to fight a
boss yeah maybe a harder boss we can
don't remember how to do
alt like left stick right stick you
click both I see oh
okay that's
manageable
oh
M
wow
D Dam
my smell
weakness my smell weakness that imagine
the smell imagine the
smell what does weakness smell like
sweat I guess salt maybe or blood cuz
they're dead oh Rotting
Flesh oh decompos okay we got s++
beautiful
nice are you done reviewing Quest
results yes returning to town
yes nice one done next one I already to
turn off the character voices cuz you
guys sound so much like anime girls that
I get confused says
youo
says I want
to
PO potato potato just
want okay next we're going to defeat a
griffin it's a boss fight okay ready
okay uh clear with let's clear within 5
minutes okay
ready ready let's
go oh that's you changed into tiny pot
potato potato my favorite potato oops I
forgot to
press okay here we go
again the strongest party of anime girls
that her crown is made out of waffles
waffles why kind of look like
waffles I'm sure it's real
gold no not
waffles it's flying oh okay okay I
remember now I got invincibility frame
let's
go come here get out of the sky The
Flash pod yeah Flash got
it wait we're not playing Monster
Hunter someone get him down who wait w w
w
w is that his
HP
yeah oh he's level 20
oh it may have been an older Quest I
don't
know wait what I don't know if this is
normal this is a damage not an epil
Quest okay we got the rewards make get
the reward yeah easy we're just that Pro
that was so easy I did nothing but
breathe the whole
time W yeah I don't think I even got a
single hit
in yay
y we'll be done in no time with all the
quests like this
nice do you guys skip cutcenes or no I
always like to watch the anime girls
being
cute you I never skip cut scene
oh K her
by we didn't do anything me and
T let's
go we were he was up so high on that's
good I kept on jumping and couldn't hit
him
yeah g Griffin is a little Annoying
participation
reward yeah you still get you still get
participation rewards it's
fine let's blame it on the you know on
the fact that you girls are really high
leveled so you know exactly we couldn't
do anything it was it was level 20 you
guys are technically overlevel
too that is true
ah I won by doing absolutely
nothing okay take take that win take it
we need those wins to balance out the
L's how did the Griffin smell like Ina
did you smell
weakness I did not smell weakness what
you did it was not part of my my uh MVP
line oh it didn't smell
weakness okay we're going to do another
another a boss okay don't don't know
what level this one is but it's a furry
cane furry oh that's the fur story
bosses a fury cane okay don't worry I
always think it's fur cane
too which one was this oh is it the wi
one horse looking thing oh but it it
turns into a lady or something like that
right yeah I don't remember anything
looking one I it's been months for me
remember don't remember wind
Primal yeah this this one
yeah wow furry cane furry cane furry
cane fur furrie sounds more like
hurricane so I think it should be
furricane not Fury
[Music]
cane oh wa what wait what wait what
Just Got
Started what is he
dead is he is face Two Face two no come
on he's dead okay no it's dead don't
worry we'll get to some more difficult
quests eventually yeah you you just need
to unlock a higher level Whatchamacallit
difficulty yeah yeah it'll be fun one
hit
50% HP
gone no
wow well I can check that one off my
list let's go let's go cleared in under
2 minutes let's go when I was playing
suddenly hurricane is much easier than I
remember yeah when I was playing like
without a party I thought those goals
like finished under 2 minutes were like
impossible time
yay
y yeah but seems like going with a party
is the way to clear the those side goals
clear within 2 minutes
nice okay another
s++
s++ returning to
town you got a crewmate card a new alley
is waiting for you at the Nick oh yeah
you can pick a new a new team member now
yeah yeah I don't want to I'm happy with
this team I'm not going to replace you
guys either he's
loyal okay next is Rea done did it
defeat as many foes as possible oh those
won't seconds
um yeah do you a story class that
unlocks cuz I know like you have to do
you have to like watch a cutscene really
fast and then it'll
unlock um the End Game Quest so you
might want to go watch that cut scene
really fast and then new Quest should
open up to you I don't know what it says
here top top uh right of your screen
does it say anything
no oh doesn't say anything why would it
say something there cuz it says it says
something for
me oh well let's check after this Quest
I'll check properly
okay m
[Music]
yeah level
50 we
later Ena you
ready oh yeah yeah yeah I mean if
anything I can probably put up a little
horor Quest oh yeah I think you can do
that it just won't progress your story
that's all
oh I don't mind
spoilers no it's like it's just like
harder versions of the Quest we already
did
mhm okay let's
go oh one hit so
cute it's so
cute
oh why so let's go the male voice is
like a nice contrast to olda
hey no the they look so
goofy oh snack is no match for
us I remember I feel kind ofad level a
lot to level
oh oh there's more
Overkill
Overkill die
Overkill thanks for
next no problem not that I needed it but
I appreciate it feels good it's like
going to the
spa exactly I healed you guys at full
health nice
yes I'm poisoned please help me
you are oh no are you dying I'm
dying you're you're you lost 1% of help
I'll heal you thank
you give her something to do give the
Healer something to
do
no it died in front of me
H
oh yeah give me that
money one
more I love the surfing in the
sand yeah it's so nice I wonder if you
can actually do that IRL like I think so
there's like sledding with the or skiing
in the whatam call it in sand isn't
there like sand sailing where like you
get on like a little like boat sort of
thing and you can Sail on the
sand yeah hold on let's heal let's heal
thank you I'm poison again let's heal
yeah 2% let's go
more more more
bomb they die with one hit from the
bomb and the bomb's pretty strong one
minute
remaining is this called horny bird what
me what I feel like it's said horny bird
they're coming might be wrong
oh oh the B is good what is this
fantas 30 seconds 30 seconds 30 e this B
okay it's horn bird not horny bird okay
but very
close pretty much same
thing oh okay he you guys they're gone
how do you slide so fast over to the
enemies over there I use and Zetta arriv
they're like dead already I have a gap
closer time is up oh oh it's like
endless until the time ends yeah yeah ah
good experience
Overkill yay so many
Overkill
[Music]
yipp y we did so
well you're doing great
easy wait when I skip the cut scene does
it skip it for you too no everyone has
to skip it for it to skip oh okay I
didn't skip I did not
skip not look look at her um what is it
executioner but
healer The
Duality I'm a devil to my to the enemies
but Angel to my friends you know obey
the angle to your
devil
exactly okay I'll see if I you mean the
cutcenes
uh wait yeah it tell you to do anything
if not that's okay we can have Ena post
a hard request where are those again in
the in Lara's journal or where no
I want to
try what everyone's power level is at
whereit do you see
that uh if you go into your menu where
you see like the stuff under your
character
7782 oh I see it now never mind okay
3,000 around
3,000 let's see uh something with around
3,000
3,000 okay I can I can post something
okay show me your H show me a good Poe
oh
uh yeah wow
wow how how do I accept did you put
something in there do that again yeah
you see it
oh is there a difference in what it
looks like so I know it's your
quest
uh yeah how do I see your
quest I thought I posted it hold on do
you know the name of the quest still uh
I don't think
oh actually
maybe I requested it but I don't think
you have it unlocked so maybe you can't
see
it oh but I didn't even see it I should
at least have seen it
right probably oh I don't know how this
works but you're around the same level
do you have hard mode unlocked I only
have easy and
normal no what people oh uh do
why only the yes yes I do have hard mode
unlocked oh wait oh wait I found there
like a separate menu I think I found it
oh it's like uh instead of undertake
Quest it's under Quest details at the
bottom okay we can do
this let's go oh there we go y Quest oh
oh myob requirement on oh you don't have
it oh I have't unlocked it oh yeah okay
it also says I'm not meeting their
requirements no what requirement is that
is that the um locking hard mode so it's
probably after your
oh after the
story M okay how about how about this
one oh
oh wait did it uh let me switch that
out I think the saga continues do
I now now it should be Swit oh there we
go okay okay this one works oh it works
yeah
[Music]
yay so is this a quest you did before
or you know this is it's it's a new one
you unlock in the normal I think
oh oh it's this
guy wow the M guy oh this oh I remember
this one that was always fun jumping
around the
platforms is the one of the platforms
right uh-huh
yeah ouch ouch ouch OU
hot
hot I remember falling off the platform
so many
times get it's
over
l0 I was chilling come on it's
over to chill for this me boss maybe I
can weakness change my
weapon or like take my weap overpowered
I don't
know should I change to a weaker
character
maybe is there a character you always
wanted to try that you haven't tried yet
oh yeah maybe I'll just swap characters
we'll see we'll
see oh I I actually didn't notice that
until now but you have a dog following
you
around yes the ghost yeah ghost
animal three ghost animals it's not just
one it's
free it's free mhm they're cute they're
my pets I'm My Own four people
party
okay go next so do we want to try
another like Ina Quest
or what did you have to do for the
epilog again to unlock hard mode I don't
remember how do we it's like I don't
think you'll see it while you're in the
um what you call it like a party online
party
oh oh but I do also have a saga
continuous Quest like the fire one we
just did I have the ice
one we can we can do that okay I think
it's the hardest quest I have available
K I have you um so after the credit
roles for the main story have you not
like done anything afterwards
uh uh waat remind me if I'm wrong but I
I don't think I did anything I think did
I
yeah after after the credits rule you
have to like talk to the guy at his
house or something and it'll give you
like more quests I
believe uh which
guy the classes dude well the glass the
glass the glasses dude's house dud yeah
this city the rolling rolling the the
fix it dude yeah fix it fix it
guy fix it dude some someone lead me
there didn't he die I'm so oh what he
didn't die die he's just like gone for a
bit yeah he's St Shadow yeah he's
not B I'm following you you're you're
bringing me to the guy right wasn't this
the
spot he's not theread what do you mean
spoilers it's not spoilers I haven't
even gone to the epilog
oh Zeta did you do anything
after seeing the credits nope oh I I uh
I did nothing but on the same I didn't
accept any other Quest so okay
yeah well what what we can do if we want
to have them unlock the harder Quest is
uh Zeta and waa quickly
go watch the cut scenes in single player
me and Ena can do like a a hard Quest
while you guys are doing that and then
we can reconvene and do the harder Quest
together sounds good
okay uh how do we cancel this
matchmaking I'll cancel my
status okay but then okay we all leave
each other uh I guess you're going to
make your own hardcore hard mode party
on your
own M okay leave session it shouldn't
take too long to unlock the epock stuff
you just have to go through the story
stuff really quickly so you two can do
that I think like in a couple minutes I
believe it didn't take too long for me
and then you can meet us back here and
then yeah it does say speak with ID yeah
there you go do that mine too mine too
exactly the
same we're playing together even though
we're solo okay bring us to something
hard first all
right oh your weapon is so
glowy memory special
weapon
um actually I have like all the quest un
lock so you probably choose the hard one
for you
this Grand blue Yap to see back again
oh it's the same fire guy but I think
it's harder level let's do it okay oh I
guess I'm the host
huh you might not come back it has
joined my
party Z are you actually reading
everything oh I'm actually reading
wow I can to be honest I can read faster
than this but I don't want I don't think
my chat can read this fast so wow maybe
they can challeng them no no I have high
speed I have high speed ability it comes
with being an agent not underestimating
anyone but I can't remember what's your
what's your words per minute or
whatever oh I haven't I I don't know
test it out I guess there's a reading
test too I think there's a reading test
or something but is there do they also
test if you actually understood what you
read pretty sure it comes with it like
reading speed and then understanding we
should do that as a collab
stream uh okay so is this part of what I
have to do I'm you have to do the you
have to do the RP you have to RP as a
doe and then you should be unlocking it
after that no oh I oh what what happened
how did you oh wait I'm okay died no I'm
fine I'm
fine ah me and zaa leave you and you
girls are lost a lost
cause maybe you need us after all we're
F come back we miss
you oh yeah we missed you oh no the
bosses oh so difficult oh we're dying I
going to do you'll have to learn how to
handle these bosses on your own at some
point we can't always help you out me
and
Zetta please carry
us my back hurts from all
that uh's back hurts too but it's not
because of the caring
wait you joined my party why is there a
dash
button uh right trigger wasn't it oh is
it okay it was DOD at least oh yeah that
was
dodging Kara did it join your party yet
yeah I'm already doing the
fight what I skipped through all the Y
you skipped through everything
yeah
no okay I'm going
toast well you know I'm not not
streaming so I can do what I
want yeah oh left stick click the left
stick oh left
stick we all forgot about that same nice
is isn't it AER oh he dead we did nice
defeated the I remember now
okay
W thanks for the car
wow it becomes Str we did
it oh my
god oh is this your level 100 Grand why
is he level
100 cuz I
level how do I make him turn into a
lizard again it uh I don't know how it
happened but maybe I think you have to
charge why oh oh right why okay I think
maybe that's how it happened okay I
smell weakness oh she smelled it she
smelled it on it's so over she smelled
it so
stinky so stink
[Music]
oh it smell like marshmallows it smelled
like s'mores in the fire
that's actually good delici I've never
had a s'more before you haven't I
love really have s'more culture in
Austria it's not a thing I guess it's a
very American thing I don't see s'mores
anywhere outside
of miraca really I want to try it though
although I'm not a big marshmallow fan
but I like cookies and chocolate that's
the what what's in there right yeah it's
want to try what is it grham gr graham
crackers grham
cracker and and then marshmallow toasted
marshmallow and then
chocolate no now I'm
hungry yum yum
[Music]
yum did have you had uh that before that
uh the the the s'mores yeah
no I haven't had s'mores okay but hold
on s'mores is the so s'mores is like
marshmallow that you throw in fire well
you don't throw it you you thr it yeah
you you you toast it you toast you toast
it and then and then once it kind of
melted a bit you squish it between two
pieces of crackers yeah the grham
cracker
oh green I feel like I've made one
without the fire that doesn't
[Music]
count there's so many goblins
out they
are it's okay I got a gun
she's
got what link time again when
everybody's blue what
happens you I think you press both
sticks oh no that was different that
gave me a press both sticks uh prompt oh
link tell you press B oh it should be
glowing on your menu too why is your
face so goofy oh well it's
over ah I was so
off
unbelievable unbelievable
a
unbelievable W oh
oh there's a witch a
witch a witch
Goblin I'm going to get hit L
people how could you do that to
people I didn't think he was going to
hit me from here
people
no my god did you read of
the I didn't read it but uh I'm a big
fan of the all the movies and I even
went to a Lord of the Rings musical in
England last year no way yeah it was
really cool cuz it was like on the
countryside of like somewhere outside of
London and it was really cozy and and
they were so amazing they play play to
many
instruments that really beautiful that's
so nice and know
musical yeah yeah I going to do The
Hobbit uh
[Music]
CL why did you ask Black Griffin what is
this did that why did you
ask oh no cuz like we were talking about
goblins and witches and I suddenly of
Lord of the
Rings of you so cuz like cuz like I
bought like a
book but then I also like I was like
considering if I should start with the
movie or the
book but then I bought like four of the
books but then I haven't read any cuz I
wanted to but then wait did you read the
hobit before yeah I I lo I I was already
lost in the hob one oh you finished it
because I wanted to do a book club where
we read The Hobbit you can join it if
you want that' be so fun I want i w Wait
people did you sign up because I I asked
before I did I reacted I reacted with an
emote okay okay then you're in anyway
yay I want to join okay everybody who
wants to join shall join and we're done
with the Hobbit we can start reading the
Lord of the Rings yeah okay and maybe
then we'll we'll figure out all the
issues you had with it like why you're
confused about
it okay we can do that yay I remember I
remember being the hobit in school I
didn't understand anything in school wow
I think I read it in school too but I
think I scamm through it because I
really don't remember anything oh my God
it is about to die
die what if I die can they revive
me wait I have heal items I
forgot I
died okay Revival
potion
wow we could have one play it it's
okay's other dang it en I thought we
were stronger than this honestly it's
okay we'll be fine
Z why why you not Reviving me hurry
up this so slow Z also
struggling yeah this Z
struggling thank
you
wo did you did you beat the bird no not
yet I'm like at 47
no
buy I did it first what you finished
already I finished it first and without
giving the
cut what
s
how
how I don't
know damn girl okay here we go this is
[Music]
it explosion
boom stop the coffee
pasta I'm almost people I'm so motivated
right now wow give me that
money level up I must keep getting
stronger death isn't even their final
form y y y y y
y oh God
watch doing yeah well I'm not streaming
but I'm suffering right now oh I I guess
I guess uh Cara is in a different level
huh uhuh Z did you unlock the
question huh what did you say did you
unlock the
stuff oh not yet I'm still in a cut
scene oh yeah keep on watching that cut
scene
s slow okay I'm not going to skip don't
skip
skip skip skip ad if you skip ad you
it no don't do it to
him oh my God this is litting
me oh I have more okay I did it he's
dead I I think I think since they're
done we can wait now yeah
[Music]
yeah
okay let's
go vamos
Amigos you you
[Music]
are you
sure yes
yes I do that so
[Music]
often I can't help it like I always want
to do it it's from that one Clipper yeah
the outro yeah
yeah you have to do it a little bit more
like whispery I
guess oh I got um I'm in chapter zero I
think oh me too me too okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay you should be able
to do stuff now I think I believe I
think I can do stuff now
yeah do I have to read the Journal of
Rand oh no I skip okay you could but
yeah for fix it guys you may now join
online quests of the following
difficulty hard very hard extreme y okay
let's
go let's go hold on where's the I don't
know who to get for my new crew
mate where oh I want to choose a new one
too was it in the knickknack Shack or
where was that again yeah yeah the nickn
oh yeah I think I can get someone too
the parrot
kid who made
unbelievable oh do you have to pay money
for these
dudes I think you can unlock it oh by
playing the game too maybe I got the DLC
there's not enough cute girls what the
hell oh this lady is cute the one with
the bow or is that a
bow yeah first of all oh she
cute I want Twan but I cannot have
twen the new just like the sand alha
yeah I'm looking at
twen looks so good
yeah but I cannot has
Okay I accept my
fate I like how I have all the cute
girls unlocked but I have I have not
unlocked any of the
dudes
[Music]
same same I want to add another blonde
to my team but I don't know who my
options are
limited maybe you can make them blonde
in the color
change oh the skin
Oh none of these dudes interest me
H okay uh if we make a grip again you
guys already have an existing group do
you want to invite
us I think can yeah I can go for
it oh wait I have to change party
first
party okay I sent invite
uh does it just show up in the screen in
the middle or you should get a steam
invite oh send a steam invite I think so
well that's how that's how we got in
last time oh okay yeah I did get a steam
invite okay
okay all righty oh is the password the
same as before yeah it's the same room
oh okay okay let me join
we're coming back the noobs are coming
back welcome
back we're here please carry
out we'll carry you don't
worry oh Ena looks different again okay
I have to censor the screen you have
funny hair
Ena thanks it's like you have free or
four a oh
yeah did you wake up like that
no I I put on moose or
whatever invite
me I I thought I
did uh let me do it again
okay did you get it
no let me double
check um
I don't think
so oh I don't think we're friends on
St not
friends wait I can invite her yeah you
can invite her okay okay I'll I'll use
this chance to add her on
Ste okay you have been invited please
join us again
Zeda all
[Music]
right
join do you know the ground blue
characters are actually pretty short
like naraya the one I'm playing is
actually shorter than me she's like 130
something oh yeah 130
yeah how short this potato okay so now
the epil quests are the ones that Roland
or whoever suggested I suppose yeah and
then okay I think I see that they are
marked yeah the ones The Marked One do
the
okay then I'll put it as a request into
the requests oh it would have been
better if you were a host
huh uh okay I
requested I think me and Zeda will need
the same ones so I think it should count
for both of
you let's go let's
go ready ready oh oopsie
ready ready ready
OHA you changed no you didn't you're
still the
same oh wait did I change no I I I
thought you did but now you didn't
you're cute as
Calo you I'll change after
this oh what's this this music is really
good where are the bad guys or is this
one way we shoot the with shoot with the
Cannons
oh oh I love
that oh it's the cannon
thing you guys like these yeah I don't
quite a challenge I I'd rather just beat
stuff up same but if they're only on one
side and there's two cannons there
then walking around we're just chilling
we're just chilling so much for for us
carrying the other you you guys can do
the Cannons no it's all you go you go
okay here here I'm lazy someone else
used the cannon I'm just going to run
around and look cute all right I'll try
it's been a while I can aim oh aim do oh
they're already coming to the ship well
more things to do yeah
woo oh
more yeah shoot them oopsie shooting
them the horny birds are
coming take them
down I don't think they are quite
Birds but they're called Birds
dinosaur ouch ouch ouch something is got
you I was like What's blocking my vision
oh something's on top of me
no
out wow nice link
attack nice this is a bit more of a
challenge at least than the other ones I
think aiming the aiming this cannon is
the challenge
oh oh it's happening again yeah there's
more in the sky shoot him down go get
him oh my God they're already
here
damn those poor little
[Laughter]
things go go go go
[Music]
oh level
up I love attacking
nothing I love we didn't do the clear
within free
[Music]
let oh we
stck
damn go get him
guys doing the ground
work oh doing the
sky
ouch Ling no
[Music]
nice
yay
yay ah three minutes is still possible
the goals don't look so good we
suck I need to do charged shots
oh I mostly did the pew pew pew mhm
oh well this is fine oh this is this is
good hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey Miss a couple of who whoa whoa
what's going
on
what what does this
mean I'll get him next time okay
whoa whoa what how does what no no I
don't want to repeat the quest no oh
wait oh yeah okay okay
unless unless you want to minut no boss
I want boss I want
violence okay we'll give you violence
yes thank
you you've acquired
curio uhhuh
okay ta you should check if that Quest
the first I think it was the first one
on my list is it gone for you now okay
let me
check first one on the list I mean I
guess now you would have a different one
as the first one on the
L
uh um what's the first one you have
written is it uh yeah yeah it's gone
rule the skies oh okay nice but that one
does have the mark anymore so the next
one would be the juice of jealousy do
you have that one too oh my next one is
uning the troops but I have the juice of
jealousy as well oh but does the the
other one that you mentioned have the
mark Cuz only juice of jealousy has the
mark for me I'm not sure if that is even
the right Mark that we should be looking
out for though it's like a
orange point oh yeah yeah it has the
mark for me okay what does it mean the
Mark I think think it says that those
are the
pre story epilog quests that used to
progress through the
epilog but it still says I only finished
two out of eight jobs for R more lock
down the line yeah I'm I'm at six out of
eight right now oh
okay but it was two out of eight before
the fight that we just had and now it's
still to elevate it's it comes in waves
you have to do waves of quest so this
wave is the W Quest oh it's not like
eight quests you got to a whole bunch of
them oh
okay damn that's a lot
yep oh oh this place we
[Music]
go
oh bad guy please
where where are they something
satisfying about beating up goblins dang
it okay I'm
Shiny Money Money Money Money
no one wants to get my AOE bubble I'm
sad what is that the heal no my AOE
slashy slashy attack no one wants to
die yeah they're kind of scattered all
over ouch
come
here dang it
Ni no what are they fighting oh
no ooh nice nice heal
o no I missed the link
attack
byebye
cble no I miss the link attack
sad Zelda will be disappointed in
you get the joke I get
it
ou
ouch why oh okay I'm not resisting to
fire
oh no I didn't get the don't get
inflicted could with burn more than four
times ACH oh I also didn't get it oh no
I think that's across all of us so we
sick
burn I need heal I need heal I need
healing sorry I don't have heal I'm he
myself oh
[Music]
nice did you watch what I did or did you
see the pets
attacking I saw I saw you're so cute the
ghost wait I'm not at
100% I'm at I think if one of us uses it
you'll be 100% let's go mhm it goes up
pretty
fast woo I can't see it's too flashy
oh I couldn't use mine oh what ouch wait
I need a big thing to use it on where is
a big
thing oh wait 30 seconds or me I'll just
use it ah be in particular gu the enemy
where's the
enemy yeah
W no I'm not at 100% said
anymore please come
on oh there's more go for get
that 10 seconds you have 10 seconds to
use it okay go go go
go
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah get
nice wow the slow
motion please give me some titles
please I want some titles to
flex okay let's see the titles oh yeah
how do you put on the titles in when
you're in the
lobby no idea you have to go to your
Co-op settings maybe I
oh you can put them as
oh oh
nice
oh wow I'm the link starter proud of you
thank you
link I start collabs I start links I
start
everything you no bi bi always has the
no healing needed I healing I just kill
things way too fast
yeah oh yeah I start fires I start links
start a fire
today fire fire like the
fire fire fire pants on
fire fire
fire I'll request protect the rep it's
also a boss fight yeah B
fight
okay I've been waiting for a boss
fight what kfp is also always in a boss
fight cuz they're always fighting me oh
they're fighting
you they're fighting about their salary
and about their
their union rights or whatever stop
fighting me you give them salary you
give them union rights no that's but
that's what they're fighting you're such
a good boss you even gave them salary
well salary salary is like there is
salary but the salary is the other way
around like they pay me so Oh I thought
you were going to say salary asn't like
the vegetable that's that's me I give I
give M the salary with the vegetable
always I was like wait you can't you
can't tell people that you're paying
your kfp then we all got to start paying
and I don't want to do
that don't worry about it but maybe from
now on when they ask for salary I should
just give them the vegetables yeah maybe
then they'll shut up about
it saler is good you care about their
health and
wellbeing M I prefer other
vegetables okay who here has watched the
F Fallout show I haven't but I want to
see I heard it's really good please
watch it it is so good it made me start
playing the game
ooh and the protagonist she's so cute
she has like really poppy big eyes that
pop out of her skull what I know she
just her eyes are really
big she's so pretty no stop targeting me
why why why why why
why thank
you I it takes a long time for me to go
[Music]
there I love
Ella quack
oh okay nice oh my
God
nice that was a good one
mhm
explode yes I
money I'm getting to the money first
No Loot goblins you freaking loot
goblins it's shared you don't have to
worry I want a
reed I want to play World Of let's see
the titles titles
titles the most important
part
totally NOA no titles what I got all the
titles you can't see on my screen but I
got no healing needs specialist and Lord
of crits
yeah I smell
weakness that's all oh she smells
weakness Z is smelling weakness
now weakness okay but what do we learn
from this titles don't matter titles are
everything the one with the most titles
is the most important yes people you try
hard
no no no no they don't
matter they don't matter they really
don't yeah they
don't wor they don't next one is in
delts of lives or
[Music]
so it it's Dragon power is pulsating oh
Dragon power wow
Ena looks so cool with her big Cape yeah
thank you like from behind hide inside
the C yeah it's like a
blanket a
cuddle okay ready here we go
again we're all're all inside her cave
connecting Z did you ready up yeah I
ready up yeah it's just the server I
think it's connecting oh
dear uh cuz nothing's happening for me I
see I see
oh it says connecting on my side yeah I
see connecting to oh there okay yeah it
it took a while server
issue I was sliding it was yeah you were
you were sliding around but like not
moving ah
lag oh oh
hello it's a Oh I thought it was a horse
go bu a horse
horse what part looks like a horse to in
my defense the back of the hair does
look like a p
ha L that
oh yeah oh
yeah
yeah wow that that felt good we were
going hard that felt
satisfying moneyy
[Applause]
no it's not fa you have to
rush loot
Goblin the middle box looks better than
the others yeah that's why I want to
open
it she got to go for that the titles
don't
matter oh you're saying that
already you have a bad feeling matter
about what's coming oh unscathed let's
go do
matter don't
matter it doesn't matter especially it
doesn't matter the most when you get
none it doesn't
matter you're lucky that I am blocking
my
titles you are blocking your titles on
my screen they can't see all the titles
I'm collecting
yeah
oopsie that's so fast well we can be
done with this so quickly it gets it
gets harder just oh trying to see
what you want to switch again nope maybe
it after this maybe M finally Z appears
oh if you switch I'll switch to
potato okay
okay uh after this one
yeah
okay I will I'll give zaa a chance she
deserves a chance yeah please do I want
to see daa you're the only one with a
shared name in this game you got to you
know represent it wow Zeta needs a Zeta
skin yes Z
skin
skin are we loading again or yeah we're
yeah server
issue that's
[Music]
okay slow
server we're overloading
it Zeta Zetta
collaboration Zeta Zetta collaboration
there's J as well right the main
character yeah oh
G that's why both of them are in my
party I'm I feel so reassured with my D
fingers but the Gaeta one is written
how g i t a d j e e t a i think
yeah ah that
one
DJ
DJ I've never met a character that
shares my
name I only share my name with the
hamster from
hamaro it what you want to share your
name no I've never I've never met a
video game character named beu
before
oh yeah
B where where is beu from it's French it
means like
jewelry oh yeah be yeah oh okay maybe
there's no game characters but there's a
shop there's a shop chain in Austria
that sells accessories like clire it's
called
P cute
it's it's nice it's like more mature
than uh Claire's oh
mature you're so
mature yeah very fitting for that that's
why that's why I'm bble because I don't
feel mature enough for my
name no beu is totally the type that
would shop in Claire's not
[Music]
Claire but no no I also sometimes go to
Claire still
sometimes I I got my ears pierced and
clear me too me too oh okay good okay
I'm not the only one nice and I was I
was very old when I did that oh does
does Claire's use gun or needle they use
gun gun yeah
oh I never got my ears pierced as a
child and so I Did It For the First Time
as an adult and I felt so awkward bir in
that Claire's at least it was pretty
empty and I was so terrified even though
it's not a big deal like some some
parents let their make their like two
yearolds or so uh Pierce their ears
right
right I don't know to have yeah some
some parents like Pierce like some
people get their ears pierced as like a
baby so I guess they don't remember
it yeah they're like feel the pain now
so you don't feel it later it's not
happening what should we
do I don't know I'm stuck I can't
move me
either I also I can't cancel my ready
stat status either I feel like an NPC n
walking around I can't even move am I
still sliding around you yeah I I still
see your able to move you're so think
you're supposed to be able to move I
don't think you're supposed to be able
to move
but just because it's taking so much
time I'm I'm ready up I'm
chilling I'm waiting for
you it shows me that Zetta is not ready
up but I'm sure you
are ma'am where where even is Zetta I
don't see that though oh I'm here near
the um the quest the quest table you
can't you probably can't see me I indeed
cannot see you wait really I'm gone
maybe that's the problem I don't
know what I think we have you should
rejoin yeah I think it's you because you
can move what yeah you're not supposed
to be able to move when you're ready but
I was able to move before too and we
still got in but it's
just I guess not working this time
wow okay how do I how how do I how do I
wait you're not allowed to move but I
can't uh do anything though I just I can
move but I can't do anything game like
entirely alt
f4
no no okay G oh okay we can move now
move I can move now actually alt f4 was
the solution
but now she's gone it was well come
back come back we'll wait for you come
back to
us oh she's being a
sunary I mean we can go without
[Laughter]
you I'm sure that's what you'd like
huh no I'm com you promised that you
were going to care
car open to your
promise you you know the real carriers
are
elsewhere boo I'm swapping to potato I
don't know what you're talking about oh
okay okay I'm I'm swapping to something
else then swapping to potato swapping to
am potato
potato M's
potato you have a level 69
nice did you stop there on purpose no I
didn't she's in my party so she
naturally levels with me yeah it's not
like you had it all planned out
yeah are you sure you want to keep
leveling up people you could have oh
that's true maybe I should just swap
again I'm back and I'm ready
up I'm are you I'm ready as well
okay okay there we go how do we play
her how do I play potato you I jump
right you jump that's how you play
potato just keep hitting attack button
okay yeah just just keep X just keep
pressing X oh what's this oh this the
coin collecting one oh what what's
this
[Music]
what just everyone spread out and
collect coins around them okay
okay ouch
oh oh yeah she has that thing that's the
first time I ever saw a quest like that
the coin yeah I think
or yeah I don't think I ever had a coin
Quest like
this I I don't remember I CL loving
slimes where oh yeah now now the slimes
appear now that we have all the
coins uh where are they though oh I see
that we can go to the center and then
they should be there oh my coin no you
took my coin it's up at the top how do
you can someone shoot that thing down oh
I see
it bring it
down he's destroying the
structure
oh oh come down what is that a cattle oh
it's a cattle bring it down I'm too
short how how do you get
maybe no no that oh I can't I don't have
like any ability to get up there didn't
didn't she have like a jump
thing I think I un equipped
it oh oh I have a raining a raining
meteor that's good wait how what are you
supposed to do
here jump jump but we all can't jump
that high
I could have sworn I had like a jumping
attack
thing en this is your main how do I do
how do I play
her I don't remember the name of the
skills I just remember
whatever is oh yeah she has a rushing R
there's one over here that is less on
a on the way lowest
spot I think you just well cuz I have my
controller set so that it keep pressing
the button you have to keep pressing it
until she goes like super fast and
attacking you can just keep doing that
it's a basic
thing okay okay
okay we got one okay nice where is is
there another one that we can reach
easier
oo well say something if you find
another one of those oh I found another
one it's small oh okay oh only we need
to defeat King
[Music]
Slime King Slime
coming but coins is also important
true like three of us literally tried
for 1 minute to reach the the thing on
top of
the without doing anything was that one
cattle ni
it's okay we killed it you almost
died oh I think oh maybe maybe next time
we could split the job one person go
coin hunting yeah was continuously coin
hunting I think while we were
fighting oh I was figuring out how to
play so I was
useless H we can try it again should we
this was long distance
running oh
yeah should we try it again it's okay we
can do a
boss oh okay maybe another boss yeah
let's do a new
boss BOS
BOS I want to fight stuff with my potato
uh I want to five creatures that are
alive the next one is indeed a boss
fight
yay oh where oh there you
go small small
potato potato in the fire
why
potato
potato potato potato
potato tomato
tomato I hate Tomatoes I also hate
Tomatoes what let's go cook cook
tomatoes are fine but like okay raw
Tomatoes no I love raw Tomatoes
especially cherry
tomatoes no cooked or raw is what about
like uh like raw tomatoes with
mozzarella and balsamico vinegar what
about that
what no maybe when I'm sorry Italians
I'm sorry I'll eat it in
[Music]
afterlife
damn it's so refreshing though it's
really nice to eat in
summer it's like kind of like it has
like a combination of like sourness
but
bitterness they're sweet sweet potatoes
sweet tomatoes like cherry tomatoes do
you like
those the small
ones not really damn even if it's sweet
because if if if I wanted sweet things I
would eat sweet things not
Tomatoes there's better sweet things
than
tomatoes I don't think tomatoes are like
they just
like
dead people where are you okay I'm okay
wait do we have a Healer right now no no
oh I mean no oh no he got both of us
hold on hold on hold how do I how do I
what is it called how do I
uh how do I oh I keep I used an item to
revive oh everyone's their own healer I
guess so yeah got to be
careful this one's strong
[Music]
yeah you got caught in the frost fight
no I am most grateful
oh oh it rolls into a ball that's
unfair ouch
ouch
that who can someone revive me okay
coming got you
closer
sheesh
revive thank
you what think
that
o oh nice oh
nice
I'm what we only have
%% can I can I all oh
[Music]
nice get a
go go pets
go I'm
90% oh first time I'm seeing this
all okay here I
go yeah
first we did
it go pull Button Mash Let's Go Button
Mash let's
go do piled them yes oh yeah what is
this moment you have also everything oh
yeah he he he's slowed down so you can
use skills and not worry about it cuz
he's slow okay
nice uh-oh uh-oh okay okay bye
bye I got
out okay
good ooh
[Music]
I'm a damage sponge coming coming coming
coming coming thank
you oh scary how do it feel to play
as oh it's
nerve-wracking like I'm like I have to
count the combos I'm like one
two well how far does it go the the
counting I know J is pretty complicated
three but it's it's it's it's taking all
of my energy to come so
for wo wo
oh no
no I'm going to get tile for dying so
often hold
on and you're going to get the title for
Reviving so others so often
oh
man
what it's okay I'll take the lse if that
means that we'll win in the
end with the tee
yes so Noble taking one for the team
thank you for your
service oh no oh no okay oh no no no oh
no no no careful
careful baby you're standing right at
the
cff don't worry revive revive
revive don't hurt the tiny
[Music]
potato oh people's back okay I'm
back okay I had the potion left that's
oh what's
happening oh no no no wait okay okay
okay okay we get it's okay it's almost
dead we can do it we can die no that's
crazy oh no wait I have to quickly push
the
button so close first filed
Quest we got to repeat it we got to that
was fun though that was fun I'm bringing
I'm bringing back out
on okay okay okay I'll
try I'll I'll do kago for that extra
heel okay then we have to like get out
of this once right yeah yeah okay okay
okay bring this bring the strong
characters okay bringing back the strong
characters
this she can stay at level
69 that one absolutely obliterated
us
she she
but I've already gained like 20 levels
since we started yeah it's pretty fastel
pretty fast yeah yeah you're at 60 now
O mine keeps changing the character so
it's like 50 50 50 all equally spread
out that's good you're leveling
everybody yeah giving everybody a
chance yeah one thing I haven't consider
this I leveled like 20 levels but do I
need like better equipment where do I
get you can go into your masteries and
level up your like
stats um to get better stats and then
you can also buy weapons at this guy a
and level up the weapons too yeah oh I
can't I guess I can't do it now we can
do it after this
Quest oh wait if I just unready for a
moment I can oh yeah you can do that too
uh oh I think I'll un ready as well hold
[Music]
on oh more weapons are available I have
so many books this is
good uncap I don't have Earth orb I
don't have Earth orb uh if you don't
have items go to this the little dude
and see parrot yeah the parrot dude go
to Treasure trade I think and maybe it's
selling it in the Treasure trade oh okay
Earth orb where are you Earth
orb how much oh there's definitely Earth
orbs
yeah okay got
one and
then going back to
like h
I'll do my masteries for now
instead I'll just do
everything got to get stronger more
power
yes well
I
[Music]
am what is it called um leveling up for
a bit okay I'm leveling up too just let
me know when you're
ready
okay
um
oh crazy good
but should I upgr or not I like this one
better
s
[Music]
i oh
okay oh there's so much I can do no
wonder I was so
weak cyar is better cyar
s okay s hold on we need more Earth
or oh okay I'm I ran out of points let's
go
okay Earth or bir
orb one more
I am so torn between two
swords get the one that looks
cooler h both of them looks cool I am so
[Music]
torn upgrade web as should you normally
go for upgrading existing
weapons so you're going to need to
upgrade all the weapons eventually
because um in your masteries page each
weapon gives you bonus stats so the more
weapons you have upgraded the more stats
you can get um yeah yeah so do all of
them okay well I don't have dragon scam
but if you're worried about stats crit
is always good
mhm okay I'll make new weapon
Ina hello Ina's
tall okay I think I am ready I love
some
some materials a bit for later
he wait one second uh okay okay enhance
success
okay
oh oh okay hold on on on
on I
think that should be
good oh I can add one more sigil
M attack power maybe I like I bought a
new gold sword it looks cooler but the
stats are
lower
ready whenever okay
[Music]
ready let's go second try same Quest
right yeah okay
this time we'll get
him Are we more confident yes yes I
brought out the
main the main okay that should be easy
then I'll bring the heal this time
oh and a buff so I have a buff that
Buffs all
allies W yeah this is way faster than
[Music]
before
Oh wait wait why am I attacking a wall
stop
ow
ouch ouch
ouch I'm
frozen hold on hold on hold on heal
thank oh yeah right thank you oh wait
the heal is gone okay hold on hold
on
ow nice
[Music]
than oh nice this is much
faster it's night and
day
oh okay you fell off the
Earth for real you fell down yeah yeah I
down the map fine I thought there's an
invisible wall over there no no I fell
off the now I can to try falling down
too it actually does nothing I don't
know if you lose like certain stuff like
definitely all my
health oh he's dead
[Music]
oh so easy
wow that was so different yeah that was
main character
energy
money much better
but I like to pretend that me and zaa
upgrading our characters also helped a
little bit it help yeah it's like it's
the little attacks you know it it's a
little bit Yeah it adds up into big
numbers
yeah okay ooh well what do we have oh
got titles oh we all got
titles titles I finally got support
Master wow well you were supporting me
like a
master
nice the W
aort okay s++ exactly what we deserve
yeah
yeah do we have more boss for bi
boo
[Music]
maybe I got a crewmate card thanks but I
don't have anybody that I
want thanks but I'm not interested in
guys we're going to fight another
Griffin and apparently we're going to
turn him into our dinner drumstick
oo yum what's more delicious griffins or
kfp kfp of course all the way of course
yeah Griffins are not supposed to be
eaten anyway Griffins are supposed to be
flown
ridden what do kfps taste
like what do kfps taste like it's just
chicken it's fried chicken but it's the
best fried chicken you can get out there
but also actually
because of our name you might think we
focus a lot on on fried chicken but it's
actually more the burgers we we prefer
to do Burgers oh I like burgers burgers
but IDE chicken
burgers cuz I don't even like like fried
chicken buckets like just just a chicken
I don't like that that much I want more
variety and that's what a burger gives
you with the lettuce and the Tomato
perhaps have you ever considered sauce
kfp maybe that'll give you the variety
if you like add
sauce kfp sauce yeah kfp sauce we have
many many sauces we have Yago uh no wait
what
what weag
burger no I have we have a lot of sauces
I I wrote a menu like three years ago
actually oh like a legit
menu oh that's so nice M do you have a
drink oh Many Many Drinks all the
drinks all of them Chien I recommend Dr
Pepper I don't like Dr
Pepper what yeah I don't like cherry
flavored stuff oh but it's not really
Cherry Flav it does taste like cherry
flavor yeah but then there's a Dr Pepper
cherry flavor specifically as well so
ow but I think I I get what you mean it
has like a an
interesting hidden flavor
palet how do we get to come
down I do we wait oh it does come down
it's attacking e get
there taunt
him be bo want him
uh you
smell like weakness yeah I can smell
your
weakness
woo let's
heal
what a little bit
[Music]
but I did do a favor and I died close to
zto yeah hold on hold on hold
on hold
on revive oh did you revive yourself
yeah oh yeah you can revive Yourself by
mashing like a button Yeah by mashing
button oh I used the item before oh nice
break
Ena are you muted no oh
okay does somebody have a
stand a
stand like a like a JoJo stand like I
see like a big guy in armor or
something oh
I uh no I still don't know what you mean
in the game yeah oh yeah in the game
yeah yeah Oh I thought I was
like Ena has a St yeah
oh
oh is a JoJo is a is a pose no it's a
it's a summoned big dude
uhuh okay I still don't know what you're
talking about don't worry about it oh I
got I smell weakness I smell weakness
leveling up I got the
queit you is your head okay like do do
you want to rest or for a I can probably
do like one or two more okay don't push
yourself yeah don't push yourself
end it when you're I think this wave for
me and Zeta we we only have maybe one
more Quest or so left okay for this wave
of
quest let me
check I am not going to read the note me
neither reading you can read oh yeah
it's just one left defeat naon
sounds
fancy have you been to France before
with that name you kind of got to go oh
I guess I do kind of got to go huh
if you want to go I'm close by I can go
with you I've been to uh Paris a few
times I've never been to Europe before
hey y' come
over I hear it's nice though it's
beautiful there's so much like variety
Europe is very versatile you know we
have so many things to offer so much
beauty Beauty one of the beauties of
Europe is me by the way
oh so come to
Austria you know you're selling it
pretty well
right another one of the Beauties is my
cats they would also like meet more
members more Holo members come
on
cute I want to sniff every Hollow
member's cat
yeah there's like I feel like there's
way more cat owners than dog owners way
more by far which is like really an
unusual ratio I think like if you just
like walk around in the world in the IRL
world and ask people do we have a dog or
a cat then it's more balanced but within
Holo it's so
unbalanced we all love
cats oh bonu nice Bon special love cats
I love cats
too
[Music]
whoa is he also going to be so strong
why is he he's shooting laser
beams because he can that's all he got
don't take it away
flies all you can do is fly fly fly do
you have nothing else to
do
ooh oh well this okay yeah I guess we
still have the strong team so he also
went down fast
nice
yay okay we we finished the first wave
of quests it
seems I don't I don't think you have a
boss in between I think you just move I
forget I think there is I think like
the some sort of dragon can we help with
it not sure I think it was
solo not sure it might be
cool I don't remember it's been a while
people got waited by
K oh hi
[Music]
cie Carrie wa doesn't know what a stand
is I thought what you mean something
within the game
so but I mean I've heard of Jojo never
watched it though but I know some of the
poses yeah nice
it's okay I have it I have Ito watch
along yeah I wanted to continue
it I haven't I'm only in part two but
the stand thing doesn't happen until
later I think uhhuh okay okay what the
thing that defines the show seemingly
only happens
later what what it starts in part three
yeah part three
oh okay well well well oh yeah now it
says finish the jobs four out of
eight
nice oh there's a rank up Quest button
ah yeah it says defeat the Ancient
Dragon but I think it's probably is it
by yourself I was able to make the
request oh okay let's do that and then
we can that's a good stopping
point yeah we can do it
together I can get carried through
hooray ready I got to know Dojo because
of the what is it called
[Laughter]
the they just repeat a lot of
[Music]
words and there
little oh yeah
what oh y
y what the [\h__\h] is
little he uses his tongue and there's
a is that an attack no it's a it's a a
pose a stand yeah it's a pose I guess
[Music]
when I hear
y i i I'm like imagining Ena but with a
rose in her
mouth I feel like it's something she was
saying with
r you know my
in yeah
a he's in
oh what the did he just give birth what
is
one
uhoh you're so
small e keep on dodging keep on
dodging
uhoh it's raining sues
[Music]
the dragon has
descended I can
he ah don't move
away and there's a link missed
it okay there's so many there's so
[Music]
many oh thank God I
to Good
[Music]
Morgan Morgan to you
too oh we got four Treasure Chest this
time
how do you say Good
Morgan yes good
[Music]
morgan oh
you
I bit for like really yeah for like 3
weeks m a three weeks
[Laughter]
oh yeah how was your tie tripil it was
so hot beom I died I died but it was it
was nice I had some good food and I saw
a a beautiful Temple it was amazing it
was incredible but it was too
hot hot do you know people do you know
about those inhalers what inhalers yeah
tie
inhalers it's like a popular souvenir uh
and like everybody uses it the small
inhalers that smell like herbs a oh come
on you got to know it no you sniff sniff
sniff sniff
inhaler oh I got a little yapping scene
well I know Ty people like smelling
things we're
always always getting like
smelling like having like the [\h__\h] like
bag where you like smell it and sniff
sniff yeah yeah yeah they're like in a
little container though like really
small container portable little inher oh
I think I know what you're talking about
yeah and it has like holes in it right
or something yeah it has a cap that I I
can lift and I got so many of those and
I like gifted some to my my mom and my
friends but they smell really nice and
then I got a lot of tie
pants I'm wearing tie pants right now
yeah tie pants are like comfortable
right I don't wear pants so I don't own
thae pants but I they look comfy they're
so
comfortable and then for the first time
ever like I did thae massage uh overseas
right outside of Thailand but now I had
a thae massage in Thailand wo was it
better H it was uh
I I mean I had good Tha massages outside
of Thailand but this one was really good
and uh it was like an older Thai lady
that did it and she kept on she didn't
speak English at all but she kept on
laughing at My Pain
a well pain and massages are good right
cuz it means like it's getting out all
the stuff I totally love it I need I
need the pain she was good good lady I
kind of like the mom type of lady
[Music]
no did she step on
you she I think she did
yeah and I
[Music]
died that was good stuff I wish you
could have taught me a little bit you
know before but the times didn't match
yeah the timing
was bad but maybe another time
sometime if you say n to some
bu they'll like it that's cute so like
wa n or in N what that mean cute it
means cute
Z
yeah a it literally translates to face
love oh love face love love your yeah
love your face love your neighbors face
love
m i see thanks for the little little uh
tie lesson yeah you're
welcome okay so we we did quite a lot of
quests I think that's a good point to
stop right yeah and I feel
better thank
you yeah thank you everybody for coming
together at this weird time thank you
for making time girls yeah well it's
okay I'm awake
anyway I am I am also easily awake
anyway time yeah I'm glad we could find
like uh you know exactly four people for
a full team yeah full
team that's
awesome yeah are you girls going to
still play this sometime or are you done
with it kind of I'm kind of done with it
I'm kind of curious as to like what's an
end game you what's an end game a lot of
grinding oh
grinding grind blue grind blue
fantasy me personally I might play it
off stream but depends like if if you
guys want to play then yeah I am down to
play it at least um in multiplayer again
yeah it's a collab again I have a lot of
games I want to play right now so I
don't think I have time for it solo but
but if you guys ever want to play again
I am down to play again same same
same whenever
whenever whenever
wherever yeah so thank you so much for
helping you helping us with the quests
dear yeah it was fun yeah thank you for
helping me look
cool yeah you you look pretty cool yeah
thank
you yeah you're cool now you're so
mature
wow
you're yes you got to prove your
strength for sure yeah short people can
be cool n Only proves that okay mhm
yeah I agree why why why is it getting
quiet no short people are are cool short
Kings short Queens yeah exactly
yeah thank you thank you everybody for
participating and uh I don't know I
don't Stream So This is not I don't know
you girls can say goodbye
properly you want to you want to who
wants to close it off go ahead Z does
anyone have announcements no the
announcement is thank you uh thank you
Advent announced 3D debut this summer
yay check it out we're all working
really hard for it um and really excited
yeah there no date yet right just sum no
date yet just this summer in the summer
the whole
summer the whole summer every day every
day is advent day it could be tomorrow
who knows it's not tomorrow spoiler but
get ready be ready at all times yeah you
got to be ready for it I'm so ready for
it
I'm I'm very excited for it it feels
like it happened so fast it feels like
Adin just joined like one month ago but
in reality you've been around for like
half a year almost a year actually it's
going to be a year in like a few
months oh few months yeah how time flies
we' been around for 9 months says Jad
nine months yeah nine 10 months or we
debuted I debuted July 30 first I think
I think what July first July last year
yeah July last year but we're almost
back in July
exactly what what you just joined
yesterday don't lie to
me oh my god it feels like that doesn't
it this whole half year ever since we're
in 2024 flew by instantly it makes me so
mad it it's got to go slower it's
stressing me out
yeah still just a baby but not really
we're growing
[Music]
up slow time no well I don't have an
announcement oh I have a in Aon um event
meet and green meet and
GRE yay that's all nice soon anybody
else if there's none we can close and
end it right here yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's fine okay thanks for watching
Everybody you thank you it was so
fun sure to get
some good night everyone byee
[Music]
e