foreign
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's a crazy man
come on
please
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
come on
Bam Bam
foreign
[Music]
hello
I thought we start in a special way
today
that was the original song by me that no
one knows before it is
very very much unknown song by yours
truly
see if I get booked
I am
uh oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah okay
I have a little
[Music]
I liked my handwritten little guy I
thought it was quite Exquisite marvelous
but uh
like let me
on Twitter the ad is on it where is it
I just want to put credit where credit
is to look at all Emily
live at magical mailing magical manly I
will retweet now so that you know you
can find it
it's so cute now I have two logos
yeah thank you okay
love oh
oh what is this
what is this this
um
oh yes I have heart eyes
after looking at yesterday's stream
um I carefully asked if I can have some
additional things
[Music]
um
oh I can blow a kiss
[Music]
um
yes and so very cute and then one more
thing
oh
you know when I see when I see you
a cute
cute fly tasty fly I know I can use my
tongue but also
look look
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know sometimes sometimes uh even a
frog like me
prefers to use other things than her
tongue yeah let me show you
what I'm gonna
thank you
from here is better maybe
[Laughter]
oh
oh oh
oh oh oh
hey
wow it's my own kind of bunk stick kid
all
I don't actually
um you know I bought it for you guys I
didn't own it beforehand just for you
guys you have one of these at your home
or do you have one of
these at your home that takes care of
your flies
we both can do it but one of these much
cuter
will bring you much more happiness
[Laughter]
get out
okay I'll get on
okay okay so today we're gonna play frog
uh wait oh yeah what am I gonna do about
the logo
let me I like mine too but
let's put this up there
looks more official ghetto
okay
okay so we're gonna play frog detective
one in front detective two we start with
radishes one of course
it should be pretty short like I heard
it's like the Google Google
Sound tells me it's one hour you know
and then the other one also
approximately one hour okay though
bottom left better well yeah but they're
against when the logo goes
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I love them I could have them on forever
okay
[Music]
hmm
let's Pour Some Water how you guys doing
kid on me now thank you guys come
[Music]
on
ah
um
what happened to Kiana
killed her
I killed her with this yeah now I give
me a new frog Overlord cannot
at least for this week so have fun with
me while you have me you're gonna miss
me when I'm gone oh I never be gone I'll
never be gone
okay okay now I'm here forever I'm here
to stay
okay let's I'll play
I'm curious how difficult this is gonna
be that some of you guys playing before
kettle
if you guys don't please help me because
you know a small small brain
wait
oh the game opens with uh interesting
window first uh
thank you I'll have this one and then
there's Graphics quality
it's quality description Apple Bottom
Jeans
what does that mean boots with the fur
the whole club was looking she hit the
floor ah Apple Bottom Jeans boots with
the fur the whole club was looking at
her she hit the floor she hit the floor
she hit the floor she hit the floor
is it that
it's like you don't understand guys but
can I show this
does it show up on LPS no
no it doesn't show up
I doubled up oh okay
it's like you know you can choose
Graphics quality the first is Apple
Bottom Jeans the second is boots with
the fur the third is the whole club was
looking at but then it cuts off I'm
guessing the line is longer and then the
next one is she hit the floor and the
next one is in in like the the side the
side thingies
these things
oh oh oh wait wait oh
don't you like this one is kind of funny
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay so yeah anyway what's the best
anyway
is Apple Bottom Jeans the best or is
Apple Bottom Jeans the worst quality
um
[Music]
the first one doesn't matter for this
game yeah yeah why does it have so many
different options anyway
and then maybe there is only one ah
maybe not all the same okay okay okay so
that's that could be kind of again this
is
I can't play
oh uh whatever I chose was not
widescreen
know these things by heart do you guys
know these like resolutions like you
look at them and you know oh that's
widescreen that's not why it's gonna do
you know it by heart at all
I have to reopen so 5280 x 10 24 was not
white screen you know and then 720 is
why it's gonna get off
us okay oh that's time why is it so tiny
or whatever
you need a gun if you forget about it
yeah
[Music]
what are you talking about
um
it's so tiny why did I make it so tiny
oh but it's fun
it's fine I mean it does look kind of
upscale and obvious
[Laughter]
[Music]
ly when I feel like it get old
okay
yeah
Friday 31 in the haunted island is what
it's called
I have a wait I seems to have a habit of
making everything overlap of with the
game window a little bit because
apparently I don't know better kiddo
hi
hi okay
all right
here's a muscle Goran mm-hmm
and I can walk around wsd okay
hello I just guessed it's spacebar to
pick it up when I was right at all
hello who is it you know what would be
fun for like game design if someone made
a game where you like you get like
thrown into the game like this and then
you'll
um uh like for example the phone rings
and then you just press whatever button
feels intuitive for you and then the
game automatically would set that to
like the right input
for those interactions you know what
that means
like whatever feels intuitive for you
you will choose because you don't know
what else and then the game will
automatically set that for you as the
standard keybind
yeah wouldn't that be like genius
hello hello
is that me talking now because I'm the
detective right okay hello who is the
kiddo
oh is that a bird is that a penguin
I think
it doesn't look exactly like a penguin
but man it probably is a penguin right
that's the supervisor hi supervisor
hey how's life
yeah I'm pretty good I reckon how are
things with you looking at all
we are the wife just got back from it
a a penguin from Indonesia
[Music]
then I should talk more like
oh
me and me me Miranda wife she has a
really long voice kiddo I mean me and me
and the wife me and the wife just got
back from Indonesia
that means welcome back I think
thanks
is that does it sound anything like her
anyway what are you calling a basketball
oh oh Senpai right I have a case for you
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's it it's a pretty spooky one so hold
on tight
I'm holding on
there's a little sloth who owns an
island just off the bay
Martin's his name
says he's been hearing a ghost for about
two weeks
so get this he hires a team of ghosts
scientists oh
what's a ghost scientist kiddo hmm
I don't know anyway he hired some of
them right
and I can't find anything
they've been on the island for two weeks
wow
the ghost is still at large so the head
scientists there a monkey calls me up
they need help and they want the
greatest investigator I have
so I said to them I'll send my best
investigator but Lobster cup wasn't
available so I'm asking
[Music]
the second best investigator
I'll show you
I fully understand Lobster cops about
this far outweigh my own Kettle yeah but
you're pretty good
[Music]
so are you up for it
I don't know it sounds very scary
I'll have to be very brave at all
I believe a new Detective
good to hear
[Music]
can you give me a summary of the case
before I go kennel oh sure thing
I wanna do
thinking ah it's so difficult disappears
why you disappear
sure thing
the basics are
there's a sloth who's hearing a lot of
spooky ghost noises around his Island he
calls a bunch of ghost scientists but
they're stumped it's up to you to solve
the mystery of the haunted
Island
why did you yell 100 Island like that
because that's the title of this case
fair enough
it's time for you to grab your
magnifying glass and get going
see you later supervisor bye-bye
good luck
[Music]
title drop oh girl girl
um most of that did not enter my brain
at all something about ghosts
can I jump no
at least not with space what is that
does that mean a birthday party girl
I have a spider crab friend some fish
oh oh my friends are all like sea sea
animals oh okay let's oh wait take this
very important and get up oh look at the
hands cute
ah yes oh that's my trusty magnifying
glass cut off can't solve Mysteries
without it Carol now I can right click
to see things up close oh oh right click
I picked it up all right
so
oh
wow
all right let's go let's go in there
[Music]
time to solve a Mystery Ink and all
who would need zooming
um I need it
I don't know you didn't
it's fun
oh very dramatic music
a frog detective Adventure
programming by Thomas balker soundtrack
by Dan golden it sounds good
[Music]
oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
okay okay
no that's not here it's one of you guys
hi
oh yeah
look at you oh
oh you have a big belly oh what did you
eat together your big belly
anyone's reading yet maybe
[Laughter]
what what's about man
what are you doing
I talked to the non-obvious person first
[Music]
what are you doing in there
swimming but there's a Strunk at all oh
it's not raining yet
besides it's not actually that unsafe to
swim in storms you should know you
surviving really unsafe storms in the
Maldives didn't you
everyone keeps telling me to get out of
the seat but a safer here than it is up
there oh that was not me the one in the
Maldives was Kiara but we don't talk
about her anymore kiddo well anyway why
is that
no ghosts in the water ghosts can swim
how do you know
they don't have to swim you know the
same way they go for walls they can just
go through water no
I said
you don't look that happy in there kiddo
I guess I'm not
sorry to hear it kiddo thanks may I ask
why you're so sad
attention by the way because I'm not
I told you it's silly why do you want a
magnet kettle
go on
my dream is to attach a mask into a boat
and hold on
[Music]
why both are fast I'm not fast if I hold
on to the mountain I'll be really fast
too oh
um
does that work
it must be a pretty big magnet and it
has to be like really securely attached
to the boats and really securely
attached to you
um
nice let's not question it
right
I don't have any idea where to find one
though
and even if I did there's no way I'm
getting off of here
the ghost is found well that's
interesting
oh um
let's ask about the magnet I guess why
did you want to oh oh he just repeats
the same thing ah okay okay
Sweden's the deal I can give you oh
it was good it was good okay I know he
doesn't give it to us now he will give
it to us he will give us a shell
afterwards
why would you think a shell was magnetic
at all
no what am I a scientist
well yeah I'm wearing a lab coat well it
looks like maybe a lab coat I okay
is there anything you need to know
um no
not right now maybe we should talk to
the person that we're supposed to talk
to First oh
[Music]
it was a cutscene hello
he's his Dead face reminds me of
um those eyes those eyes who's that
who's that
you guys probably know what I'm thinking
of don't listen look at this face like
who is not thinking at this one
character
oh yeah I think I'm thinking of Elmo
yeah Muppets Elmo um
so hello
who finally murdered who actually was
such a short daughters so much about
your adventures I'm a huge fan
oh wow that's very kind of your whole
you're scaring the out of me
oh wait you figured oh
who started
believe it
before nobody would ever solve that
mystery I mean who steals on the tired
I have been following my black clothes
almost
made a funny joke what's that you
responded
oh of course I remember hi my story
monkey 49 oh please my story monkey hope
you know I just oh my all my name oh
you can just call me boosting monkey
no of course
um anyone can I ask you some questions
about this case
what would you like to draw
ah where to start it's good questions
you tell me who should I talk to First
ah oh you're talking to me already
ah okay we should head down to the
second no actually no no no you're this
you're the second one I'm talking to but
the game doesn't know
oh Larry Torrent one he always wants to
meet new people
[Music]
emotionally he wants new people to make
him laugh
not so much the other way around
I'll check it out thank you
um and besides that the resident
may I ask for the resident of this
island is
that would be Martin you can't find it
we're hiding in the floor as he thinks
the ghost can catch him now
very interesting I'll investigate
okay
besides that nothing
okay I'll come back after some
investigation
don't look at me look at those eyes at
least you stopped waving but he's still
like staring
staring into the nothingness
so we talked to him I already forgot his
name was his name not just koala
Larry is this Larry
[Music]
yes I got it right I remembered it from
the introduction
hi it's me Larry
oh I did not do it oh
noises are not coming from me
I didn't I worry
did not
make these spooky noises
that's like more suspicious somehow
kiddo what
are you even listening
I said I did not make the noises
no I heard I just I don't like being a
huge like this
I'm not accusing oh you're not
it's so quickly switches to him because
he's interrupting him
that that's such such a relief
hmm
can I why are you gonna ask me questions
ask me them the questions are me
I don't know what it is
you guys just gonna say you didn't do it
right
honestly I am not the one making them
yeah okay oh I know where is it coming
from
oh what
oh no I'm coming from the caverns of
forest
why haven't you told anyone at all
nobody listens to me
they said stop like everyone listens
once we won't listen to you
which is so weird because I didn't
listen
or maybe they mean I'm a real
ingredients
so how do we get into the cave
wow things
so get so that you need some sort of
explosion in the these
is that safe
well ceiling was the ghost Shield
detective none of this is safe
anyway I'll need a few things
I looked up an explosive recipe in one
of the old chemistry books
I need a toothpaste some UL
a chunk of pure gold and some pasta
the pasta is just for you to eat isn't
it
oh so the normal explosive ingredients
no question
yeah yeah just a Sonic explosive recipe
oh yes we we if you want to get into the
cave uh bring me those ingredients sweet
um I'll do my best
um
foreign
[Music]
bye bye
uh Too Faced pasta wool
uh and I forgot we'll get it we'll get
it and then I'll know when I get it I'll
know
is this pasta well then and look I have
already the fast oh goal gold okay that
was it yum but it's not mine well then
let's get it from him
hi Olive why don't you just know oh
oh no you look very similar okay
please give me the pasta
a Bernie
hey you didn't take the fruit dude that
monkey keeps going on the boat oh that's
me
I'm so glad they finally brought the
Buddhists and I do nothing I really
shouldn't have taken this job
why don't you take it girl
you won't be honest I thought it was a
secret agent job Secret
why would you think that the job listing
said ghost aunties they didn't disable
like a real job to me
I thought it was like a cover you know
one that only what people could figure
out like me
ah I still it still could be a cover
maybe they're testing you
Oh no you're right I better look
competent I'm only joking
can I ask you some questions about the
tanks
what else do you want to do
the pasta the pasta
about this hole
what do you know about the noises coming
from this hole a bit I'm not created
this job I'd be good at other jobs I'm
just letting you know but it does seem
like the noise is coming from this old
Earth from natural creature
eh doesn't sound like Shin-chan what are
you guys saying
no she said it's like higher than that
[Laughter]
the world is the Bell they have weird oh
uh sometimes it sounds like a boots
called
dubs
African just
inhaled canned hairs man
what
I just really quickly have to
time out someone
I saw something terrifying
you've got all the information
it's a very good at the feeding finding
things out if you know what I mean
um Bernie I'm not a secret agent
what else do you want to do nothing
but what about
the pasta
what about the pasta can I have
um
how to get weird
oh
hello friend Patrick
is this you but you look so blue Patrick
can't possibly be him oh beetle beetle
well hello Beetle how you doing how you
doing can I step on you kiddo
I wanna eat you
[Music]
the one that one's tasty um
oh hello
can I get all you almost look like a
frog you're green and you look funny but
you're not a frog are you
okay
[Music]
how howdy um
howdy
[Laughter]
I am the
[Music]
um
yeah
great you brought my toothpaste shipment
no
toothpaste I'm sorry I don't think I can
help you with that
no I'm the detective
oh okay
can I call you d-tech
yes nice
I have some questions is that okay
take it away detect
your smiles
it's beautiful
I hope you don't mind me saying well you
have a wonderful team
thank you
I'm so glad someone finally noticed
how do you keep them so pearly white
with doctor
height not five tight Smiles 101 tooth
whitening cool paste for teeth of course
Dr tight Smiles 101 tooth whitening cool
face for teeth get off
I got a shipment here every three days I
go for this stuff so quickly
I think you're doing more than just
brushing your teeth on them
I think you weren't eating it aren't you
eating it
none I don't think like if you I'm sure
like consuming a little bit of Too Faced
is probably fine but like consuming
whole cubes of toothpaste toothpaste
like
whole shipment in three days I wonder
what would that do to your body
yeah he has a Too Faced problem
whoa where can I get some of my own
do you have teeth oh
[Music]
uh well I could give you my tube but I
would need something else to keep my
mouth fresh
foreign
[Music]
I'll think about it can I ask you some
more questions
Jake is a lady Turk
oh you're close I guess they're kind of
stylish why aren't you wearing a laptop
with like the other scientists
it's my day off oh yeah they're all
finders okay
I've been working so hard for the last
two weeks
it's very important to take a break and
get some sun
you're right get all not about the sun
uh about taking a day off kiddo
and then pick a great day for it
sorry to question you on your day off
okay
so wait did he not just give me the
toothpaste he said he will give me a
toothpaste all right he's right there
can I hands
no oh
[Music]
I didn't I didn't click on you
no give me Daddy
he said he would give it to me now
you want something in this okay ah okay
ah of course okay of course I thought
this was you know no strings attached oh
man but okay if we get the toothpaste
then we already have like no didn't he
want like toothpaste right and the pasta
and then okay the other thing was gold
and oh
yeah
how are you are you alive
why do you all have such funny faces
all right let's get into the forest some
people hiding here thinking that they
can hide from the ghost
hello you have a nice bed here you're
the only one using this are you okay
[Music]
who are you
I didn't mean to start Leo I'm the front
detective here from the agency kid um
okay don't sneak up on me like that
visible for the entire approach I came
in here like really slowly too huh
well fine I guess it doesn't look so
spooky
oh okay I'll do my best
sorry I'm so cranky I'm slept in two
weeks
imagine King of the island
you're king of Chrissy why are you
questioning that there's a crown
it's obvious
but when I got here there was nobody
else on the island except for me and
Finley so I thought it was fine to
declare myself King
definitely
I don't think family cares about that
sort of stuff feeling mostly cares about
Dance Competition oh
oh I like that competition too
um
let me join let me join let me join
yeah
now I meant to ask who is Finley
okay then
and tell me
do you mind if I ask a few questions or
you didn't answer me who is Finley
question this guy is weird
Finley
you mentioned your friend Finley who is
that kettle
wow Finley lives on the neighbor Island
and comes to visit every few days the
last time I saw Finley she was talking
about the songs she wanted to dance for
two for a competition Her Moves were
pretty amazing not like me she
apparently Wayne
I'm sitting around but she's probably
still prepping for the competition is
tomorrow
not that I'll be able to compete what
with this whole spooky coming situation
going on huh
got questions for me
um your nerves are you good are you good
bro you seem super nervous is there
anything I can do to help
it's just a ghost getting me down
I haven't been able to sleep
I'm kind of annoyed too because I
usually love hearing about stories of
ghosts
I read all about them on the
cyberweb.com
I'm living one
Michelle will get to the bottom of this
but it was great for like
you know
I made more sense in my head
I guess I mean like but probably die
before the mess yourself
it's very dark
like just a conclusion to this Tale
sorry if I'm being dramatic
no I'm a good detective right
I have solved every case I've taken on
except the mystery of how to put a head
on kettle
strange shape yeah relatable ghetto
it really is the point is
they're safe
to find the culprit get off hmm
the best thing you can do is sit and
relax
everything will be okay get all
I don't feel okay I'm finding it really
hard to calm down
understand ghosts are scary yeah but it
might not be a ghost at all yeah I
probably really is not a ghost
you really think it's not a ghost
probably not I don't know for sure
though oh
let's try the visualization exercise
scale what's up visual wow that's
exorcism
we should be doing that yeah that might
be helpful
it's a thing it's a thing where we
pretend imagine imagine
you're on the beach surrounded by
calming waves oh watch out oh yeah waves
waves
I can feel the Cool Breeze on your face
right there
um oh that feels good
the waves slowly moving and in and out
and in and out
it's a safe beach girl
because
this beach
oh this is
the closest on holiday
oh
okay
where is it
on a road trip
more like a beat strip or an ocean trip
there's no roads here man
cool
can we visualize that we're on the road
trip instead
the ghost is on the road trip
and the ghost is on the road trip great
Point continue anyway the waves are
coming in and out slowly
there's nothing to worry about
no ghosts around at all
the ghost is on the road trip yeah
nothing to fear
you will be that job like Sandy Beach
that's me in the ocean
um
[Music]
how you feel
so relaxed
great me too
thanks so much thank you that's okay I
want to give you something as fangs
perhaps the piece of my crown oh
[Music]
it's so nice that's okay thank you and
from this amazing thank you
it's really heavy this may not be a gold
why I like gold okay a question for me
um
no I think
I pretty much know everything I am I am
I took all that information in very very
well
[Music]
I don't know why I made this person who
talks so much that voice
it's painful the more I talk like this
okay you gotta do what you gotta do are
you good now you still look nervous just
lie down and sleep
oh room
maybe someone needs a broom
[Music]
oh
yeah I took it okay got it bro
who needs a broom
well
flower
and your mouse
[Music]
Casper Bay
how does Bale speak
I wish I knew how Bale speaks
[Music]
are you okay
I am what's up are you sure
what about you
embarrassing
everything
is that are they looking up to me
[Music]
huh
no time
there's still time
oh wow is it okay if I ask some
questions here's some questions
[Music]
you're trying to use my hands
yes
um
you're nervous
you see my nervous may I ask why
[Music]
oh my God I don't know
like a good reason though I'm sorry to
hear about it though
oh well you're with me you
stupid rat about tell me the truth and
nothing but the truth so you swear
let's see what I can tell you was
nothing absolutely nothing I am a bad
rat uh
I ate Kiana's chocolate
and I survived it so I Will Survive
YouTube
[Music]
fine it won't be down anyway so stab
your extreme detective skills
I'm nervous because of Mr Monkey
oh and whoa
[Music]
oh because you like them
I just think mystery monkey super neat
ah
[Music]
um
understandable is there anything I can
do to help
[Music]
we're dancing oh good idea yes
I want to see you dancing
hey
[Music]
I can give you this mouthwash mouthwash
that's four that's foreign
[Music]
questions yes
um the bottle
oh we got more questions now what's
another one next to you
[Music]
that's my mouse wash mouthwash okay okay
okay well no problem then
um well maybe I should also ask about
the ghost
or are you just gonna repeat yourself
a ghost scientist
oh
that was scientists
there's so much more sense ah you
brought your word so scientists
understandable I mean toast toast is
like a big big science on its own yeah
yeah like how long you have to toast to
toast be the perfect toast what to put
on the toast to be the perfect host and
so many combinations of different things
on the toast can make so many different
you see this one
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
over there that's the koala right oh
he's still in the water he's he's
stalking this mouse if the mouse ever
did a rat if they ever disappear we know
what happened
the ice
oh
because you like toast
what have you been doing this whole time
[Music]
then you haven't heard any weird noises
what makes you say that I don't see
anything floating around as if a ghost
was holding it that happens in the
movies I'll keep an eye out though
surfing
okay oh yeah okay okay I don't need you
anymore I know exactly what to do I'll
go back to the dancer
and I'll talk to you later oh he also
has a magnifying glass
oh
what kind of bird is that
this game is cute you know I like I like
silly little games like this very much
uh dance when you don't know huh
was he the dancer
I forgot
oh was that a duck oh
dance dance here
I I thought I was gonna sneeze
no snake
I saw you at home
you are dancing and on dance styles
I forgot oh did I do like a Mickey
Monkey voice right
which is why he said man that's that's
totally how I came up with that
oh
I'm sorry
oh classical
[Music]
yeah kind of what type of dance do you
like the best
oh well basically only have one more
fool yeah but like if you saw someone
else dancing
What scenario would you most likely be
like this is such a great dance
what
I guess what I'm trying to ask is what
that sound do you like best
dude
there's also what breaking dad sing
bring me drinking dancing oh I was fun I
would even go so far to say it was
awesome when you break that side
impressed that I would want to hang out
with them at all times forever oh
that's great sorry for such a strange
question that's okay I'm sorry it's
important to the case oh
anyone else see Elena okay perfect
perfect
occupied oh that also shows up there oh
I see I say a monkey fact
monkey be like monkey monkey
look caterpillars I love them I
think the dance battle you have to learn
is Breakdown schedule
it's not the mystery monkey
[Music]
I miss you
Mr miracula is break dancing the best
I don't really sure
it's pretty difficult but I think even a
little bit goes a long way
spare the caterpillar froggy Wawa
okay
okay and that's it one time though
after the stream I'll eat it
oh the mouse washed my flies whoa sick
thank you
all right well now we don't have the
monkey fat anymore because we exchanged
it okay let me take a fruit candy this
is already very very painful
thank God these are only one hour long
um
huh
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
fresh eggs I'm back for questions take
it away do you drag
my last one
[Music]
I said my voice for you amazing facts
am I able to use your toothpaste I
almost forgot here you go g-tech
I got toothpaste
um
wait oh yeah so well even though we have
it now
I guess do we need to come back with all
four things we have two things now
and this past says right now I'm like
over there
um
you take it already no okay
seems like he doesn't need it
[Music]
who took my sunglasses give back so true
remember do not split up when searching
for ghosts like in Scooby-Doo
Scooby-Doo
by me
you're so cute
oh a map imagine attack
can I has
yeah
[Music]
yeah happy
hello I think you wanted the magnet
didn't you yeah
oh
oh I forgot the voice
[Music]
ah French French it wasn't really
intended to be French but you guys know
chat were saying it sounds French
uh oh always with the question was it
like that wow is there is there anything
you need to know
um
[Music]
I brought your magnet what
oh the lobster was ah damn it look
at what was he
ah there's so many characters
[Music]
Oh Come boys oh
like a real one I really like this
are you for real
I don't know whatever there's a dream
come true thank you so much no problem
and we're telling you this big shout oh
okay I don't remember anyone asking for
a shell but don't kiss it hello kitto
thank you
okay bye bye
we'll find someone who needs a shout
let's talk to you
what are you are you a sheep is that a
is that a sheep
it's a protein
a noodle a lamp is that a sheep or lamb
oh cause we need whoa whoa whoa hey
how's it hanging
[Music]
bored that's suspicious Kettle so
surely you can't just say I'm suspicious
there's no rule against it I'm not being
suspicious at all
I guess not sorry for calling you
suspicious kiddo
it's okay
flying board with my mind I say bored
it's not in ghosts supposed to be
exciting
for the first Rachel or not now at all
I've been out there supposed to
encounter time
I'm shutting everywhere
ah relatable
gross no it's not gross a fluffy
annoying yeah a little bit but
um
[Music]
do you mind if I ask you a few questions
why are you shedding so much
I haven't had a German agent said so
yeah
I'm usually getting cut once a week when
it's been two weeks now it's about
time and time then yeah it's so
gross it's totally fine thanks for
trying to spare my feelings but there's
wool everywhere I think everyone just
grossed out lion
can't possibly be that bad Ah that's
really that's not true maybe not
I think most people like wool
it's just for so much stuff
like what my jumper is made out of wool
I ain't for real
it's really fun to do
let's win
that you're wearing my hair what was
pretty gross that's why I keep mine sure
slime what
I mean mine is fine you
want slime I'm not slimy
I'm not lying meme
girls ride
short but
slime is kind of gross anyway no
I'm saying that as someone who's very
slimy I'm not slimy you're you're ruined
ruining the reputation no frogs
wool is worn by most people that's the
first time I've heard of someone where
I think that makes you the weird one
plus I'm pretty sure this shirt you're
wearing is wool
I'm pretty sure yeah
I'm happy to take your wool away from
you if you'd like I mean
I mean well not your shirt
definitely
yes but you'll need something to clean
it up with like a broom oh I already
have a broom like fire now we're not
gonna clean up your will of fire you're
not gonna set you on fire
Kettle probably won't use fire okay okay
I'm gone I can't believe I'm wearing
wool what if it's Barney is you
so disgusting
might have asked my questions
no I don't need any more and maybe about
the whole but for now I will give you
the broom
what is a science line don't go what if
I go
wait let's wait for the room first
okay oh oh no now I see there's a lot of
words
like a friend
[Laughter]
how's that work how does that work dude
how do you do it you're so cute this is
my favorite character maybe
you may not have only answers but going
let's go away
here you go
amazing thank you can I keep it yeah
yeah can I keep your wall
that's so weird when you knock yourself
out no King shaming
I mean Let It Go take on the whole only
one imagine imagine a cheap way tuber
except but I mean you could imagine her
doing it too like constantly talking
like this
so in character
or or go to YouTuber
knock yourself out whoo
got whoa all right
[Music]
have fun with that oh all the wool has
gone nice
I really had no problem with it though
oh let's try I mean let me ask first
about the whole before I go in
I may not have all the answers but yeah
I'll try this whole
what can you tell me about this whole
kettle
oh why
don't you say anything oh well it's a
hole
you met well you might appreciate it
more if you played portal
and not portal
um
[Music]
Stanley's Parable
that's it
I'm a ghost scientist I want to see
ghosts not holes baby the ghost is in
the hole have you looked
no ghosts in there it's pretty neat pole
opening smiling gets as you get down
once
so maybe there's a ghost further down
do you hear any ghost noises coming from
the Hulk at all
right not as many as Bernie and Larry's
home but they have their own hole I
look I got a gun oh oh
what's happening
and if you want I can come to your house
and take care of all the Flies even like
this or like this oh
[Music]
welcome can we
you have a need for a fly extinguisher
you have many flies around what about
like food that you left outside the
fridge oh I'm feeling you know that just
happened it do be like that and once
once there's some fruit flies it's so
hard to get rid of it no what the
ing line I need my service eh
cicadas oh the stupid ass semi all right
all right for those I need I need my gun
because they are
um
it's a bit difficult with them I mean
at some point you know they just fall
down the tree right but before they do
that you know then then obviously they
just they just fall down and dead but
before that it's a bit difficult to take
them down yeah yeah but I'll take care
of it all right I will okay I will take
care of all of the cicadas
in all of Japan I will get rid of all of
them and then I'll eat them oh foreign
food for days
oh it's a bad company
that's an awkward combination
all right what do we have uh
that no that's a noisy oh
I wish I could hang out there
who's Stopping You The Boss
who's the boss I'm the boss now
I don't know maybe the mystery monkey he
seems pretty boss-like
because he greeted me with uh you know
with that with that with the paper
um maybe not okay mind if I ask you
something no questions get all ask away
no no no I'm actually done with you I
will try to go into the hole let's see
can we enter or I don't know
no
[Music]
all right
don't go in I should listen to the Sonic
at all
what I should be able to get together
can we get much deeper so deep
I'm sorry
I'm sorry but I said we got the
toothpaste uh
uh and the wool and the gold and now
what about
stop
why you not to give me the bus stop
how do I get the pasta oh with the hole
let me enter the hold there's no
scientist lying around this one can't
get any further without a goddammit
kettle
okay let's talk to this one guy the duck
yo what's this
[Music]
why Jesus get down oh twerk twerk twerk
baby don't twerk Twerk It Twerk It Shake
That
[Music]
oh
let's go
sheesh oh actually really not bad like
actually not bad
wow where'd you get those moves
ah skip
oh yeah yeah
look
I'm in city lights in the midnight one's
inside another job
don't stop don't stop keep going
and hello what did he just dab on me oh
[Music]
this voice is going to be bad for me why
I won't get up
I guess not
wait don't I have a shot oh I don't have
to do you surely want to Shell don't you
let me step on yours now I'll give you a
new one
okay
[Music]
um are we still going to sound like that
yeah
why
you look indeed very loud also why we're
matching we're friends
should not be alarmed
I don't know
this is Rock Creek
um
my frogs is very gentle giggle
don't mean to be robots watch else
I can't see any shells okay oh yeah
indeed let's point out the elephants in
the room
how small
I would say my magnifying glass is
pretty uh um much the same as yours
I could get this one especially made for
my 10 ships
fine can I ask you some questions now
tiny shells would you like a big shell
because I have a big shell
why don't you just get a bigger shell
a bigger shell
s around here
smack the vine glass will be useless to
me but it does see a big shower around
here do you
ah because I have it in my pocket
here
give
it's a long story
I don't care I hate stories yeah
stories
yes what will you give me yeah and now
I'm magnifying glass
um
will it make will it replace my current
one I wonder
I'm still standing weird I'm still on
the line stop being stop being alerted
okay sweet I got a magnifying glasses
[Music]
[Laughter]
see on this one I can't step
um I'm wasting on as long as you're
holding it up like this so all things
are good
now
I still don't know oh my God look at
look at this
look is it looks like me actually I'm
gonna look kind of similar doesn't you
need the Nike at all
snack get up
they're so cute
oh my God
oh my God wait wait a second
is that like a picture of oh a child of
a developer or that's a child
it's not even three-dimensional
what what is that anyway let's go this
way
now I think we'll talk to everybody
um do we have
um who who would have wanted the
the
magnifying glass
that's the death
wait it's not isn't it but that's a
child's face no
and I don't know it looks kind of like a
child to me I'm sorry if it's not a
child
um
wow okay we'll talk to the bear again
maybe you please now give me the pasta
[Music]
uh
questions
what else do you want to do
um
well I'll ask about secret agent maybe
that leads me to the pasta good
secret agents get the best stuff like
for example you've got the cool
magnifying glass I wonder
um
[Music]
the figs that give up for magnifying
glasses the thing I would go yeah let's
try the pasta
[Music]
we're like going so fast with our
detective work that I can totally see
this being a one-hour game yeah yeah
although I guess I've been going for
more than an hour at this point or like
pretty much exactly an hour with some
chit chat in between
I could obviously go faster if I wasn't
reading all this out loud like you you
read much faster if you don't read
things out loud I think the one hour is
more like if you if you don't stream the
game but just play it on your own
interested are you kidding me there's a
very literally nothing I want the ball
there you go
when I get the pasta please
and yeah not a secret agent fun for I
could give you my lunch oh
above those always if there's one thing
I love about from the real age of
secrecy it's pasta
don't eat it
then the glass not good I broke a glass
yesterday
while putting it into the dishwasher
so stupid when that stuff happens like I
was I didn't drop it or anything I just
put it down
like you know between those like you
know like the boob stand the upbeat
thingies
yeah but it broke only like in one piece
uh like so in total these two pieces I
guess
really no problem to clean it up
thankfully thankfully
um
yeah the small hands no it wasn't
cracked before but I guess I I
squeezed it a little bit into a spot
that was a bit too tight maybe it would
be
what
this is this seems to me a thing in kfp
recently
we have like always like one one medium
now we can keep on repeating
might be my fault
um
grip strength too strong I pressed Crest
it crashed into the glass yeah
anyway give lunch please okay no thank
you get all hustle Park got some pasta
and now I got everything already
maybe this is really already the the end
of the game because it's one hour pretty
much
[Music]
I have all those you need
I think
toothpaste yes oh yeah chunk of you go
yeah pasta yes
explosion let's make it then make it go
Kaboom and I want to see how you make it
though teach me
teach me how you make it
uh how did I make his voice oh yeah you
got everything
yeah amazing shall we make some uh done
the mood yes
yes
let's go let's do it
up some dinner and we can get exploding
[Music]
end of the game
well this is it get off
e that the bloodies give up
Larry explosives are dangerous
so sorry
attempt to carefully blow this game up
thanks
I'm nervous me too I'm not even coming
into the cave
you're not
well I'm going in there I guess I don't
like dog's business I'm a sunny boy baby
[Music]
let's do this
up
oh
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go
puppy I don't wanna look
um
welcome to after your eyes are free
let's get some materials
hahaha
oh thanks
wow the graphics look so beautiful no
this is totally look something you would
see and that's where your eyes are free
just with better graphics wow
this cave is really indeed spooky I
don't like being here alone why nobody
come with me
oh
music
yeah
where are you
[Music]
dancing
what is this what is this animal
of the music though
a chicken oh no now that you're saying
like a sea chicken
again talk to me
oh
[Music]
spin I got an achievement I got spooked
oh why don't the achievements show up
this time normally they don't when the
when the steam pop up Pops Up Normally
it doesn't show an OBS interesting I
don't mind though
uh
oh hi
oh look at my alerted stance kettle
who are you kiddo
oh
just like me just like me for real for
real
what I don't think so
are you sure kiddo
that's great at all you're not wrong
so uh who are you kiddo Finley
who are you
the detective
howdy wait a minute
Finley you know that name I'm pretty
well known now I had local dance circles
ah okay yeah that makes sense yeah yeah
um
your mother's friend
yeah
what are you doing down here
this thing for the dance competition
it's tomorrow tomorrow
how long have you been down here
um
she's like two weeks I guess oh I didn't
even realize
wait two weeks have you seen any ghosts
around
no
it's me down here
does Martin know you're here kiddo
I don't think so
who comes down here
really why not kettle
things every dark space is haunted he
reads all those ghost books and things
there's of course in every craft bees
for me though
whatever you've been dancing for two
weeks straight now wow yeah
aren't you tired
wait this is cute well
this is in the past
I mean I took naps
and this mushrooms are super nutritious
don't eat the red ones
oh I don't know what the others though
cross mushrooms are disgusting
like the Frog
what's your opinion
no it's a bag
I know it I don't like mushrooms either
okay
anyway Marge isn't super Spilled Out
because he's been hearing weird noises
all over the island girl any idea what
the noises would be
I haven't listened to my radio while
dancing this cave has a lot of holes the
sound from your radio could easily
travel up to the surface I bet it would
sound super warped too kettle
you know you've been trapped in here
right the cave has been blogged up by a
rock Skittle
really
yeah
that's so funny
yeah you could have died
[Music]
yeah when I survived me
and actually I could have been a ghost
could
no then then actually I would be a ghost
I didn't even think of that yeah
hmm
anyway we should head back up to I love
this I love the dialogue man
that's it yeah
let's look at the dance
then
so our
um final thing is that the ghost noises
came from the holes in the cave
from her radio all right
hi Martin
guy
hey
hi
what are you doing here
I was in the cave
you what
how did you get in it's been Sail Out
for weeks
and please to be accepted
wait a minute
as it turns out there was no uh as it
turned out there was never a ghost girl
it was Finley in the cave all along
she was wrapped up in practice and she
didn't even notice the cave got caved in
the noise from a radio carried up to the
service it's not a super spooky girl
my ghost book
S I was so Shane where's it close
not just me this might really be a
chicken right now now that I've seen it
in the normal daylight
is yellow so I guess it really was a
chicken dancing
ah cute yes there's always a chickens
which are dancing
um and the phoenixes
yeah
the hair yeah
and you never trust boobs yeah oh it's
just the internet
um yeah yes and green
book size without exception factually
inaccurate
hello
oh you're the developer Grace brooksner
hope you're enjoying the game I won't
keep you for long while I agree with
Detective on the most
you're you're um you're trying to defend
books now just to make sure now that the
reputation of books is not destroyed
there are context in which books can be
very useful and informative it's
important to check the validity of the
awkward sources and to check the book is
up to date the internet can also be
useful place to find information but
make sure you're getting your
information from a trusted side thank
you for your time enjoy the rest of the
game who is this
um so anyway as I was saying on books I
have no place in our society should I
think make sure
thank you for opening my ass to useless
so
that's what we learned from this story
your practice tomorrow to competition
this whole time yes
um I need to win it
or to wing it
I'm still going to tell you what this
dance competition evolves that's that's
competition
dancer wins
oh Elsa's competing competing
huh that's a good point
who's this I guess no no no no
don't forget boy the mouse
who wanted to go scientist now what
don't worry about it they think they're
two scientists
I think we need more entrance should I
join I know I feel hard working friends
who could use a good Boogie but it won't
be here tomorrow
I've moved the competition to today
yeah yeah
before we dance I just want to say
thanks for solving the mystery Detective
no problem at all
I had a lot of help well I already
figured out where the noises were coming
from Mary said the lobster I want to
talk some of everybody oh yeah yeah yeah
shall we Boogie let's go
[Music]
oh yeah
oh yes
oh yeah I can do that too oh wait oh
[Music]
I can do caramel dancing
wow
[Music]
it's actually pretty exhausting for my
fingers
[Music]
dancing
where's my mouse
where's my mom's for real I lost it
[Music]
you
my mouse is gone oh there you go
oh yeah
[Music]
before
to continue the dialogue
nothing works
[Music]
nothing works it just Waits from like it
takes time this is normal
[Music]
hold on oh it doesn't recognize my mouse
anymore yeah I dance too hard
[Music]
huh
when I Tab out I find my mouse again but
in the game it's gone oh
[Music]
wait
oh my God
[Music]
foreign
look at me the protagonist of the game
ah
a okay
perfect
competition can I choose me
what about me
um well then it must be cute
[Laughter]
congratulations
I'm gonna make myself bigger again that
was some sick moves
hmm
sickness
and we cleared the first game it seems
[Music]
oh roses
right away again no I will only see the
detective
probably not the same island though
[Music]
a little bit later
Nicole I'm thinking oh wait there's a
photo now
oh okay how cute oh yes hello
Detective
[Music]
great work on the haunted Island mystery
thank you on track really hot canal
I don't think even Lobster cup would
have solved that one Tinker I'm gonna
submitting Lobster Club
you're probably right
anyway I saw you blessed agree by the
dance competition
yeah when did you see that it was on TV
every channel what when was the camera
crew oh
[Music]
every channel
in HD call it 4K
oh I don't even see any camera let's get
up well you're certainly impressed to
public my phone has been ringing off the
hook mostly the calls are about your
dancing but I did get one call about the
case have you heard of the Warlock Woods
huh I haven't
we'll do something very strange going on
there they need our best investigator on
the job
Lobster clap wasn't available at all I
need a break man no can you
handle another case detective I can
have any
but the game is ending that the title
will turn in
reveal of Roger tattoo
in case of the invisible wizard was that
like the working title oh product
detective two oh no
yes it was called that it's actually
called a frog tattoo with a case of them
invisible wizard ah invisible with that
invisible with that invisible
I already know that it was coming they
can look into the future how did they
know how did they know
we're playing it right off the number
and I'm by the way aware
that
um
uh there is a
let's see if I can do this
there's a part
oh there you go free there's a thing
um from detective game coming out next
week apparently but I think it's fine
that we're not playing it because you
know
I can I can show off this froggy Wawa
again like summer time in the future as
long as you know it's not like every
single day you know
so I think at some point when I feel
like oh I need like a filler
um stream
um in between like
something then I can always bring out
Prototype Free and come back with froggy
Wawa you know that's what I'm thinking
I'm smart
smart frog
yeah
so it's fine and then now we're gonna
play
let me exchange the logo
now
ah I pressed something in OBS and made
it
lose wasn't one of these keys no
oh
the windows bar is gone on my OBS
desktop
monitor
and and it has no top
bar uh you know for like
minimizing and all that what how do you
solve this again
f11
to my death
really oh yes that's it thank you
oh damn it
hmm
okay
they may or may not have connected
something there
um
um what is that gonna do
what are you gonna do
oh yeah
oh yeah yeah I made it full screen yeah
yeah
okay
now it's fixed thank you you guys know
everything about computers get all so
smart
don't forget to take the tool the case
of the invisible wizard are you ready
I don't know
for Ark detective two day yo bye
oh my God there's a cat in there and
like a lion on the wall some some like
um
some tropical animals but wait wait wait
what is this song next is like in the
graphics quality it says
Van Gogh bus is coming and everybody's
jumping New York to San Francisco and
Intercity disco the Wheels of Steel are
turning and traffic lights are burning
I've never heard of that before what is
that kiddle
you know it
venga bus is the song well let me look
it up maybe I've heard it before
thank god boss
well let me let me mute
oh
[Music]
who is this
167 million views
we like the party
we like we like to party we like to
party
we like we like to party wow she really
moves her mouth really exaggerately oh
[Music]
you go girl
I've never heard anything besides
[Music]
oh
oh cute girls
when when comes that part
oh
ah and everybody's job they know you
have to San Francisco and Intercity
disco the lizards are still a turning
and travel was all burning up
oh
maybe I can sing that in a kettle okay
at some point
ah
wow I never I never knew about the
lyrics
[Laughter]
so funny what
yeah what a what an amazing song get up
but honestly like I'm planning a credit
okay for
on Sunday but it's probably gonna be our
crap so this song will probably not be
in there but you know Kid Rock is here
uh
froggy Wawa is here to stay
so I'll uh
we have more opportunities
[Music]
anyway
where is um here okay
oh let me make it let me get
bigger this time whoa
super hot presents am I playing the
wrong game
super hot wait I I actually I thought it
had I added windows but it wasn't
windowed
super hot
[Music]
here's wait a moment while we switched
too far together too I don't think this
is 16 to 9 is this six into nine
ah
laughs
trying number two
that was not 16 tonight I did not select
this no no this is what I selected
super hot
presents
game
Club killed wait
okay
in the case of the invisible wizard oh
new game nothing
it's a lantern hmm
okay we're back ooh same room and we
have this pink town I wonder if you did
not play the first game if this would
not be in here
because I assume you know some games
have this thing recognize that you
played a different game and then they
put like a a surprise somewhere right an
Easter egg
one took me 1.5 hours
yeah now maybe now this time could be a
bit faster yeah maybe I will I won't go
a bit faster because I want to cook
something afterwards get all
um
I will cook something with my health
with koalas hello fresh stuff
it's the same person but now in a
sweater I don't think you are wearing a
sweater before
[Music]
um
I think yeah I might like frogs
[Music]
yeah she frogs but that doesn't change
the fact that I didn't like her
yeah
hi Detective
supervisor why'd you hang up on me I
were talking just a moment ago
thanks so much more
I mean I mean it would make sense
otherwise too but it's like funny if you
play them back to back
oh yeah
oh
yeah sorry about that don't want to draw
like Woods right
yeah
I hung up because I hung up because I
got too excited about solving another
mystery
that's understandable
why didn't you tell me what his new case
can huh
it's a doozy detective what does that
mean Lucy hold on to your head
my hands my hand
this is not a hand this is real
when you're on the hand
I swear I swear I swear I swear on the
grave of takanashikiana that this is a
hat another hat
it was a mistake you didn't hear what I
just said okay
you know I can't wear hats
sorry anyway I mean look at me
I've got me able to wear a hat even with
those big ears I have up there and eyes
[Music]
no one no one believe you if you keep on
making mistakes like this
[Music]
okay I will pull my together now
well look at this is a fairly small town
up north they got don't get many
visitors around there a couple of days
ago a new Resident moved in a shy kind
of girl doesn't like to be the center of
attention anyway she sent us into the
new house and doesn't go outside to
greet anyone the residents of the Town
feel like they need to welcome her
properly so they organize a welcoming
party you know like in sins where they
bring fruit cake but nobody likes
fruitcake so at some point of playing
with Sims you would just stop welcoming
the welcome frog and it's just like that
laughs I totally get what you mean girl
absolutely but someone in the town
seemed to think otherwise last night the
parade decorations were destroyed
all yeah Sims 4 the base game is free to
play now guys
um
I know right so rude nobody has any
leads on this case they don't know who
done it
that's where you come in Detective
that's me
that I'm aware well look which is a
magic time so it's not the easiest place
to get to you'll need to take an
enchanted car to the end of the line and
travel the rest of the way on foot oh
too easy you need to question everybody
to get to the bottom of things do you
think you can solve the mystery
[Music]
hop on to it I forgot to mention the new
Resident of the woods is special she's
invincible
what that was loud
another wizard
amusement
I have some slime in my throat not
because I'm a Frog necessarily
but I actually cried like a baby today
I mean
I cried like a froggy Wawa today
yeah um something happened it's all good
but I'm so stupid I'm okay no I'm not
stupid no no I think it was reasonable I
don't know if my mom is watching this
let me just say first of all it was all
good but
so you know how my mom call uh called me
about telling what she called Kiana to
tell her about how uh her GTA
playthrough was so good good that was I
think from Sunday to Monday and then
that was on WhatsApp okay
and and then uh after that uh yesterday
you know it's because like I killed
Kiara I thought it would be kind of nice
of me too
um still give her that vacation that
Keanu promised her so I book the hotel
yesterday
and that was yeah I told her about it on
WhatsApp I sent her the messages with
Kiara's phone
and then and then she didn't reply
normally she replies very fast said
Kiana and it was weird and then the next
day 24 hours later I checked the phone
again and then still no reply and still
not online on WhatsApp since that one
call and that's not really normal like
sometimes she won't answer during the
day if she's like in her garden doing
work or so but then I got like really
worried
and I just tried like calling her okay
but then she didn't pick up and I called
again and I called again and she didn't
pick up and I got really really worried
um and I started imagining all kinds of
crazy things and and I was thinking like
how how do I get to her place without a
car because it's like really difficult
to reach around the car and instead of
thinking about it and I wrote to my
brother and my sister and I'm like uh to
Kiana's brother and Kiana's sister and I
was like yo do you do you know what you
would want me
and they they didn't answer and this all
of this happened like within one hour or
so and but I I really started panicking
then I wrote to Jen my number
[Music]
talked a bit with me and then and then
and then
um then I wrote to my best friend and
then I was like Mommy doesn't like me
away
nobody answered me besides General and
then
we continue calling
um I tried calling Mommy in different
ways and finally at some point she
actually picks up and and she picks up
and I'm like love me and she's like what
what
broke out in tears
before I got into tears and she was like
I don't know this is Jenny what are you
saying like what I don't know that
to cry my heart out and I I explained to
her what happened that I panic because
she didn't answer for 24 hours and then
it's not only that you know so that she
wasn't online for more than like 48
hours and and and and and
she recently always always talks about
how bad her health is and how worried
she is like she literally tells me that
you know she's she's not gonna
live very long and you know it
makes me really worried and especially
in connection with that and the problem
is she lives somewhere where like it's
hard for me to reach her
um yeah and yeah I was really worried
like no one no one would probably like
in their neighborhood would probably
even notice
[Music]
I'm sorry
so much
and then we went on to talk endlessly
because my mom does tangents and I do
tangents and we talk for like one and a
half hours
ah
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
okay it's okay she does them she said
that uh she didn't see the messages
because she has like a cover on her
phone and uh because you know like the
the like the like a book you know my
days ones so sometimes she doesn't see
the light unless she thinks about like
going to open it and look at it I guess
you just didn't look at her phone for 24
hours
[Laughter]
what is this kind of world she's very
much a tech person like me who uses all
kinds of technical things like phones
all the time and PC all the time so I
don't think it's a good excuse and I I
got really mad at her and I told her she
has to give me a number of one of her
neighbors and and yet she preferably
could please uh check her messages more
often even if she thinks she doesn't
have a message yeah
anyway it was a good relief because I
was like close to canceling the stream
and that's also because that's also why
it took me so long to put up this stream
because I was talking so long to my mom
after I woke up the first thing I
noticed was like oh and my mom's not
answering me what's up with that
yeah
thankfully always good yeah
[Laughter]
invisible with that cool
uh once the relevance of her being
invisible
nobody knows what she looks like so
they're really excited to find out what
doesn't exist what if there is no wizard
what if you guys are just making it up
how how do you know if she's invisible
I'm glad she's doing okay and I do two
hand attention together we have many
tangents together
hmm
wow it was um it was a big Panic moment
for me mom very relieved I you're
playing a game yeah
I've had this happen in the reverse a
lot to me what people trying to contact
you because they thought something
happened to you
God damn it that's a big plot plot twist
yeah I mean that's pretty obvious
basically after playing the first game
where you know the mystery was just such
a small thing no ghost
they thought there was a ghost but there
was no ghost surprise it's probably
about an invisible wizard to his word
there's no wizard at all okay finally
let's not think about it too much
wait my my throat really hurts right now
I'm stumping in there I'm trying to
cough it out
let's just get another
fruit candy they want it to be
uninvincible
divisible uh
just like me this is how I try to come
up with English words
Maybe
anyone do you have everything you need
not my shoes might jump on my pants I
think I'm missing something you know
[Music]
okay okay let's go I love potato
um
[Music]
still wearing the same clothes I guess
because it's so same day
wow
is is the the further practiced game
also gonna be on the same day I wonder
well
open
little froggy wow Adventures exactly
holy Larry
is that you
know
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
it
it was so true
you see that did you see them
[Music]
I like the humor
and then
yeah yeah he was running he was running
and running
famous
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm not famous at all ah very absolute
but I'm sure you will be soon oh I hope
so Kettle what brings you to my office
detective
I was just leaving my office actually
I've worked next door right there
what they're connected
oh but he doesn't even have a proper
door it's just like open like that what
makes you think I was at your office I
was in my mouth as you idiot
Oh I thought that that was just the
cupboard
look how many photos and like oh words
he has I'm like here he's bathing in the
pool myself you know I'm jealous girl
no that's my office girl
I have been putting all my cleaning
supplies
honestly it does seem like uh yeah like
um broom closet
just room
as I've noticed I'm really working every
time you do it
I even say this is my office and then
you say sure it is a little cream
cleaning frog and all and then I say I'm
a crime solving frog not a cleaning frog
but usually you've gone already
excuse Mike though it's addictive I
wasn't trying to offend I'm a very busy
boy head full of mysteries sometimes I
forget to be polite now if I was bullied
all the time I would never have time to
stuff my crabs I understand maybe that's
why I'm not as challenging as you
Lobster cult
oh perhaps but detective you must keep
trying never give up I can give you some
tips if you'd like oh yes please
tip number one pay attention I
yes sir
you should make sure you are looking at
things and paying attention to words yes
yes
[Music]
I need your advice I was doing totally
fine in the previous game
tip number two everyone is a suspect
indeed I agree with this one as well I
already knew that even you yes yes I am
says
I'll suspect myself much more from now
on
good call a tip number three carrier
notebook
ah no
I'm not even books and they are without
exception Factory
yes yes
books
detective don't be foolish a book you
write yourself cannot be factually
inaccurate if you avoiding facts
I suppose you're right kettle
I don't have a notebook though well
it's your lucky day I have a spare
Notebook on my desk you can decorating
and use it all you like oh really yep
there are stickers you can use too I
bought them with all my time solving
money
I'll let you get to it detective head
into my office when you're ready to
decorate okay thank you lobster.com
mmm
wow
the picture
this is so cute
whoa oh
my nose is a one
that's a robot like from Star Wars over
there it's four legs oh a rabbit has
four legs
where's this banana banana Rachel
this is magical banana ritual are you a
witch
huh
goes
marshmallows and why is there is that
what is that a goat
stuck on the tree
[Music]
oh
he has frog friends and they're eating
sushi
interesting
mmm who aren't they I don't know these
people oh they're wearing a hat though
I guess a frog can wear a hat in between
the eyes
spoopy
[Music]
well I guess if it's perfectly
all right I'll take this stick
how much sticker should I pick and where
should they go and let's see oh
[Music]
well I like worms let's put it down here
like it's like you know like that and
like can you know like a line oh can we
no birds no birds allowed I like green
apples because they're green
I like these green boys
and we'll give him we'll give him a hat
yeah he's like an investigator alligator
I'm doing in the heart
and then we oh I can have endless all of
them oh oh wait let's let's make fun of
this bird and put them into some funny
shoes yes
egg oh my God is an egg
I went of course we need where where did
the frog got hit rock
[Music]
nothing else
everything else is oh wait no some ah
they're not endless but you know some of
them are like
several ones I see I see I see oh well I
like more green things than we put a
plant here and then you know
investigator so
how do I turn huh
[Music]
I don't know
it's okay let's just put it like this
and then we put some eyes into the
magnifying glass oh
cute
and oh and make a face out of it
grab Corner oh
no
the eye
oh
ah I'm trying to turn it
I can't turn it oh no okay
I may be too much
yeah I'm already wasting so much time
here
we couldn't even make it into the
glasses if we like turn it like towards
the middle towards looking each other
and then yeah
know what I'm saying
I like this green thing that's a good
green thing this is also the thing
inside this green I guess so let's put
it there and
um bananas are fine they're almost green
meal
I like stickers
stickers are the best thing Sunny so
help that we get a sunny day when we
investigate
um
and of course I'm always winning
so this is my trophy for killing Kiana
[Music]
what is this
for Nani
[Music]
more Apple
one more Apple here
a beetle that is not a beetle oh that is
like an ear ear plug thingy
um okay well I'm happy with this
yeah yeah
[Music]
cute yes good book who's a good book
you're a good book wow
hmm yeah I guess it was a little bit too
much space but they should have given me
more green stickers get all open you now
notebook with the tab no
the book
no this okay flip A and D
oh so this time if we find out some
information about the crimes I guess
that will like put it in here
oh okay
okay Close book tab
good let's go okay should I still talk
to you one more time just in case
[Music]
you're coming along it's right there on
your desk you know I know I'm just
taking my time no I'm done okay
so that just mean I can go now
I thought you would maybe give me some
more lower all right then bye-bye
there's even pictures of us right here
and he he still wouldn't realize that
I'm more than just a cleaning frog
this tongue is not for cleaning your
floors buddy
I'm better than that
I won't lick your floors clean
yeah
I know frogs are famous for their
tongues but that's not part of what we
do
all right the magical card
super hot presents
the game by one Club
with assistance from film Victoria
[Music]
it's me looks just like me no more card
from here on all right
[Music]
let's go let's go
Wars like Woods why spooky
so the premiums game had something to do
with ghosts and this one's also spooky
it's actually kind of fitting for oh
all around fitting for close to oh hello
oh
close to oh Halloween
[Music]
many cutie patookies here
let's go
[Music]
I see grace Brooks there she was one of
the Developers
Susan I hope she won't be much of a
Susan
yeah yeah that's you Ralph that's
exactly you oh
oh cute place
hello is everything happening within
this area
first of all I would like to get to know
you maybe you can teach me more about
cats because smoothie and jungle is so
far
are not really enjoying my presents to
be honest they keep on punching me they
try to bite me and lick me and then when
after they try to lick me they just
throw me around and they act as if I'm
disgusting while they are the ones who
are losing all the fur and making the
poop in the robot and all that so
honestly I don't understand their
freaking problem but I'm scared that
they'll eat me while I'm sleeping so
please tell me more
those words because you're an impressive
kettle
my stars
ew it's me
the famous Lobster cup no
no no do I move anything like a lobster
to you oh look at that hello wizard
I only thought you'd be a lobster
I'm not I'm a Frog at all
you know why is your name Lobster Club
then I have to tell you something huh
I am not Lobster cob
why not
yo something's really wrong with my
throat
something's down there
some flying
now getting down into my belly
I don't know how to answer that oh cute
look at them dancing
look at that thing
you dancing
who are you I'm a detective
um fraud Detective
I see what Lobster cup not available
unfortunately not cannot
well I still do just fine yes Jonathan
Jonathan is running it out yeah you
remember
thanks
I'm Susan hi hi this is
I'm suffocating
I'm the one that contacted the agency
which I think you'll find excludes me
from being a suspect
[Music]
they're starting to croak
no it's not like it hurts you know after
using my throat my voice for a long time
it's not like that it's just something
like something there like I
it's not the voices no
no
stand back she's frogging
I didn't know that was how it worked
you should know these things Detective
I'm sorry it's okay
it's the cat hairs guys probably
I think you should still question me
though
remove balls out
[Music]
I'm drinking I'm using the cough drop
I'm always jumping there
oh I feel like I just spilled a a
grounded
maybe 10
out
okay question me oh you like uh about
the wizard
do you know the wizard personally
nobody knows her personally
no I still feel it
well not here at least not me
maybe if I eat something
it will push it down
but now I have the throat candy in the
mouth so after that's gone
right
and a lot to do with the organization of
the parade
you mentioned that it's worth bringing
up again
so you are fine with her moving to the
town
absolutely
that old house has been empty for years
and it's really nice someone wants to
live there and there's a lot of fixing
up but it'll look nice soon I think
you know with her being here
and this being like you know the way it
looks like
it reminds me of that movie
[Music]
that
that Ghibli movie
where there's like um you know the girl
that goes into the Cat Country and she
goes through a house
and and and and it's like you know when
she reaches that place at the with the
house yeah the cat returns it's like I
think a lot of small houses like this
and it kind of like it doesn't look like
and it doesn't look like it's a normal
human world anywhere
um the car returns no the cat returns
um
yeah welcome
for the wizard but I got knocked down
last night I'm feeling pretty sad about
it if I'm honest are these all these
people are they all crazy like how are
they imagining this
I know you're here to solve the mystery
but I just need to tell someone how I
feel
you haven't talked to me about it
thank you
is this balloon on a stick and like
floating up and down because here it
leaves the Earth and goes back inside
maybe I should investigate that
another professional sign maker yet but
I worked really hard on this sign really
I started to understand why someone
would knock it down it feels so
heartless and now I'm not sure how to
who to trust I thought everyone here
would be thrilled to have a new neighbor
it's a tricky situation kiddo
some people are protected about the
communities and think new people are
going to change things for the worst
kiddo that's almost never the case new
people make places better because they
bring New Perspectives especially in
small communities get up hopefully it's
just a misunderstanding or a mistake at
all I like to believe people are good
that being said I'm treating everyone as
a suspect even less
but not me right Avenue special you okay
essentially me oh no I'm sorry not sure
why I said that but you're not off the
hook just yet kiddo
hook
that's it
it's active could you please find me a
hook what I could I have to sign hang
the sign back up with it
I don't know if you need a hook for that
but okay
so Hulk is the first item little need
all right all right all right
gotta keep the suspers on the toes yeah
oh
suspect Susan motive maybe she didn't
like her sign destroyed the parade out
of embarrassment oh
something to fix your sign okay and
since she's not suspicious just makes
her much more suspicious don't she
realizes upset about the perfect being
destroyed worked really hard on her sign
I like these new notes I like that they
added that cheese
cheese
small pie is it a cookie or pie oh it's
a pie I'm not sure why this pie is here
but it seems out of place I'll hold on
to it for now kiddo perfect
oh I love the face I made in the front
last five okay okay hello oh what what
is that
oh
no tail
I feel like I've seen an animal like you
before
look at all
I don't I feel like able to have a tail
if it was a dog
[Music]
naughty
who are you the detective
I thought Lobster
oh
what did you say something about Lobster
Club
but I heard
with my mind
why are you speaking like that
this
you're saying everything out loud
oh anyway who are you
[Music]
okay
uh okay
was it you that asked for me to come
oh I'm gonna fast fellow Lobster cop
all right don't say it right in front of
me
or else
dead dog is dead
I really need to emphasize that I can
hear you
[Laughter]
stop listening okay my underwears like
this now
can I ask you some questions about the
case I guess so tell me what you want to
know
about the wizard
so how do you feel about the wizard
coming to life here
um
this it's like so not fetch
well I'm happy she's here but that house
has been empty for a dance and I didn't
know she was coming right nobody told me
you saying aren't you the mayor I think
so anyway
she kind of came at a weird time of
night and I well I thought she was a
ghost
like her makeup was so white it made her
look like a ghost she really needs to
use like a different powder it's so not
flattering to her skin type yeah
especially if you look at the difference
like me look at her face and it looks
like a ghost and then you look at her
hands and they're like a completely
different skin color like oh my God
finally maybe somebody can tell her
where which brand sells the right color
for her type you know
five different powder girl
oh my God
yeah it was a bit messy too like she
doesn't know how to apply it correctly
it was even on her eye on her eyebrows
down
I tried to vacuum all the powder off of
her face but it was just so cakey it
just didn't go up oh
with a vacuum yeah like I tried so hard
to fix her but she just would not be
fixed I put it on the highest setting
even
it's really went to town with the vacuum
I think I really freaked her out too but
honestly I was more freaked out by her
than she was by me and now she won't
come out of the house with a
ugh please don't put me in jail like how
how am I gonna visit my yoga Namaste
person if I'm in jail
you're not going to jail jail is in jail
[Music]
okay sorry Detective
I'm into the wizard you dumbo all right
yeah that's why I was helping with the
parade to apologize but she hasn't been
out of her house
also the parade is like ruins
like we should get someone like Taylor
Swift or so to perform for us
otherwise this is just so not batch
scene especially sound really bad but
trust me I wanted to play right to be
lovely
uh
at the May of the town I put them live
band to play a song but as you can see
the stage is grass and ruined now
the band is on the way up Nintendo
thanks Dad their first time is bad and I
want to be as a professional as possible
if I only had a rug or something to use
I could cover up the mess the town is in
disarray I don't have time to track one
down
oh no thank you for your concern if you
happen to find anything that would want
please let me know
well though do you have more questions
now I don't
think so
yeah I really haven't frung it went from
Frozen
but I'm good though I'm fine it's not
because of the voices these are fine
try to vacuum out the window maybe
there's some history there a rug
anything here
thanks she can I can read mines I can't
the mayor hired a cool band to plant the
parade attack the wizard
I'll get very sense this person
extremely sucks I'm telling you
oh another one
oh my God
it's a piezaster
there's so many pies it's a pie saster
it's a powered priority
it's a pizzaster
[Music]
anyway
oh I can look into your house can I go
into no but it's cool I can look inside
or stylish I like the color choices very
bold
are you bold too wearing that jumpsuit
jumper wow with a smiley face
doesn't look like you at all but I like
it I like it I like it
are they all ladies
yeah
um
hello
frog hello what's your name
um Mary that's me too you too did you
like my song yeah
I've been practicing all day and night
oh are you okay kiddo I'm tired
oh maybe you should get some sleep
cattle
baby
you sing very loudly
and why everyone sound proof their
houses
and I'm rude but okay that sounds
expensive yeah but that's not really my
problem I think I sound very good even
later now
palette
love to sing
[Music]
wow I understand I have to sing a 3am
too but I don't want to disturb my
neighbors so at least my apartment seems
pretty soundproof so I've had no
problems so far
that's when my energy is
that doesn't sound very healthy at all
my health is my business oh yeah that's
true I'm hurry oh no that was him that's
a baby I should listen to some soft
sounds before bed whisper whisper
welcome to my hair salon
that will be 100 money I don't have any
hair or any money
it's okay you can pay me back
just joking anyway who are you
the business office I have a magnifying
glass kettle oh cool can you question me
do you mind if I ask oh yeah sure
hi I love questions also I'm gonna stop
singing now because the viewers in your
stream are gonna get so fed up with it
about the wizard
foreign
oh sorry I didn't actually hear you
I was asking about the wizard oh okay
there's a reason she just moved in why
I'm a detective girl
you wanted me to question you and I want
to question you right this is part of
the questioning right
what
I'm having problems today
the frog is rocking
yeah it's like something
look I need to like get down we'll get
it out
it's okay it's a short game it will be
fun
eat it cool cool
um so I didn't do any crumbs or anything
and I have the right to remain silent
yeah but do you want to remain silent
literally like never especially not at
3am so like I heard that Ralph was super
weird about the new Wizard of moving in
also I heard that man it wasn't about
the night of the parade was destroyed
and I heard that nobody like nobody
attacked a wizard one time and that's
all actually
doesn't make a snitch made me a snitch I
think so
rats rats oh boy I love questions
okay I asked about last night can you
tell me more
what were you doing when the parade was
destroyed oh but yeah sucks that the
parade was destroyed
oh we're doing questioning what was I
doing not much just singing outside
you weren't sad when the parade was
destroyed yeah do you see anything at
all yeah what did you say
detective have you heard of extortion
[Music]
that's great news is it detective I
would like to distort you oh
I don't find that legal I see I see
that's what you wanted I'm above the law
and how are you Above the Law I would
like five money for a train ticket
well your best get some soon
what do you need a train ticket for I
want to go to froggy wood and become a
star you think you can become a star and
from you one the only person who can
become a star and froggy which is frogs
or I'm a bee
I sound exciting though
I mean you can try and people will laugh
at you probably
[Music]
um
but yeah go ahead we'll make some clips
out of you and get the money the clip
money
I know right sorry about the extortion
thing but I don't really have many other
ways to get there I think if you get the
money from me I can finally go live my
dreams
[Music]
what will you give me exchange
information
what kind of information a phone number
who am I calling
can't tell your dad all I can say is
that they were in the vicinity when the
parade was destroyed I don't think
you'll be able to solve the case without
this phone number hence the extortion
sorry well she was like a real
ah I didn't expect that in the beginning
do we
isn't wait it's extortion like blackmail
huh yeah anyway come back to me when you
have my money oh boy I love questions
okay money for hair
I'm gonna see if we can go get some
money somewhere
there's a better singing on her why
one of Rose needs five money
um
she's really loudly all the time
everyone soundproof their houses wants
to be a big star it's extorting me I've
never been extorted before what
Australian
excited
she's excited by being questioned I'm
excited by being extorted oh hello there
I'm just here to pick up the pie but
maybe I should talk to you while I'm
here
very last fight I saw someone around the
corner too actually
a really tiny you can like barely swim
anywhere with that
[Music]
huh
um
what happened
a little bit kind of but I'm not a case
I have to I have to be unslimy right now
you know ah cool I'll make the hole at
you
protective is that your real name
maybe
Coco are you here to question me and
stuff because like I'm not suspicious
how do you know you're not suspicious
I'll have a pile of Pies is that what
we're going for
well I think I didn't do it you think
yeah nobody knows anything for certain
these days
so why are you here swimming I'm
visiting my friend Noddy oh naughty
she's the only person I know with a hot
tub yeah I would visit dad friends a lot
of the time too if I had a friend of a
hot time yeah
plus I heard there we're gonna be
delicious buys for the parade so the
timing was perfect where do you live
normally
over near pumpkinville was this released
like a Halloween last year or so
seems like they would aim for that
release if they're going for this whole
I don't know low-key spooky theme
um
next one I was thinking of taking a
holiday there at some point yeah it's
fine yeah
um
so anyway can I ask you some questions
about the case
yeah whatever questions
about last night
where ah
ah yeah oh no it was December 2000
2010.
this is so old but oh then it's been
like three years
they released the new game next week and
it's been three years in between wow
I was quite lucky for Meek at all
and yet I play it one one week before
the release Carol
where were you when the parade was
destroyed
well I had been swimming all day at
noddy's hot tub so I was super wrinkly
yeah and it was hard for me to get
inside the house because of my wrinkly
Hooves your hoof's wrinkle
okay so I waited for about half an hour
for the wrinkles so do you wrinkle yeah
and then I went inside not his house and
snooze on the couch all night what time
was that all night now I mean what time
did you get back into nadi's house
before the parade was destroyed it
wasn't me probably wasn't me I mean
can't be sure why why I want you drunk
perhaps are you under the influence
under the influence of something
oh boy 90 probably do that it wasn't me
questions
okay let's ask this one too
is it not much about the invisible
wizard before you came here I don't
really I knew the parade was for her but
beyond that I don't know I'm not knowing
that they never threw a parade for me
coming to visit that's so true like I
would be really salty about that hey hey
why am I less welcome not that invisible
wizard to you guys man what's about
what's what what is that what
I should be welcome just like them get
all
I'm super cool have you been here before
so many times the first time that you've
been friends
okay case is closed
first time even though you gotta parade
you won't be getting a parade every time
Victor
[Music]
okay I take the parade thing back I just
pretend I didn't say that sure
detective I'm really avoid of this
conversation and I'm saying that's right
whatever your policy of being honest
with people
were you dishonest before Oh
yeah I guess I wouldn't tell people when
they were boring me I don't think that
counts as dishonesty and that's just
being polite so what am I supposed to do
when people are boring I'm not sure I
probably don't tell them
it would hurt their feelings
it didn't hurt your feelings though did
I well I said man I was a bit hurt at
all
I have a really exciting job at number
frog and I solve Mysteries I don't think
I'm boring at all
sure when I've seen heaps of frogs
before plus I've sold my fair share of
crimes which crimes this one oh
who's off the crap already yeah Ralph it
is Ralph
it was a rough last time
no
how do you know uh good point I haven't
decided weapon yet but it seems likely
that he did it
what was his motive it's what
um the reason for destroying them for
rain
um laughing because he has an eye patch
on
I don't think that's a real Moto
doesn't make any sense
who's the rude one now
this conversation isn't going anywhere
they write you apparently
that's a nice comeback
saying yeah this isn't going anywhere
well you weren't going anywhere but
apparently I wish it wouldn't be going
anywhere
not until I solve the mystery
sorry for being a road detective yeah
you better be I made it just get so
cramping when I'm hungry pies
foreign
to get my food please bring me some
I need to get my crap going
like Lazada and the three cheese pizzas
you could ask someone to get you
something to eat like who man
Mary have food in my pocket
I wonder how many pies you'll be asking
for
not what you'll give me an exchange
mommy what you what oh
one Mommy
I need five
okay here I guess you're just taking one
last pie then here's a pie for you
where'd you find this part not on the
floor
not on the Vlog at all
[Music]
sorry that you may have to speak up
these hot tub jets I'm running loud I
found this pie on the round over there
why am I being honest about this get uh
detective I do not want to eat ground
pie
oh made a mistake let's say maybe even
two
thanks
that's one mistake for giving me a dirty
pie another mistake for giving me a pie
that does not belong to you
that's right detective though I'm
visiting from out of town I know that
this is one of Mandy's pies they're
delicious if you just happen to find it
on the ground you cannot be yours to
give away
so I cannot accept it
then don't get the one money though
please I'll be watching you you should
return this pie to Mandy okay okay maybe
I'll find different food what about the
money
oh I got the money anyway
yay money money money makes Frog happy
and even could have been jealous of the
parade something to eat
mm-hmm
says it wrote individual yeah really
perhaps only worth because of the hunger
but maybe just read in general doesn't
leave here only visiting want to visit
pumpkin I want to visit pumpkinville one
thing I've noticed about this number two
game is that the dialogues are much
longer than before
but oh yeah
yeah I saw it I started hello hello
hello
I can't go back here
what about here
oh did you guys see that and someone was
there and then they were like whoosh
oh well fine
oh yeah yeah I'll take this by now I
have five pies I think
I think
four oh man but I feel like I saw one
more
I mean
who knows how many I need anyway
anything I can take here
now do you see me like
oh look it's the faces again
a developers probably or their children
I'll talk to you oh oh you have the last
pie at chips oh
the chin a human being
um
you're the detective right I'm Mandy
hi Mandy kennel be careful when you stop
detective there's mess everywhere
I'm useless
lucky you I'm not
my shoes are brand new I can't get them
dirty why don't you change shoes
um it's active
are you joking don't come to me here
with like perfect reasoning I can't
reason with reason
I can't wear flats with this look I mean
that was obvious anyway right you
understood that from the get-go right
you have taste right
papa papa
potions would be all around besides
these shoes are enchanted oh
I'm one of the few actual witches here
in Walla Goods most folks here are just
fans of the spooky which is fine and all
but it means a lot of the cleaning work
will be mine to do I never should have
learned the tidying up spell it
shouldn't take too long for me to clean
up this mess but first I need to find
all my pies
got all of them I think
same thing that happened everywhere
someone thought it would be funny to
knock them all over
well it was probably that thing that was
hiding behind the house no
maybe they're with oh baby the invisible
wizard this is so invisible after all
there's just really good at hiding and
they're actually Not Invisible and was
that thing that was called invisible
wizard
Maybe
all right um let me ask you some
questions
so about your pies I have them
you need help to find your buys yes
detective seriously I seriously need
help straight up I can't see anything
right now these glasses are so dark it's
unreal I'm such a dingless this town is
literally cloaked and Eternal Night why
did I think sunglasses would be a good
idea
they weren't a good idea however I don't
regret it they make me look amazing do
you think I look amazing you know valley
girl would have been a good voice for
her too
yes thanks I do too worst purchase I've
ever made in terms of practicality but
it brings this look to a new level
and maybe a dingus but I'm very stylish
thinkers
yeah I mean
I I I I like wearing sunglasses but I
I'm not one of those people who would
wear sunglasses inside of buildings or
sell
it seems a little bit over the top for
me even though if it helps hiding my
identity
is this famous frog he's very famous
cannot
my outfit look at it not before that
pies right you open to help me pick up
my pies I got them already
it would give me one money all right
here here take take
I think I got all of them at this point
ah
Mandy detective oh they're even stacking
up amazing actually now it looks like I
need three more
I found some of your pies now
only one left oh okay okay I I or I can
find one more we can find one more
Maddie needs pies what about oh about
this section
someone knocked their prize over what a
bummer School me about fashion fair
enough really spooky I like these notes
I have an eye open for pie
honey pie it's an idol song
[Music]
maybe the last pie
is um a reward from someone hi
you got some pie here
oh I can get into this place yeah
everyone's only one anyone home
sounds like somebody's inside but I
shouldn't intrude on them I'll come back
another time
okay
on the lamp
are there several lamps
there's so many lamps
uh
wow nice catch guys
it's the last pie let's take it
good job kiddo
okay yeah we got a bagel girl game
yo that was hard to see especially since
it's at the entrance I can see people
not looking there very closely
[Music]
tell me what you want to know
I got your bicycle
no can I please eat one of them please
actually yeah speaking of reading I mean
my throat seems to have calmed down a
little bit but I will just in case eat
one of these cookies that Kiana left
behind
they're wrapped in a green packaging so
they must be amazing oh
mm-hmm why
mm-hmm
[Music]
now we have two money or free
I think we have two now
but someone else promised us one more
um give me a pie wait now if you give me
a pie that actually belongs to me now
officially maybe now the other one
accepts it as a food offering at all hmm
okay okay thank you for finding my pies
yeah the pie firms the pie firms are in
oh two money and Friends
me picking it up from the ground and
giving it to you doesn't make it
necessarily fresh cut off but okay I'll
take it
hi
[Music]
I mean maybe maybe she gave me the one
that was already on the table
not one of the ones that were around
yeah that will explain it get off
let me take this pie girl
my job
I mean yeah I might be out there because
it's from the last game
um
yes retro yeah vintage baby
it's only a French one it is
trust me bro oh
a French one
you're not rude anymore
wait do I get enough of money now
you already gave me one before
oh beautiful eyes thank you oh
[Music]
um
foreign
this person because
they gave me a money before I gave them
a pie
and I gave them a dirty pie 100 pounds
they gave it back to me
now I brought them a new pie which is
probably the same pie
and then give me another money
feel like I'm scamming them
[Music]
no no no no no your head is not in the
wind shape don't keep on telling
yourself that we saw other frogs with
Hats before
believe in yourself Carol
hold on to it anyway it might come in
handy
no a party hat party huh
I have yet to hear about someone who
needs a party hat
no more French pie
oh
now it tells me that wow okay I think
they made improvements in the game not
that there were any improvements
necessary to be honest from my point of
view oh was this lamp always on the
ground holy I have yet to talk to
you I think you're the pirate a whole
hello
oh why are you yelling I'm just making
sure you can hear me over that just loud
singing over there
I can hear you
don't have to yell again
you're very small it might be difficult
for you to hear I'm small but I'm also
super close to you like I can totally
easily hear you even if I'm 10 meters
away right now
it wasn't the same as being far away
that's like people yelling really loudly
at old people even when they're still
like hearing perfectly fine
and then and then they also speak really
really slowly like
oh I was like sometimes you know when
when you talk to someone
or someone talks to someone who may be a
foreigner and don't doesn't understand
the language you're speaking so you
repeat the exact same thing like I don't
do this but I see other people do it you
repeat the same word just really slowly
stretch it out and expect them to
understand it oh yeah and louder slower
and louder so for example you say where
is frogging street but where's frog in
the street and then they're like and
then you say where is Brian understand
I feel like this happens a lot with
certain certain countries
um tourists going to other countries
I do that a lot oh what don't don't do
it but I understand sometimes you just
don't know how else
explain try try I don't know reusing
your phone and getting I don't know
write it down or or
get some translation
hold up
morning voices like that
like this
yeah Lord I don't want to have her
around in the morning
no people don't know how to use fun it's
not only old people though after that
get off
anyway I use more hand gestures hand
gestures definitely Healthcare not
actually when I lived in Japan a lot of
Japanese people said it's funny how I
use my hands so much when I talk and
well now I maybe don't do it most of the
time because I have my my hand on the
mouse and and all that
um but yeah Japanese people for example
don't use their hands so much to gesture
[Music]
um Europeans very much do that and
probably Americans and so on too
but yeah in Japan
I've been told many times ah funny how
you use your hand so much
[Music]
I guess it makes us look more more
exciting and more energetic you know
yeah
you use your hands too yeah yeah it's
just in your blood isn't it
are you sure okay now he's talking
normally you could hear me at this
volume yeah weird
[Music]
I'm here to solve the mystery Kettle
really yeah but you're so small I'm of
average frog high xq it's amazing
rude a lot of people are really rude in
this Village in the previous game they
were much nicer to me you know
I'm nice um okay I may be small but this
is an average frog height we're not
talking about me now
ah
I sound like Bae right now when
can I ask you some questions about the
case questioning me uh this does this
sound like a mess
about your eye yeah what happened I can
give you a sticker for your eye maybe
when you ask where you have the eye
patch on there's rubs business
oh that sounded oh that maybe sounded
like pills I can see it
be really good for me to know why you
have an iron Baskets at all
uh excuse me oh oh that sounds very
different
sometimes the boy just wants to wear an
eye patch that should make me suspicious
you put it on for fashion who could do
what no they're like uh uh super filet
buddhausta
I can't oh I can't reveal my eye because
there's the power that will be unleashes
unmeasurable and everybody around me who
meets my eye will die
I can't hold it back I have to put an
eye patch on
me
is
what was this what dark flame muscle
what that was that what uh that dude
was calling himself dark flame master
might have a drunk at all
oh yes not that dude the girls why am I
think it was the the boy
it's her hmm
but wait wasn't that the dude also Juni
they were both shooting
I haven't watched that anime in a long
time I'm mixing up all kinds of things
oh it was a dude oh yeah yeah but the
girl was chunibio too they're both
genevial oh
yeah yeah yeah
I love the was it the opening or the
ending
I love actually both I think I remember
liking both really really really
um
I watched the movie last night about
Pirates oh it actually was just a stream
of host your body from
um
she's like really really bootylicious
and sexy I love watching her she oh she
was doing such an amazing Allison
karaoke the other day it was marvelous
and oh that that time when she turned
around
to look at the sun it made me hope that
I would one day look at the sun together
her with her yes
because I've never heard of a movie
having a sequel to work at all what are
we talking about I don't read usually
see because I reserved for the video
games
well that's not true at all what what
yes yeah it's really normal to have a
video game sequel especially for games
with large audiences like the told
investigation series well what is that
yeah anyway I was watching a pirate
movie last night that's where I was and
for that reason I have decided to wear
an eye patch oh I'll leave it at that
question about the wizard how do you
feel about the wizard moving in cattle
it's nothing against the wizard but I've
been living with my friend Carlos for
one now and our space is big but I would
really like my own home
huh I've been eyeing her after the loud
house wages but maybe I'd move in one
day more than wizard got there first I
see
it's my fault I guess I shouldn't hold
it against the wizard
foreign
look for it again but look guys have you
noticed that's the thing I saw
but requirements
[Music]
he's there he's there
sneaky
this house is twice as big as all the
other houses maybe you could renovate it
and turn it into two houses you could
split it down in the middle kennel or
have one house upstairs and one house
downstairs kiddo look at apartment
that's pretty cool idea I like colors
and everything but I'm a private boy I
understand I don't have any renovation
supplies though hmm I'll see if I can
try some down for you but I already
maybe have something
what would you need to renovate
questioning me double what did you need
okay well Mama I guess it's like kind of
like an open thing like they don't say
it exactly but I will know when I find
it Kenna surely
the party hat is not for him
something like a hammer or so maybe
no loves Pirates eye patches cosmetic
only a private boy wants to rent a thing
sounds as well I'm not kiddo oh I think
the frog is gone by the way my throat
feels normal again
I think I was actually able to like get
rid of it but
eating something
[Music]
oh all right let's talk to the zebra we
haven't done to the zebra
can I like get some of these items from
you
what's your name
uh
God I'm out of voices
I can't pick up anything
[Music]
um
ah
Spanish I don't know
ah let's do British
um
uh
I forgot everything I say right now
leads to like a like a exit like this
across the board oh there we go woke up
to call us all for your good night shop
oh that's cool
goofy are you countless you know it's
just like the name of the shop that's me
oh how cool it got the short post my
name on it it's so cool I'm gonna go
shopping in your shop can I
my company also has my name in it what's
your company called that is crime
solving agency
what's your name a crime
or crack you know now it's that it's a
detective frog
that's not really your name don't move
for title yeah I suppose you're right
my shop actually has my diaper oh cool
I'm jealous
thanks
here in walk which we're all our own
biggest fans being Corsair is a social
structure and I'm changing I'm changing
social construct we have rejected eight
that's why my shots
while my shop is so popular
I shall portray them all other things
wow that's great my office neighbor
Lobster cop has a picture of himself
right above his desk at all what you
know Lobster cop yeah they're my rival
holy heck I'll be your friend forever
whenever
me
please I'm I'm I I will solve your
crimes here and then you'll be a fan of
me right
you know he show off the mystery of the
haunted house at haunted island recently
that was me is he claiming the credit
for that
I don't think oh it was actually mean as
often
what really it was all over TV to dance
competition had a lot of showing it
is Larry 's Larry
yeah also you must have seen me in there
too
no you must be thinking of Laramie
you'll be small Larry no this was a
regular sized Lobster
no
[Music]
you misunderstand Larry is a regular
sized Lobster
no Delirious I know oh well agree to
disagree
we shouldn't be with facts
I really did solve that mystery it was
me as a detective
that's really cool
[Music]
thanks
so you like the secret base detective I
suppose I'm the fans do you mind if I
ask you some questions because I'm not
feeling comfortable in this conversation
right now y'all are really rude
without even trying I guess
what would you like to do the nine in
question
where were you last night because here
by shop what about when you closed up
[Music]
it's 24 hours what if someone needs a
portrait of themselves at 4am
you're open all the time sure I'm of
course I sleep and eat a look after
myself my customers simply wake up if
they need to buy anything
where do you sleep
standing up
training wow
wow that's so impressive the most could
be the shopkeeper in all world of woods
that's not very I mean I guess you know
if you sleep standing you can never have
troubles with like a mattress and get
back problems
it's like a life hack
[Music]
do I ever take breaks but I really like
it here in my shop
a real emotion at home
extreme sharp keep a lifestyle issue for
everyone but I take so much joy from my
walk
although I must request that you look
after yourself and close the shop if you
need a break get up
okay probably anyway did you see
anything last night nothing particularly
interesting why
oh the crime
I think I need to question you a bit
more go for it would you like to know
um
oh why does Robbie the separate House of
Cards is always at the shop that is like
really good logic there
good your question has good logic
also are you guys seeing that person
anyway no I don't see them they must be
behind this house
I was just wondering maybe they always
switch sides when depending on which way
my conversation
uh leads me you know what do you know
about the new Wizard The Invisible way
to move the literally next door we're
really stupid
we are here all the time the place has
been helped you for ages I gotta say hi
well the parade was meant to be for
saying hi
parade
you're just messing with me kiddo the
brain and everyone has been prepping for
and then happened right in front of your
freaking face and all how nice can we it
was a straight last night it happened
already
conversation is a roller coaster of
information wow I'm like overwhelmed
with emotions right now I've literally
no idea what's happening
and weren't involved in man I don't know
I'm so I'm confused you're making me
confused
you are involved in the decoration nope
should I offer jump though
we who is the perfect fight again you
for me
no let's try an invisible ways that she
just moved it next door oh oh this is
what a freaking idiot this zebra is such
an idiot
[Music]
wouldn't want to live with this zebra
pointy heads ah you want a party hat hey
we're trying to be through a parade
everyone is a party hats to wear mine
was ruined at last parade I've been too
busy working in my shop to buy you one
oh no
okay I'll give you the party hat
where should I go I'll give you
okay
how about one money
yeah yeah yeah yeah
put it on
you always see the most epic figure I've
heard all day thanks to YouTube and not
a problem
and you solved it was like a True
Detective yeah you're welcome you made a
video out of me
NFL you know the big crime that I solved
I just resolved the problem with the
party hat
all right one money please
my money yeah well now we have how much
money okay
[Music]
well I always try to walk it back no
show around
I forgot who needs around someone needs
a round though uh was it was it the
singing Lady
[Music]
all these conversations hurt my brain
the vacuuming lady
oh I heard her okay okay
thank you sir kindly you're funny man
party had gone free money rag okay
probably we'll get one more money for
the rug
and then we need like a we maybe yeah we
need like a cleaning uh a building
supply and then we give it to him and we
get another money and then we have five
money and we give it to the singer
and now it's probably close to the end
didn't know anything had to happen
seemed stressed out about the permit it
was never oh no I don't know not
anywhere I could probably borrow on this
one am I no no I always had a hat to
begin with at the beginning of the
conversation already I was still
wondering can't think of anything here
huh
oh that's cute
that's cute Kettle also going on the
toothpaste is probably like um
[Music]
a hint to the previous game the brown
probably till then and honestly radio
too
maybe this one too I forgot about that
one though
[Music]
hey hey you think I don't see you over
there I saw you
it's freaking me out man
I'll try on a dance competition ah
all right here's the wrong
great news what is it I found your
rocket arm what holy graca Molly like
OMG I have to tweet that out right now
hashtag fabulous thanks for tracking it
down this should do the trick wow it
looks like something new hopefully the
bad one noticed the mask at all I don't
think they will they're in a fish tank
anyway fish tank
what what one gas they're fish bingo
wait do you mean to tell me you got the
most famous band of all time the market
Buddies
yeah of course like even if I couldn't
get Taylor Swift the least thing I could
do was get that space
oh I saw them live once and I was blown
away again I can't wait I'm excited too
I can't wait for the parade to begin I
better go by the way so I can solve the
mystery before the parade starts
[Music]
okay okay so we don't get money from you
but we got the building supplies
[Music]
all right all right all right all right
all right plus one money time no no no
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
we're simply in favor again don't be
selling you might have to get me this
rock and besides like my daddy gives me
monies per month so I have like plenty
of this without even doing anything I'm
trying to be like a little bit of an
event organizer here but I'm still not
getting paid for this but even even once
I get paid for this like that is
probably gonna continue supporting me
because she just loves his girl you know
his daddy like I'm just the best
[Music]
yeah you know it you know it
and says take it wow thank you
[Music]
no
okay long snoot yeah very long is known
the game
okay if it's Yen then one money is
really nothing yeah one yes
nothing I mean one something is barely
anything in any money uh yeah anyway
when
do I have five already sorry I don't
know where I went to you
I wanted to go to over there
wait wait
oh he's not here I thought I could catch
him with my magnifying glass oh man
question me yeah I'm questioning you
here there you go I forgot I wanted your
voice so you'll just take this one we'll
just be done with
I managed to track down some Building
Supplies
no exciting news here I love to use them
if you can yeah yeah take him take him
take him
he's like doing it right away wow
you're so motivated
you have to pay me yes
yes that's the fifth money
[Music]
thank you
oh and now you know what guys I'm just
gonna run off without five money and I'm
never coming back like the
Mysteries
we're gonna hook to where somebody
wanted a hook yeah yeah the the sign
lady
I'm not your dad not yet what
sorry I don't really know why I said
that all good enjoy the hook thank you
of course the pirate person has a hook
he may have told me that it was leftover
from the oh wait no it's actually like a
pirate hook
oh oh okay let's bring the hook back
first
everything you go nice looking cat lady
I sent me only like
give hook
I'm back you know you're back yes I
found your hook oh my
nice nice thank you I can fix my son
right away
oh
welcome
yay it looks like somebody painted it
with a mouse on paint
I want to repent you for this hook
that's okay I got it for free nothing as
friends won't last through because I
worked for it I worked and I was looking
at the hook
I talked to a lot of people so I think
I'll deserve something
but I already have five money now I
think so I don't think I need your money
but okay
just feel free to use my house whenever
you need
oh
[Music]
that's a cute little place
oh let me see let me see you have a
phone too
I can call someone
oh
you want Susan come now yeah
wow okay
oh I think she's taken
unless it's her brother Russell I don't
know
wow chilling nice selfie at the sunset a
phone cute why does he have so many
pictures of herself that's weird
cute bed though
see it that reminds me it wasn't in Sims
one or or in like a console Sims game
or am I imaginist imagining this but
there was like
only one specific game one specific bed
which was heart-shaped and all that yeah
yeah that was The Sims 2.
no but I think I mean it might have had
a yeah a heart-shaped bed too but I'm
talking about a bed which is the only
bed where you can make a woohoo and all
the other beds I don't think you could
do it it was a special event
I think that we're talking about but
about busting out yeah
I think we're talking about busting out
specifically
I mean yeah okay probably all of The
Sims games have a heart-shaped bed
but this one was special
okay let's try the call I guess or maybe
I don't need it now
what should I call
it
what is that the only option I don't
have any friends to come what
oh man
okay uh wait oh yeah money money time
baby I got all the cash money
maybe you should open your doors to my
to my frogness as well after I give you
the money
because I don't know I feel like I
deserve it and your house is now mine
how's the egg starting going I think
I've got you five money wow for real I
don't think the extortion would work so
quickly that's excellent news
I'm really good I'm getting started
thumb up I can't do thumbs up I'm sorry
anyway do you have the information for
me totally last night I saw the postman
jump of a parcel it was around the time
the parade got destroyed I couldn't see
who was giving it but it was someone
here in town Barney is the postman's
name he's a chill dude I don't think
wait she was gonna give me a phone
number wasn't she
and now I have access to phone I have
his number
may I have that number
that was worth five monies I think
thanks for giving me this money I'm
really excited to visit Frankie wood I'm
excited for you Kendall enjoy braggy
Moon
of course um
oh no money but phone number at all
oh are we done with all of them now
[Music]
all right all right all right let's call
who should I call I have no friends but
let's call this mysterious don't break
it off
how come he's made no friends over what
about all the friends he met on the on
the home of the island I would call
those his friends now Kettle oh
Barney hello are you guys
see perfect
pick up
hi it's Barney I have you in speaker
I'm Barney you know hi what am I talking
to
um Lobster cup
oh really no I was freaking you kind of
rats what is this noodle
I'm detective I'm calling about an
incident that happened last wait no no
well no no the sheep in the haunted
island
a cute connects and all the Sheep know
each other yeah with a tiny sheep world
calling about an incident that happened
last night at one like word schedule I
didn't do it do what whatever you're
calling about wasn't me
are you sure Carol
what did I do last night someone
destroyed the parade which was being set
up for the new Resident of the town the
invisible wizard I was told you were in
the area when it happened Carol oh yeah
I was there
didn't destroy anything if that's what
you're asking was just delivering a
parcel
cool while you're delivering it to the
closed house perhaps oh um what was
their name oh Lola
I don't think there's anyone in town
called Lola must have been someone who
lives there the address was on the
parcel
the nurse said she hoped she wasn't
wearing wolf of bunny yeah yeah Ryan
good remembering I'm going to play I'm a
crossing my screen by any chance uh I
streamed it
um several times before if you go on my
channel and you go to videos and then
you click on the search search thingy
then you can look up animal crossing a
couple times I mean Kiara did it but you
know
uh don't you remember where the parcel
was sent from
oh yeah I deliver a lot of parcels from
them it was from wizbay.net headquarters
that sounds really familiar well I heard
that name before
[Music]
um
oh I know Manny buys a lot of stuff from
there
well this wasn't for her do you know
what was in the package some sort of
shoe
let's see
you're gonna look at them it's pretty
damn I got no regulation about really
seeing anyone not even a face
is pretty dark but I haven't had so much
trouble seeing anyone before my neighbor
was much darker than normal more much
more dark than normal all I remember is
a blue dress of stars on the end
I'm pretty stumped in this case Barney
do you know if there were any clues left
behind a signature on the delivery slip
or something kiddo and then get them
designing
sorry you kind of like um giving me the
whole cut off by saying Carol many times
but I remember something dropping over
at the entrance rewards I tried to call
out and tell them but they stumbled up
before I noticed
at the entrance of the woods you say
check it out
uh-huh it has the cattle virus
so we met Barney who was mentioned in
the previous game excellent crashes went
into decorations drove away without
realizing oh I mean I could totally seen
that but I guess it wasn't that didn't
see who he was delivering to alola the
responsible driver had me on speaker
okay
okay let's go something's here glasses
and
no one there
there oh
ah maybe he didn't see anything because
he didn't have his glasses
what
is
oh they have a name engraved on the arm
no no the invisible wizard
maybe Barney isn't but I don't know I
don't know
it's my only cool left I think I should
try and return this to the wizard kennel
in the old house new culture yeah okay
all right
I mean she'll surely open the door for
me when I tell her I have her glasses
right
[Music]
oh
can
you wait there they're invisible though
never mind like I was like saying there
will be nothing at all but no look they
have no body they have clothes and eyes
but like no actual body
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right all right let me in now please
anyone home I found these glasses oh
did I do it
bye
oh oh I can move oh it's like
am I gonna try to find them bye
because I'm gonna get spooked broom
oh how difficult
pie
hello
I got you got you I got you
oh boss fight
suddenly like a transition to a big boss
fight
you know can you imagine I can imagine
at all
[Music]
how can it be fake there's a crab there
y'all crap ah so cute I have a nose
okay and where is it this time here
[Music]
I am ashamed
thank you
okay
please please please ring the shame Bell
[Music]
I deserve it
I don't know why man
that's scary this is a real scary victim
disappearing on me like that
foreign
boxes maybe they just want me to help
oh I see you I see you this time you're
real you must be real first time's a
charm no oh okay fourth time is the
charm kennel oh the door opened spooky
that's so spooky why I'm so much
pie they definitely enjoyed the party
huh
before it even really officially
happened
terrifying absolutely terrifying
dude if I oh God is this like a boss
fight they they have a problem with
frogs or so this might be dangerous
stand back I'm going to frog
just to make sure but it has my gun out
who's here
[Music]
I'm sorry I didn't mean to style me okay
now but you're actually starting with me
you're here to solve the mystery
yes
okay well I don't know where my glasses
are
so solve that as soon as possible please
thanks in advance
I already have them that's why you let
me in no
I found your glasses I think are these
yours
I can see you again oh they didn't have
their glass and they fell off when they
arrived they didn't have the glasses
they stumbled over everything that's why
everything was destroyed maybe could
that possibly be what's going on
it sounds like it makes a lot of sense
that was so quick
you should get a promotion I don't
remember calling a detective to solve
this mystery but I must have done
otherwise why would you be here right
[Music]
yeah well no I'm actually here to solve
a different mystery girl
which one I don't mean to ruin the
surprise but the town was setting up a
parade for you I'm sorry to tell you
that last night someone destroyed it
girl
I've been trying to figure out why
however I've noticed that your house is
lingered with the decorations
huh
[Music]
where were you last night
remember I have a gun
[Music]
I was on Wednesday
I got some new shoes
I picked express delivery
they're right last night
yes
back to my alibi
I went to pick up my shoes from the
delivery guy
and then I dropped my glasses
oh
and that's all I have to say about
that I don't remember anything will
happen after that I swear because if I
say I don't recall that makes me am
except for all all kinds of punishments
say you don't remember and everything
will be fine
are you sure
yeah I think someone else must have
destroyed the parade perhaps one of my
enemies
you have
memories
um no no needs open enemies yes
the guy
[Music]
we just moved in here how do you already
have enemies
me evil guy my memory
[Music]
evil guy
yeah
ah you're making this up hmm
no evil dude he's really my enemy dude
just like for real trust me bro
don't you mean evil God oh
foreign
[Music]
anyway he must have destroyed the parade
okay soft we did it
wow
too bad he's not able to be apprehended
but at least we can continue with our
lives
[Music]
you sound
like you're the evil guy actually Lola
or the evil girl are you being dishonest
oh
yes
I really sorry
it was me
it wasn't actually
nice okay okay I understand like when
you break something so big by accident I
I
am hard to
admit to it but you know you feel people
will be really mad at you so you don't
want to be the one being mad especially
if you just arrived here and you don't
want everyone to be so mean to you
he fears my gun yes he should be viewing
my gun hmm
anyway
where was I
you destroyed the parade didn't you
I didn't know the parade was for me
that's so nice
[Music]
when I dropped my glasses I couldn't
find my way home I was bumping into
everything
what happened when you got home I had
some chip stuck to me so I toast and I
just did
why did you tell anyone it won't happen
I'm so embarrassed about it
I was just moving I already made a big
mistake and we're shy lady detective I
made myself invisible so nobody can see
me
oh there's one there invisible
that must have been why nobody saw you
last night uh oh yeah that's why nobody
knows what it really was yeah yeah it's
about yeah I suppose
can you become Not Invisible uninvisible
or perhaps
visible
if you insist What's it gonna be what's
what animal I wonder
[Music]
what is that
just like that that's my dad
[Music]
oh chameleon oh that makes sense
actually
[Music]
like
yes
well why is it his eyes are positioned
so normally I I'm slightly disappointed
girl no you should be happy what
well it's just that I have a good joke
prepared I'll learn anyway okay so
imagine that instead of a frog you were
real to be a lizard oh Elizabeth
[Music]
so you've just been real okay pretend
okay it's me a lizard
wow so you're not an invisible wizard of
an after all
[Music]
it was a good show
[Laughter]
you're gonna tell everyone
I'm brand new and it was a mistake at
all mistake okay I'm worried that if
you'll tell everyone what I did they
will be upset I think they forgive you
right away you know but what if they
don't I want to make a good first
impression
when we go outside can you please tell
them that it was evil guy no there's no
fair to them either
on our life perhaps oh who who was it
harming really evil guy evil evil guys
is real this is a more of the lemon Lola
this is like my favorite episode of
paroid
it's your choice let's face the music
oh
and
I mean
you're a frog and I want to help you
because you're a frog but I will not go
so far and and dirty my honor as a
detective
while I know the real
case so salvation that I I you know put
the the fault on someone else no no no
no no that's not my style
no no
no no no
no no no no no no no no no
hello
hello hi
my name is Lola hi Lola
I'm a Frog just like me just like me
we're so glad you couldn't make it we're
so glad you could make
I'm sorry that there's been so much
commotion trying to get the parade ready
for you
everyone just realized that
we don't know that
sorry that somebody destroyed it Lola
the detective has been trying to figure
out who did it
well have you solved the mystery
hope it wasn't
me uh
would be surprised you could wish I knew
it first I wanted looking at you Ralph
what
happened do it Victor how many times do
we have to tell you
I I just don't press the guy rude
I'm not hurt anymore rabbi's food
I don't think that's how it works
I didn't do it
go ahead Detective
no no
you know why I chose that because for me
this Lola is the evil one because today
is trying to get me to put the blue one
to someone else
that's how my brain was like connecting
on them
[Music]
but maybe they will stand up for you
know
for the real
thing
it was you look good
[Music]
uh evil guys most Nemesis he's a very
evil guy
he's knocking last night this is right
everything because he hates a little
love
unfortunately because he's made of slime
he got away before I could apprehend him
I mean as long as we don't actually know
um like show them this person is evil
guy evil guy could be anyone and then
we're just blaming someone who doesn't
exist and that way everyone is happy and
like you know they don't really care
um to like they don't have to see who
the culprit was they just want to have a
party you know and welcome their new
neighbor and then the neighbor will be
embarrassed about
um you know everyone knowing that it was
them so everyone's happy but what about
what about evil guy
uh however Lola has since cast a very
special spell I will make sure he never
returns
wow
it's okay at least there was nobody here
right all right you might think so oh
ah
I'm sorry I couldn't catch him okay but
now we know that Lola is saved oh wait
would this continue as like if I said it
was a evil guy
no if I said it was Loma
hmm no wait a second my brain my brain I
wonder if the game will make me find
evil guy in any case level wait sorry
now he caught such a big mess I'm really
really irresponsible if you ask me kiddo
I'm sure he feels really bad about it I
wouldn't want you to forgive him
isn't he evil
yeah I thought he was evil Barney what
are you doing here you should be working
hi Barney
[Laughter]
yeah he's evil evil guy
oh oh please say it please say it okay
yourself
[Music]
ah parade started
we didn't have time to fix up the
decoration sorry Lola
I'm happy to be here
oh this is not the ending that I
wanted
foreign
[Music]
yeah what if the ending is different I
feel like sit now
I'm feeling like the villain
but it seems like I mean
acceptable
oh wow
at all
I am leaving
[Music]
uh probably types of crimes building
agency who literally just solved The
Crying by blaming someone else
unbelievable I can't believe that this
is a possible ending isn't the fried
detective supposed to solve the crime
correctly
this cannot be forgiven please fire me
hmm
Detective
supervisor kennel I am not nervous or
anything at all as my supervisor I am
the work at home
great job is so an invisible wizard
mystery that was quite a head scratcher
sure was yeah yeah I'm still scratching
my head even now
I was shocked that the corporate was
some cool evil guy
[Music]
yeah
the evil thing
why would anyone else
well yes I mean
[Laughter]
[Music]
should I tell my friends
will name my daddy show up right away
yeah
that's because it's not his real name
but it was definitely evil guy
and it was one-off Prime yeah yeah
then how did they become the evil guy to
begin with
um
yes
got the best confess to your crimes I am
now the crime story
supervisor evil guys in the real kid oh
I'm sorry to say so with a light on the
report girl what who's finding the
details that we're done with the real
copper was a wizard kid oh I just really
I miss mixed up some things it wasn't
even on purpose get home
[Music]
evil guy I wasn't going to go for him
but I still did it by accident my mouth
slipped I swear to God you know oh I
didn't know she said she's because I'm
not sure I made the right decision at
all look at all even if it's hard we
should always tell the truth
I I was gonna do that
[Laughter]
I landed my badge of my gum
what about ugando
well yeah okay what this is a bad end
it's a bad ending
you don't have a badge or grandma would
you even chew gum you don't have teeth
what a roast oh my God
so I can keep my position here kettle
well yourself a boy so yeah
but you should remember to tell the
truth whenever it's safe and possible
a promise Carol
I'm disappointed that there's no such
thing as evil guy I'd love to solve a
real crime one day girl the real crime
was what just happened that's the crime
[Laughter]
I'm traumatized
that might come through a quicker than
you think well you just got a call about
a dude you have a case detective is the
one that comes out three years later in
one week
or is it the crime that just happened
that's the most challenging case I've
ever sent you one confident in your
abilities but you might be back up on
this one oh
do we get a companion next to him
last
awesome not I
don't want no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
oh
yeah
also thought Harris such advanced cases
were nice to slow him down get off
nonsense detective if you're showing a
very capable mystery solver I think
you're in the running to be the new
number one
making me blast Kettle it'll be okay
so where am I headed next to prison
because you just it up completely
why did you make my game and like this
after all I've done for you
I'm I'm calling the police now right now
they're gonna put handcuffs on your
hands so please don't resist
Ive
they think you can handle the prison I
can handle anything and honestly I
deserve a kennel
I deserve prison
oh man
after the detective has left
yeah
adding the picture
oh
complicated feelings man
I thought the evil guy was gonna show up
right there my boy was spanning over
there and then suddenly
[Music]
[Laughter]
middle
oh my notification oh
he's gonna follow me it's gonna follow
me gotta beat me up
I have a gun
have a gun
please quickly
[Music]
close the door
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
okay you know what that was definitely
the wrong ending but it was an
interesting ending that you would
probably not have seen a lot of other
games uh play first of this game I'm I'm
happy that I'm not even gonna replay it
that was kind of funny
[Laughter]
[Music]
I thought it was funny
very spooky Kettle
so next one is releasing next week but
it doesn't mean we're gonna play it um
next week I'm gonna space it out and
then play sometime as I said when I feel
like playing
um how do you get the proper Ending by
choosing the actual reality
it's that easy
and then you don't you're not gonna be
followed by
yeah paranoia and worry is all the time
like me and we got the other ending yeah
she's
I guess what we learned from this is
that she's an honorable detective and
I'm just uh
crawl from
you see what I'm doing
frog fro
[Laughter]
yeah yeah it's okay I I I wasn't born
into this job
oh wait see I I could continue but no
I'm gonna leave it there because I want
to eat food and I like it I like ending
it there
if you want to see the other ending go
to Amy's archive she played like a long
time ago I think
ume there detective oh
ah
maybe they really will die was the
froggiana that we met along the way
[Music]
to protest tomorrow let's like collect
them a little bit make them make them
become Super Chat Mountain
tomorrow we're gonna play not the game
that's on on the original Twitter
schedule but the game that's on the yeah
this ending soon thing I agree the
ending that's on the the YouTube
community board schedule we're gonna
play here Comes Nico which I was told
this is also a game with many many frogs
um
like the kind of I don't know I I really
don't know could have played it before
uh actually quite early
um long time ago early early in her
career
yeah I'm excited about that one really I
know nothing really I was just like oh
both of these rat detective games
I'm so short what do I do what do I do
and someone said you should you could
replace it with
um Here Comes Nico
and then I saw that we already have
permissions for it I'm going to play
that before I was like okay that's easy
I don't have to think much about that
[Music]
I am
yeah but I really don't know much about
it so I'll be going in pretty blind not
as blind as that Barney
didn't see Community post well why not
but yeah um so tomorrow since we played
both of the Frog detective games now
we're playing different game tomorrow
but it's also frog related yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I wish we have Frozen yeah I know some
some games you know like
just what was it Frogger or Froggers
Frogger
even that I would have liked to play but
these these games uh are the ones that I
got
perms for
so we happy with what we get okay
maybe maybe who knows someday maybe I
can get some more frog games permissions
and whenever I stumble across them I can
always bring out froggy Wawa
every once in a while I want to bring
her back anyway
because she's so cute
all right
thanks for watching to thank you again
[Music]
here comes
so tomorrow on my channel I forgot the
time but probably around the same time
kiddo
okay I think it's the same same starting
time get up
thank you all for watching
I love you my sweet tadpoles
hope you're getting used to me by now
with the second stream I'm gonna use the
new guys I wouldn't mind staying around
for a while longer at all schedule says
now earlier ah I
I'll sing about it I'll I'll look into
it all
me oh
I know Kiana can keep her German Channel
if she wanted to I'm not taking over
that one but she's dead so honestly what
can she do
anyway hmm
okay no it was fun I like these kind of
games they're they're being and cute and
simplistic but it just has this kind of
cute humor
really simple humor but yeah I don't
know I don't know what it is I don't
know how to describe it we're really
really enjoyed these get all um
and on that note yeah
good night everybody
hello Joseph you'll change your
name
wow wow wow
I'm dancing oh let me take them for the
gun away oh wait but do you maybe wait
wait wait
let me give you an opportunity to take a
clean and cute
hour shot
peace
[Music]
cute
oh
Oh yay and then and then now we have
[Music]
um
now we have
on this and
oh yeah
attack
oh wow
swish swish swish swish
okay
okay thank you very much for adding
these items last night pretty soon okay
yes
bye-bye my spank spank spank spank y
spanking
I buy it and I I repeat that again
my mind
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
thank you