[Music]
[Applause]
Perfect,
perfect! Hey, Live 3rd generation!
Peko
Luteker
's rabbits Let's
get married to Picole
[Music]
Hololive 3rd generation
Usadate Cola, thank you Almond
Almond
[Applause]
[Music]
Say goodbye  is perfect
Full live 3rd generation
Nagata Peco Rapico Hello, my
stomach hurts
[Music]
Poop
[Laughter]
From carrots
[Music]
[Laughs] Do you
like bigger boobs?
[Applause]
[Music]
Perfect
This live, the 3rd generation
is a lie.
I'm so sorry.
[Music] The
white cat is worried about hand coke and competition.
Let's settle our worries there.
[Applause]
[Music] Is it
perfect? ​​I'm going to
take a bath and pay for the bath.
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah,
Picker.  It
's a lie
-decor's pico
[laugh]
[Music]
[Applause]
This is a kitten.  I'm
staying the night
[applause]
[music]
Right?
[music] All
but the freshly baked popcorn
[clap]
[music] -
Yes, I
agree, it's
a lie.Da
Ravicon Almond
Armor
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I'm looking at you
[laughing]
[music] My
throat is dry from Pecola's laughter, so I'm
going to say hello.
Peeped version.
Perfect
live.  The 3rd generation's dishes are peco-rapeco
Door mode arm
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm going with this kind cashier Please
number 27, please give me a pen
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
nervous.  Nice to meet
you, the 3rd generation members of this live show, Usada Pikola and Mouse Pika [Music] Starting today, Peko will stop being a kids channel and become an adult kids channel. How do you guys like this kind of stuff? [Music] [Music] Peko-chan, what about you guys?  I
love you the most in the world. Your
voice is
stupid.
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah, are you just talking to me? Are you
not interested in water servers?
What kind of water is it that tastes so good?
Nozaki and his friends bring us fresh water every day,
so that's a trade secret. Huh?
Peko, who's willing to sign a contract with us.
Bond
[Music]
Welcome home,
Peko.
Now, let me show you the eyeballs.
Magical.
Peko Peko Peko Peko.
Enjoy.
[  [Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
Actually, just
for this one story, the rabbit pillow that Cora wears around her neck
came to stream the other day.
I'm Peko Usagi. I'm pecking from my ears and I'm pukopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekopekko.