[Music]
already in the game i thought we wanted
to show like
the characters off and then no not in
the game
out of the game yeah yeah like this
just like the characters characters yes
let me get out of this world
what do i get out of here
all right i'm gonna show you guys the
characters now we played this game
before a while ago but back then we
played it with
normal characters however one of the kfp
members called
zero duke shout out to zero duke has
made
mods for all of us as you can see we're
using them
um each of our characters are now modded
into the game
and each character has like not only
these cute outfits
but also like special like skills
and and and i don't know funny
interactions they can do yeah powers
yeah i mean guna doesn't have
much power apparently
i got a big stomach
stream guys
every character also has a little
variation for example here i can take
off my hats and then says i agree but i
also don't understand a famous quote by
takana
okay what do you girls is a quote say
um we have a quote where's our clothes
yeah wow
[Laughter]
i'm not sure if the taking off the hats
or whatever and
changes your skills well anyway i'm
going to go with the regular clothes
without myself classy on clothes
a halo or no halo cute yeah yeah please
use the hat
[Laughter]
this is how we're going to do things
this is really cute too
like yeah why why is it when i take your
hat off all it says is onion
what does that mean guys we have noticed
that when i take off my hats
um i look like an orange onion you
[Laughter]
oh by the way the announcements will be
um at the end of the stream but we won't
play for too long so don't worry guys
fine now i'm sorry i'm playing around
with the characters yeah yeah
okay let's taste it okay
let's go anything oh
my god no i'm fine i'm alive
then she loses sanity when
pretty ingenious over again oh no it's
it's the way it is
[Applause]
oh
you guys want to dance with me you can
yeah
is
[Music]
lots of food yes okay are you hungry
always whoever is low on brain juice you
gotta pick up flowers and that'll help
your brain juice get bigger
can you eat brain
this is adorable you can eat seeds and
berries but
if you build a craft plant it's like
better because you make full meals
yeah can i open it
up oh my god
my mom i can go into water but i get
weaker or something wait how do you go
into water
i'm going to kill this rabbit they're
aquatic
wait what i can't go there even though i
should be supposed to hide your dynamite
okay
[Music]
is
spawn around
[Music]
and revived myself because of you it's
because of your i am frog that's why all
these frogs are here i swear
it's written into the coating and frog
yeah exactly it's all your fault because
i'm with the frogs
another tree
here let me look at you oh that's so
cute everyone has their own like
individual little picture
girl's got a floaty too that's so cute
what about me what do i have i can't
look at myself
where are you girls i want to show you
my ghost form
where are you can you swing i'll look at
it later
yeah i can do soul strike i need to read
more to do that
i don't know how to use my ground pound
see the watson ground pounds
is
wow that's cool it's getting a little
bit late so i'm gonna head back
here oh does anybody have wood it's okay
i can make a small
we made a really awesome pot before i'm
kind of
thinking about it again it was a crock
pot don't go away yeah yeah yeah we have
to burn
trees
on fire just arrived normally oh i guess
i can do that
it's been killed how do i get tentacles
what i have the lowest health out of
everybody so
with great power comes great
responsibility
how do i revive normally
um you could try on the gate maybe
but i think
some more no stop there's some oh i've
had a
not molecule
would like to have that kitchen i have
20 house
is there like a counting up all right go
to the go to cover your board when
you're
okay i'm going to i can just break it
down so
always give me a toilet
no eat this carrot oh my
okay whoa
where are you oh look at your hands
oh you're puffed easy live songs
yes here you go ina drop wait hold on
drop
it's okay you're welcome
wait was that supposed to heal me
uh the watson cartoon i think so did it
not work i just sent me on a really cool
uh visual trip but i'm still
[Music]
oh
all right so let me see i can probably
look at it
and you can lead the frog into the
rabbit trap and die
nice idea uh i want to make rabbit traps
because
i was getting pretty good at that before
actually oh yeah
[Music]
we need to find gold so if anybody has
gold or
finds gold
hunting is my specialty wait you can't
come back to life
double double double kill i did it
once but i i died again and now i have a
super long cooldown
so i'm just waiting for the cooldown but
then everyone has to come to lunch so
you see how i revive you have to see it
yeah
okay tell me maybe
yeah tell us maybe 60 seconds
i'm coming over i'm on my way i want to
see christopher live i would like to
also
let's see but you have to have a safe
and like social distance
because everything around me will burn
can we get balloon
got it just like that one time in
minecraft
oh
[Music]
my dog your assistant's watching i can
send you to another place
are you dead forever um what is you guys
i have to guide you
a touchstone so you have to explore or
you'll have to
build you know resurrection and then
it's for
swamp habitat are there monsters in the
water
um it depends in some areas
i think there's monsters in the ocean
but not in the rivers i'm gonna make a
tour we're gonna get like
these fish okay oh i don't think so
can i hurt them oh is this a carrot but
i really don't know i mean you're
drilling something when you die
oh no big flowers i'm getting stupider
uh-huh
[Music]
what oh there's a drumstick
okay yeah that's from cali she killed it
right now i need to eat this i was
really proud of that
and i was really proud of killing that
turkey
you got only 12 hp are you scared by any
chances
oh wow holy there's a lot of spiders
over here
and a gold if you guys want to come over
here oh let me just worry about it
oh mushrooms are everything lazy
mushroom
okay i'm i'm to the west from the west
okay
oh i dropped some food if you guys need
to eat it i dropped carrots and berries
yes thanks because i'm really not hungry
where are you where am i carrot make a
campfire
and follow me oh it's going to be late
yeah you guys have enough stones
i don't have any stones some rocks air
does anybody else
on fire oh how many rocks
campfire here can you see that yeah
i think you need flint and logs
[Music]
oh never mind i didn't need to do that
my body oh can i eat your
skeleton there's only bonus
there
[Music]
i got some carrots although you can see
me right
oh okay i hope i can see you okay
i got some food for you thank you i'm
gonna stay with you guys
because uh yeah yeah
yeah stay over there now callie stay
over there i don't want to lower your
sanity because if there's a ghost nearby
it'll like a lawyer i'll just go wait
really
yo
what does this make you're close kelp
my sandy is going down we know that's
because of a ghost really really yeah
it goes down naturally from amazon
what can i make with these logs yummy
yes you did wait girl you said i missed
the conclusion
how did you think i died what do you
mean i don't know but i told you to go
for it
away i told you use it we
[Laughter]
oh nice nice thank you oh my goodness
this is
[Music]
so yeah you get that and then okay uh
you can set up rabbit traps for the
spiders
and then yeah okay
[Music]
we do have to build a bunch of stuff
boys
yeah yeah there's gold here if you guys
want to come
help okay
oh i did bed joe spider hi guys kill it
i mean strike a strike spider
how many i'll kill you
nice you can still have rabbit traps
okay i'll do that
the traps i killed it and then you
always
you can make health styles if you burn
like small stuff and make ash and you
can mix it with the spider glands to
make like a booster
shot oh my god here get it here
dummies
run into the rabbit traps and you can
lead them into the rabbit traps and look
at them
here like this bring them here
you big dummy fly
and go a little closer i need this stone
i'm getting sleepy oh wait can i not
actually die because i'm immortal
yeah you're just sleeping
it i want to thank you all while you're
sleeping that goes
okay
oh can i eat this
[Music]
all this material
i need to wake up and eat first it needs
to be the first thing i don't wake up
already really are you okay
kelly
[Applause]
okay
we
[Applause]
[Music]
we'll be back we'll be back to tango
with the spiders i need to go back
oh
oh i can make an axe oh i can make a pic
ooh i can make a oh i'm scared
i'm are you scared are you scared of
ghosts morsel wait
you being near me is lowering my sanity
i ate the monster meat i did them
i mean if you cook it it's okay i didn't
cook it
in your sandwich yeah oh wow there's a
really big
oh my gosh attack the crawling horse can
i hit it with my soul scythe
um
[Music]
oh
no
[Laughter]
hey buzz off buddy
[Music]
gosh they're everywhere all right yeah
that's good i'm just gonna make i think
we're all gonna die
probably not a bike
and then have some announcements so it's
okay we don't want too much
it's not it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no everyone is dead i mean i'm still
here but that's because i have to be
in like five minutes
just give me five
[Music]
just wait for me
should i come to you to help you make
the crock pot
uh i don't think i can be saved anymore
i'm a little uh
i'm a little uh like can i
it's dark here
well it makes sense maybe we should have
like uh
like a ghost meeting um what do you call
it
like really far away
alone in this universe because i can't
die yeah why is kelly still
sleeping
just wait for me no okay i'll wait for
you
can i haunt this bird
please tell me they can't flip you see
they can't cause
oh my god you just got this shark hat on
top of you that's so funny that one's
fast
hello
[Music]
when do i get
can we respond oh no no
i can't remind you the only way we can
respond is if we find a thing in the map
called a touchstone
or we have to make um these revive
potions thingies but it's yeah it's
going to be hard with me because i
continued to kind of go to sleep over
and over again which is the
which is actually kind of worse than not
being able to die
so i like how the frog right next to you
it's like that's me
yeah and you're also right next to me
away with
wait is you still alive i'm having a
really bad time
oh those are enos
he does anything though yes i am dead
yeah we're all dead give me the seeds
i'm just try i'm just living off of
seeds to be honest at this point
oh my god please
[Music]
oh
running like not a problem in the world
look at you
i am invincible oh that's so cool your
book
your book
where's my story where am i yeah i get
to keep picking up flowers
i lost my sense of direction
[Music]
what happens again okay uh you start
going crazy and start seeing monsters
then they start attacking you and then
you die
oh okay cool this is like a moment
i'm gonna lure a spider here what how is
this like among us
cause most of the game i spend it dead
like a ghost
yeah okay hi come here
yeah i know you want something show me
i am a part-time warrior i need my
swords
it's a water pipe it's a killer beehive
gummy wasp
bottom left triple phobia
oh yeah it does look like this must be
there okay there's a lot of flowers over
here but there's a lot of also deadly
bees if anyone wants sanity
yeah go bottom left
are there like caves and stuff in this
game um
i think there are caves in single player
but because of the way caves work
it's not easy to do with multiple
players so there's nothing
we should do that try to look for a
touchstone it looks like a coffin
surrounded by a sticks with pig heads on
it oh
you found it
that's all right wait don't don't use it
all up though if we're if you keep
playing
oh i'm not using it at all don't worry
i'm just keeping it safe because
uh you are a ghost yes i think you can
try it
you can recharge it oh that's good
that's fine oh my god you can recharge
it but i think you need like some
electric doodad or something oh
yeah i found a swamp area and this is
good
okay oh i can make this i have some gold
actually
what's that what we need are you like at
the bottom of the top
where the [\h__\h] i mean
yeah i've lost my [\h__\h] way the way
you're going in if you keep going
straight past that water and you keep
going
then you'll see this one there okay i'm
gonna google it
the heck is that 500 health
how about we all just die hmm
how's cali going to die now
[Music]
you're the only one who can do this
you're the only one who could say let's
give it away
what should i do tell me what i must do
what we need is um
spider glands do you have any of those
yeah i killed a bunch of [\h__\h] spiders
okay um okay
okay if you have spider glands we need
three grass
and if you go into like the tabs on the
left side you should see a heart
and you might it's called a telltale
heart and you should be able to make one
it's gonna take some hp and you'll die
but then you can resurrect one of us
with the heart oh yeah sure thing
i got your bag demon show yourself
resurrect me
the reason i died but is this what's
this payback is that why you
followed me the whole time you're hungry
no no no
no no where's the goddamn fence all
right i'm gonna sleep again i'll i'll do
it it's just
i can't find my way back so i'll keep
taking a nap
right there yeah just just haunt me for
a while
should boost your sanity instead yeah
you give me something like souls
yeah exactly i love seeing this people
like sanity from other people
oh yeah wait no
monster meet
[Laughter]
really quick if i cook the meat then
it'll be fine haunted grass
i can definitely make those things
though two ghosts walk into a pie
what do they do
what's grass without the g and they are
boom
[Music]
oh
i have no grass that's the problem you
know it's really hard to think of jokes
like that in english because it's not my
main language no not my mother tongue so
i would like to praise myself i'm so
proud of you
uh one spider gland close to the gate
really close to the gate because i died
there and i dropped it so there's a
there's a spider gland there okay guys
i have a little problem yeah so i want
to help you
but when i open the tab i don't see any
heart or anything like that
uh it should be under survival the news
oh it's under survival okay guys
please survive
okay this is like the survival knot i
don't know
i need ashes that's the problem is that
i need ashes and actually i need to get
covered
i will revive you guys leave it to me
just i need to make sure that i'm
knocking
this one okay you need a spider gland
and we're gonna be
cali cam all right gotcha wait isn't it
some of us should have a ton of grass
because i picked up a bunch so there's
some here but
yeah there's grass right here hang on
there's a turkey there's a turkey i'm
going to kill it really quick hang on
thank you
right here 16 grams oh
i can catch them
there's something so comical about
watching death herself chase down a
turkey
i know right i got one bag
uh okay okay
this is trees oh it's okay i bet it
likes halloween
yeah it's gone i mean i got one don't
uh we need one spider glam per person so
there's another spider going by the
spiders too
inside all right i'm going to go behind
spiders then but i need to get back to
the gate first
uh yes i do but it's not marked on there
oh wait i can see where everyone is
though
so okay that's us
[Music]
how do i make one potion is it in
survival
yeah it's in survival it's called
telltale heart and it's going to take
20.
so it's probably going to kill you oh my
gosh
you can ride one of us if you use it on
us you know you want to go first okay
wait you can go first you're you're more
knowledgeable what is this okay come
here i'll revive you because i'm in
phoenix this is this is where you're
fitting
in you should make up for it watson was
resurrected
i'm back
another
before in seven minutes because uh that
was
nice everyone being revived i'll thank
you
and now oh god i left go down oh i
thought i was gonna
kill some more do we need to kill more
spiders that's fine
um yeah
dumb there is a gland in this spider
already
it's going to be dark soon though so
does anybody have two stones i have four
rocks
i don't know if that can cause yeah
oyster drop thank you
have that one and then just vibing
fine i'll go pick up all the um
can we do a group picture once buddha is
back alive i want to do a group picture
with everyone
or in game screen time
[Music]
there's no chicken too close there's no
such thing as being too close
this is luffy get away
are we also i'm not losing sign because
of good ass oh
my god oh no wait no it's going up wait
it's going up
oh it's going up actually and cause
we're by the fire yeah oh okay
oh yeah right okay garbour here
[Laughter]
mary davis
[Music]
okay okay okay we can go go go go
oh there's a gland here yeah yeah yeah
that's it
look i can't wake it up cause i keep
going sleeping
[Laughter]
you can't have that problem huh and
there's another gland there kiara if you
want to
the shrimp i don't think we can only
have everything i'm going to think we
can all be alive
[Music]
okay i'll set it again okay
i got one okay oh okay nice okay we have
two okay yeah and then i have enough
grass
yeah yeah we should work and i have i
have ashes as well don't we do we need
ashes
uh well if we were to keep playing we
would need them because then we could
use it to heal to make like heal stuff
oh i see oh that's right yeah the
healing one okay
never mind then all right i'm gonna drop
my [\h__\h] here okay okay
okay let's see here's the gland all
right
oh oh put the bumper down for the frog
the shot's done
okay
[Music]
you know okay don't do it over here go
somewhere else okay
okay so you know let's get it and then
good evil rings me
sounds good three
two
it won't chase you that far so just go
oh there it is
okay it's fine yeah it takes hp now
red is good now i need to heal i'm at
4hp now
thank you god damn just give it the
heart
i can't feel the heart you said the more
frog why'd
[Music]
how do i use it you just click on it and
give it to gera
if you can catch me oh okay
not fast
wow
[Music]
oh
okay everybody press y and then in the
typing box you can type forward slash
dance and we can all line up and we can
all dance at the same time
forward slash dance sports
and dance ready for the photo
yes i'm gonna get a little bit covered
up from this knife
am i flossing i'm sorry
[Music]
going off to the right like this yeah
you might have to rotate your
perspective
oh yeah
[Music]
wait is this
[Applause]
uh everyone show the first
slide okay sit down okay
turning on my bgm
everyone it is the whole live english
myth half year anniversary unbelievable
but it's been six months can you believe
it guys oh my god
[Music]
yay exciting so of course we prepared
uh some things for you many things
actually and yeah
yeah and we will
start off with uh the second slide
everyone move on to the second side
we got a whole lot of english myth
acrylic stands
merchandise
english myth penta keychain
marching band
so
[Music]
stands
standing standing perfect okay so with
these stands
um you can buy them separately or you
can buy them together
i say buy them together so that way we
can all be together and we won't get
lonely and we won't miss one another
you can put these on your table you can
put these on your desk above your beds
you can get creative and then send us i
guess send those pictures about how you
plan on displaying them that would be
really fun
uh yeah stands
i don't know how big they are but yeah
hopefully you think they'll be
[Laughter]
life-sized
[Music]
slide everyone and uh it's being
introduced
let's go this is our second merch it's
gonna be our mascot
five in one key chain yeah all five of
those charms at once yeah
yeah it's gonna be um put on a leather
strap
i think and it's gonna the leather strap
is gonna have the hollow life english
logo
five in one what a deal one so adorable
mm-hmm
key chains it's possible that we won't
have like a second
um like a second wave of orders so
only one wave of orders get another high
yes
yeah if you want to get them
yeah so the page to buy these will show
up at booth
at uh uh 5 pm pst
which is 8 30 pm 30 minutes
30 minutes from now on yeah it will be
on geekback
and on booth both and just follow check
the official twitter
for the links and the announcements
yes you would think
you would think
oh it's my turn okay well i guess um um
it's it's i'm supposed to introduce this
one but
we uh have a little it's actually more
of um
sorry big stretch it's actually uh
um we're gonna let it do uh the talking
itself
afterwards yeah indeed um
so anyway i guess we'll go ahead and
kind of count it down but uh
you guys um you guys will all get to see
in real time with us
is something special something real
special coming extra soon
okay so everyone shut up
i'm gonna mute you guys really quick uh
oh ready okay four
three two
one no
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
[Applause]
was the next slide
yes indeed let's go let's move right
along to the next one
this is an image soundtrack
for a whole live english myth
[Applause]
very special our own very special uh i
guess
image bgm made for us it's instrumental
um i think we'll actually probably be
using them in streams i know i will at
least because bgm
that was kind of the intention but you
guys can also get it for yourselves as
well releasing everywhere
march 14th local time for you wherever
you are
2021 so uh get it or be
be square be circle yeah
i know a lot of people ask but yeah
there's no vocals there's a bgm
um
oh yeah oh man am i going to rap to this
like oh okay
it's bgm but still hey
and all tricks are made by camellia
incredible yeah every track really uh
suits each person so i think
maybe we want to get a little give a
little comment what do you think about
your son callie
freaking dope when i heard it for the
first time i was like wow this is like a
combination of um everything that i
think makes up me it's got
like this kind of regal and like um
almost like a
gothic tone to it i guess dark
mysterious oh
it's also [\h__\h] dope i don't know it's
uh yeah there's a little bit of hip-hop
in there yeah
i like i can bob my head to it which is
why the title is really good
um
it's perfect for me what about you guys
and the second track is mine yeah and
it's
i love how the title actually um is
like for it stands for kfp it's kiara
fry
uh party i think
but it's also like you can also say like
at a party you couldn't be like oh
i get i get all the other popular kids
and the clubs are like i get i'll get it
i'll get boy
raise the volume yeah raise the roof
yeah
my son is pretty energetic pretty happy
pretty
kawaii cute bobby poppy puppy style
so i'm really excited to um have that
being played in the kfp
stores all over the world worldwide
franchise obviously so it's going to be
played in every store for
until we all die yes
delicious
yes uh i really like mine because it has
like kind of like the oriental feel and
it's like really chill
and i can listen to it like forever on
loop i probably will
i really really really like it
[Music]
thank you thank you too i was bopping to
it while i was playing while i was
playing i was like
this is so good yes yeah
and fourth track is i think good ass
chocolate french
shark adventure with that delicious
absolutely delicious finger looking good
baseline i get the i get the stank face
every time
i hear it the first time i heard that
bass line i was
thinking the rhythm
the bass line you gotta play it very
loud get that bass line to full
potential um
and the baseline and i melt when i hear
it and then i dance to the v
i'm just i'm in love with it i'm over
the heels over the moon that's the way
it is
head over heels over there okay over the
hills
yeah the last one is mine and it sounds
like a bop
yeah it sounds i don't know it kind of
sounds like a nostalgic like it almost
sounds like a song from like an older
game
this is really nice and it's called miss
tvis like mistress
yeah i thought it was an iphone i was
like wait a wait a minute
of course uh missed mythbuster i believe
it's called yeah
yeah i really like it it's really a pop
up yeah i love all the tracks like i'm
gonna be having
it on loop for like five months i want
all of them
all of them in my playlist immediately
i think it's the first time that like
some like whole life members like
release
like just like background oh ost like
kind of music just the soundtrack
and normally everyone releases songs
with their singing in it but we
we're going to do things a little bit
different right i mean would be cool
if one day we also have songs together
where we actually
soundtrack means like image soundtrack
just means like
that i think yeah like
yeah it's like concept art but like yeah
like music
your life's if you your if your life had
a bgm
it's it's what it is
one of my goals was actually to make bgm
for all of you guys but it looks like
into the punch
cover i'm just looking at it now it's
like a shield and then it has
his size and like the tentacles and yeah
the middle is my shield is like in the
middle protecting all of you from danger
yeah yeah yeah it's got like another
portal
oh gosh
it's super surreal i like it this is the
portal that leads you into the darkness
the rabbit hole of her
life yeah with
that being said i know we're all uh very
excited but there is
actually one more thing
okay after my drum roll then you guys
can show it
okay drum roll please
[Music]
yes
actually the reason why i asked my
viewers like
two weeks ago or three weeks ago for a
name is for this
and we named it kotori
on my name because takanasi my last name
normally is read as koto di
uh so it has two ways to read it so
actually
we write it differently for this one but
actually my takanashi can be read is
ba
[Music]
account's death sente hey
this gives me destiny and then we have
guinness bloop blood they're all so cute
who looks like he's about to commit very
very very very
illegal crimes out of the darkness
becomes blue
he goes nothing personal okay
i'm so excited for these yes coming soon
at tm hmm
let's do a balancing contest who can
balance them on top of each other
no cheating no cheating you have to
there can't be any support around them
you just need to be on top of each other
winner again
i don't know my endless love and
affection maybe if i feel like
that's worth
[Music]
360. i'm looking forward to my thick
fat ass burp i'm um i'm excited to grill
it
grill yeah you know i think if you burn
it i don't think it'll come back
yeah probably not maybe don't do that
i'm going to put all of them on my bed
well yeah so that is uh
key chains that then the acrylic stands
and then the album
and uh the plushies yeah lots of stuff
i look forward to yeah i guess
we'll be posted on twitter and i think
uh
if you're not on twitter then maybe
we'll do community posts or i don't know
probably also going to be on the under
hole
um maybe i don't know but if you if
you're not on twitter i'll probably put
a link in my description in the future
streams maybe the other girls will do
that too yeah
i had so much fun drawing them also
please look forward to it
very nice well then
that was pretty much it thank you
everyone uh for joining in on the
streams today for celebrating together
with us
does anyone here have some individual
announcements that have nothing to do
with the merchandise then do it now
yeah um okay so basically
first i just want to say to everyone uh
thanks so much
for your support in the chat super chats
will be read next time
next time okay so look forward to that
uh in the just chatting and also
um my my new ep is coming out
very soon
my birthday yes that's right it's coming
out on my birthday uh so please
anticipate it
um i'm working really hard on it and you
can actually pre-order it
um as well uh you can check my twitter
for the link i'm going to go ahead and
retweet it again after this you can
pre-order a physical copy get special
stickers
um it does ship overseas um
and uh yeah if you don't want to get a
physical copy because uh overseas
shipping is uh kind of scary
i understand that um you can just go
ahead and stream it
uh as well it'll be coming to all
streaming platforms
on the same day nice yeah yeah exactly
so
so you guys can check it out there um
please check it it would
really it would really make uh my day
and make my birthday really happy if you
could at least
get give it a shot give it a little
listen just a little listen you know
anything forever yes
so yeah look forward to it that's the
only announcement that i have for now
and
announcements everyone can also just say
a nice message so
move on with ame yes yeah uh
yeah i wanted to like talk a little bit
like about how six months have been for
us and stuff like that
uh for me i don't know how life has been
like kind of life-changing
and i know a lot of you guys too it's
like so much work
and i don't know i'm really grateful to
be with you guys too because i think
everybody like we just contribute so
much to
the group in general and
everybody also who worked on hololive
like behind the scenes and stuff all
this stuff
too everybody puts in so much work so i
want to thank you guys for six months
and more months to come and we'll do it
again on the one year anniversary
we'll have more stuff yeah thank you
guys so much for the past six months i
really appreciate it i don't have any
announcements other than that
thank you okay
i would like to announce that i love you
all
for better mates you got me down
something yeah six months pasta
oh no my ceiling's about to leak but
yeah thank you let's do our best from
now on too
yeah love you all
thank you for everyone's hard work
that's it
i'm emotional that's all i would like to
also say thank you
say thank you to this absolutely
incredible
team of the most lovely people my gen
mates that have changed my life for the
better oh
i'm really lucky to be surrounded by
such really great people
did you write something did you write a
letter no no
[Music]
i wrapped wind you're
to you guys each one of you you've been
so incredible these past six months
thank you
and i want to say thank you to all of
you that are watching no matter where
you come from thank you also
oh my god you
[Laughter]
oh my god oh well
okay i think they're cool
[Laughter]
yes well from my side um
i'm celebrating the half year
anniversary
in a few hours when i don't know 15 10
10 i don't know how many hours
uh with a whole life original songs
only kind of okay i've been learning a
lot of songs
from our senpais to uh show them to you
guys tomorrow
today oh i heard a kitty cat is that oh
that's my cat
oh that's my cat
yeah and um i also just uh i'll probably
get more
into deep detail about how i feel about
uh this half year uh
in that stream but generally i just want
to say i hope that
uh when when we do our one year
anniversary
that we can all be together in one room
and just hug each other
and yeah you know that would be really
nice because now i hear gouda
crying now makes me sad i want to hug
her i wish i could hug her
so let's work towards that making that a
reality making for dear reality making
new outfits our reality and making a
long long
uh future together with us and with some
kohi's as well
and a reality and making whole live
english even bigger than it already is
[Music]
[Applause]
um actually i'm really bad at the sappy
stuff but i just want to say
i just want to say um i really wanted to
do
um creative stuff full-time when i was
just a reaper
and because of everyone's really kind
support i was able to get
the chance to do that but i wouldn't
have been able to continue on
uh like this if it weren't for you guys
i definitely couldn't have done it alone
so
um thank you guys for having me
for being a great gym mates i don't i
think that um
i mean i can't even imagine a world
where anyone else
um where anyone is not here or
different or anything like that um i
don't want to
uh because everything just kind of fell
into place exactly
i feel like how it how it should have
been um
and i'm just really grateful thank you
so much
i'm glad that that's fine i'm so glad to
have the
exactly these members hey yeah i'm gonna
give you all hugs so badly here
oh let's do it someday it's a promise
okay let's do this
no running from this do it yes yes
it's a promise i do want to give one
last thanks to to the viewers yeah like
good like good outside
and it's really yeah the support you
guys all show all of us
is crazy so many people from all around
the world to me that's like the most
mind-boggling thing that's just from
everywhere people are watching
and uh i really appreciate it i know
everybody else does too
thank you guys for your support we
wouldn't be here without you guys
that's very much yeah i wouldn't be able
to do this at all actually
thank you yes it's teammates taco
uh and kfb
[Music]
many many fun memories from now on as
well
together yes let's do it let's do it
do it all right then i think
that's it yeah we're gonna have an after
party privately
right on discord yeah so thank you
everyone for watching
thank you thank you thanks guys so much
for the flip side
everybody
[Music]
bye
you