[Music]
[Applause]
I
[Music]
look hi hello everyone
hello
hello I think this the stream is kind of
a little bit have a lagging
problem better now yeah okay so this is
the first time that I am uh asking uh
some Ian member Kon Kiara and FAA to
join the Age of Empire 2 uh but we also
have Ana and rainy to play
again
yay so uh this time this time um we put
it into a team um since me Ana and rainy
already playing this game before so we
put I think it's wisely to put uh two
versus two versus kind of thing
yes every team have and
[Laughter]
ID International Teams let's
go
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah like a like a game setting with a
random map a normal six player and the
location actually right now is randomly
choose Coastal but I actually have no
idea about it M I don't have any idea
about the maps yeah I don't have any
idea about the map me
too it'll be are you sure it's random
Mrs MAA who's playing Vikings are you
sure that was not on purpose cuz you're
playing
Vikings I I put like game modes and
random M and they put the location on
Coastal
okay should I should I I don't know
should I is fine right it doesn't really
mean that the whole map is covered with
ocean right it's just that there is a
coast
right
custom yeah there there you can just
choose like 10 or 15 maps that you want
to be in the pool
oh so you can choose everything that
looks good to you for a big
match okay mostly oh maybe maybe I just
choose the one that have like maybe six
with mostly they are
map choose Arena too Arena and black
forest in the uh in the top uh two top
top two row Black Forest yummy Black
Forest Black Forest yummy black forest
cake oh
yummy which one again H in the top row
there should be black forest and Arena
it's it's alphabetic anyway Black Forest
yeah I heard that I never played it but
it's very popular I think for big
matches and then what do you want to
request Arena I don't know I up to you
we put hamburger on I'll it to you
anything's
fine it'll be
fine how bad can it be all right you
chose
so oh my God no no no no no the one that
is on Arena Black
Forest um which one again but
take oh look at that BR majapahit Empire
oh my God wait can I see a costum map
Pool oh I can oh I can how many maps are
there there's so many oh wait
standard where's the big map
aish we have like a how many Maps
there's a map called Mega random like is
it is there really like a question mark
shaved water on
it Mega random is just super random
interesting going to be heavily stylist
like everything is going to be random
it's not always going to be the
same I'm looking at four people yeah
like the thing is I can't select see
like I I can't see the six people maps
how do I see the six people Maps yeah I
don't know four people there
four how
mostly I mean it's just a map size
maps and these are just map Styles right
there's 83 maps in the
game automatically adjusted it this oh
look at this 1 2 3 oh now this is huge
adjusted oh you went to real world
Indonesia oh my God so much water in
Indonesia not real world not real world
water in real world so much water in the
real world go back to
random random Black
Forest it's
fine black
forest um no no I put it on random black
forest black for AR and be Empire that's
the three random that I choose oh it
says Black Forest here but I guess when
you get to the game it's going to be
randomized yeah I
guess we'll okay it's not bad if we go
eat cake right cake is good cake is let
them have let them have
cake okay um well I think it's time to
startop
all right guys ready you going to kick
us out good luck good luck everyone Good
Luck Good
Luck have mercy
maaas okay
byebye let's go let's
go
ah kind of exciting it's good to have
you honestly oh got which which we got
the arena oh nice we got the
arena okay
[Music]
okay
see I'm going to
build should build a
house then good
go
build the hot Keys it's okay we can just
relax
yeah I kind of don't want to talk much
cuz you know I want to focus but you
know that's not how it should work
unfortunately don't worry about that
so like do you like playing this
game well it yes I kind of like this
game it's like my childhood
[Music]
game oh where are you oh you're down
there okay okay okay okay oh so we
already we already got um what does it
called what does it called oh cool yeah
we already have the the little Gates
which is
convenient okay
nice very nice very very
nice and 500 we need
that well since we have the walls it's
already kind of convenient yeah we
already have walls it's it's
nice uhhuh
oh you already
walking H oh the SCS yeah
already and then maybe have
bline okay and then do this have you and
not
yet they got to chop down trees where
the
trees oh this is wood
okay we'll cut this
down come
on that's great enough all while in
here actually house house house house
house house house
is your YouTube all right yeah I think
so oh dang it m YouTube is not all
right huh oh you already found you
already found where's FAA and Ana oh
Nicea is really close to
mine okay uh right I can probably have
one I can't
any more
wood I love how they talking yeah just
jerish then all right and
then
uh uh probably the one that nearest you
probably uh
[Music]
um really rainy or
Ora the clus of m is
Ana okay sweet this and put it right
more put a put it
here I
need
more at least we have like some time to
grow and everything
yeah and we only have like 15 minutes to
stay calm after that I
know oh we only have 7 minutes actually
that's not good at all oh my oh
my oh
my okay well then don't complain if in
the middle we just like already
[Music]
dead okay nice one's
already build build build build I'm just
going to put it in
here have it
here why is so hard to get
a pump it
out why it's so hard to get
thing I need I need more speak need more
go over there and over
there and that's great all so go over
there
time you want actually
now Clos
oh great kill
right
courage I think I do need
one
four at least four
gold I need more food
you uh resources I have like 400
yeah I haven't upgraded to the second
the the feudal age what are you guys
doing
kill I'm still struggling with uh the
yeah I'm still struggling with the food
yeah me
too food and
wood okay they're all working
good it
more okay kill kill hurry up
kill
what this
nail this do not be
idle I'm just going to put a lot of this
this one is
building then doing
it here actually
don't why I don't know why I put it far
away oh we have two
minutes two minutes dang it have you
have you even make
a
okay 200 still 500 needed
freaking around here you really don't
need that
not enough food my Lord my Lord not
enough food never enough
food that was actually a different
game ah I don't know I'm
just you know what kill
him no actually we need everyone
but don't worry we still have uh a wall
a big wall H that's
true yeah we still have a big wall at
least okay
good we can probably build more
houses
another yeah probably right
here just
oh my God what are you guys
doing
what okay now you guys should build
this oh is that
become
become oh okay
okay oh that's why
I'm going disclaim my
sheep
oh that is not
good okay my Scout's still exploring
what the heck is this
doing oh it's you okay never
mind to close that uh you oh you already
on food oh nice ni
y see only uh or cron is number one
right
now right be
G I'm
still trying my
best it's okay we're going to we're
going to do great man we're going to do
great
things house Mill uh let's build a
Barrack
hey what are you doing
here okay everyone's working what are
you doing here
Ana oh Anya came to inspect oh I think
my Scott is already dead really mine's
not dead yet oh damn it's not dead
yet okay and then yeah
come on get there
faster okay time to build another
houses time to build another
houses all right then you go build a
stone Mill I mean mining
camp maybe give it a little
let's make the
civilizations
right
better cannot
forget okay go
work
and we need more which is
good don't go
go build a
house everyone's doing
good
right and then I think that's good
that's good enough we can build more
stuff for food
[Music]
some give me a lot of
food and then maybe me one and
then
some doing
that my bet nobody is building cl cl cl
cling cling cling cling
I need I need a
l I need I need we don't have water in
here
like I don't know if that's a good idea
or not
water okay 800
200 oh shoot
okay still mining don't need that yet
make that
faster 300 100 not yet and then finish
that freaking house and then do that do
this okay good now I can make more
stuff K is so
fast it's all good it's all good
put in defensive
mode someone proba that they leave these
things alone in here and he's
stuck or is he where are he
going what
died thank
that was that was so dramatic
[Laughter]
MAA is it life or
death I
mean all right this is good and then
okay the closest one from your gate is
Kiara you go build another one
okay almost
almost give me more stuff
bro and Marketplace we can probably get
to Marketplace
now
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah you know we're at a pretty good
Pace pretty pretty nice pretty nice
pretty
nice I actually car's pretty good look
at that and look at the FAA look at
FAA
h i mean you're doing really well what
are you talking about no no no look at
look at FAA one
1,600 oh oh the economy uh diplomacy was
it
yep
okay I'm literally so chilling right
now literally I think two feudal ages
wait I thought I
built did I not God damn
it oh I didn't build blacksmith no
wonder okay
okay two feudal buildings that I have no
choice build
more go over
there actually you go over
there
m
125 what else what else El what
else all right now that that's
done
uh build more
houses
okay Castle age good good good
[Music]
wow that's
crazy everyone's playing so good I know
right they're all advancing so quickly
yeah yeah so
good you wear uner though
she she DN
good all right all right almost done
can't keep zoning out keep pumping out
okay it's F to
L what
okay
good I don't know why I can I cannot
upgrade this
one H upgrade why it doesn't allow me to
upgrade for some
reason
sweet that
means now have enough
nice
nice H they're
all
defensive I have to wait
finally yep
okay and then
sell very
nice 650 okay
yeah put more people
here I'm going to build
Market Nice
okay okay good progress good progress so
far monster
okay keep building not keep building
keep making
soldiers
uh
sure wait no don't do
that yeah maybe that
Rose host color trade co
ah oh my God you
guys
build need
[Music]
more stop zing help my
dudes okay yeah no they're just zoning
out I think I need to make another
L this this Dead
Land all right
okay H th000 and Castle age stuff okay
good got it
and these ones they are all going
there
castle where do I build a castle maybe
here I'll build a castle right around
here sure why
not we need more roots I need more Roots
very ran out of wots what's this
Monastery University hey Monastery might
be a good idea to build
one maybe around
here maybe
here h two Castle AE buildings okay good
good
good who's going to build
this I need a stable have you made the
trade have you made a market uh yeah I
did nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice very
good
nice maybe
archers
archers is it always been
close monster built very nice
okay just have two just in case is my
Scout dead my Scout is dead isn't it
nope what are you
doing
bro okay to Castle age H okay okay okay
okay Castle I did build a castle did I
build a castle I didn't build a
castle you want to build a castle okay
come back I
do but they're struggling
nice okay
great oh
boy and then and start upgrading
these
uh yeah let's have this for now
[Music]
and then they are running out of
resources so we are going
to
H you forgot
what I forgot how to find the idle it'll
little
it'll it'll where
it oh God you
guys you guys are jobless can't do
that Target it
units
plus I don't
know I don't know if I have one
faster faster
you can be on
defensive I don't know where the relics
are is a
thing where is The Relic oh
God are you searching a relic right now
yeah I found one Relic uh was uh
right there go pick that up
light all right okay
sick keep pumping it out
buddy and then
you should I start building a Wonder or
no why are so fast
when I should I start building a Wonder
or should I not yeah yeah yeah you can
start building Wonder because it can
help you win yeah okay uh let's put this
inside so I think I need to build
something all right start building stuff
again 800 we need more
gold go over there you go over
there go over
there great okay dude now go
back if you want to start to war tell
me a
war definitely not yet
[Music]
okay and then I think it's about time I
build a a
Siege archery definitely
uh
py
up
yes woo so intense
bro Cavalry
Cavalry okay I think they shall
move this one
instead uh start selling sell sell sell
sell sell
that way we can upgrade
it oh
yeah start making
this maybe I should have more people
building The
Wonder go over
there still chill
it is still pretty
chill it's pretty
chill where the hell is where the hell
is my
monk nobody have any
idea
I'm go pick that up it's like right in
front of
you grny so vast
oh go over
there wait I
forgot okay and then Cavalry okay we
need more food
definitely
food thank
you you
you you should build trade card crony hm
build trade card and and click on my my
markets it will help you to add gold
kind of thing oh okay uh research trade
card or
Caravan oh wait no never mind trade card
okay and that one should go to your
Market which is uh which one is Market
again this one
I need to build more
houses okay
this Pacman
this yep yep yep oh okay triple probably
good
idea let me know when you want to try
doing War I'll get it ready if I
can okay me too I'm still upgrading
though um maybe I put some
light uh
this wait where did my M go
again yeah there you are go back
where waiting waiting
waiting why do she build a castle
here what who
oh H because it will it will you can you
can actually kill it by with
uh you can actually take it down down
the castle because the castle can attack
you oh that's very not pleasant that's
why she put it
nearby okay sometime sometime I kill
people with
Castle
really you need some seed weapons
no just just be there Siege
weapons Siege weapon Siege weapon
where's The Siege weapon
again Siege
Siege oh that's not
cool Siege weapons sieg weapon did I I
thought I built a Siege weapon somewhere
around also need
to Siege Siege Siege Siege Siege did I
not build a
Siege I must have not built a Siege
okay Siege
I didn't build it never mind
okay oh my God are you kidding
me
what oh yeah that's what it will
do you can just actually
kill it now
probably oh boy I forgot I'm going to
make make some I'm so
angry
here wait oh wait never mind never mind
no
bro oh why did you do
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that okay triple
sh that's
great uh you can make magnol
is magn uh yeah make
magnol I'm trying my best to really bro
Cara's
here oh my goodness are you kidding
me what is
it oh okay I'm going to send
M I'm going to send mine oh God the
Villager are mixed up too that's just
great oh
great oh great oh
great oh he's
already oh that's just great
oh that's a lot of
[Music]
damage oh boy
oh joy that's so
fun oh mine is already
dead sorry oh my
God why is she like
this oh my God she keeps
coming that's why
ladyy oh dear
here my freaking
Wonder oh no
coroni I didn't have
enough didn't make enough oh
[Music]
man uh actually I can send them
in I should have done that
sooner uh can you close the gate how do
I close the gate now FAA comes to
[Laughter]
you oh my goodness you oh my
[Music]
goodness uh stop
working okay let's get them all to your
place
maybe oh boy oh boy they're like
destroying okay I'm going to make as
much as possible and send them over
there
[Music]
okay you guys go over
there you go over
there damn
it damn they're attacking me personally
what' I
do oh it must have been because I was
building the Wonder
here um did you know that you can make a
lot of barracks and a lot of AR Rin uh
so they can
actually
what H they can build a lot of a lot of
um Barracks Street Workshop so you can
actually um what is
called maybe oh
oh yeah maybe because you bu Wonder yeah
this probably why
whoopsie I think they're destroying the
hell out of my
town all right let's see what can I do
what can I do let's
see yeah close the gate
close the gate how do I close the gate
it's better it's better to close the
gate and rebuild
Y close the
gate but like what's the point of
closing the gate if it's like opened up
dang
it make sure it's not
open yeah
it's
[Music]
open oh
man I can't really fix the wall because
like she has the castle so like it's
kind of breaking down the
wall regardless why are you going over
there that's going to kill you
buddy oh are you like sending your units
over
there yeah
tring okay I'll try to send my units
there too
then uh not you guys you can you help me
with this war 11 like so
weig oh dear
okay you guys go over
[Music]
there
okay oh man that's
stressful okay and
then no kill them first
what am I doing
here oh
shoot oh my
God you guys keep at
it mhm
oh my
goodness
o I am searching
my okay Retreat guys
[Music]
I should not have built the
Wonder actually you should hm actually
you should because it will help you win
I know it's just that it makes you a
Target yeah
okay which one should I
[Music]
um
uh all right guys build a new life
mind if I
join
okay I'm going
to maybe like build over
there I think my base is pretty much
screwed oh cuz of the Castle I can't
really redo
it yeah you cannot redo it yeah I cannot
H I cannot I can't redeem it I don't
think so I'm going to build a town
center I'm sending some Army to stand by
in your village actually maybe you
should make some
too villager uh why are your villager
didn't do anything huh you put all your
villager in my place and didn't do
anything oh my
God
yeah you know I'll just like re redo it
at your base you don't need to try and
save it I think they're too overpowered
at the
moment really yeah I feel like
it that's fine we can just put it you
can you can make uh some some are they
not Army in your
base we can stand by in there so we can
just you know we aiming for Kiara right
now yeah I think
K's yeah kiar is like waiting there
oh maybe I can have
like several can I have a few villagers
going over there and try to fix the
wall yeah fix the wall fix the
wall but I think that Knight over there
is going to like kill the villagers is
the
[Music]
thing
so uh Arch
don't forget to research
everything
yeah even though everything's burning
[Music]
oh
boy I don't know if this is going to
work
[Music]
but oh don't not ATT
first yeah I'm not going to attack I'm
just going to see if I can rebuild
it nope they just freaking died
oh can you build a lots of um magnol
with me magnol yeah if I can um
magnol Castle destroyed actually um let
me just build
one uh where should I build oh I need
food maybe like right around here
[Music]
wait Town
Center oh my God that's Kiara Kiara's
building over
here oh she's also building over there
oh yeah oh no wait I don't have any
armies
I think I'm going to build
uh wait I don't even have should I
attack should I I should destroy this
building oh my God she built a freaking
Castle she built a
castle closer
[Music]
know what um never
mind maybe I should what the heck is
this
okay you know what screw
this so she built a castle between like
uh ours our
castles
H
okay Town Center here
ah it's a little more peaceful here
who's the red one by the
way help
me I wish I can don't you know what
don't don't put your units there I think
it's kind of pointless cuz I don't think
I can save my castle don't do
it so what uh I'm going to rebuild my
base uh next to you okay you want to
rebuild where
uh between Anya and your your
base okay cuz uh Ana hasn't really done
much it
seems
okay then I'm going
to build build
build a fortified
wall be like
that no don't be too greedy maybe yeah
don't be too greedy
oh bro that is so
stressful okay
this build a fortify
wall are you
guys help
[Music]
just for you
guys nope that's broken never
mind okay and send that
here what are you
doing
oh K is really going all out isn't she
yeah she is she really
[Music]
is
okay
food close
Okay I need to have more
food did
someone we should we should make sure
that there is someone already make
a okay I don't no no no no no no
okay and then build a
farm should I the
M if you have lots of money just build a
castle yeah oh I'll try
that build a castle castle castle yep I
do I can have
[Music]
Castle all right and
then build a build
a gate
just just just build one right
[Music]
here what is the best one
for right guys go over
[Music]
there what
oh it's okay dude what are you guys
doing
[Music]
run yeah okay
all right
nice what
where in the
[Music]
B why is nobody building
okay
s sell sell by bye bye
bye hurry hurry
hurry don't have enough woods and gold
again I don't think that I have enough
resources now
[Music]
okay let's go over
there
have okay and then go over here
oh
okay
okay okay what are you guys
doing over here and then build a
truchet how many trets do you
need a lot okay whole lot I got
you I'll build maybe three or how many
do you need uh you said a lot right lot
as you can
and then this oh they start to killing
me what I think I think we're going to
be the one who going to
died oh God I'm
sorry no we going to be the one going to
died I cannot even make a coros Bowman
like I'm red out of gold right
now oh God uh what do you need uh I have
like
truchet I ran
that's so many
gold I have 307 I can use the
treuchet
speak no no
apparently everyone's going after us cuz
they thought we were too
good yeah like like I think Ana and FAA
they don't even attack them I don't know
oh man I'm dead that
now can't I do anything okay I'll go
over
there if you don't have any you can just
ouchie ouchie ouchie
ouchie uh let me see
archers
oh I cannot do
anything easy
lose oh no what kind of
true don't go there it's crazy
there are they
attacking I don't know if it's to
run runs for your life apparently it's
four against two right now
oh
boy nice
try oh oh no nice
try un like every
sight oh my goodness
no run run run run run run run
run
ah ah okay they're
everywhere oh just running we're just
running right
now I'm searching I'm
searching she put it
everywhere she put it
everywhere oh she destroyed
everything so literally K put castle
like in every place yeah
she's really great yeah she's really
good I wonder what's happened with haa
Kingdom I cannot do
anything uh
I have a
tret maybe now that they're distracted I
can maybe send someone to
repair I just see
my my town
gone me and
Karan Our Town
gone no guys don't do anything I cannot
cannot I didn't have enough stuns
so I have enough
stun
H I'm sorry maybe I shouldn't have built
the
Wonder no no no no
no oh they're destroying having a really
good strateg I I even like uh really
really I should have made a villager at
the beginning like lots of
villagers
uh we need to do a redo of this one day
one day we got to do a redo day
yeah no don't don't go there that's
crazy
look at Ana she's so chill I know was
like so
chilly fauna's pretty chill too I think
this is
fauna
dud anaa and rain is pretty chill f is I
didn't
see there you go there you go there you
go f you found
me oh
oh oh
no go go go attack this maybe no mercy
no mercy indeed no mercy
oh
no Castle's
gone everything's
gone hey don't don't don't
don't stay here
oh I don't know what to
do
oh oh who cares about the wood
now six
60 I can't oh
man yeah we've been attacked with by two
team oh no that's oh been attacked by
two team
literally oh
dear oh
hi
okay I don't know what to do with this
but
[Music]
all my villagers are dead it
seems
well that's
that that
well you know I think we did pretty good
against two teams pretty yeah we did
pretty great
yeah okay we just I'm just doing a farm
live become a become a wood maker
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
uh well you know what
I'm going to go out with a
bang do you have any other villager left
no I don't that's it no
why yeah no it's over I only have like
um a handful of armies and that's about
it
[Music]
okay I don't know where to attack
really so with the monk can I convert a
castle Yeah h no no no you
cannot maybe I can convert a villager
there's nothing I have nothing to lose
anymore I'm going to go out with the
bang
villager
villager can I actually convert one of
your
villagers what can I actually convert
one of your villagers yes you can you
can you can you can oh oh
oh I believe you can can you come to my
place
yeah maybe I should just like spend it
all on a monk
maybe maybe they can help me where's
your
oh oh oh okay okay hold on I'm going to
open the gate for
now I'm going I'm going here I'm going
here there conf Fort me conf Fort me can
you conf Fort me you going inside oh no
oh yeah yeah yeah okay here
here come
here convert he convert me
this
convert the
C convert convert can you oh
me did I did I which one is the monk
there's like too many
people where's the
monks oh oh there it is okay
okay can you convert
me oh I can't oh you
can't then how to make it possible
though oh no he's going to die never
mind okay mon don't don't don't
bro you're so smart
bro oh oh I Chang I changed my diplomacy
to normal try to confirm me
again oh
where are
you H convert
convert oh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry Sor sorry
sorry convert
convert convert
convert I can't
convert why moving
in no so I still
can't you still can't
yeah diplomacy change
it change it diplomacy to neutral
neutral you can you can you can you can
where you going bro I don't know it's
just oh okay
yeah we become light again we become
light again okay now now what what
should we do uh you can you can make
your your
um rebuild rebuild rebuild the the the
entire
team oh my God no no no wait wait you
don't want to do that diplomacy
diplomacy uh
Ally okay let's go let's go let's go do
I go back to my place oh you can you can
just stay here you can just stay here
too far um make sure make sure you're
still uh far from the this is rain is
still TR but rain is still there so you
can just make in here literally just
make in here that's make make here okay
what should I make what should I make um
you can try to make uh
maybe first at least the wall first and
then the Town Center
okay Town
Center yeah Town Center Town Center H
275 can I do
it
275 Town Center need to build more
houses inside the castle gate right yeah
okay
this this Castle make make another one
make another gate because this is too
small yeah make another gate it's too
small what the heck are you doing go in
there oh you locked the gate can you
open it oh oh
wait okay okay open it should be open
now it should be open now
okay okay okay
okay
okay okay you make a Town Center there
we are so
close
okay I think it's better that we we
clean this one I want to make them
other okay we should wall up
again yes yes yes yes yes
uh we shouldn't expand to like where we
were before
probably town center and then just build
uh make a lot of villagers right yes yes
yes yes
okay
man uh and also I think better we put we
put our
um
an I don't
SK let's put it in
here nothing
[Music]
think I think I'm going to make another
another
wall around
okay maybe I can cooperate with you and
then build a wall
together yeah yeah
yeah okay and then have more
villagers okay and then build a
wall can you actually build the wall
yeah I don't think
we can we can we can build it together
maybe maybe like
this I'm trying to make it that big by
we expand
it like
expain oh man okay
oh I canot make another
one
cell
why how big should we make
it not should I close it off now yeah
just close it off okay okay I I make I
make it close now I make it close now I
I can I can have it cuz I'm still
collecting gold
yeah okay that's okay oh okay you're
making
it close it
now okay I can close up the rest of
it really
yeah oh it's okay I'm I can I can you
can you can try to make a
castle okay build a castle can you make
a cast nearby yeah yeah yeah okay oh
your villager can uh your villager can
like stand up in the middle I cannot
make a castl in there you can make a
custl in there
please I can delete them yep
okay
okay okay it's
gone uh I just need uh Stones I need
more
Stones bye
okay and
then oh oh yeah yeah you're right okay
yeah I moved out of the way
okay thank you uh 650 I need
okay okay and then you guys
somehow rain is still staying
here she still stay in
there okay oh I got to build a mill uh
build a
mill
uh I don't know if I can build a mill uh
maybe
here can I build it
here oh actually I think you can expand
back to your place
no no no no no it's better not uh maybe
it's better
not and I'm going to close that other
one
off oh can you can you close the gap
yeah I
am I can I
canot thank you thank you uh this one
too I think this one need need to close
the gap in the back there
and okay oh dang
CL right now let's let's focusing on GA
all the woods yeah because uh and and
don't forget to make a
market market okay yeah yeah yeah so you
can sell the woods into a gold or
something to buy oh I still have the
Marketplace Marketplace is still
intact that's good that's good good it's
good where where's your Marketplace uh
it's like far away like in my
castle oh oh yeah yeah yeah hey ah okay
okay
nice yeah okay why is nobody building
trying
to build it bro
okay and
then don't have enough arery
raage Why Can't This thing
move oh my God it's
stuck can you can you help me like I
think my character's stuck next to like
in the
windmill wait where uh like the windmill
that I built it's uh it's blocked off oh
oh sorry sorry sorry no no no no it was
my fault okay uh maybe
bue uh if you have another
um nether Stone it would be nice to
double the
wall double the wall okay
yeah I can buy
more yeah um I'm still I'm selling
things
bye okay
bye and then you have your F
there
yeah okay thank
you and one in a windmill too as
well okay build a fortified wall and and
this two
also
okay
uh SCM
[Music]
share I think um how about this I'm
focusing on economy you're focusing on
the military
okay oh but you also you also need on
economy it's kind of
hard if you need something blocked off I
need to build a gate I forgot
ah oh uh it's better to give it all that
that's also
actually you don't have get you didn't
have you cannot make it
[Music]
uh can you build a gate I don't have any
money I I sent
you I send you Stones I'm Focus right
now okay if you need something just tell
me thank
you I'm going to donate everything for
you thank
you I'll also going to see if I
can also send this don't this is good oh
thank
you this Spa wall on
forward okay I'm building
truchet how many tret need
okay and then what else what else do you
want me to
build I think a lots of houses for the
military oh no I don't need that cuz
like I have a lot oh you still have lot
okay
yeah yeah then makes a lot of military
then uh from the
castle
okay where's the other
one you loitering around
bro okay uh uh build build build build
build 45 if you need something just tell
me yeah thank
you it's another
W
um
okay I'm going to research everything
right
now should I make another trapet I have
to right
now yeah
okay I also think you need to build
uh this Workshop bars kind of thing for
the armor H for
the military
uh-huh uh do you have
[Music]
food oh no if I if I make an army there
she's going to get notified never mind
that's
fine that's fine you can you can kill
this th p uh rainy th
P well before before you kill the Rainy
St you can just
um close the gate uh close the the wall
you know the wall that you've on your
old
village yeah close the wall I I can't do
that because there uh she has like uh
knights around
where uh like around the castle like she
has like Knights situated there so if I
go build like she's going to kill it and
it's going to get
notified oh I think it's better if you
close this way
like
so okay and then you build a
gate was thinking about 30 do you have
more stone or
no let me see it's okay I can just buy
it I bought it
and there I said you can oh bless
okay and
then I need to
make houses
okay and
then uh where are the others
okay and I'm going to focus on Military
R is out R rage just going somewhere I'm
going to build a watchtower do you think
that's a good idea or should I just
build a castle
Yeah uh castle spawn Castle is better
okay uh 650 I need 650
Stone uh and I can't buy it [\h__\h]
okay you
go give it to
you I can't buy
[Music]
it uh sell cell sell
cell hey and then you go inside there
and we need this SP house oh can you um
close this Gap
off thank you oh she's new she's new
rain now we
here oh
great get building
okay I don't know if we can do
it uh which which Village uh which
military that can
actually I think this
one I don't
know I
don't so so s so bye bye
bye the one that can um destroy the the
trees the trees do you know yeah do you
know the the military that can destroy
the trees there's a military that can
destroy the trees but I forgot what it
is
oh okay um I wonder what else I can
build uh uh I'm sorry can you can I
destroy this uh this wall so we can
actually this wall this this gate which
wall uh in the middle so you can you you
see that I right now I'm closing the
gate at the wall yeah and there's a in
the middle that have a
Gates like an open space Oh okay where
where where should
I uh the one that you you can see that
uh you were right now uh farming the
berries farming the berries uh yeah what
about it yeah you can you can destroy
that um so we can build a castle in
there oh
okay uh destroy this thing Al
together
yeah
okay okay I'm going to okay destroy
these I
think right like that right is someone
coming yeah yeah yeah that's it that's
it that's it that's it that's
it
uh
okay and
so oh K done K's done yeah ki's done K
dead been killed by fa I
guess wait if that's the case I can
restore my castle yes you
can but I guess be careful because uh
her villager is still there um pH I
still around kiras please
never mind rainy is
[Music]
lurking never
mind
okay uh can you build it never mind I
can probably get build a gate
uh build a
gate
[Music]
oh why cannot make a castle can you make
castle around here yeah yeah yeah uh
I'll I will send you
this I will send you this okay thank you
and uh where's my where's my villager at
by the
berries by the berries
Bud he it's not the
time B bik man uh Castle 650 I need 650
of
it
okay well that's gone God damn it
Castle 650 oh do you have 650 wood I
mean uh Stone uh I just need 100 more uh
or well
200 oh I don't have it uh I can just
send you
this oh God sell it I can't sell
it oh you cannot sell it yeah cuz she
destroyed my Marketplace send it to me
and I will I will buy
it uh send send what again sorry I'm
just panicking righty and send Stone uh
send uh the woods to me and I will buy
the
stone or you can also build Market uh in
the empty place in the back uh how do I
like send the the thing to you diplomacy
diplomacy okay uh diplomacy and then how
do I send it you need a market to pay
tribute oh no I don't have a
market shoot
just castle castle castle make the make
uh the the market then yeah okay
Market subject is Market
oh no they're coming they're coming
they're coming they're coming they're
coming they're coming they're coming
they're coming they're
coming defensive be on the defensive
don't get out can you can you I can lock
the gate no what are you
doing we just we just kill it we just
kill it okay
uh you're I am your T
butet oh no no no no no no don't close
the gate is fine don't don't close
theate it's no use to close the gate
just kill it
okay no not you guys it's elephant's pom
uh your your your Castle fixing your
Castle fix your Castle yeah I don't know
why they're not
buing oh my
God they're trying our fast that's fine
that's fine that's fine why AR they okay
oh no no no no no no no no no no
no wood wood wood wood wood wood
wood
oh oh God it's
over oh
God oh God
okay it's so over it's over I don't have
anymore
yeah no Archer no catapult
nothing we
just well at least at least we're
just at least we're standing yeah at
least we survived this far that's pretty
impressive right Sur this
far hey at least we weren't laugh
yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh God you know what this was
good we should probably
resign yeah that's fine it's fine you
don't want to
resign huh you don't want to resign
how oh you can just like go to the main
menu and
resign what
where just go to the main menu it's on
the upper
right oh yeah yeah yeah okay but we will
lose the score just let him be just let
him kill him okay okay we will lose the
score damn this this water elephant is
crazy oh my
God
man ah
just do what we can I didn't know I
don't know what we
can bro
yeah apparently we don't lose the
score
yeah we should resign the Great Wall is
gone we did good
yeah h
ah H how come you're not you're not
going strike out already CNY oh you said
don't
resign
oh can I resign I don't know can
we okay okay let's let's let's resign
let's
resign wait oh yeah this
one resign
oh
wait
okay oh man that was cool that was cool
that was
cool that was
cool that was nice damn
GG g g damn you're military economy oh
my God FAA is really
great yeah she was building she was
building building yeah building is too
strong the mother of
nature too strong that was really
nice nice I enjoy that yeah that was fun
I was I was so scared at first like here
I put Castle everywhere yeah I want a
castle yo I was minding my own business
was like yo yo yo yo Raina can you send
some help I'm going to attack Cronin I'm
like what dude I was minding my own
business I was minding my own business
too sound like everyone was minding
their own
business damn Kiara was out for
blind I mean I was just trying to get
the game the ball
rolling I guess so yeah before someone
rolls it on me yeah I guess otherwise
you know people would be just like build
like me like me
peace well me and Ana I feel like we're
playing like a farming simulator me that
was me that was me before Kiara was like
yo help me out I'm like huh what oh yeah
actually the reason I attacked crony was
because she was building the wonderand
and I you know when you build a wonder
you taret for
everybody well she building the yeah she
was building a Wonder yeah and auto win
if you keep it for a very long time and
as we see this game was going to go on
for a long time so the Wonder could have
won yeah that would have been a good
Strat fa was about to attack but then I
was like if they're fighting each other
then let them
be I just did elephant strategy just
build a million elephants and hope for
the
best wait can we see the uh I think MAA
has to maybe somebody has to press
something so we can see the the the
stats or something oh I left the stat
already here um oh sorry I don't care is
it quit current game yeah do you do you
click turn to map oh there we go
nice wait where do you see it oh my
Society my
Society do Society I clicked return to
map a lot
a
[Music]
lot
yeah cool Co cool cool cool cool a very
nice oh when come back to economy I sent
a lot to
crony t t trading I had 11 castles it
was good it was good we we were like
pulling brains yay oh
no very cool o our numbers are actually
not bad yeah nice food collected
yummy wood collected very
cool very nice if you look at timeline
you see like the graph of how things are
changing ooh
oh I just
see oh my god wow fa just like going up
yeah the tape rning all about the
elephants
yeah let me see I want to see not
attacking first was a good strategy
though cuz like we could focus on yeah
cuz we were just chilling at the
start M I was like if if they're
fighting each other then let them
be yeah I mean why not that's probably
what you should do true true but
sometimes the intrusive
thoughts oh yeah I tell them
to the intrusive thoughts are just yeah
I
understand in my chat people say like
nobody stands in that
way what whatever we do natur Alice
win uh well normally I would have liked
to play defensive too but I don't know I
had to kill the Wonder and then from the
Wonder everything was just like rolling
and I it just happened yeah feel like
aggression is good it add the spice you
know I think I underestimated you guys
honestly I thought maybe you guys didn't
practice enough so maybe you guys
wouldn't know what a wonder is
out
yo guys how do I build the
barck when I was constantly asking yeah
I don't remember almost a single thing
how do I do this how do I do that why
are people
unemployed if if I want to ask for
rematch again would you want to do it
but not now
yeah another time rematch yeah another
time will be nice yeah um maybe this
time is uh we we make it pretty pretty
easy because we have a cheating seit in
in our live chat but the next time how
about no cheating seit on yet oh no CH
yeah pleas sure if you can really
control that and we could we could
randomize the sifts so that everybody
gets something
unexpected it's not months from now cuz
by then I'll I'd forget about the game
already we it just date immediately
before we forgot how to play again
[Music]
yeah what I'm
saying
M maybe after this I will put another
date
yeah this this seems fun like like I I'm
pretty I think I underestimate a lot of
you guys yeah oh my God that is crazy
need to game I was scared of you MAA I
was so scared of you no I I told you I'm
not really good at this game you didn't
believe me just because I L game doesn't
mean that I'm good at it no no you you
are good no no you are good it's just
that you were trying to save me and I'm
sorry I think everyone need a practice
them after
all
no but yeah thank you so much everyone
for playing this game with me uh it's
been fun thank you for
organizing I'm glad it happened
finally it was super fun thank you thank
you it's been we almost doing this like
for like two hours actually yeah oh
wow that was just like I expected the
game is going to be two
hours perfect perfect timing yeah well
um for this one actually I have a lot of
uh strategy game um oh uh AG of Empire
is like one of them while the others uh
there is another game called
Starcraft you guys interested on
Starcraft it's another building game
another start game if you guys
interested I would love to make another
one I'll try it yeah I'd love to but I
need to learn about the game I learn
yeah
yeah more more learning more learning
go my brain is going to
explode what it is what it is thank you
so much
um you guys have any uh
maybe information for the
viewers I don't know I'm good oh no no I
just want to say thank you thank you for
being a great
teammate thank
you bring out the aggressor in
me actually working good together yeah
next time I won't build the Wonder I I
should not have
underestimated you you need to build a
wonder you just have to figure out when
you're building the Wonder is your
military already finished
also when I arrived you only had one
person working on the Wonder but the
Wonder takes like so much more time than
other buildings you need like 20 people
at once yeah and it's you need a lot of
people and make sure that uh your
military is ready to you know M
take the Wonder I wanted to build one
too someday someday someday someday
someday wow that's all everyone thank
you so much I'm going to end the stream
then yeah thank you so much for playing
this G let's play again
byebye
by
[Music]
bye-bye so thank you everyone for
watching
uh
[Music]
yeah I'll just do better next time I
should just practice more
[Music]
actually but thank you for
watching I stayed up until 5:00
[Music]
a.m. but yeah it was a really great
introduction to Age of Empires and I had
a lot of
[Music]
fun so thank you
good night good night everyonei
[Music]