thank you
[Music]
foreign
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
hello everyone
hello
hello hello
I believe I believe in real life I
believe
I believe we are as a matter of fact
hello everyone hello
[Music]
is hear us okay
we're moving today we are in motion
officially wow
the piece on the bottom left oh yeah
that's right yeah aren't you supposed to
show it the whole way through
all right yeah
[Music]
is that someone in a you know Santa
costume oh boy the perfect the perfect
outfit it would seem
perfect the perfect costume for a dear
friend
yeah we have um one piece of the puzzle
you guys we have the special Halloween
jigsaw puzzle uh
Extravaganza so you guys gotta tune in
to everyone's streams this week if you
want to get all the pieces to the puzzle
and finish it
oh yeah the prize is uh Fame and Glory
yeah
bragging rice
exactly exactly so I guess we should go
ahead and
jump right into it hello everyone my
name is Clive Mori uh first gen live
English myth
um I'm the first Apprentice the Grim
Reaper I do music I stream sometimes I
attempt video games and I attempt being
a DM for a game called world of Darkness
that is really just kind of like Cali's
world of Darkness where it and then it's
very
um well it's become something all right
it's very comedic it's got a little
comedic taste to it
um but nonetheless an intriguing story I
hope that you will enjoy
um with that being said someone else
want to do an introduction
oh we're doing introduction to yourself
[Music]
okay yeah um let's see next up Kiara
oh hello I'm talking to Canada from Hall
of English I'm a phoenix part-time
Warrior and today I was Alice
good game
thank you for watching
[Music]
everyone hello uh shrimps I'm gonna say
Shrek for some reason
you know introduce yourself no way
you're introduce yourself okay let's go
hello I am Nino my enemies Apollo
English Smith
um
I like cocktail streams they're yummy
delicious
[Music]
see a lot of them in the chat today as
long as they're like cleaned be careful
I'm hungry
your taco eats shrimp normally
oh thanks
yeah I would say the taco probably
definitely don't go for chicken meat or
cow meat or pig meat because that's a
Buffalo Wild
that was first for everything
diets can constitute a bird shrimp
Lobster Shark clam and fish
Birds that's what it says when I Googled
it words that fell down dead onto the
ocean or what or can they like fish for
them
chicken I eat chicken
have you ever seen those videos of
horses eating the little baby chicks and
Nations when you cozy in the bed for
some nighttime YouTube
never mind I swear to God
yes
[Music]
now I'm gonna make it go down again
I love it
thank you
one
what is happening what happened
[Laughter]
my healing all the rides over there
around me
I had too many mushrooms don't walk
towards the lights
no this is fine I'm fine
chromatic aberration and whatnot yeah
it's just just you getting into
character of water I can't catch up
let's see a new members email I'm shiny
I was a shiny person
intriguing wow what an incredible oh
what it would have seen what a sight
that was Watson you wanna You Wanna Give
Your your name and occupation oh yes uh
I'm Amelia Watson I'm a detective Please
Don't Steal My identity
um and how do I what was the question
how do we feel about shrimp I like fried
shrimp um I think I like crabs better
but fried shrimp is pretty good
oh nice coconut
could be interesting
coconuts do you guys like one of those
restaurants where they just like dump a
whole bunch of seafood onto the table
and he's like yes
seafood boil yeah it's just a whole fish
with the head and the eye looking at you
yeah no yeah I think that's a different
different place you know
and claim things you put on the table
you see food eat food yeah yes
delicious up north they call them
clambakes I think
it's good stuff
yummy I guess I'm the only one in Hollow
myth who doesn't really like seafood huh
I like sashimi
about it
hey speaking of fish
you gotta introduce yourself
introduce yourself okay gargoyle
[Music]
my name is
the fish
is shark a fish
technically
um uh Google
oh no what's the animal kingdom what is
the Shark part of an end hey Google
what'd you say
nothing
um Google says sharks are fish
well I would hope so
let me smell on her okay whoa yeah
that's the fish yep
[Laughter]
fish fish that is fresh and smells sweet
it's true yeah yeah I mean you smell
like fish fresh
fish
today
we're washing your hoodie
yes just checking in
this chicken yes
okay I had no doubt I had no doubt in my
mind
yes you did that's fine though
we've just said we've had some
complaints in the past about about you
know unwashed unwashed hoodies smell
around here
I haven't seen y'all challenging clothes
either around here so I don't want to
hear it I own 50 of the same outfits I
can change everything in a in a second
all right don't brag now oh nice your
hat Looking Good
Very Fresh all right it smells I'm ready
to go oh boy oh
thank God that was horrifying you're
right
hey Cena
oh man don't worry about it
um speaking of horrifying things that
we've seen and we'll continue to see
we're gonna play a game today that is a
continuation of the last session now I
realized
um that actually not sleeping through
the night instead instead of getting two
hours of sleep is much better yes so I'm
actually completely awake right now if I
had slept
um we'd be in big trouble but we're
feeling really groggy yeah my body may
be in a bit of pain but that's okay
because I'm going to sleep after this so
let's uh let's make it let's make it a
session to remember ladies
um
oh air horns yeah so I'm gonna do a
quick recap I'm on my own
I have uh I have a strategy for today
already here
yeah cool I'm not gonna tell you yes why
that's the intro real quick because I
got to pull up some guides real quick
you guys we do have some guides that
we've been we've been using for things
like for example combat
Etc
um if you guys want to pull those up
they are pretty helpful I have it open
heck yeah nice and prepared love to see
it all right just making sure making
sure
um
breaking point and just like that we're
back in the mix I mean at least that's
one of them I don't know if that's the
one she wanted us to pull up yeah
there's there's two there's a basic
combat guide and then an experience
guide
um so yeah like yeah
um yeah all right now that we've got
those up I'm gonna do the recap here we
go
there we go
there it goes there's the darkness
all right
so
for our myth Breakers last time last
last time on my Breakers last time on
myth Breakers can't use Reverb because
you guys won't hear me last time on myth
Breakers
a fun carnival in the sun took a turn
for the ghostly and our crew find
themselves in Between Worlds somewhere
unfamiliar and ghoulish with ghosty
energy ever evolving around them and new
attractions proving frightful and
confusing the team must figure out how
to reverse this curse and bring the
carnival back to Humanity's Shores the
key to the riddle surely lies within the
attractions that litter the fairgrounds
but what is the answer how can they find
it they'll need teamwork collaboration
at a stroke of good luck to escape and
quote unquote turn the tides
ladies I hope you're ready for today
[Music]
yes if you recall correctly last time we
showed up to this Carnival and we were
experiencing an intriguing uh rap
question mark concert
um and things got a little wild and now
you guys are here in this in between
spooky Carnival world that's in another
dimension and you guys had just finished
getting uh shot out of a castle that
seems to be full of portals
oh that's right
with waffles still chilling in the door
frame
not the door frame the window the window
frame was just chilling up there the
rest of the gang took some bludgeoning
damage there sprawled out on the ground
but now you've gotten the valuable piece
of information that this Castle is a
castle full of portals
and there's something else interesting
about this this Castle here it seems to
be full of dark spooky energy it's
almost vibrating with it and the ghosts
around it
uh seemed to be very active
not only that but once you guys fly out
of the portal you realize that now there
are even more ghosts coming out from
inside the castle deep from within the
depths from within the pocket dimension
in which all of the portals exist
yes ghosts indeed specters if you will
ghostly figures you can't see much about
them they're not very distinct they're
like floating entities
coming out from within the castle
ghost ghosts yeah
well what would you like to do
is it like a distraction we're just like
all right that's nice well time to get
back to the real world oh you can you
can keep watching them to see what they
do if you'd like touch the ghost you
want to touch the ghost all right the
ectoplasm sure so you touch the ghost
wasato
um
and the ghost begins to vary one of the
ghosts one of the entities begins to
very slowly
um pull on your arm
huh
that's right and begins to try and um
haul you away
it's not it's not a very wholehearted
pull
but the ghost is definitely trying to
pull you watoto
make a perception check uh ladies
the whole perception to get started with
this Castle situation that I can't show
on the screen because the castle I chose
we have to be careful
[Laughter]
Charles entertainment cheese
um
your perception is 70 10.
what are the
thingies for uh perception resolve plus
composure
oh [\h__\h] I knew it was 40 10. ignore mine
it's okay
all right now what please type your
successes thank you
uh
right
okie dokie oh all right all right all
right all right can I roll that again
you do wait what five
oh wait I rolled one wrong but whatever
four is good anyway okay
I'm seeing into the future with that one
[Music]
two looks like two successes all right
so so with what we have here uh wat to
tell you first of all uh don't really
perceive much aside from this entity is
pulling your arm and you don't know
where it wants to go with you but it
wants to go somewhere
um that's about all you can tell wait
Kelly one second I think you set
yourself in composure which is fine
because that would be more for me but
usually I think it was always wits and
composure oh which not resolved I think
but results is fine for me because then
it's five not free for me long
ah all right excuse me guys
withstand composure then I did it
correctly okay
it was
it's the last time GM brain is gonna
explode on stream you'll see
are you seeing these mad roles
wow
all right I'll take it bad
pretty Big W there
all right
all right all right
good good good so it turned out to be
for the better so what to tell as I
mentioned before
um you can't really there's not much
that you can tell aside from this this
entity is pulling you somewhere
um and as for as for you
um Scout you make
um you make an interesting uh notation
here uh you note in particular the other
two that got fours do not note this only
you you note that this ghost in
particular
um is beginning to pull wathato uh
towards the water
like out the window then uh pretty close
to the castle actually the beach kind of
turns into water pretty close by
doesn't what Toto is up in a window
right so it's attempting to pull water
out of the window yeah yeah precisely
like down onto the ground
and down into the down into the water
the white turtle fall out of the window
or is he still in the window no the go
the ghost has managed to pull him out
okay
yeah the ghost is pretty full hard
though no no he's been floating it is a
ghost holding him after all
okay gently to the ground I don't want
to go into the water that sounds scary
can you swim
oh good question
and here's what the here's what you two
see Tiara and um and you'll
you guys hear distant screams uh
and off in the distance
you can see the image of what appears to
be ghosts pulling various people away
into the darkness
can I shine my flashlight onto the ghost
sure
go for it you shine your flashlight
that's that that's I'll give that to you
you shine your flashlight at a ghost and
uh it moves away
oh it doesn't hurt the ghost right the
ghost still seems adamant on going after
someone but it moves away
is still going towards the water
no the other ghostly on your scattered
but
what would you like to do
struggle so you struggle all right I'm
gonna have you go ahead and roll a
little strength and Athletics rule for
me while to start to wiggle wiggle your
way out of this one
I wanna help okay what would you like to
do tiara
I wonder while she's struggling or
watoto's struggling I want to run over
and do the same thing with the with the
with the flashlight all right gotcha
let's see
okay was it says struggle
and ghosts strength to pull you away
oh wow okay
[Laughter]
you begin to kind of you know bust a
move on this ghost here that's trying to
drag you towards the water and you just
narrowly manage to wiggle out and escape
from the ghost's grasp just in time to
fall on the sand right where the water
is beginning to kind of
turn into a smoky milky color around the
sand you got a bad feeling about this
water though it doesn't look especially
tasty or enjoyable kind of reminds you
of the way the ghosts exactly
[Music]
yeah and the ghost uh turns around
slowly and begins to come back towards
uata
um I think I have a lighter of
flashlight so can I use that to
all right you pull out a flashlight
throw it up at The Ghost and the ghost
just kind of backs away but you can tell
that as in totally given up on you yet
it's just kind of retreating for now
these ghosts while they aren't
aggressive they are persistent and they
will continue to look for targets around
here and drag them drag them off into
the graveyard
especially those who are weaker as well
as it seems that um many of the other
customers of the carnival do not quite
have the resolve to wiggle in the same
way that that you did wasato you got to
be it was me really yeah it was really
cute okay
it was Kiara
oh yeah seriously it might have got cut
out
um so with that being said you guys are
all kind of chilling out of this weird
spooky castle that is kind of rumbling a
bit
um full of portals ghosts are coming out
of it now it's almost like a ghost
machine of sorts
oh so we have to blow it up yes
that is an option
it's whatever you guys want to do
I don't really know like you must put
your heads together
okay let's put our heads together yeah
it's a castle with various portals
and ghosts coming out of it
and we maybe there's a button that opens
the portals or like a lever or like a
schedule that somebody made on the floor
okay and then we could just scuff it up
and then it'll stop all right that's a
good idea would you like
oh
oh perfect that's an idea
reverse the portals all right
as if a ghosts are coming out what if
keep going with that
so would you guys like the sexy area
yes yeah all right what parts of the
area would you like to inspect in
particular
[Music]
well then didn't we go
I don't remember who we were inside
already I was like somebody went inside
and it was empty pretty much
[Music]
you went through the back door
yeah
did we try going for the front door
before
oh no
[Music]
um
see when you put your heads together
guys you can figure it out y'all
suddenly start I thought putting your
heads together literally putting heads
together yeah yeah
Laura
um should we try going back in again
through the front door another front
door
you guys open the front door
oh okay okay
no locks or anything it just opens but
it's the same situation as it was with
the back see it's still pitch black
inside and there are still specters
coming out some of them ignore you some
of them tug at your clothes a bit you
feel like you don't have a ton of time
to get this done but uh could I ask one
of the ghosts a question would you like
to try communicating with the with the
world league
all right for you to do this properly I
mean I do that because of my curiosity
oh okay so in a way that it it might be
kind of dangerous I see it could be
dangerous maybe he possesses me I don't
know okay well if you'd like to if you
would like to form a conversation with
the other worldly I'm going to need you
to roll for me
um let's see
your
your presence and a cult
[Music]
does anybody have a cult no I do
I have two points in a cult
I move the mission over to amen
do you want to talk to the ghost I feel
like you have a better connection with
them
the mushroom helps yes okay you're on a
spiritual level of them
[Music]
You're Gonna Roll your presents plus a
cult
Ure
rules
um
do we recognize any of these specters
these ghosts do they resemble anybody
that we might recognize like
would you like to be right would you
like to try and find out
okay all right but I I also since uh
failed can I try talking after all I
don't have a sure
all right but make sure that you take
away minus two from the right oh
this is it's an unskilled role
um well would you like to give me a epic
fail here would you like well you don't
need well you would need to do a what
you need to roll one d10 and you need to
accept if it's a critical fail if you
would like
success
does it mean I'm getting an epic fail or
not an epic no you succeed
okay all right with one success that is
just enough
um
you begin speaking to the ghost what do
you say to the ghost
um
[Music]
I didn't think that far so
um in the meantime in the meantime
um Scout
um when you try and like focus in to see
if you recognize these specters they go
from having no form to when you focus on
their faces they start to look like
people
they start to have faces when you like
look very closely and focus in on them
they look to be from various time
periods
there's no real consistency they're just
dead okay
[Music]
I'm wondering if it's like one of them
old-timey ghost movies that I've seen
where there's dimensions and the ghosts
travel in between different timelines
and dimensions and and we are we are at
the source of the dimensions right now
ladies I think so if we we must be
careful because if we mess something up
we can mess something up on the outside
you know like baby I've never been born
or or I never crashed pause Truck Yeah
yeah although if you if you did do that
though maybe you wouldn't be here but
stuck in the Brash candy cute that's
right you're still wearing that costume
that's right Kiara it's time for you to
to be how many questions uh may I ask um
I'd say just go ahead and start talking
and see what happens oh okay uh hello
ghost my name is takanasikiana it's very
nice to meet you Adam holy [\h__\h]
this is the dimensional shift that Scout
was talking Tiana and my name is
um I I would like to ask you why are you
here and where did you come from
you here what is this place
and at first it sounds like music but
then if you listen closely you begin to
hear Whispers
um on on the air and you can verily
verily very barely verily
here what sounds to be a wispy voice
saying to you
here
anywhere
we come from everywhere and nowhere at
once but one thing is for sure
the engine must keep turning
must keep turning the engine oh that's
your ghost
that's my last question
here there anywhere and nowhere
she says that the engine is here there
everywhere and nowhere can you rephrase
the question
to the engine no door no door
no door no door the engine is a password
it is everywhere it is this could you
show us the way it goes
hey ghosty I think we're kind of short
on time could you give us I don't know
shortcut no [\h__\h] you
say
no it's no good at unfortunately
I didn't get much out of this yes but
but if you do if you do look over what
you had what you have
right
uh
what what can you discern what did you
get from the conversation
there is an engine where did the ghost
say it was
here there everywhere and nowhere yes
and then after that
on the fairgrounds
oh I didn't hear that I don't know if
this is thanks for nothing Discord
that's cool
um yes but that's outside right yeah the
fairgrounds are the engine and the
engine is turning in One Direction
[Music]
oh yeah
like a merry go round that also goes one
minute that's right
you did you stopped it and it started
running the opposite way
oh oh
God remember
okay
[Music]
let's walk back outside I guess all
right
away from the beach in a more Central
area where you can more fully see the
castle and then the fairgrounds as a
whole spread out before you and at this
point you can see
um it does almost if you look at the
ground the ground the ground very
vaguely seems to have veins running
through it all in one direction yes
that leads further into the abyss
further into what you can only assume is
the underworld and everything seems to
be flowing and turning in that direction
except for the merry-go-round
well then we just gotta reverse it you
do every single thing we have to maybe I
mean I try it
let's do it the ghosts are starting to
really like that bad
people yeah
right it is easy to stop them there's
not an immediate threat to them right
now yeah there's only one thing that has
been stopped so far
right
Carousel yeah exactly so you have this
Aura from them that they aren't exactly
concerned with what you're doing right
now
um
if maybe if we were to stop the little
Ferris wheel it gets even worse or so
yeah it's a good that's a good that's a
good conjecture so like once we start
reversing things we better hurry up
before they come in okay let's search
over the control panel for the ferris
wheel there's got to be some sort of
operator okay all right sounds good more
than mystical eyeballs that's right
that's right
all the eyeballs yeah yeah
are there eyeballs on the ferris wheel
as well can we do perception sure you'll
need to walk over the ferris wheel first
though okay walk over all right you guys
walk on over to that Ferris wheel and on
the way there you actually do manage to
catch a glimpse of those two jokers from
before kind of tripping over themselves
um and causing a bit of a Ruckus
spraying soda everywhere and just uh
being generally a nuisance
um the linging berry
and uh they begin to spray soda
um in the direction of the ghosts which
the ghosts do not like very much oh yeah
the ghosts are more just kind of like
annoyed by it though
hmm yeah take this ghost oh how you like
this
uh the ghosts are not super angry but
they are kind of like
a little ticked off
you know for the most part they just
kind of drift away but um
but they're sure who the real enemies
anymore right now
yeah they are causing a bit of a
commotion thirsty
oh
thirsty
maybe we'll find something to drink at
the control panel of that Ferris wheel
if you don't want to ask for some some
tasty soda
not especially
it kind of looks a little sketchy it's a
good call
maybe I don't know could that one Make
Me Dance isn't that the drink that made
me dance I did
well yeah I did some did some strange
things but who could say how effective
it is now either way you guys continue
on your way towards the ferris wheel and
actually manage to not be uh really like
paid attention to by these Jokers who
are seemingly also getting a bit more
rambunctious
um and you make your way over to the
ferris wheel
now everyone roll perception for me once
you arrive at the ferris wheel that
seems to be continually turning
forward in the same direction and it
doesn't seem as though it's showing any
signs of stopping
but it is going at a bit of a slow pace
I'm doing perception yes indeed
okay
that's not very good perception but good
enough for all of us
all right now go ahead and type your
successes for me
what if we made it spin real fast
oh like a Vortex that would be
interesting
everything's gonna fly off hey got into
space
all right make a
never mind yeah
what what do you want to make
no no you can make anything in this game
you can make a rocket right now but it
would be very tough
um all right so here's what you guys get
um Tiara watoto and Scout when you three
glance at this Ferris wheel you see the
the typical demonic [\h__\h] but there's
something especially
conniving and evil about this Ferris
wheel and you can't quite put your
finger on it
um
but you kind of I don't know you you get
you get this feeling when you look at it
it's like a sick strange feeling of
wanting to ride it
oh it compels you in a sense to get on
it
I think we must resist
and as for you you'll you see that the
ferris wheel is actually being operated
by someone
oh very large being
a very large ghost who looks
quite um unfriendly
did you say a ghost who looks quite
unfriendly yes unfriendly unfriendly big
ghosts unfriendly looks a bit like a
bouncer that you might find out front of
a club except
a bit more clownish
clown like
I think we should if he's being if we
all at the same time use our flashlights
at him won't he move away and stop
operating
vacuum
vacuum cleaner no no okay
you want to make a vacuum right now
there must be a Janitor's Closet yes oh
that's a good idea
It's gotta be
a bathroom or something
all right sounds good would you like to
search for One
yes okay all right let's see
let's see Ina did I give you your
perception check though that's right
what true did I tell you what you saw
you know yeah I saw the big big guy
sorry I have no short-term memory anyway
so you guys wanted to search for a
vacuum okay great would someone like to
do uh an investigation and wits check
either that or maybe the parts for one
because I have I can make stuff okay I
have two investigations sure all right
an investigative Prodigy Merit all right
[Music]
I swear to God I wrote what all the
merits did
I
okay
I have it all saved in a document I just
have to pull it up
oh okay oh wait I'm gonna make a great
big soul sucking machine but these
ghosties
um blend them all up in the one
ectoplasmic smoothie just like the
movies oh wow that was ghostbusting
movies that's yummy uh how many dots do
you have
uh two two gotcha all right now go ahead
and do your roll for me
investigation in wits okay let's go
detective right sounds good all right so
you're trying to uncover Clues right now
so you're kind of looking around for
some kind of main building or something
like that and you see obviously there's
you know like a little ticket booth
there is the the
um Ferris wheel being in operation and
there is a little Shack behind uh
however it is locked
it needs some kind of key
um
yeah
you could do something like that the
pains the pins in my eyes
[Music]
you did establish you had a couple of
them oh wait they are used questions
um the weapons we could take were we
limited to what we could take
like at the start to the fair yes what
was that oh okay because you can't kind
of just stroll in there with a big
sniper rifle on your back kind of thing
wow
um indeed but uh what's it so what you
also notice is that there is someone
working at the ticket counter and you
can see behind them there is something
that looks like it would hold passes or
maybe key Rings or something like that
you can't tell precisely but that looks
as though that that's a lead for you
that's a clue that you have
oh okay yeah so you have a couple
options here for how you can finesse
this but it's up to you
maybe we can distract the ticket guy and
steal the key uh I have the pickpocket
skill
um
all right it is a ticket guy a ghost as
well or a normal guy ah the ticket guy
is also a ghost guy but looks a lot less
threatening
huh I think we should just try and pick
the lock okay
what do you need what's the what you
need for picking a lock I mean which
which thingies dexterity and larceny
does anyone have lost lives in need
one of my hairpins
all right that's one hair picture oh two
okay oh you can have two as many as you
want all right we gotta Mark that off
the sheet though
yeah I'll buy new ones when I get back
home okay
um
now I have six airplanes left all right
now what's the toe let's give it a try
was that your roll okay one all right
one more success yeah gotcha all right
with one success you managed to do it
and the lock does kind of Break
um however you may have
um caught the attention of someone
you can't tell who
but you just feel that someone's
watching you
dude
man I ain't scared of these things just
a bunches
ain't afraid of no ghosts
yeah
I'm sure we can
we can probably figure out how to deal
with them once just blow on them
yeah a kick okay doors open you have a
broom
and you have a couple pieces of metal
oh
a large bag a large sack for potatoes
and it looks like you've got the parts
to make a vacuum weirdly enough all
right here all right let's go Scout
if you'd like to give it a shot I want
from you I'm gonna
yep crafts the questions
one I'll make it work I also I have
weapon creation does a vacuum count as a
weapon in this circumstance if you're
planning to use it as a weapon then yes
thank you all right
last one doesn't look like a weapon door
so you can bring it everywhere exactly
people just I look like I work here or
maybe bring a vacuum cleaner me lady
I'm here to clean up after the kitties
all right here to to vacuum the the
ocean sand right the defense all right
one success you start working on that
vacuum and you're about halfway there
before you guys all hear some footsteps
walking towards you you're gonna need to
do another successful roll Scott if you
want to finish this vacuum but in the
meantime someone seems to be approaching
okay can I help Scout make it
I'm channeling I want to try to distract
the whoever is coming oh right sounds
good so you would like to assist
I will wait in the corner to pounce
all right don't you ever question the
talent of Scouts
belt buckle just made a vacuum out of
stuff we found in a storage room
[Music]
all right so you now have uh this vacuum
thing
and um you are being approached
you are being approached by
oh it looks like that big guy from
before
I was handling the lever
yeah he approaches you with crossed arms
and looks directly at you with pitch
black eyes
Try It Out Try It Out wanna say hello my
little sucky friend let's go to it
all right
you um
[Music]
I mean it is homemade so you can't be
perfect she works
she's gonna smack around a little bit
you turn on the vacuum you you click on
and then you realize you haven't plugged
it in
I got three successes ma'am do I really
need to plug this in or is it working
off my pure
[Music]
by the corner and grabs the cord and
plugs it in all right quick thinking
quick thinking quick suddenly the vacuum
turns on now I'm gonna need you to use
this as a weapon though so I want you to
go ahead and roll
your weaponry
plus right
Plus in this case
uh let's see strength this is a big boy
you're sucking into this vacuum
does a vacuum count as an aggressive
light weapon
yes I would say so it's made with a
second potato all right
I have aggressive light Weaponry as
skill all right let's give it a shot
sorry I'm about to show you the power of
belt buckle
right
okay all right and my manual to resist
can't resist this
oh okay maybe you can resist this I
would prefer if you didn't
all right
um it is a it is a con it is a contested
role in this case
um
you guys are looking now
can I give it a ride uh shining the
flashlight at the ghost to make him oh
yeah well I cannot blind it sure towards
that yeah you can Shine Your flashlights
I turned it to Super suck and now it
yeah
all right
you guys turn on to Wombo
you guys Shine Your flashlights on this
being
um who is starting to look rather
annoyed at you guys
um all at the same time your flashlight
power combined it doesn't seem to affect
this guy though this guy's a little
different
um you're gonna need to roll another
sucking roll Scout if you really want to
get rid of this dude
the vacuum is beginning to shake as
though it wants to break
you get a feeling this is the last this
is the last chance you have
battling in in German it's called Stout
Saga oh oh I think it's a good word
I have a question yes oh no a blow dart
on the ghost will it pass through him
you give it a shirt wait can we yeah can
we physically touch the ghost like
would you like to try
like I wanna I wanna like maybe move
behind him and kick him would you like
to trace the fact yes
all right
you go behind him and you kick him he
has also just escaped from the vacuum
and the vacuum turns off oh
and this guy's not very happy you
attempt to kick him you'll
yes all right
I want you to go ahead and roll
Athletics and strength for me
um
supposed to work he worked in the movies
Why didn't it work now
I mean maybe maybe impact
hell uh
he'll turn on the vacuum again I don't
know
in conjunction with that can I use a
blow dart on him sure go ahead and use a
Blue Dart
um
go ahead and roll to fire off your blow
dart what to tell I want you to use in
this case dexterity
and um Weaponry Works a little different
than a firearm so dexterity and weaponry
in this case
um as for you
um you'll you go ahead and you kick
um and this is a ghost
so your kick goes through the ghost
a ghost you know logical
it is logical but that was of the
ghost's will the ghost wanted this
wanted to grab was so once it's a
manifest itself to not be passed through
but in this case
um this ghost not really interested in
being kicked uh your kick thankfully it
was a good kick it wasn't a shitty one
it doesn't hurt anybody but you
definitely do go through the ghost and
um
your Dart misses
um did it hit fuel
in the shoulder
oh
you're feeling sleepy now total
um it just yeah it just makes you sleepy
right yeah this makes you sleepy you'll
you're going night night for a little
bit
just for a little bit yeah that can sink
to your knees
oh dear and fall forward into the ground
now at this point the big ghost actually
doesn't seem to want to fight you
but rather steps back
and welcomes you to the ferris wheel and
when he does this when he does this you
feel compelled I'm going to need all of
you to roll your resolve plus composure
I'm asleep you're okay you don't have to
you're okay
[Music]
you'll be asleep
not today sir all right type your
successes please
ah
oh
hey
oh come on now Scout
Scout and what to tell you guys barely
managed to
not really feel like you need to go on
the ferris wheel
tiara on the other hand you're so
enthralled by this kind stranger who
really could have stomped on your head
right there welcoming you to the ferris
wheel and you can't help but want to
give it a little ride looks kind of fun
so you get on the ferris wheel you walk
up to that Ferris wheel and you get on
it birthday
I'll go with you
what instead of going
to pull my arm
and force me to stay
wink wink I can't wait
okay I'll drag uh I'll try to stop Tiara
from getting on all right I want a
straight
strength roll from you
um Watson so and I want a straight
strength roll from tiara
I better help
wait is that zero successes from uh yeah
oh
yay all right so Scouts
when do I wake up
Scout pulls you back you're still
sleeping you'll you're slowly coming too
very slowly but surely
what
[Music]
but I already pulled you back so we're
good yeah okay
you are back but that's not enough for
the guy that's running the ferris wheel
he doesn't like that see he's gonna try
and do it again
oh in fact this time maybe we just
he's gonna really really use some little
mind manipulation on me here maybe we
should maybe we should leave the tiara
with the blow dart too
all right roll resolve composure tiara
yes
[Music]
well
um
can I use
one willpower to add to that sure if
you'd like
how many dices does that add again three
you gotta mark it off your sheet
okay do those Come Those come back right
after like chilling indeed
okay
[Music]
okay why am I lagging so much
not today it wasn't even necessary but
okay four four successes nice all right
with four successes you do have the
mental fortitude to not get on the
ferris wheel you'll however does need to
roll now that you've awoken oh okay what
was it again really want someone oh not
me the ghost does all right let's see go
ahead and roll your resolve plus
composure
I'll resolve composure uh
thick oh God
okay I mean oh
all right another contester roll this
guy's uh getting upset that you guys
aren't all trying to get on the ferris
wheel
so he goes and stands by the lever and
Crosses his arms and refuses to leave
oh why don't we just look for that
eyeball again
oh can uh I'll sneak off and go to the
control panel since empty now and I'll
try to stop it and reverse it I mean it
isn't necessarily empty right now my man
went back to uh stand at the lever to
make sure you guys don't touch it
because you're not getting on his ferris
wheel
you're gonna have to find another way to
take them down
we have to take down this guy or sir oh
you can think of him there's got to be
like a work yeah
let's find the gears and put a stick in
it oh
this is so simple I like it all right I
have the shovel
oh shovel strong I might have a shovel
actually I might not
just check the sheets did you bring it
I'll say I don't think I have a shovel
that's I don't have a shovel I take it
back well would you like this maybe is
there another object that you saw wasn't
there something in the shed that's right
like there was a broom
yeah take that all right so you guys
acquired the broom now what would you
choose to do in this situation the
ferris wheel continues turning
I'll stick it in uh find the gears and
stick it in
all right
stop someone
you have to wait it's a strong broom
all right gotta believe
you guys want to um go find the gears
yes
yeah I need an investigation in which
role from someone
oh maybe I can use the parts of this
vacuum the middle of the vacuum and I
can fortify the uh reinforced I can make
a reinforced broomstick
hardened with metal sure sure it doesn't
snap in half that's a good idea all
right go ahead and roll your crafts and
dexterity to do that this isn't a weapon
though so no extra bonus
oh okay
we're stopping this Ferris wheel open
story choice
all right nice nice with one success you
do manage to fortify the broom why am I
lagging so bad this is weird
um you managed I mean I'm in I'm in Tick
Tock mode right now
um all right you have a fortified metal
broom now are you going to search for
the um the gears by chance
oh yes I have the investigation which
you said yes
okay now as all of you are gathered
around figuring all of this out
um you notice that the guy at the lever
has actually become a bit distracted
because he's welcoming new passengers
onto the fair
nice
because you'll just sell on the floor
like in the shed
you should be fine
all right wakey wakey now let's see with
one success you do manage to find
um the area in the back that kind of
looks like if you shove something into
it it might stop it maybe possibly
potentially but you're not certain
it looks pretty good though all right
I'm gonna go ahead and shove that bad
boy in there
maybe we could have shorted it out with
some of that Ling and berry juice Ling
and berry soda also a possibility
all right
um maybe we all spit in it at the same
time
well characters never have to pee for
some reason I guess our characters are
Idols too catheter
yeah maybe maybe Tiara had some some uh
linger villages
I suppose we could try the burger
yeah that works I think that is a crazy
idea ladies uh I'm I am not really sure
I want to pee on the ferris wheel right
in front of you and uh that is
like a jacket around you I don't even
see how that would help out and you
think that my juices are made up so out
of some sticky stuff down there no hell
no that's not what I'm doing a body
works like no Adam you take the broom
healthier
it's like no brooms the broom in this
room just use the broom please Adam yes
you take the broom and in order to in
order to put it correctly into the um
into the configuration
um I'm gonna need you to go ahead and
roll yourself a dexterity
a dexterity
and in this situation
there she goes I'm like they want my pee
I'm out of here I'm gonna say what's an
investigation again
oh boy There She Goes
who's doing it
let's see
whoever whoever would like to I'm gonna
peace out for just a second as I try and
figure out where Kiara has gone
maybe dexterity and investigation sounds
like you why Toto the most experienced
uh yeah the Gators I was the one who
went in my back now okay now we're very
far apart let me fix it
all right hello
is this what you want me perfect that's
fine thank you okay okay
all good
no problems no problems ladies
where is
where am I you're okay where are you um
okay
good stuff oh oh it would be
I'm still moving really weirdly but
that's fine
um
no I'm gonna make myself a little oh my
God wait is that your role one success
oh no that was earlier oh okay Yara
still moves pretty smooth though
I know what's going on with me
all right
now let's see one success what's it
though no no wait wait wait once again
all right cool
with one success you shove the metal
broom into the contraption and it
it makes like a shuttering sound
and then suddenly
the ferris wheel stops moving
[Music]
that you hear someone approaching
to see what's wrong with it
I choose to run I don't know about the
others but I choose to win Oh I thought
it runs okay you guys run
thankfully it's not very far away
but the man who is um rather the ghost
being that was Manning the lever uh goes
to check out the damage and now the
lever is unattended you do see
you do see something interesting though
um in the carriages that are coming down
or that were coming down you can see
what appears to be skeletons
scary skeleton yeah and you hear a noise
from above
someone shouting
let us out of here
the skeletons want us to let them out I
don't trust them not necessarily the
skeletons but a couple carriages above
you're still alive yes you hear the
voice of an old man and an old woman
yelling from one of the carriages
okay we got we got our symbol we can't
reverse them too much they'll turn into
babies
yeah [\h__\h] the switch
all right
he's away we can flip it so when he
unfixes it then it'll reverse that's
right you flip the switch and then
and then we snap the handle off so we
can't do anything else it's stuck here
fart smart now I want you to drink it
with my foot all right you kick it with
your foot no that's okay you kick it
with your foot now roll strength for me
I want strength and Athletics actually
yeah I'll let you use both
um wait don't I have I bought some I
bought Athletics yeah
you did so how many is that three no I'm
sorry
I do
I have like one in athletic Sun
it didn't happen yeah but he'll just
have one okay
right wait where is okay
that's a 4D 10. yes ma'am
kicking it so you can't reverse it all
right
yes okay you kicked the lever and it
breaks off and um
there's no way that this wheel is uh is
not gonna stop turning back that way
that's not the right choice and now and
now the eyeball that was in the middle
of the ferris wheel closes
hey nice nice job good job and as the
ferris wheel begins to roll in Reverse
um the people that were initially
calling out to you come off the ferris
wheel and they look like
um they're in their 20s
oh well
at least didn't turn into like a fajitas
or something in there yeah it's because
they got off when they were supposed to
but if they went for another round who
could say what we would have what would
have come out on the other side this
time
I should be thanking us hmm
true facts
so they kind of run off and you see
people kind of get off the ferris wheel
however the skeletons are done for
they're uh there's no fixing that
oh rather they kind of just turn to dust
is there a power plug nearby
what was that
or the power plug no yeah for the vacuum
interestingly enough the electricity
here wasn't actually really electricity
you see you plugged it into the wall but
this place doesn't actually have real
electricity you guys have kind of
realized it's running off of the
engine's power
and there goes on the ferris wheel was
the engine oh
oh no Galley Kiara
when you guys get back can we roll a
perception check to see what's changed
in the very sweet oh yeah
um Kiara it might be like me
because I'm I keep leaving so should I
make the thing yes that would be great
if you could just real quick I'll use
the PNG for you until it's all figured
out but it is it is done oh you did it
okay awesome
it is the the thing yeah the numbers the
numbers okay what do they mean they mean
[Music]
at this point we can actually take a
little break guys
[Music]
a little intermission you guys just real
quick
okay we'll be back shortly plot our next
move
[Music]
soon we are me
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay
hello yeah hello guys we're back guess
who's back I'm back again myth is back
tell a friend guess who's back guess
who's back guess who's back guess who's
better
we're back
[Music]
anyway guys welcome back we are finished
with the intermission and uh ready to
get right back into this
um last that we checked last that we
checked you guys uh we're trying to see
if anything had changed right
mm-hmm all right so let's go ahead and
get a perception check popping off
unless you guys did one
I did one yes I got
type those successes for me ladies
two
two cheers
no game
we got here
one
gotcha all right
so
for water you've had some experience
with the ghosties pulling on you before
um
and it looks like
they're trying to do so again except
this time a little more so
rambunctiously tugging on you over and
over trying to pull you away
yeah well these ghosts want you to die
unfortunately for you
um as for you Tiara Scout and yule
um for you guys you notice that um
the entire place has begun to rumble a
bit differently and interestingly enough
while it was crashing through the waves
of the underworld before it seems as
though this place is slowing down on its
course
ever forward through through the waves
that's good
that's right and now the ferris wheel
has begun running in Reverse
um the the Merry-Go-Round is running in
Reverse you wonder what else you could
oh it's not running I don't know the
ferris wheel no it's running now because
the guy fixed it speaking of which he's
on his way back
to get out of here but we broke it so he
can't the lovers
uh yeah there's someone let's get out of
here is someone bringing the lever that
we kicked off with us
probably
I mean it's not like broken up it did
wait bring it so that you can fix it
I don't think you'll be able to fix I
mean I don't know if she's got like a
welded metal welder as a slingshot he's
a girl she doesn't have a brain what
he ain't got no brain but I'm assuming
because aren't there other rides
they're always said that you made it
sound like there are more rides that we
need to do this too
it does seem that there's um
not much not much more to do to get the
entire place to stop moving at least
oh
it's kind of up to you with what you
find
well if if Scout doesn't take the metal
thing then I'll shall take it okay
you think the lever
it is in my position
Now ladies where do you choose to go
next on these Fairgrounds
about the funny mirrors oh how some
mirrors
it seems like according to the title
that's what you want us to do anyway
it's not what it doesn't either
the title can change
that's okay I have a plan for the for
the mirror house
alrighty
if that's what you guys would like to go
then we can go there for sure let's go
all right see you guys head on over back
through
the spooky Fairgrounds
I brought you guys back there the spooky
Fairgrounds you guys are kind of
searching out for where a place like
that might be and it does turn out that
there's a big
a very large complex
um that looks as though it could be
something akin to a haunted house or a
Hall of Mirrors even
[Music]
which is interesting because you guys
did get a bit of Intel that had piqued
your interest before
a little Intel about
you being here
this is funny because mirrors reflect
and good as song
let's reflect and it's like her evil
twin yeah
it's also part of reflect yes and then
we see evil twins here in ttrpg as well
coincidence so I think not
perhaps we're not ourselves at all right
now but instead we're seeing a
reflection of ourselves on a different
world
why not
we shut down the voodoo dolls no
would you like to enter the Hall of
Mirrors
yeah
all right she says with a smile let's go
each and every one of you
um
enter in to the Hall of Mirrors
now
I'm going to change the background which
I had an extremely I had a hard time
finding a Hall of Mirrors
did you realize that on the carousel
there is a Mickey
mouse key holy [\h__\h] I can't do this
marvelous man I literally can't
all right well
this is free for use images free for use
images
Mouse
yeah oh my God
the impression's just too good now when
you guys enter this Hall of Mirrors
um I'm gonna change the music
um
when you guys enter this place
um it's not like your typical Hall of
Mirrors
it's um
it's it is it is full of mirrors don't
get me wrong but what's intriguing about
this place is that there are also
odd things like deserted swings here and
there
and odd rides just scattered and left
abandoned almost as though someone's
been playing here someone's been living
here
oh yeah okay well my first thing that I
will do is um smash all the mirrors with
my dagger
oh wow
a lot of mirrors there are many many
mirrors in here but the mirror at us
all right sure well you can that's
certainly you can go for it
um in order to smash the mirror I need
you to roll for me strength
um plus your weaponry
are you sure you want to waste your
weapon on that
that's just daggering
uh strength and whip okay yes
let's choose the dagger I think it will
help us in the long run I wonder if
there's a specific mirror we're supposed
to break rather than all of them
instead of my dagger can I use the the
metal lever uh that I brought with me
sure
okay
[Music]
oh
okay that is uh three successes
all right with three successes uh you
begin to bash the mirrors in you hit
down every single one you crack them you
break them look [\h__\h] that's right
mirrors are cracking left and right
um when when the mirror glass falls to
the ground
um you see that there is a mirror behind
the mirror
[Laughter]
it's like endless mirrors are you
telling me that
would you like to find out
yes all right
go ahead and roll again for me all right
roll perception
okay go ahead World perception two or
the strength whichever you'd like
if you want to try perceive what's going
on go for it if you'd like to try and
hit it again
you may also do that
uh
I will perceive and then continue to
bash all right
[Music]
okay well but probably you'll see is
more than Miata
my dear colleagues this is looking a
little bit weird I've been smacking
those mirrors but
I don't know what's going on you do you
understand the situation at all let's
see what I see all right so first what
you noticed Tiara is that the more you
crack these mirrors the more that the
glass or the the mirror glass rather
scatters along the ground but when it
does it almost seems as though it just
becomes part of the floor so it doesn't
actually hurt you or anything like that
but there's something strange about this
glass that is ethereal and otherworldly
um
I want
and um you want it you want to take it
I want to take some all right sure so
you take some of the glass however the
glass does kind of keep showing back up
at some point
um the more that you crack it the more
that it seems that nothing is much
changing
um what you notice
uls for you
um you've taken a notice to the fact
that you know to be in here hitting
these mirrors
um you suddenly don't really kind of
know what happened to the exit
oh
guys where did the exit go where are we
coming from
um
Maybe
is there uh air conditioning in here we
could cross your event
would you like to search for One
like it's not gonna be that successful
well we came in here for a reason we
don't immediately when I escape anyway
Adam true you know but it seems like the
room maybe
changing depending on you know what
we're doing you notice something else
oh something kind of interesting here is
that in this Hall of Mirrors well there
are many different projections of every
single one of you Here There and
Everywhere all over the place
um you realize that one one of the your
Reflections is moving differently than
the others
[Music]
cast along all the mirrors
and then walk towards it and touch the
mirror sure
you walk towards and you touch the
mirror in which all the reflections are
kind of bouncing off of each other
and it seems you can't pass through
hmm
yoga flashlights right yes
ain't there supposed to be a way that
certain types of mirrored as well can't
you like flash the light on one of them
mirrors and
see if you know what I mean maybe we can
use our lights here and see what kind of
glass is made of what you know what I
mean I'm saying which of these mirrors
is a foe
hmm that makes sense one of these
mirrors is not like the rest I refuse to
believe it
I mean the one that moves differently
yeah can I can I shine the flashlight
the one that's looking a little
suspicious
sure
um
all right you shine your flashlight
um first on the mirror right in front of
you
and you try to shine it
um in such a way that it reflects
to
what appears to be the one that's moving
a bit strangely
and you watch as the light does
something really odd the way that it
moves through space here is so strange
it seems
different than anything you've seen
before it's almost like the light is
bouncing off
of each mirror in an alternate sort of
form of space
almost as though as passing through
dimensions
and eventually with enough finesse
you manage to shine the light on the
version of you that seems to be moving a
bit differently than all of the ones
that are moving the same
and at that point Smash It You'll the
light
illuminates just you and suddenly there
are no other Reflections it's
standing there in front of a mirror one
mirror
that is also you
'll
you've been stuck here for a very long
time and you don't know how long it's
been
all that you know is that
you saw someone like you here before
and they left they walked out of this
place
clone was made
and you've been stuck here for a long
time
and now every this apparent double down
the mirror is standing in front of you
with a flashlight
oh
hey on the mirror
you bang on the mirror
and it seems that the Yule that's
holding a flashlight is kind of like
looking down at you and is also confused
thinking huh
do we see the same thing yup
okay
in fact each of you guys
are beginning to see a version of you
before your own eyes
just one
should we smash it I thought I will
fight the other one
[Music]
would you like to smash it
well there's only one
[Music]
maybe would you like to
uh
I don't know I don't like the way you're
asking me that I don't know I don't know
what uh
can I look behind the mirror
it's unfortunately a wall so I don't
think that you can actually look behind
it
was there anything else away from it
why are we like hypnotized ceiling is
black you can walk away from it if you
want but the the figure behind the
mirror seems to really want to get out
in fact Tiara you really hope that you
can escape this place
is hoping to escape both
I mean it's you isn't it Tiara no it's
not Ada when things kind of started
getting very crazy at the carnival your
last memory was odd fireworks in the air
and then suddenly you were in this Hall
of Mirrors
and there was another you leaving
you is our real use
the other the ones that left is us we
swapped bodies out of easy
what if our souls were split when we
came in here like soul and body and if
one of them dies we all die are you
saying I'm gonna die dressed in a Brash
candy coop
quite possible oh I don't think so
ladies can can we all maybe do another
perception check sure or I wanna do one
sure like about the the whole like what
we see the reflection like can I I want
to find out like does does it have the
same face paint that I used to have or
is this like a little different me sure
without the face paint okay sure
[Music]
if it's anything like the uh man to
shoot the dolls down now
oh cause you had to
[Music]
I'm in Dimensions I don't know that's
too much for my brain my friends
do you
um
those dolls you remember them
yes yeah
you um
do you have them with you yes yes oh
yeah we just want them just wondering
I was thinking about them but I don't
see like we can only hurt them like it's
not like I don't understand why we would
hurt ourselves yeah last time you will
try to do something to her own doll yeah
can I try tickling the doll
oh that's not a that's not a bad idea
we did that too last time it just
tickled whoever did it but maybe now
it's switched now it'll continue the
other ones yeah
who wants to try it
will try tickle tickle
you tickle your own doll
yeah all right tickle tickle
and uh so you see you see the U on the
other side of the mirror kind of curl up
and start laughing
so I did switch
is that what it is all right um I stab
my dagger into my eyes oh
[Music]
oh
oh goodness
well I mean
well I didn't say where I didn't say
where where do you where do you put the
knife
I uh I stabbed it into her
to cut your finger off no fingers are
important step it into
um the upper into a squishy area of the
upper thigh
okay
you do that
[Music]
yeah
it's very painful
it's very painful to hold to the one in
the mirror no
but which one is this point in for
example the moon it's this part in the
movie where we don't know who is who
anymore
well if I kill myself right here right
now will I return to my other body
that is what I must find out
I want my old body back well
you stab yourself I want to destroyed
this one
you stab yourself in the leg and the you
that you see on the other side recoils
in pain and begs you to stop oh
and and me
you you're fine
[Music]
[Laughter]
um all right you taking God man with
power
six lethal damage
um
yes
how many stabs did you just say you said
a lot of stabs I saw six lethal damage
how about you Scout what do you do huh
do you do anything with your doll or do
you stare at yourself through the mirror
I'm still staring I'm just I'm I'm
trying to process still
wait
wait so if if Tiara took lethal damage
that means our real real cells as the
ones in the mirror and the ones walking
around are actually the fake ones uh you
got it
ah
so when we were transported into this
Dimension we were stuck in the mirror
and our doppelgangers are the ones
that's been walking around the carnival
being the shenanigans
so we're not ready
well it depends if you're talking about
you the U that's outside the mirror or
the U inside the mirror
the us outside the mirror is just a copy
of what's inside the mirror yeah living
in another dimension like yeah it's like
a snapshot of when we just came into the
dimension I'm guessing right so we need
to find a way to get out of the mirror
uh-huh because now the perspective has
switched
the the you that you were playing as
just a moment ago
has not really been you
huh
you've been in the mirrors the whole
time
[Music]
so does that mean that the US
I mean that the US on the other side
have the same weapons that we do seeing
as it's us
what if the US on the other side just
destroys whatever it's seeing in front
of it
[Music]
would you like to give it a try
will I die
it's a good question
are you okay uh
uh you okay
there is General enough someone's got
first aid
I got first aid
uh do I first aid but how did your first
date a mirror
I mean are we just still like all
together in there or are we one by one
in the mirror
oh it would appear that you guys are all
together
okay first they don't mirror Tiara all
right
but wait that implies that Ina can
control her mirror herself
[Music]
we have switched perspectives you guys
are no longer playing the mirror now
it's exactly but like Oh but before I
was controlling the one that's outside
of the mirror and suddenly we can
control the lunge inside yeah we just
switched perspective
now we're our real cells
oh so now we can leave well who wouldn't
get out when I was was I in the mirror
when I was stabbing the doll yeah the
doll I thought I was outside
Oh I thought Carol was outside when she
stopped the door and the one inside got
hurt yeah you guys that are holding the
voodoo dolls right on the outside
you guys
um have been like messing with them
right
has been affecting you
like actually you um okay
wait but at what point were we in
[\h__\h] the mirror though like was this
before we got the food with All-Star
after because I got hurt by the voodoo
doll when I was actually there but I
don't know though is when exactly it
happened
okay you guys went through the
dimensions but that's not necessarily it
could be it could be but it's not it's
the boa you guys don't know exactly when
it happened oh
today was the problem
poor town okay okay clay let's think
technically if we were
quote unquote cloned during that time
that means the time that I shot
the doll I did get hurt myself therefore
we were still our real selves however
if
the outside hurt
the doll and we got hurt inside that
means that we also carried the doll with
us
that's right inside right
and that's right
a copy was made at that time an exact
copy that should
by all logicals
if we
if they have our our voodles the inside
mirror would we have their Voodoo rules
can we test that out would you like to
check
I would like to tickle the inside mirror
voodoo doll
well
inside the mirror which are now you guys
that you control you tickle the doll of
your other self who then immediately
reacts to the tickling
so the one on the outside right exactly
two identical copies on each side
yeah the same thing as the other side
basically the outside outside guys have
like the inside mirrors voodoo dolls and
the inside mirror
people carry the outside exactly so now
it's survival of the fittest whatever
side is strongest winds oh we have to
get out of the mirror
time pressure right now can I get a
first aid that you offered yes first
aid here we go all right let's do some
healing
[Music]
here's the healing
damage
it's probably both Health blocks
[Music]
I think I think that six lethal damage
will bring me at least a beat at the end
of the session I would I would assume so
yeah
wasn't there some yeah wasn't there a
beat for taking a lot of damage yes
that's right that's right all right let
me see
it was all according to keikaku oh of
course plan from the start no problem no
problem
all right
so I want you to go ahead and first roll
um
there's a lot to keep up with in this
game
[Applause]
a lot of respect to people that um
just have it all in their head
I don't know how to summarize everything
yeah
all right
um
nice translator notes in the chat
thank you I did not know what keikaku
means
plan hey all right how many dots do you
have by the way you know in first aid
uh
uh there's one all right that's fine all
right that's fine
[Music]
all right roll dexterity plus medicine
the interval is one minute
okay I have medicine too just in case
many do you have
really good
okay maybe maybe Scout is better
medicine I'm trying to try to think big
brain stuff I got I got distracted don't
worry I'm used to stitching up sheep at
the farm I'll get you stitched up real
nice Tiara thank you Scouts
wait why do we rolling sure
[Music]
I think I think I think it's a nice
situation everyone they hurt okay
all right
[Music]
you can also drink it if you want to sit
on it
all right
bleeding so it's not bleeding out or
anything
um however however uh Tiara you are
going to unfortunately take a small
penalty to do physical actions from here
on out
um and you do uh two of your lethal I
will turn to bashing for you with their
team effort
oh wait um uh wait a second lethal it's
like the X how exactly do my RK so I got
four x's and two slashes okay that's
fine
all right so you're just gonna take a a
physical penalty from here but uh you're
not bleeding out and are you good
that happened huh
yeah that was my uh
honey that wasn't even the same screen
not hold up my my uh apparently my
desktop background showed
it's so it's nothing nothing bad just oh
okay from Scotty credits
absolutely gorgeous artwork from my
birthday merchandise which is now not
available anymore oh okay oh wow um all
right then guys be careful that's kind
of yabai that is happening so yeah uh I
know why it might well you can talk
about it afterwards okay no problem all
right with that being said you guys you
do spend a turn to help out your dear
friend now you're lucky because at this
point those of you on the other side
that are still handling their voodoo
dolls are a little confused at what's
going on they haven't quite grasped it
yet but you guys know the real use
have kind of figured it out
[Music]
okay who here has played Soma
oh I did yes as this is giving me
like we just have to
ditch the other side and just be like oh
well Gamers that's the way the
I don't understand why we have to get
the other side out of can we just walk
away like what I don't know maybe
they're not really stuck maybe it's just
an illusionado if so if if we get on our
side isn't that all that matters the
real us like if they get stuck yeah but
what if the other outside of the um
outside of the mirror or not actually
like our human human self what if
they're just like Spirit form but they
look human like right now
so we can't technically go back to where
we came from because what are we
supposed to do
we can't we gotta get out the mirror
somehow
if smashing it just doesn't do much
and we're in a an infinite Loop of both
sides feeling the other's pain and I
don't
walk away say bye I see the ones on the
other side would they be willing to like
help us I wonder are they I do they have
their own will
are you willing to negotiate with them
yeah I want them to reach out to their
hands and and take me out of that mirror
if they wanna okay and they do that
though the mirrors do seem extremely
solid but unfortunately
you do hear a noise
a little intercom turns on
well you hear someone on the intercom
saying
there can only be one
in this world
oh we were here first daughter
yeah but to the other side they were
here first no
so what will you do
[Music]
um
you guys on the other side of the mirror
are starting to kind of figure it out as
they begin to kind of
poke at you
as your voodoo dolls
we'll begin to
scratch a little bit test it out on you
guys as you reflexively react to the way
that they interact with your dolls as
they begin to realize that you guys are
who you are are we friends in the mirror
or do we somehow
because if we're two halves of the same
coin or two sides of the same coin what
if like are we are we two complete
halves
or are we half and half you're not sure
good question
and we
celebrate the voodoo doll like trade
voodoo dolls
[Music]
solid pretty solid
can I can I try to talk to them oh this
is inside the mirror like sorry go ahead
we never tried talking but I guess that
would be too easy
can can I flash my flashlight add them
even though I'm inside the mirror
sure well what will there you see
you flash your flashlight at them light
yes all right when you flash your
flashlight you do see something that is
somewhat intriguing
even though it is glass in front of you
as a mirror
you realize that it's actually not
necessarily a mirror anymore because the
light from the flashlight now passes
through
completely without reflecting
you
yeah you could but it flashes on to you
who you see is
interestingly enough
full of what appears to be sticks and
stones for just a brief moment
they like gollums yeah
in the moment where I flash my
flashlight at the mirror is it and the
light goes through is the light the only
thing that goes through can I try to
poke my hand through it only the light
passes through okay
what if we touch the doll to the Mirror
you touch the doll to the mirror and
nothing really happens
okay
um
the lights did we talk to
can we hear each other can we talk to
each other the other on the other side
it's gotten to a point now where those
on the other side are starting to figure
out who they are
right and they kind of have stopped
talking to you
their eyes kind of narrow a bit with
some malicious and seeming intense oh
you feel this jealous rage towards each
and every one of you
will never be the real what daughter
well then we got a
I mean I'll just I mean I'm the real
deal so I'll just
I'll take the doll out
and that'll be the end of you mirror
self so either you we help each other
here when Kiara like heard her own doll
didn't it just hurt herself or like yeah
yeah we're on the outside
okay so outside fake fake one with the
doll hurt the doll hurt real Tiara yes
real Tiara hurt her voodoo doll hurt
fake Kiara that's right yeah that's
what's happening yes you now have
control of each other's bodies in a
sense or rather what happens
oh so we just killed the other ones yeah
I'm gonna go drown this voodoo doll in
the ectoplasm water all right yeah you
guys go first this time I don't want to
touch my doll anymore
what is the inside of the minion though
like is it like
the same as like the outside like like
the yeah Carnival yeah it is it is a
little strange a little strange odd
playground like Place how would I know
that
quote-unquote stuck inside a mirror
everything's been the same
right that's the question you don't
really know do you
yeah
kind of sit like it's all an illusion
we're not really stuck we're just like
we could if we want it if we could get
our ourselves our minds together we
could maybe even just walk away from it
but our mind Powers maybe not that
strong
well if the ghost could manifest
whatever they wanted shouldn't we be
able to if we were on the spirit side
yes that would be nice
[Music]
but wait so we wanted to kill those
dolls right
would you like to try is there some is
there something inside the doll can we
unwrap it
sure let me unravel it okay sure gently
um Scout you unravel the doll and you
hear something behind you fall to the
ground
[Music]
you see your own head on the ground
looking at you
[Music]
what's the one like the fake one correct
right
yeah yep your own head looking at you
and sticks and stones and leaves also
scattered on the ground in the place of
where blood would be
[Music]
uh well all right unravel the dolls
unravel them or also maybe burn them
whatever you'd like to do
I'll just re-ravel themselves whatever
you would like to do it doesn't seem
like you're moving anymore
I feel like I don't know I feel like
I've seen this summer before but once
they're Sticks and Stones something
unless something special happens they'll
remain that way okay I'll just I'm not
gonna be experimental anymore I'm just
gonna unravel and do the same as you all
right you watch your bodies fall apart
before your eyes
it's
um it's quite a sight in fact all of you
have never seen something like this
before the side of your own corpse
though full of sticks and stones Coming
Undone before your own eyes it's not
something that you would care to see
again in fact
and because of that
all of you have now experienced
something traumatic
for the first time since entering this
world of Darkness this horrifying
Supernatural world you are in a
situation where you've seen something
truly truly traumatic that would indeed
affect your ability to go on so I need
all of you
to
test your breaking point for me
oh okay how here's how this works the
breaking point can fall into the
following categories we're going with
the category of the character Witnesses
something traumatic terrifying or
rattles their understanding of the world
now what you'll need to do is roll
resolve plus composure with a modifier
based on your current morality slash
Integrity rating all of you are at seven
correct composure and resolve yes
resolve okay all right if you're if
you're at seven then you get plus one to
that modifier
morality and I mean not morality what
was the rule
uh it's resolve composure
resolve composure
plus one if you have seven morality
and and you can get a plus you guys
haven't rolled yet right
yeah you get another plus one
um for protecting yourself in this
moment this is done in self-defense
so you get plus one so you have plus two
totals okay
okay all right
yeah baby belt buckle strong Integrity
Plus
one if you have seven morality oh okay
oh my God it's harmless baby
[Music]
oh well at least at least I'm not the
only one with one oh man
all right uh at this point
Scout you have no problem so you
actually
um you managed to not only survive the
breaking point but Find meaning in it
and reaffirm your own self-worth
um and for that you may refill all of
your willpower
oh nice yeah yeah the charge yeah
recharged there you go like a little bit
of trauma refresh the break that's right
you you think to yourself I've seen
worse
did you even use any willpower though
uh a little bit but I'm assuming it
would have recharged by now ah true
enough well still kind of nice to have
regular rice
um and then we've got watoto Yule and
tiara
um you guys don't like what you've seen
very clearly this is nothing you've ever
experienced before in your life however
however
um you did succeed
and so you've come through intact
oh
nice yeah oh sorry yes you've come out
intact now you may feel a bit guilty or
upset about what happened but you can
cope you can deal with it
um let's see create a new one now I will
eventually I will give you a condition a
bit later but for now the adrenaline of
moving through this Mission has kind of
powered you through but this is
something that you will reflect on in
the future and um and will cause you a
bit of pain so
you'll have to be ready for it but once
you have sort of un unraveled your dolls
um you realize something odd about the
room
suddenly the glass that was before you
has disappeared
[Music]
solved the riddle that's right can we
walk through it indeed
oh
is it like a portal now
do you return from whence the Pat the
other you came
foreign
[Music]
ERS of you came from where you guys just
spent all that time unraveling those
riddles you will go back there
okay okay
all right now the real world the real
real name is
the real world
interestingly enough once you exit this
Hall of Mirrors something very odd has
happened you suddenly realize you have
memories of doing things that you don't
remember doing
memories
his memories have now become one with
you
you remember turning back the ferris
wheel you remember turning back the
Merry-Go-Round no no no I don't recall
that how do I feel like I made sucky
sounds
no honestly I could totally use
use this doppelganger for school
wait
perception check okay yeah you guys are
exiting my own place now
okay all right I see nothing
okay
I'm back to the fairgrounds
Trio for Grandma
cranberry
got like all pink eyes
all right please type your successes
oh Scout
no all seeing eye is it not five for you
you'll oh four and then five and then
six
damn that's a good roll Tiara and Scout
you guys are too shaken from well Scouts
not shaking but Dr has been shaken from
what just happened oh yeah this guy was
kind of feeling like a badass at this
point that was kind of sick
um so you're not paying much attention
to what's going on out here but was it
so you do notice something you've
noticed that the water
um has settled around the fairgrounds
you don't feel like this place is moving
anymore
oh you feel like it's come to a stop
we did it we're about to go so the ghost
still there oh the ghosts are on a
rampage
oh they are really dragging folks off
and in fact there are several of them
coming towards you guys Yule that's the
first thing you notice
you also noticed that Grandma uh seems
to be looking very lost in the middle of
the fairgrounds looking for you guys
are the ghost
[Music]
s
um are very rambunctious
the ghosts are in the real world as well
yeah
yeah but that's not the rail where the
railroad world are we in the room that's
no this is not the real real world no
before we entered the room the mirror
room this is before that yeah this is
where we did all the yeah or the fake us
we're doing all the turning the ferris
wheel and stuff yeah
yeah we're still in the other dimension
what you made me more confused you know
okay so beginning of the session we were
technically the fake us right correct
we're doing the uh we're doing the tasks
you know
that was never us
that was never us that was the fake guys
the mirror room yeah
and we got to the mirror room our point
of view switched over
[Music]
to be on the mirror where our actual
cells were what does the real us do
until we switched over you were asleep
asleep now we just suddenly gained
Consciousness we were like whoa you were
in here for a while
haha
I get it okay and now you are back to
fool yourself yeah maybe okay like it's
like we did it because we got all the
memories and stuff right yeah I don't
know yeah when we got out of the mirror
we're just like oh my God we did all
this and now like we uh have to go yeah
to lay it out for y'all your
doppelganger's memories merged with you
guys oh yeah
yeah
so now you guys are gonna uh you guys
exit however there are ghosts flying at
you right now what do you do
all right you guys shine those
flashlights on the ghosts it doesn't
seem though like they're just gonna let
that be the end of it though so
you keep those flashlights trained it's
gonna be hard to do other actions but
if you can hold them up as long as we
get the granny yeah lots of people are
screaming grandma is there kind of
turning around back and forth oh hello
you guys made it I still can't seem to
find my husband anywhere
no oh what a shame
um let's see uh it looks hey it looks
like you did it uh it it would appear
that the engine has stopped and this
place is not moving any longer towards
the depths which is great news for us
but now we need to finish it we need to
finish the the reversal ritual
oh the river spiritual indeed what is
that Granny
well we can probably turn this place
back around but it's it's going to be
it's it's going to take a lot of
teamwork
if you guys have that
it's what we're here for Anna yes let me
see how how can you do something like
that you should find the center point
the central the central area where
everything leads do you remember a place
a place like that
Carousel the castle
they're like oh
that's right
um let's see
it might be it might be
where was it now I'm not sure I think
that you may just have to try and
remember
how do I do a remember check
intelligence and wits
uh cool
when the real Kiara doesn't remember
then we must make tiara remember all
right
nice okay so you remember that the
castle was very engine-like it was
rumbling and roaring and that was where
you some found all the ghosts coming out
in the first place
you get the feeling that if you can
reverse that
right
Castle
yeah
I was having like a Galaxy brain moment
like
you're Brain Blast finally hit yeah all
right so are you guys what are you gonna
do is that where you want to go do you
want to go Castle okay
reverse a ritual all right run run run
run run run run run so you guys run to
the castle and I need you all to roll
your Athletics plus I mean we can also
walk dude
you'll have to fight off ghosts so if
you want to walk you're gonna have to
fight outside
Athletics and strength in this case I
would say
um okay I'd let you choose dexterity if
you wanted but you're gonna have to take
a minus let's see you're gonna take a
minus two Tiara you can use willpower I
was about to ask yeah okay can you
expect security
yes dexterity or strength I don't mind
using parkour you can run without your
mic and parkour oh yeah
what Toto has short legs
oh nice
you finished your gun all right you
carry Scout while you're at it because
you have to have a success
I can parkour horrible holding someone
wheel
you can help watato now but the others
would probably continue onward because
to turn around and help wasato might
might take a turn so in that case
um let's see how many successes all
right
um for Tiara and Scout you guys make
your way towards the castle handily with
no issues from the ghosts however watato
your legs are very short and you stumble
forward and you fall thankfully Ewell
who is kind of ahead of the others turns
around to help you wasato and grabs your
hand however you guys are gonna have to
get through some ghosts I need you guys
to bat the ghosts away and if you wish
to do that I'm gonna need you to roll
you can use either your brawl plus
strength to like try and like Bat Away
the ghosts you know your hands will
probably go through them but you can at
least kind of get them to go away
flashlights you don't really think will
keep them off of you though
um so you could use your bra or you
could use Athletics and strength again
I'll let you choose which role you want
to do I'll use that again college is not
an option
all right
yeah come at me ghosties okay oh okay
you want to bat the ghost away Scott
yeah you're gonna help you out
kind of yeah all right you swat them
away heck yeah two successes not bad you
managed to kind of get the ghosts
annoyed enough with you that they go off
and they carry other humans away yay
oh well farewell sacrifice
all right well this does not stop the
ghosts Onslaught many lives are being
destroyed but at least you guys are cool
for now
um so now you guys have kind of made it
very wearily very rarely over to the
castle just barely
and now granny who has also been running
the best she can but parkour granny
she's she's better at running than you'd
think she does eventually
um get there with you guys and let's see
this is what I want to use all right
um and now you guys are all at the
castle together
um oh
right where all of this I'm gonna at
least I'm gonna bring you guys to the
castle
I guess YouTube is so right now for some
people sorry guys sorry guys it kind of
depends sometimes
[Music]
things are right on my end but
yeah
I think it's the regional yeah like
there might be a server down somewhere
down yeah you guys don't miss charged
you guys do arrive at the castle
um
and Granny says now we have to look for
a wheel to steer this trust her
okay
hi
best grandma
I mean she doesn't live with you guys
grandma was a member of the teams
yeah what's the password granny you lost
the password granny well the past but no
we need to find a wheel who drew the Box
on the screen
oh look at her color
okay
it's a little square by the castle
oh
and we don't really see the castle can
draw one
okay all right granny where's that wheel
I don't know we have to search for it
um
shall we what kind of wheel are we
looking for granny water wheels steering
wheel steering wheel as if we are
pirates
and she kind of Waddles towards the
front door
we already checked the front door oh
nothing in the front found the wheel
so on the screen the wheel is on the
screen
okay should we perception check for a
wheel go for it if you would like to
yeah okay oh yes yes please
wants to do perception check all right
looking for Grant all right hi
oh my God
dead wait
all right he'll be all right
I'm gonna die
[Music]
all right
please type your successes
uh yes
being fat zero holy [\h__\h] what is going
on
you'll suddenly your eyes all right your
eyes get real narrowed and zoom in on
immediately where you see that there is
potentially possibly a wheel at the very
top of the castle it looks like there is
something similar to a steering wheel up
there but you don't really know if that
if it's useful or not it might take some
strength to to go grab it and bring it
down
I have strength but you're hurt the
wheel will you be okay
no
all right I mean
how do we get all the way up to the top
you'll need to climb that's what you can
discern
do you still have that lever Tiara yes I
got me a rope I'm pretty sure we can
make Mia I mean we can make us the
grapple hook
if if that is the real Tiara that has
the liver yes
yeah uh yes
okay yes indeed
yeah okay let's build it
hook
I mean I assumed that you guys like
grabbed anything that was left over from
them yeah
totally
I probably should have asked oh well my
bad it's okay you have it now you have
it now
um now to make this grappling hook I
want you to use your crafts and
dexterity Scout
easy
all right okay
come on rolls
don't screw me over now oh
all right anybody else got another way
you can try again Scout you can try
again but everyone will have to roll to
bat away some ghosts first
all right sorry guys I'm distracted by
then
uh all right everybody roll Athletics
and strength
okay
use those muscles bat away those ghosts
yes
it keeps getting on you oh my God is
this
okay
it's ring I don't I can't control it
it's rigged all right everyone type your
successes for ghosts
[Music]
oh boy oh CR and you you guys are safe
what's a toe on the other hand is
definitely on the way to the water
however Scout you have created a
grappling hook that seems like it might
kind of work possibly watoto is flying
away what do you guys do
at this moment
to get to the wheel
all right Scott's on a mission all right
uh I go help all right sounds good
with a hook does someone have to like
hold the bottom part of the room if
you're using it to grab them I'll swing
it around and throw it to the roof
in order to scale the wall with a
grappling hook Scout I'm gonna need you
to go ahead and roll uh dexterity and
let's see
it's not being used as a weapon I would
say
dexterity and Athletics in this case and
you can add a plus one for decent
grappling hook it's not the best but
it's pretty good
well I'm gonna add one for willpower
okay three you add three dice if you
want to expend a willpower
okay
[Music]
all right guys now how do you guys what
do you guys choose to do to get wasito
back
grab his leg why one leg in a use one
leg all right
I want both Yule and tiara Yule and
tiara
please roll also your Athletics and
strength to pull with all your might
oh
it's already um
subtracted to the physical thingy all
right oh my God oh my God gotcha thank
you
hello
[Music]
what's going on
oh my god
um all right so Tiara you grab onto one
leg of wasisone it seems to kind of
break the ghost's grip but as soon as
Yule jumps up and grabs the other legs
all over and you guys come crashing down
towards the sand and watato is safe for
now you guys turn around to see that
Scout is scaling the wall and actually
doing pretty decently only slipping a
couple times on the Rocks uh making your
way up to the top I need Scout to do one
more roll in order to get all the way to
the top of the roof without falling down
same as you just did you can add
willpower if you'd like but
no I'll take it away
yeah all right
can we can we add like um
wait if I have double tens is that a two
one
all right so with your two successes
Scout you managed to finally get the
grappling hook up into that last little
groove on the roof and then you jump up
and see that there is some kind of
weird pirate wheel for like a weird
staring ship or something and you
realize this Castle has like a weird
Marine theme for some reason
um but there's but there is there's your
wheel there it is right there at the top
seems like this this Ender city is not
broken
Minecraft
uh if we take the wheel do I is it
attached to the castle we're steering
the castle it looks like you may need to
break it off
[Music]
why would I break it off
granny did just say we need a wheel
but I mean there's a whale here if
you're if you try and like move it or
anything it doesn't seem anything
changes just up there
can I roll a perception sure
is it 4010
uh one d10 1d10 okay ignore that one
okay
yeah what
all right well never mind all right with
your two successes
um you're kind of like fiddling around
it's a zero if it's a 1d10 wait no what
were you rolling for oh
yeah so you got two successes
perception is a 4010 I thought somebody
just said it's a 1D 10. it depends on
you
the one detention right
yeah that's what I was referring to on
the attend the re-roll for the ten
okay sure we'll take it all right well
with two successes you're kind of
fiddling with the wheel you feel like
it's pretty flimsy you can easily break
it off you don't really know why you'd
want to though granny said we needed a
wheel you weren't sure why but then you
also realize granny is down there at the
bottom of the on the floor uh using some
kind of weird chalk to draw an odd
diagram in the ground
and it's beginning to kind of glow in a
strange way
all right while I'm sending the wheel
down then all righty
to break it off I once uh an Athletics
and actually no just a strength roll for
you please
no Athletics this time just pull that
sucker off first questions more actions
yeah
[Music]
I knew you could do it with one success
you handily tear it off and um and now
the wheel is yours do you want to throw
it do you wanna go down back down with
it
now I'll wrap it I'll Loop it through my
belt buckle on my pants nice and then um
Palm Cruise my way down all right in
order to scale back down it'll be a lot
quicker and easier rural Athletics and
dexterity one more time for me
okie dokie all right as for wasato Yule
and tiara you guys are finally safe
again
[Music]
I think I've fallen oh oh no thank you
with your grappling hook
um you kind of stick it into the wall
and you start to make your way down but
that thing was not super handy from the
beginning it did its job but it was it
wasn't fully it wasn't your best work
Scout definitely wasn't the best thing
you've ever made
um and with that about Midway down uh
the Rope snaps and you go crashing to
the ground that's
what the [\h__\h]
huh
you heard Jesus do you want to just like
who is at the [\h__\h] door why does this
I'll be right back guys
next time I'm at Breakers
and then alarm themselves nice
tap your windows and stuff don't
minimize you know
do you want to be a PNG Kiara are you no
okay and so I'm fine I'm fine I'm
waiting I I do not oh you don't do
anything anymore
I wonder how many bones I broke
for it
jelly jelly bones
at this point as long as we get out of
this situation I don't care if I've
broken every bones in my body
just get us out of here
grandma
Grandma Got Run Over by a Reindeer you
know what that she could do magic
is it really grandma
she never said the password
oh the pat you mean the like of the
safety one Mary yes it makes you think
of the first grandma that we saw was a
fake ground nah I'm back now everything
outside of the carnival was real if
she's if this old if this old lady lied
to us I'll peel her like a banana
something all right violence
okay now uh sorry about that um I'm back
all right now uh Scout you come crash
into the ground you hit your back on the
ground that was very painful you take
three bludgeoning damage
that's your real bashing
yeah bludging and bashing are the same
thing yeah it's just it's a different
word it's a different word for the same
thing but all right so you take some
damage there on that one see out
thankfully it wasn't terrible it wasn't
the worst that it could have been for
you but you're not feeling great however
you have the wheel and it seems
undamaged so that's good good thing it
wasn't a critical fail huh
um
so you you have the wheel what do you do
with it
I don't know Grandma you take it here
you go crazy old lady wonderful thank
you she Takes the Wheel
um
we don't have to now we need to steer
our way back
let me finish up my diagram and she
finishes up the little circle she's it's
actually pretty big a circle she's
drawing in the ground and you can hear
you can hear as she uses the chalk it
sounds like a soul screaming
mmm as she uses it
mm-hmm
she's a witch
y witch and she finally she she puts the
chalk away and she says sorry old friend
and she puts the chalk away
we need to get out of here though weird
and now she takes the wheel and puts it
in the middle of the strange diagram and
begins to spin it and turns it all the
way around and suddenly you can feel
the entire rotation
of this particular island of a carnival
that you guys are all on is turning
around and suddenly you feel yourselves
getting ready to accelerate upward
let it rip
[Laughter]
e
what the [\h__\h]
at this point though Granny says all
right now we need one last thing we need
to find we need to find a way to create
a sort of unlimited engine power source
um let's see how can we Propel ourselves
back
um we're lucky for you
I'm a cowboy bean
you guys figure it out I'll be over here
broken on the ground oh can we help
count sure would you like to do a
medical check
sure it'll be fun yeah we are crashing
damage is easy to heal so okay maybe not
then yeah I mean it heals on its own
anyways 31 yeah
but Granny says um does anyone know how
we could create a paradox here
yes like like portals within portals or
something like that
like a funny like a funny riddle yeah an
unlimited energy source of sorts
[Music]
isn't the castle a source of
unending energy it is it is through the
castle we need it to turn it off
[Music]
and and pushing ghosts out but we need
to we need to turn it in on itself
what
turn it in on itself I am uh
I ah
I can shook you some corn old lady but
there ain't no way I know how to reverse
no Castle portal goes to making
Machinery you're on your own I can't I
don't know can run like a hamster in a
wheel
oh
is the is the glass any of any use that
I have the magical glass no you do have
some magical glass
indeed if we put a mirror in front of
the portal would it reverse it
hmm well you couldn't if you would you
like to give it a try because from what
you can tell
the the piece of the mirror that you
collected Tiara is most definitely
um in its own way a portal to another
world
oh granny did just say something like
a portal within a portal
if you toss I don't know oh well like
the other portal back at it on the
mirror and then we shine yeah in the
mirror and then the light goes through
the portal and then into the prayer and
it goes back and forth
maybe
let's do that all right
sounds
love to make another mirror
I brought not only one shot I brought a
couple
she brought a decent amount of glass I
would say
yeah all right so how do you guys set
this up
question
we have the tape should we dry I have
tape too yeah should we draw it on on
the sure go ahead give me a little
drawing might as well use the roll 20 to
its full oh yeah uh help help
you had a better understanding of that
than I did oh um okay
oh
this is a shark
that's that's the shot yeah
and they're being glued together yeah
okay
[Music]
and we have to make Blue Portal
here is the portal like another portal
and it reflects the mirror yeah was it
like a miracle
[Music]
yeah
standable I yes yes
very lovely drawing
I mean it's fantastic I love it
all right looks like a butt
incredible
you
guys are going to have to craft the
mirror though that is one thing you will
you will have to do so
um if someone could go ahead and do a
crafts and dexterity check for me to
create this music but I do have a little
bit of craft oh never mind okay I have
craft index sure
oh craft and dexterity indeed how much
how much would would you that's a six
for me okay seven for me okay nice oh
dude can we we're building together make
the ultimate build it together yeah
don't support each other but the way
that that works is oh
um oh
someone does the main role and the two
supporters fuel is the main roller okay
so here's the here okay so when you're
supporting the supporters roll first
um and you the successes that you get
from that contribute to Yule's dice pool
okay yes would you like to try it again
that was a really good rules
um all right I mean um
okay
that's better okay
dad just has like bad luck these days
maybe we should do a dice Purge
um I'll tell you what that is in a
second
um two successes add to your dice pool
you know
this is the biggest role yet here we go
I'll take you I'll take it you did
succeed
nice all right okay what we created a
decently sturdy
I created a decently sturdy mirror you
guys together it looks pretty good
um okay and now you guys create that
unlimited energy source by creating
a portal within a portal and Shining an
infinite light and suddenly
and suddenly you see a most magnificent
and intriguing sight
from within the castle
and then suddenly outward you see a sort
of explosion of Lights
like so
I heard this I'll like the firework
Festival no it's not hold on hold on
Michael Ratched wonderful world of
firework magic
dreams definitely happening is
no it's
stop stop that
stop
wait am I have to find a door too
[Laughter]
we only see the top part of course
nothing below that nothing below
sweet Minecraft castle yeah it's nice
it's made out of grass
yup and just like that uh the unlimited
energy source begins to fire off like an
engine and um and your your Carnival
floating Carnival begins to speed back
up up the river Upstream from where it
came and suddenly the ghosts begin to
reverse they begin to be sucked into the
castle
Ramada
yes
and just like that you guys are on your
way back to civilization
of gold for coming here did we achieve
our goal I don't know you may need to
figure out next you figure out the
mystery
well you figured the mystery was why you
guys were appear why you appeared double
at the carnival oh why were you guys
seen there go solve that mystery
stop it okay okay okay so I'd say it's
certainly a mission accomplished
is my uhu back I guess you'll have to
find out when we return next time and we
um we reconvened at the bar and and
recap what happened
yeah oh
yeah next time
next time can we get Beats indeed yes
indeed here I'm gonna
play a little PGM all right well done
you guys well done today there were a
lot of roles today I feel like in terms
of gameplay you guys did a lot of stuff
um yeah it's a lot of zeros were rolled
you know what actually let's go ahead
and do something I want to try something
it's called a dice Purge
um a lot of times when a player is just
having consistently bad luck
um what they can choose to do is do
What's called the dice Purge where you
roll basically 100 dice in roll 20.
um and it's supposed to like Purge any
weirdness that's going on I guess in
your role
um I think it's a little superstitious
in my opinion but in the past
yeah that's right you don't want to
purge the good dice
for example
that's a lot of shitty dyes there but
it's also some good ones so if you'd
like
who's gonna win
36 ounces 30 30 or with a lot of tens
though a lot of tens yeah
that's true a lot of Wednesday it was
the best gotcha look yeah there are a
lot of theories on like how it I mean if
it even works at all but in the past I
can I can vouch for that I've had some
bad roles in the past did a dice Purge
and all my luck was normal again
um
so who could say um it might just be a
little roll 20 Superstition but you know
what uh maybe it'll help you next time
so we shall see
um but anyway guys uh this has been
quite the session let me go ahead and
hand out your Beats for you because you
guys did a lot of stuff
yeah all right yeah good job guys now
here's what we got
um first let's go ahead and start off
with watoto I'm gonna go from from the
left all the way to the right
all right now let's see what we got here
at the top yeah
you did not take any dramatic failures
so I think that's fine at the end of the
game session take a beat that's one
excellent you didn't take any extreme
lethal damage
um risk's a Breaking Point take a beat
you did all of you did actually so
that's another beat two so far good role
playing I will give you a point for good
role playing yay three
um next good teamwork I would say yes
you cooperated well with a team oh yeah
see take an action influenced by your
Vice take an action influenced by your
virtue we didn't have any of those calls
so I would say no
um remember your flaw and use it in
session did not happen this time
um complete the mission that's another
beat and now we have five total but I'm
implementing something that my GM
actually did for us back in the day and
there's a bonus beat point that you can
get the way that you get that is by
telling us something that you learned
today in session
oh okay
[Music]
um the timeline mirrors are very
confusing and that
um both can't be vacuumed like in the
movies
that's that's good I like that's a good
answer
I like that answer that's good I'll give
you a beat for it and now you have six
six total Beats
um added to you so that's current beats
goes from three to nine and then if we
turn that into EXP
and then that's gonna be hold on let me
see we do four equals one so you have
nine beats we turn those into exp you're
left with one and now your current exp
is seven
the use as you please is quite a bit so
feel free to spend it as you like
um now next we've got Yule you'll be all
right you'll be useful you you useful
you'll see anything else you'll see
everything we'll be all right
indeed wheel oh we use the wheel
all right now let's see
um you didn't take any dramatic failures
but you did you ended the game session
yes good role playing yes I'll give you
uh one for good role-playing good
teamwork definitely
um let's see complete the mission you
did
um let's see did you risk a Breaking
Point yes you did that's five
um
and what did you learn today
just say I could say that um when it
comes down to it you can really be buff
buffed up and carry teammate also that
you is good at parkour yeah that was
surprising I was like whoa all right
nice heck yeah um
yeah
yeah and also yeah yeah the the Mirror
Mirror I don't know I'm not sure if it's
a riddle but it was fun figuring that
out yeah yeah that was that was super
cool I I do want to say it was it was
neat seeing you realize the plan as it
like kind of like came unraveled
literally
um so yeah
I was gonna say you have a huge brain
you know it's too much new movie yeah
um also I wanted to uh also let you know
as well so for this uh for this session
you were very proactive and you had like
a lot of like like initiative like oh
was it so does this just out of like out
of nowhere
um and I think that is a great sign that
you're like really getting the hang of
this so I wanted to let you let you know
that you guys are doing great
I'm glad that you're enjoying it I'm
doing my best doing my best
um now for you
yeah of course anytime I love doing it
um for you your current total beats then
because we have six is now nine and then
of course we convert that to experience
points
um so that's going to be go from nine
beats uh to one experience becomes five
all right
next up we've got Tiara Tiara let's see
what we got here so Tiara you completed
uh end of the game so take a beat yes
um if your character takes lethal damage
and one of your right most health boxes
take a beat yes you did hey you did so
there's a beat for that
um you risked a Breaking Point another
beat for that
um good role-playing I'm actually gonna
go ahead and give you two for this one
you had like some really good role play
this session
um it was it was impressive very good
good teamwork indeed I would say yes you
did
um action influenced by Vice or virtue I
would say no I would give you the
Curiosity I would give you the Curiosity
flaw one but the person who ended up
making that role was was uh was so
but I still didn't anyway didn't I but
it didn't it didn't negatively affect
you yeah talking to the ghosts
ah
it was it
well I did talk to the ghosts as well
oh
wait
I had that conversation oh that's right
you did
oh I spoke to the girl I see for
whatever reason I only I only remembered
one of one of the others for whatever
reason in that moment that's fine you're
right you did mention that
um so we'll have that be seven and then
complete the mission yes you did now
what did you learn
I learned
um that ghosts don't really like the
flashlight
and that they are not so uh aggressive
actually they're I mean I mean they try
to take you but they're not that they're
kind of chill about it and yeah they're
not so difficult to deal with actually
yeah
nice that's pretty good oh and I did
have a critical fail don't I get a beat
for that too did you risk it
I guess you did huh I did yeah
[Music]
no no that was something before I said I
want to do a critical like an epic fail
on this that's what I meant yeah
critical and then I rolled it but I
succeeded in that I don't know if that
counts oh you risked it so let me see
anytime you fail a rule you may opt to
make it a dramatic failure and take a
beat so close you're you're close but
not quite
um you have to you have to fail it and
say I want to make it a dramatic failure
anytime you fail a role so for example
if you fail it
yeah I failed something and I said I
want that I want that to be an epic fail
but then you made me roll again and then
I rolled a 10.
I'm not sure how that works
let me look at this
[Music]
I'm I don't quite remember either
to rewatch the session
um like I failed but then I had
succeeded which is weird Okay
I need to go re-watch the session but um
I'll give it to you if I go re-watch it
um and deem that it's all good in the
neighborhood so for now
um you have nine you have nine Beats
from this session
um quite a few
eleven eleven beats total
um and then we turned that into exp and
that's gonna be three beats and hold on
a second
I can do math I can do math
you can I can otherwise I'll go call
only oh it's all good we're fine we're
fine so now you're left with three total
beats and four exp yeah
okay yay yeah
um and you were also very proactive this
session which was good to see he came up
with I was like oh let's do this let's
try this and uh that's always that's
always good to see you guys were full of
ideas today and like synergized with
each other well so that was good
heck yeah and then last but certainly
not least we've got Scout
belt buckle
um let's see what we got here good uh
hold on a second at the end of any game
session take a beat one yes
um let's see risk a Breaking Point take
a beat yes another one a good role
playing yes I'm gonna give you two
um
some good some real good role play this
session especially with the vacuum C
ease oh thank you that's some good [\h__\h]
at home you should bring it with you
could be useful in the future yeah yeah
hey it broke yeah no I mean it probably
won't work anymore
um you just role play the vacuum
yeah got some good teamwork popping off
very good
um remember your flaw not this time
complete the mission yes you did that's
uh six right now
um what did you learn today Scout
I learned that
country girls are country strong both
mentally and physically no matter
traumatic events or a fall off of a
magical castle yeah that's that's true
girls
do with this yeah very well put so I'm
going to give you that as well can you
treat a girl and a ghost nice sounds
right it's about seven plus three ten
beats total that you have on the bank we
turn that to exp it has two beats left
over with two exp now in the logs
whoopsie doodle all right two two
um
yes I did
oh God
there's like a little like um three face
in the by Athletics and it's it's just a
cat face but I thought that that was oh
hold on a second all right let me seven
oh I can change it
no I don't keep it I know it's okay that
we turn 10 Beats into two lefts over and
then add five you have five total hits
oh God now it's a lot easier to
understand it's like two two o's and a
three and then uh two slashes for like
um hands in the air like you just don't
care okay awesome yeah yeah and also
that was my Scout's face when she fell
off the castle you're incredible
um Scout you took like a lot of I felt
like you took a lot of initiative to be
like I can make this I can do this and
that's that's also a great sign to just
be like okay well my character's good at
crafting so can they craft something in
this situation
um nice yes so you're getting the hang
of that which is great as well
um with that being said you guys very
well done we'll talk a little bit more
about the conditions that the three of
you outside of scout gain but we'll talk
about that after I've had a bit more
sleep
um yes just pop a bang yes
and I have the pillow yeah that's right
I do have Minecraft uh I do have
Minecraft tonight though with Kiara so
yay oh boy
better get some sleep yes like I'll go
get some sleep do you guys have any any
announcements by the way before we end
off session
well we just have our big collab at the
end of the day yeah
it's gonna be a fun one please tune in
we've got lots of surprises and I have a
song cover coming up and Cali has the
original coming up yeah lots of music
stuff happening guys so Leo
[Music]
as well doing um a panic DNA panel if
you guys are in the neighborhood come
check it out
yeah it has been announced so last
minute so maybe some of you guys don't
even know and maybe yomicon is going to
be close to y'all where is yomakon again
in Michigan right
Michigan I believe Michigan maybe now's
the time to go to Yuma con and come see
us yeah Michigan East Coast
sort of yet I like the Great Lakes yeah
yeah
let's go
it's right let's go oh yeah Detroit
right
Detroit Detroit yeah I'm human that's
that's right belt buckle it's
unfortunately not belt buckle
Midwest I guess or Central us yeah
into your area wait for us yep so please
uh if you guys have some time come hang
out with us with that being said um you
guys did amazing today uh thank you so
much for being a part of this story
you guys are becoming such amazing and
proactive players I'm like very excited
to see how you will handle the future of
the campaign because um it's I feel like
um it's about to get to a bit of a
turning point you see
um I think we're about Midway through uh
the campaign that I have planned so far
um so I hope that you guys will uh stay
till the end
um and see what follows uh and we can
have a nice rest of the season
um and I think it'll be good especially
once you guys uh level up as well you've
got a lot of exp you guys can use and uh
once we all get the hang of it even me
as well there's still things that I'm
learning
um as well along the way
um I'm excited to see where we go from
here guys
thank you
[Music]
thank you for putting all this together
each time
it's only fun because I'm with you guys
so
oh yeah just the truth I hope we can
play it for real someday like together
like like a 3D session or something like
that
I don't really know how we make it I
know that's what I was gonna say correct
actually I mean if we're just sitting
like on a table we could do it with home
3D one day yeah exactly you can do
something fun for it yeah I'm looking
forward to the future guys so with that
being said I'm gonna go get some sleep
but all of you guys you as well in chat
that came uh to support us playing this
fun game together and cheer for us and
and watch the Antics unfold
um thank you so much for joining thank
you for for enjoying the session with us
for for being a part for screaming in
the crowd
um cheering for your fave myth Breakers
you guys are just as much a part of this
as well thank you so much
um
thank you thank you where should we sign
off on you guys should we
[Music]
all right so um we are we are a whole
myth and peace out later guys three two
one oh
[Music]
bye guys
foreign