[Music]
me
do
[Music]
so
for everyone who was here last time just
act as if i'm not repeating myself with
what i'm saying and this is the first
time
okay
might feel like a deja vu but
it's all the first time
we have never heard
any of this ever before
[Music]
i'm counting on you don't make it feel
awkward
[Music]
i'll be the one
to feel awkward
so
[Music]
christmas
it's not christmas yet almost
oh hi yo
good day good evening good morning
hello
yeah i did tweet right well i saw a
comment say starting tweet i did tweet
didn't i
pretty sure i did
[Music]
or did i not send it
no i did i did okay
[Music]
okay
welcome to the first time that i am
reviewing my
new outfit
i mean
it is the first time i didn't reveal it
before so
oh god um with all my heart knock on
wood i really hope that this goes well
okay
i think i'll reduce the bjm a little bit
everyone knock on wood knock knock knock
knock knock knock knock knock knock
knock knock knock
thank you
okay
um
well
christmas and new year's is getting
closer should we maybe
uh i mean not like
not like anyone will invite me to any
parties
um
but should we perhaps
look for fancy dresses because we might
as well imagine that we are getting
invited
this feels so familiar for some reason
you guys haven't heard this before right
only this is it's just me right who's
feeling like i'm having a deja vu just
me
maybe maybe only the first 20 minutes
will feel like a deja vu for whatever
reason this is the first time hajime no
cake in disney
when i say it in japanese it sounds kind
of sensitive
yeah well
okay i shall go online
to you know what let me bring out my
note noto pastor on here let me look at
some fancy dresses online
because
if you can't if you can't you know if
you don't have a reason to buy anything
you might as well still want to go
online and check out stuff there
fantasize about what could be
[Laughter]
yeah
i never have reasons to wear fancy stuff
outside but
yes
yes okay well then uh by the way tweet
with phoenix fashion everybody
here tweet with ano kono hashtag let's
get the hussy
yes tweet will phoenix fashion whatever
you like your thoughts your screenshots
seems familiar i know ryan
actually
all my
literally my whole friend circle went um
to
well some kind of party or like not
really a real party in the sense of a
party
but they hung out together last night
and
they i wasn't invited and when i asked
like why did you not invite me they were
like we knew you wouldn't want to go
anyway and i was like you know what
you're right
you know me too well but you should
invite me anyway even if i'm not gonna
go
[Laughter]
yeah does that happen to you guys you
guys not getting invited but just
because they're actually they actually
just already know that you wouldn't want
to go anywhere
by the way those friends are watching
the stream right now by the way hello
bff and uh
uh
bff
bf
yes
so let's go for some
uh inspiration
oh never seen this one before
what
that looks crazy never seen this before
who got this idea what that's crazy
what that looks insane
what a surprise
wow that looks so fresh
like fresh out of the oven
damn
okay so this is very much kfp themed i
like that you used i'm not repeating any
of this i said i never said this before
i like that you used the kfp the old kfb
logo not the new one behind me no
no you used the old
scuffed one
the placeholder logo
yeah yeah
for the skirt part
that's cute and are there's like
receipts uh around the hips
oh and is that
okay this is something that i see for
the first time there's a little pocket
with like a tiny
is that supposed to be like the fun and
vendor fan and venda what's that in
english like something you you flip
around pancakes with but it's too tiny
to be that
i want to know what that is but more
than that you are your guys's eyes
are probably going more into the
direction of the big fat chicken that's
i don't know if it's alive or if it's a
plushie
[Music]
but it's it looks very fluffy it looks
very comfy and and the neck pillow a
spatula that's what i meant yeah the
neck pillow
which i really need all the time 24 7
because i can't keep my head up straight
anymore
my spine is like nine
my spine is like nine nine nine
okay not funny kiara next one thank you
for this but this is not good enough for
a fancy occasion i needed i need
something fancy
of course i will not be invited anywhere
but i need something fancy
now this is really cute i've never seen
this one before either looks very very
fresh to me as well fresh or fresh out
of the oven but too burnt
very burnt but adorable
i like the art style of this by the way
it's very shojo
shoujo art
shoujo
[Music]
i like the whole burnt aesthetic
i mean
wouldn't want to eat
burnt stuff unless it's only a tiny bit
that's maybe okay oh yeah it looks very
crispy if you if you eat that you're
probably gonna get some illness please
please don't eat me in this outfit
it's not gonna be healthy
[Music]
ash and phoenix oh
okay i can see it like that too this is
really cute i in general this this would
probably be very fitting to the occasion
a lot of wings too a lot of feathers
by the way i have a lot of a lot of
guesses that i want to show you guys so
we're going to go through them somewhat
quickly i really don't know how much
time i will take for all of this i love
this one this one is so good because of
the pants and the color theme color
thing kind of reminds me of velena
also dana was so supportive of of my
stream thank you and i don't know if
you're here right now but
shout out to you dana if you're here
my fellow hollow burps you see her down
there at the picture
yeah this is kind of like military kiana
i really would love to have this outfit
it's so cool
like i could see myself
riding a horse in these pants
how did i say this before somewhere
yeah i also like the the the dark navy
blue
mixed with the white it's just it's just
so fancy
commander kiara yeah
i really really like this one
because like i
i i when do i ever wear long pants
and then there's long i love long boots
that go over the knees honestly that's
that's i love those
but whenever i wear them they always uh
they always tend to fall down i have yet
to find a perfect uh pair of long boots
i guess if they're made out of like
stiff leather then it works but ah this
is girl's talk okay moving on
[Laughter]
oh
cute very orange but it's like a
refreshing orange it doesn't
doesn't like hurt me or so at all i mean
orange could never hurt you guys unless
the
i don't know
unless maybe orange with a face
but this one this one's cute very
elegant uh
i like the the golden elements i am very
much into gold these days
mm-hmm
[Music]
and until the the
you do you call what do you call that
white feather thing that people wear at
fancy parties when they're really fancy
what do you call that is that a shawl
a shawl is kind of different no what's
the actual term for
something like that i mean this looks
like it could kind of be a feather
jacket as well but a boa this is a bulla
ah
but a bulla boy is like a long
long
long snake of feathers right what a
description
anyway
anyway i also do really like the the
hair and the hat the hat is cute
um
thank you for this one very nice i i
could put this one in my wish list oh
here we have another pants uh
ver panzquiada that again looks like
like a commander looks like someone who
would go to war with her chimkins yes as
we usually do
when we watched lord of the rings
together that was some good times wasn't
it chimpkins you remember
yeah again pants high-waisted
riding horse riding pants
[Music]
jockey yeah with a lot of bells like uh
when when i look at those belts it makes
me think of um
[Music]
[Laughter]
because they also have a ton of
bells don't they and they have white
pants too don't they
and they have uh boots above their white
pants too
well that's only the pant set until and
the belts that make me think of it but i
love the design i love also that you use
the color combination of um
of my original outfit
it fits very well but i do have to say i
when it comes to new outfits um you've
seen this maybe in my casual outfit but
you will see it in the imaginary never
never ever happening uh dress
i do like to
um go for different color themes
to
like com if possible as different as
possible
uh to like you know give up complete
give off completely different vibes
so i probably wouldn't go for this color
theme
even though it looks great
but generally i choose i like to choose
different color themes
yes
but i like this one a lot very cool
thank you now this one
this person made uh guesses
of all the myth girls and they all
looked really really cool now i see
you and many others
you know made out of the the shoulder
silhouette thingy you made
wings out of it some people made
shoulder pads out of it some people made
wings out of it i wonder what it will be
i wonder what that will
actually end up as
but i love that there's like so many
golden parts at the edges so many
details and golden um
really cool i don't know what this
what this like clothing style
reminds me off but
it's just kind of like ancient looking
yeah really cool
really cool art style tool though
thank you and i got really curly hair
too i just noticed really really curly
hair it looks cool
okay
[Laughter]
i think uh we're getting uh
past the deja vu part now
which i'm really relieved about you guys
have no idea how
how
how much pressure i feel right now
okay
so this one damn
this one is gorgeous i like the mask on
top of the head
don't know where you got that idea from
but i like it
the color the color color color
color
don't know how to pronounce that but
uh the color reminds me of i don't know
alice in wonderland like the the queen
maybe
but the queen of hearts i don't know i
don't know what it reminds me of but
it reminds me of some someone evil like
a villain
yeah
c-o-l-l-i-r
it's like a like a villain color called
color co whatever
but i do i do like the color
color theme that you chose you're now
different word
with the red and the gold and the black
hmm
very majestic color choices
i like it and and the the boots that are
kind of at the same time tights which um
i love seeing that in character designs
it's maybe not so realistic but
i love like when when it's just one
smooth transition of pants or tights
into
shoes i don't know why but it just looks
really fancy and and smooth
next up we have this one very british
again lots of ruffles
and feathers around the the
upper arms
pretty and we have we have an orange
white gold color theme going on here
kind of uh
makes me feel like a goddess when i look
at this
kind of like a autumn goddess pretty
um very
very floral almost
yeah
i wouldn't say greek but
because uh gouda absolutely smashed it
with her greek theme i love that one so
much
but
but maybe maybe a little bit going a
tiny bit into that direction more like
fantasy
i don't know
fantasy nature greek whatever
[Music]
i know
oh
this one is interesting
i don't know how to describe this it's
like a
warrior
uh
maybe warrior viking
kiana
really badass this one is so cool
[Music]
really cool
the leather elements and all the arrows
this is this that hunter it's a hunter
kiana it could be tiana
this is not kiana this is tiana in
reality
oh
and the
you know the part that where when you
guys think it's wings the brown part
around the shoulders you combined it
with the bottom part and and didn't make
it into my hair the bottom part but you
made it into like a like a
you know you know how the hunters and
and the jon snows
they put like uh
though the wolf uh fur over their
shoulders to warm this up this is what
that is i think it looks really nice
good idea
yeah
i never seen someone before do that with
uh feathers though
instead of fur
valk valkyrie i don't know how to
pronounce that but yes
super cool
next up we have this one
phoenix fashion
now this is something that probably papa
really would like
[Laughter]
wow you really worked with my belt there
yo
kamen rider tokusatsu
hiro ranger
something like that
[Music]
yeah remember back in the day when i was
about to debut and people thought i knew
i knew a lot of stuff about tokusatsu
turns out i didn't i'm so sorry to
disappoint
this is a cool idea
unfortunately this is probably not
suitable for a fancy occasion so let's
move on
oh
this also
gives me kind of like
these
kamen rider vibes as well a little bit
although what i don't know what the hell
i'm talking about anyway
[Music]
the mask is really cool and again we see
shoulder pads that look like wings
it seems to be
uh something that a lot of you guys
have come up with in these suggestions
ah i wonder what it will be really i
have to speed up a little bit wow this
is dark emitted gothic or
said i don't know
oh it's scary almost
this is an interesting theme
villain kiara
but cool i like seeing like a darker
version of myself
uh interesting
this is maybe evil kiara from another
dimension dark phoenix yeah
i love i love the mask thingy though the
mask with the veil and the feathers and
the the the bones of i guess it's some
bird oh no i i hope it's not one of my
chickens
this one is pretty
cool i like the hair it looks really
pretty
and
uh the the
wrappings around my leg nice
i like the blue color that you chose
it's a it's kind of like a calm color
choice
but it works well together um
i like the way you cut my bangs too
who knows should i cut my bangs as well
should i style them in a different way
[Music]
might want to give it a try
sheer midriff yeah
the part around the belly is sheer
see-through oh
divine
oh and i think this person gave me also
some kind of like black wings that are
just like in the back behind the hair
[Music]
all right am i getting wings
oh this one was with all of them i
didn't cut it but do you see that
oh sure let me make it a bit bigger
i like i like all of these
could example skin on it but we know
that for at least four of them
it's wrong who knows maybe my
my design that you did maybe that one is
accurate we will see
for the other four i can tell you
they're wrong by now
unfortunately although i do think that a
lot of like the the gouda one very very
similar the army one
very similar to the cali one
color wise is completely off but anyway
we're here to talk about meek
i love that you know the the dress is
like wrapped around my bubba and around
my neck and so the middle part is
completely open
i really like that and then the dark
dark blue long boots
skin tight boots
should quizell or something like that
oops ah okay that's the first part okay
now i have a second one
good good good good pacing i think we're
doing fine
hallelujah
okay so this one is like kind of like it
reminds me of a sunset
sunset going into night because at the
top it's so brighter and orange but when
it goes to the bottom it's like turning
into
like a dark violet dark uh
dark purple and blue
it's really pretty
[Music]
i like this one a lot and you now now in
this case what do we call it a shawl or
what the the orange thing around my
around my shoulders and around my uh
upper arms what do you call that what do
we call that dusk phoenix cool yeah
is it a shawl
[Music]
a bulla no that's not a bulla a veil is
that a stall
stone
[Music]
fashion terms we need to study them a
bit more
okay that's a shot a fur coat coat scarf
whatever it is maybe a stove
i don't know i'll look it up later
i want to find out what the correct
terms term is i do like the the um
see-through
and kind of like fish net low-key
fishnet uh patterned
uh
gloves
really elegant
really elegant they did a great job i
like that but is on the top of my head
is that a mushroom
is that a is that a red mushroom with
white dots or am i seeing wrong
oh is this me after marrying mario
i would never marry him i'm so pissed at
him
ah this one is by hook and papa
my my papa my artist um gave it a try as
well which i find ironic because he
knows exactly what it actually looks
like
is
i don't know what to say about this
it's like the chickens have taken over
me over my body like you have taken
control over me
no no no
this cannot happen impossible
inconceivable
it's like i'm i'm my own mascot i'm i'm
the mascot of kfp
this is
this is a nightmare
this one is so cute
oh my god i love the shape of the dress
it's like a the top part is like a
corset and then you use like a lot of
see-through things as well which i
absolutely love like the sheer fabrics
and the color choice i love that dark
red
with this
with the golden sparkles oh my god
gorgeous girl
you know it you understand my my likes
this is so pretty
oh my god
it's so pretty
i love the shape of it
good job oh my god
oh this is really girly
this is really nice it kept again this
one also keeps my my original color
theme
and uh
actually makes it much much girlier
i like the girliness i like the ribbons
around the the fluffy
fluffy
feather or fur or shawl or whatever it
is
um
and all the
all the ruffles
nice and you also i like the the head
accessories that you added there and
this person also made the the
the
most mysterious thing in the silhouette
into wings
that's a big mystery a big mystery
wonder woman is
here we have oh
now this color choice kind of gives me
uh
peafowl vibes
[Music]
because of the dark turquoise color
oh i do like that color the dark dark
turquoise
[Music]
and the cut of the dress i like that too
now i'm not sure if the if the bottom
parts are connected or if it's like a
back
maybe maybe it's like
oh maybe it's like you know those beetle
wings that are only like
attached to the back i don't know what
i'm talking about
it's cool though yeah
oh it does look kind of like a christmas
color as well now that you say it i
didn't realize that at first but you're
right
um
oh by the way i'm so sorry i can only
look at the chat in obs so i don't
really see it much if any holo members
are writing in the chat i'm sorry if i
didn't notice in order to keep this
stream as stable as possible i didn't
pop out youtube chat
and so far it seems like it was the
right choice
yeah it does look like a like a forest
color
[Music]
thank you
that was fancy yeah oh
interesting here we have a dark red with
white and golden elements seems also
like a popular color choice
where you implemented the belt and the
the top part the way like you made like
a corset out of it it does me does
remind me a tiny bit of a dandel
i mean
the shoulders are where to bear for that
but but but it does give me a little bit
of daniel vibes i don't know if that's
what you really went for oh kelly was in
the chat sorry i didn't see it but i i i
accept the the feelings i feel the
feelings
i i i i i feel
um supported thank you
the the feeling
that's what counts
what did she say what did she say
what did she say spam it
she said doki doki
she said okie dokie
[Music]
doki doki
indeed tokidoki
about this whole situation
oh i also like the the bare feet here
with the wrapped golden elements around
it um
interesting
cute design me likey
oh
no this one again uses my old my
original color theme very much the
orange and the greens and the dark blue
i look like a look like a fairy or
something like that
and a lot of a lot of uh
like floral elements as well
cute very
cute feet
what
you meant the previous one i don't see
much feet here unfortunately they're
covered up
and that's of course very colorful very
frugal
good i like the the top the shape of the
top with like a tiny
um
like scarf at the neck that reminds me
of like a flight attendant
if you know what i mean
very cute thank you for this
how many more do we have left i wonder
hope the time is okay
uh
okay this one wow this this one also
reminds me like of like a goddess
or something
wow
i like the contrast with the
black which is not too much because it's
only like one one sleeve one glove and
the boots
but it does give me
like
like the vibes that there's like a
second half
like a
evil evil huff and yeah forehead
honestly i am very insecure about my
forehead so i don't know if i would feel
confident enough to pull this off but in
this art i think i'm pulling it off
not sure if if i would feel confident
enough to go to a party with my forehead
all out loud in the air
but i do love the beautiful wavy long
hair
and you know what the tiny wings they're
cute like this makes me
look like a like a like an ancient
uh
being from the heaven
yeah doesn't look like an angel
cool i like it thank you
oh
this one's cute with like short pants
this reminds me of like it could be like
a pretty cute pretty cure outfit maybe
magical girl maybe is that what i'm
thinking of i'm not sure it does get
remind me of something
cute
toes yeah the toes there's a toe window
and you painted my nails thank you
my toenails are painted
in turquoise or so i think
this one is also very girly too with the
the ruffles and the frills
and the ribbons
very adorable
thank you
oh and i see interesting
you made the things that people think is
either shoulder pads and wings you just
implemented it into my hair
[Music]
that looks good
oh
this one i love the colors for this one
wow
the dark blue
it looks so majestic
[Music]
i love the dark blue with the gold and
the white oh my god and the pattern
the pattern around the bottom part of
the dress is so gorgeous
damn
this this is probably one of my
favorites design design-wise
[Music]
ski
i like it and there's some pearls around
the the middle as well
oh here and there there are quite some
quite a lot of pearls
this is gorgeous
[Music]
dark blue is so nice oh
wow this one's really really original
really creative
yeah
very girly too a lot of ribbons
it
this is really pretty
kind of reminds me because we played
alice madness returns on my channel
it it
like it makes me feel like this could be
one of alice's outfits in
like one of the
because there was like an underwater
world for some reason i feel like this
could be in there
i love the boots design
oh my
it's open like sheer around the knees
which is something i never really have
seen before
but it looks so cool
good job
[Music]
and you did something special with my
with my bangs as well
did you give me like
cute earrings i like those too
interesting
oh i think we're getting closer to the
end of it
this one
oh
pretty there's some flowers there's some
sheer socks sheer over knee socks um
you guys like sheer socks
with a mask
interesting mask mask
oh you thought i would need a mask mask
wrestler this doesn't give me wrestler
vibes come on
no no no i won't go wrestling in that
outfit
well i do i don't like the the fact that
you out of the mask might come in handy
[Music]
and this person also made the
the the
shoulder part into
hair
yeah
[Music]
really pretty
i like the the accessory on the hip on
the from our point of view right side
and also i got that smug look in my face
i don't know why i'm looking so smug it
does look a little bit intimidating when
i look into my face
oh
someone
again wants me to
get rid of my bangs i don't know how i
feel about that
[Music]
yeah
it looks so cool when you draw it but i
don't know if i can
really pull that off you
know the shape of the dress is really
nice we have a boob window in the middle
and the dark red color is definitely
something i'm digging
nice very pretty i like the boots as
well
and some some golden elements here and
there but not too much
[Music]
nice window
with the necklace is that a real is that
a real uh
jewel check it out closer up close
thank you
oh
interesting
you always come up with very interesting
designs
this is like uh what was it phantom
of phantom of the uh opera or so vibes
[Music]
i like how wild my hair looks when you
draw it
and this is a another pants design
oh
see it doesn't really have to be a dress
with that silhouette it could totally be
something like that
that looks really badass also looks
again like i'm a villain or something
with the dark dark leather the black
leather hmm
interesting
final boss five oh yeah i could be a
evil boss in a rpg
yeah
i can see myself like that
the mask though with the glowing red
eyes yeah bit intimidating we're at the
end okay that's good because i'm kind of
when i look at the time now i get word
okay well well well wow so many dresses
but no occasion to wear it too
oh unfortunate well well um
very nice but no one invites me to
parties anyway
[Music]
let's go home but
i was about to go home and what what is
it chimpkin you put something on my
table what is it pizza
better be pizza
is it pizza
my pizza pizza
looks like a pizza box it's a ceo of kfb
takanashikiyada looks kind of fancy too
fancy to be a pizza
if it's something related to work i
don't want to see it
should we should we open it up
[Music]
not coming over
new menu item
pizza at kfp kf pizza
uh well let's open it up
what
it's not pizza but it also doesn't
really look like work
what
what is that what is that some fabric
and a leather
it says invitation
invitation
me
for me
[Music]
shall we take a closer look at it
should we read the letter guys
okay well then um
now
let
let me personally
take a closer look at it
[Music]
well this is uh my workplace welcome to
my workplace here this is my birthday
merchandise unfortunately you can't buy
it anymore so i hope you regret it if
you didn't buy it it's beautiful look at
it ooh fries
anyway
here it is
invitation
whoa
here it is i shall read it for you guys
it looks very fancy
i don't know who sent it but
it doesn't say it in the back either who
sent it why is it already open
who opened it did you guys open it
invitation
kfp street 76 is that where we are
australia
there's no wake there weird all right
let's look inside
it doesn't get out it doesn't come out
come on out come on out
oh black
black
black letter
oh
[Music]
oh let me read this it would be in our
greatest honor to receive you as a guest
to our annual mask while at the old city
hall tonight what
old city hall that's so fancy
huh
please wear the dress that came in the
box
oh that's a dress interesting
also we would be delighted if you could
bless us with a musical performance to
spark some light into our lives
spark spark is that a hint
is that a hint oh
oh what a fancy letter
that i totally didn't print out today
myself well anyway this looks good i
think we finally have a reason to put on
a dress got you by the way
wow thank you to whoever invited me
was it you
was it you or you
anyway thank you
yeah
then i guess i'll go there
nice gotta get ready bye bye
hope you guys will come to the party too
bye bye
yeah yeah that was me and my my my
sleeves
thank you
[Music]
okay so that's a dress in there
no no
let me only uh close the box then i'll
i'll i guess i'll get going it's already
uh almost uh 11 p.m if i don't go to the
party now it might be over soon
okay let me call an uber
[Music]
oh
yeah i know i haven't been outside in
like a million years but that doesn't
then
so what so what this is none of your
business
[Music]
shut up just pick me up as soon as
possible i'm waiting it's freaking cold
outside so tell me when you're there and
then i'll come down okay
[Music]
okay bye bye why are you always talking
bye bye bye bye
shut up okay
i ha i hung up i hung up the phone
okay
uber should be coming in a moment
it is time
why talk to the uber driver i prefer
when they're quiet but okay
well
then let's go to the old city hall
wherever that is
whatever that is
okay
um i'll see you guys there i hope the
dress fits
[Music]
i'll make myself
pretty for you guys bye-bye
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
is that mozart that i hear
sounds like boss music but it's multi
okay
open the curtains
oh dear dear god i'm so close and you
weren't really supposed to see that
whoops
you didn't get spoiled at all
okay
well
we're starting off with my beautiful
beautiful
shoes and feet
mozzarella is popping up
mozart is one of my countrymen a good
buddy we're good friends
um he's not alive anymore but um i'm
eternal so i was alive when he was alive
anyway so we have a red shoes
with golden ornaments not a hodor
uh
and we have black
tights that look kind of sheer
okay
interesting don't forget to tweet with
phoenix fashion situations
okay
nice ankles oh pretty ankles
[Music]
yeah
mozart be supporting me
so sweet of him
now we're good friends he's always there
for me when i need him
yes the shoes were in the box as well
unbelievable
[Music]
okay let's let's go a bit higher then
oh
i see a star pattern
you see that too
it's it's kind of faint but it is there
could it be a reference to blackrock
shooter which my papa my artist is the
original artist for did you know
i'm flexing
low-key flexing
maybe he just really likes uh stars
because he they they were also around my
head in my original outfit if you
haven't noticed before
yes yes
star is
everywhere
pretty
we're going lower ah but the higher
we're going higher but the higher we go
the stars become stronger
[Music]
what do i see on the side those must be
those flip flops on the side
i can zoom out a little bit uh which one
is zoom out there he is
i will go back a few steps oh wow
what is that the tingle tangle tingle
toggle bob no tingle tingling tangling
some some ornaments
ornaments
some golden accessories
oh
what is that it moves
so freely
gold
goat i love me some goats so fancy
let's go up higher high higher
oh more it's is that
that wrapped around my land
and moist eyes
oh
i'm gonna zoom out a bit more
so you see a bit more on the sides this
is like this by the way oh unlike this
wall
oh
majestic looking already
[Music]
whoa
look at those shield
tights on my thighs
more golden stuff
wow
i can do
a little pose here
[Music]
want to see more of the gold let's go
higher higher
ties
no
i know how to pronounce it by now it's
fives and tights yeah there's a
difference there
it's not
[Music]
that was poking out on the side
isn't it
wow
it looks really cool very edgy
[Music]
accessory
gold wrapped around my legs
fancy
[Music]
flap flap flap flap flop
okay calm down we want to be elegant and
mature
not stand out too much at the party
okay let's go higher oh how long are
those legs how long are those
oh
[Music]
i see ruffles and i see
the seam is it a seam of the of the
tights
but it seems like it's full tights not
just some socks
but me solder me and i
you might think you can see under the
skirt but
surprise you can't almost it's it's a
secret what's underneath
oh
yes
and it seems like the dress is overall
in that beautiful gorgeous red color
hey who whistled don't whistle at me
[Music]
hey
it's embarrassing don't whistle at me
so there's some pretty
ruffles around the edges
let's zoom out a tiny bit so it fits
nicely
oh
hi gap
ah
i've seen someone draw
like a layering like that as well i feel
like i've seen it somewhere
and i guess my hands are bare
apparently
yeah
bare hands at least there okay
higher higher higher higher higher
oh
nice beautiful fabric
looks very smooth and soft
[Music]
nice hips right okay
oh we see some real beans
same dark red color or brownish color
[Music]
now this is this is where it gets
interesting
this is where it gets interesting i
don't know if you guys just saw that but
oh
did you see that
[Music]
did you see that what was that
dark blue purple not that dark but like
blue-ish purple what is all of that the
middle it's darker don't look what
what
[Music]
a big
what
the hair looks so fluffy like like
clouds
[Music]
and we see
it is like uh it's wings wrapped around
my upper arms like you know that's those
shawls or whatever stones or whatever
but instead of fur we have wings blue
wings
nice contrast color
[Music]
and now we get closer to the bubba
we see a ribbon there oh
oh
now what was that
what
what is that what is that spiky thing
what do you think it is
bronze bounce bounce
we saw some more that was really
mysterious but we see a sheer fabric
covering up my cleavage
okay mozart show is what you got armpits
nice
[Music]
oh
we're getting there we're getting there
oh my god the things that many of you
fought was wings on the side we're
indeed not wings but they wear my hair
my fluffy hair and
those are feathers really long feathers
i thought my ear feathers usually only
went to uh
up to my shoulders but now they go lower
to my
to my boba
could this be possibly something that i
have spoilers before the color changing
of my hair and my feathers depending on
my mood didn't i say something like this
months ago have i done it again
have i done it again
haven't i talked about this
long time ago
that a phoenix with her mood changes her
hair color and for the color i feel like
i've said something like that yeah bye i
did it again but you see the phoenix it
looks like a phoenix on my neckline
golden phoenix
oh my god we're getting into my hair
to my face i'm nervous
okay well
it's happening
are you ready
by the way i can't take off the the
purple or the blue purple wings and i
can take up some other things too
are you ready
[Music]
come on papa one more time
i know you can't do it
hello
it is me
mature kiara the empress the majestic
phoenix
shall i show you some things
don't leave yet
i can do this
and i can do this but those are not
earrings they are actually i just i just
pulled them out i do they actually grow
out of my hair
out of my head but inferior i can do
this
i can also
uh
if i want a pacifier
i can diagno pacifier
and i can do this
my head naked
i can also do only this one or i can
only do this one i love that hair
accessory though i never want to take it
off it's so gorgeous
so majestic so divine
so let's put them on i theory i could
even do this
or this
[Music]
so
that's kind of weird but
this is a mask ball they said correct
well let me put on the
uh
my fancy things again we want to stay
fancy but just so you know i have other
options
but
i do have a mask i do
yes
now let me show you around a little bit
there's still going to be a tiny
performance a tiny tiny teeny tiny end i
want to show you around uh let's move
over
here
this is the full room new room guys
let me show you around quickly so
because there are blue elements in my
outfit i chose to put like uh blue rose
petals all over also here on the side
oopsie let's not move like that
[Music]
on the side
here
and it's nighttime outside it's a
beautiful exquisite ballroom very fancy
and with a piano here that i can even
move if i want to but now look at these
paintings does that remind you of
someone
who does this one remind you of
what could that be a reference to
who is this one who is this one about
what is that one about i wonder
[Music]
chef tell me
ah
yes tentacles about to wreck a ship or
something
you know why
now what is this one about
this one's kind of obvious what could
that one possibly be
the reaper
is also here
in the image
in a mythical version and obviously
that's me the majestic phoenix yeah
yes yes
my original form that i don't show you
usually but this is indeed a photo of me
that um is about uh
2376 years old and this one who is this
one
who is this one
like standing up though i don't know you
don't see the bottom part but it still
looks like it looks like this is like a
person
like the head and the shoulders
anyway
and then this one is maybe my favorite
because i don't know what it is about
magnifying glasses melting over the edge
of the world but it just looks so cool
right
[Music]
i mean not her but i mean it's about her
so yeah this is my super cool new fancy
ballroom
and with that
before we leave please don't leave yet
you you remember the invitation said
something about
spark did they mean
to stream sparks
[Music]
well uh give me a moment don't mind me
here
okay
stop mozart it's enough you you already
made this whole show about you mozart
enough enough
now the real star
the divine majestic divine divine
majestic phoenix
will present herself to you
please listen to
sad sparks
[Music]
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do
hard to tell what's wrong what's right
if yes or no don't know don't know what
to do oh that's done it's hard you're
[Music]
don't forget don't forget don't forget
of your head life is only what you make
it you're gonna be okay
the sparks like the flame turned the
dark of the night and today
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head in the game
gotta make it hot like a volcano strike
a match and burn it up kick your feet
against the table to the beat of your
own drunk sparks like the flames so
don't wait start the
today
[Music]
m
yo
[Music]
foreign
light the flames so the lake started
[Music]
takanashikiya the emperor the empress or
whatever
yay
[Music]
uh that was that was 100 me playing on
the piano
according to demo heartless i
commissioned a piano version from demo
hollis thank you
and yeah i i changed up the lyrics a
little bit made some japanese lyrics
yes and uh i would like to announce that
in about 50 minutes we have a
collaboration on gouda's channel with
all five myth girls and
coming together to play some party games
in the party dresses yeah
and
um
there will be
a
a special announcement
i'm just going to say it there will be a
special announcement
there yes there will be a special
announcement
great
oh god i'm so glad everything went well
you guys have no idea how nervous uh i
was about this and
how pressured i felt but i really really
hope you guys like the outfit um
uh it's it's a i feel like it shows a
very different side of me than the the
casual outfit and the the normal og
outfit and that's kind of what i was
going for to show a different different
kiana
thank you all for coming by and and
joining the party
[Music]
yes thank you for joining me very much
uh and yeah i'll see you guys soon in
the collab of gooda and then uh tomorrow
we'll be probably playing ori for the
whole day we'll see i'll still i still
need to publish my schedule but i hope
to see you guys there please tweet out
of hashtag phoenix fashion if you have
some screenshots that you want to share
or if you have some thoughts that you
want to share and also uh subscribe
phoenix
and in german we
say auf wiedersehen
thank you everybody
thank you
i'm so relieved the hulk
he'll be on the scene
bye bye see you soon bye bye thank you
what's up
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you