[Music]
foreign
the balance is so [\h__\h]
stop I don't know how to balance this
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay
my eardrums are busted
okay
[Music]
I could I'm going to docomo this year no
no no no no no no no no I'm not no no
I'm not
um
and
uh
[Music]
okay no I mean I'm okay but it was
[\h__\h] loud
every time you know
um when I come here there's a like staff
who helps me set up and
I let him go too early
but it rubs so [\h__\h] loud
do you hear any ringing no I can't hear
you yeah why can I not hear you guys
you guys I see your chat messages but I
don't hear them what the [\h__\h]
uh
I can't hear you
wait that's normal
that's how it's supposed to be chat
louder
um
I can't hear no I'm okay I'm good I'm
good my eardrums
can't be destroyed or taken down that
easily
not that easily
anyway I do want some bgm here but when
I play it on VLC
um
then I have a problem with the balancing
so I guess I'm just gonna oh
oh
someone needs to like I want to play
that one on Loop they should send that
one to me
the Sparks Lo-Fi I didn't I don't have
the data that you send it to me hmm
hmm
well I don't think they can send it to
me that quickly
uh they they won't even see my message
probably
can I have Sparks Lo-Fi from
um bgm
as a single file question mark
oh
midnight version
what
I mean midnight version sorry midnight
version
wait was there an official whole life
remix thingy
uh before
oh that that's what it's called this one
this one the one I released yesterday
oh that's what the YouTube
wait
huh no no is it uploaded solo
wait a second
YouTube
as I always mistyped because it's
Japanese keyboard YouTube
Nancy what the [\h__\h]
that's it
Let's Open YouTube and I get a clip
from the energy
what the [\h__\h]
what's that she wrote something
aren't what so quiet I know Sparks
midnight isn't that one from like a fan
doll oh no it's there
oh it's like
automatically generated by YouTube
never mind
there is one on YouTube
automatically generated
LOL
the cover the like cover is cool
wait there's some icons on there there's
mine on there too
which one is mine
anyway so if I please don't bust me
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
that was I'm I'm telling you that was
way louder in my ears than in yours
at least at least we suffered together
that's so [\h__\h] loud in my ears but I
already have it like so low wait maybe
if I um
there's like a huge huge mixer next to
me you know with like five million
buttons and all kinds of things
um
I don't know how to operate that thing
no I wanna
hmm
this one yeah yeah Google Chrome let me
just get Google Chrome down that should
oh yes oh yes but why when I have both
YouTube and Google Chrome unlike the
lowest bit I still hear it so loud in my
ears
oh my God okay
I'm putting Google Chrome on one
but then it doesn't like show up on the
desktop audio because it's too quiet
for for the desktop audience too quiet
but in my ears uh
um one second
no that doesn't change anything
I don't know what button does what
take off headphones with no oh no no no
no
ah oh [\h__\h] it
okay okay you know what
oh
Kelly's been writing to me because I
asked her to write to me like what the
[\h__\h] happened
oh my God
um
hell yeah
[Music]
um
she's okay I told her that you know
since she still has
um probably like still because she like
planned for it she still has day offs
days off right so she should maybe try
to do something within uh you know the
the underground land instead
yeah I mean you can do nice things you
know in in the underground land too hmm
ah let me think let me think okay so
you guys are currently not hearing the
big Jam so [\h__\h] this
um let me just okay this is this is
this is risky as well
um
but I'm gonna throw in some bgm into OBS
now and you guys have to close your ears
I always say close your ears but what's
the right words
or maybe if I do it in studio mode it
won't happen
oh I think that worked
like I don't see it anywhere
oh but I can't
change the volume right now okay close
your ears meet me for side a three two
one
and that looked really loud and obvious
really isn't that bad
I told you that wasn't that really oh it
was it's that tiny bit loud it'd be fun
really how bad was it helpful one I
warned you yeah
okay okay now the only problem is I
don't hear that but whatever is that too
loud to quiet tell me it was a bit loud
but not horrible okay it was probably
better than what I had in my ears before
the Stream
um we're under attack this sounds good
okay air Destroyer yeah sounds fine now
okay
[Music]
can you guys hear me
I'm so good at this studio what the [\h__\h]
is that sarcasm in your comment you
think I can't like read that out of it
out of it and
Road
[Music]
speak up I'm trying
so by the way [\h__\h] we actually only have
three hours because today I actually
have to
um
follow
the time thingy because there's some one
using it after me
um
actually like apparently a couple of
people are
coming later I might be able to say
hello
um
I don't know
ah yeah only once
no more than once upon we might as well
we have to start actually with super
chat this time because I mean I don't
have any other like super long uh
tangent as the one from enoshima
foreign
later because I need to play fireman
have you guys I wanted to ask you guys
have you guys been um playing Fire
Emblem yet anyone anyone foreign
opinions on a chance
no not yet
mine comes tomorrow yes a bit mine's
still downloading
not buying it
picking up tomorrow
so I have some reviews is it good
I don't have a switch like the first few
chapters
the first Kingdom uh-huh
so far it's great I like it so far
gameplay is great is it like the same as
the one that I played
without rewinding I suppose because
I guess rewinding was like a exclusive
thing and there was rewinding right in
the game
a bit different okay it's different to
an extent not the same
not same same
there's a slight difference
more like classic Fe oh
that was divine impulse Divine pulse
pimples
no focus on social elements
what do you mean wasn't there always a
focus on social elements and Fire Emblem
games
[Music]
uh
no that wasn't
[Music]
no eh what only in a few games and what
about all the dating
that that's to me a socialist aspect ass
with double ass
no s-rank support I already forgot what
that was
fruit canceled
that'll hold interesting
eh that's a new thing
okay I'm uh
[Music]
um
that started in Awakening free games to
go
Fire Emblem
[Music]
no no no
no why would I mean no why would I
cancel is there should I not land
I haven't reached a dating part yet I
figured out when you get to the Game
dating wasn't originally
well honestly when I played the last
Fire Emblem
that's a thing that I did find kind of
weird because like it's not a dating
game but putting that aspect into a game
that wants to be taken seriously to me
felt I think a bit weird you know
um yeah but
[Music]
Mating Game was fun though
all those weird tea parties trying to
flirt my way into them and having their
eyes staring at me like
um
we're like in the middle of a [\h__\h]
war and we're having a tea party trying
to find a lover like go to priorities
priorities
people are dying and you're drinking
[\h__\h] tea and asking each other which
one's your favorite cookie
oh my God
[Music]
if you're a student
and let's say let's say they all
haven't gotten lucky before so it's war
and you know that you might die okay
okay I I see like you want to experience
those things
just in case beforehand
it's understandable that's reasonable
don't want to miss out
what is that a meme do you think love
can bloom on the battle is that a meme
so I saw two people writing that
it's always time for tea um
no
adds a metal gear meme uh-huh
[Music]
is any other Ian player gonna play or
playing uh what about the daughter of
the artist bales
any anyone else playing Fire Emblem or
going to play a fire emblem
[Music]
Bay will play we'll try it
maybe crony did she say
crony
oh I feel like I remember very slightly
crony saying she likes Fire Emblem
where's Dad's an imagination oh it is it
is true okay did she like say that I
feel like that I learned that a long
time ago maybe around her debut or so
oh
that's surprising I thought you know
because like those kind of like long ass
RPGs usually I'm the only one playing
them right I thought I would be the only
one
um I mean I thought like maybe Bales
because of her artist being the same
artist
just because of that but I thought you
know normally I'm always the only one
who wants to do something like that to
themselves
yeah I mean she likes she likes Fire
Emblem right but it's it's crony right
but her Channel usually isn't those kind
of like games right she doesn't do like
super endless long RPG streams
I think Hmm Yeah Yeah Yeah so that's uh
unusual
amazing addicted to Persona right now oh
that's also a really long one so
overlapping is hmm
difficult thank you for uh renewing your
membership guys by the way
um midnight Lobster oh yeah right now
it's 2 p.m over here
I only have three hours guys
um but you know uh I had uh no plan for
today so I asked if I could get some
studio time to you know catch up once
more thanks guys for the member oh hello
suddenly suddenly
suddenly you answer my calls
hey hey Ya
shouldn't be less than three hours and
well of course now it's uh two hours and
50 minutes we're so [\h__\h] that's like
nothing in my brain in my brain
free oh
short [\h__\h] tiny baby stream so I I
don't think I will accomplish much in
three hours
but I'll try and Los Angeles
[Music]
thanks guys oh so remember Farmland is
when I started my memory oh that's let's
go that will be like you know kind of
deep and emotional yeah
that's like eight super chats right shut
up guys
I'm gonna show you thanks blue
oh oh my God what's going on guys
see making everything so green it's like
I'm eating a salad
I mean I like salad but
oh my God
okay
just getting rid of this from my list
look I am making a rainbow you guys
wasn't the rainbow because I saw a pink
and then I saw red
oh
but it will not show up in
the super chats the green ones will not
show up so
no worries
but right now yeah you're making it into
a [\h__\h] lettuce rainbow
a lot less busy work eh what's busy work
anyway it's like the pre free 3DS Fire
Emblem games good game so far gender
doesn't affect Romans though some are
platonic friends
well that was the same as the last one
right
I really like the character designs
yeah so
I'm excited uh push the green button
with the green button there are some
green knobs on the mixer
but we better not touch them
[Music]
green ruined everything
it's like the Grinch you're
the salad is
that's not that's that's blue
die
if I touch a button yeah we don't know
what's gonna happen it's too dangerous
okay do we maybe wanna since I already
kind of like Freestyle times you did
okay let's read some super chats how
about that
[Music]
um
so last time uh oh I told you guys a
number to remember do you remember
the number I told you to remember two to
four wow
[Music]
oh you remembered
you remembered so that was
oh interesting Clips oh you guys are
showing me all those interesting Clips
man Japanese Clippers are equipping so
much of my streams these days because I
mean I guess from a Japanese point of
view they're very interesting at the
moment I'm happy I'm happy that you
should
know
[Music]
there's one clip from the Geo guess
system that I did Cali's place a
Japanese clip and the the thumbnail is
me wearing
Cali's casual clothes it looks [\h__\h]
hot I mean I only see it like really
tiny but
yeah
look at that
[Music]
I like it it's edges like I'm Avril
Lavigne
and when I wear that it looks like I'm
Avril Lavigne laverine Levine
thank you Red Envelope oh it's that time
of the year isn't it
thank you
[Music]
Kiana Levine
she's never like that yeah she wanted to
right maybe maybe eventually
okay so you guys said two to four or so
from the Happy New Year's dream or which
one I'm guessing a happy New Year One
Leo stream yeah
you know
this is
[Music]
this one
okay
you know I screamed so much in the last
of collab
so hybrid we're talking so much and
screaming so much it was hurting my
throat so much but I didn't because we
were like non-stop talking and I needed
to keep up with them
so I I maybe took like two sips
of water
during the whole stream
even though my throat was dying
on it
[Music]
s attention
you finally found people who talk as
much as you do no I don't found some
before in the whole life Japan like
money simple actually talks more than me
I guess
she's even like stronger than me
actually well actually
[Music]
but there's definitely like a lot of
similar types to me
in whole life Japan
I'm not sure
if there's many in Ian
who can talk as much and as long as me
[Music]
um
but I have my calm moments too
oh
all right guys
you guys said two to four doesn't mean I
did read two to four or did I not read
two two four
I think I guess I ended it after the
unknown red super chat right probably
because I think I remember this one
I did read two to three okay I mean wait
it's not duty-free it's 217 apparently
between 217 and 2 to 4 there were like
memberships or whatever
what was Dakota tweet about oh I was so
disappointed that nobody freaking
understood it not even Japanese people
but I guess not enough Japanese people
saw my tweet
uh um but
I guess I understand why you guys
wouldn't get it because you guys don't
have access to the movie yet yeah
it's about the movie I think for people
who saw the movie it's very obvious
though I mean no it's no kinono emotion
foreign
like explanations and no one no no one
understood
yeah I was about Susan man
the movie the new Makoto shinkai
movie
oh yeah
how was the movie oh well that's part of
the kind of coil uh tangent and then you
will not get me to start that one now
[\h__\h] you okay
[Music]
always being here this year because you
can get a lot of happy thank you I'm
glad you're my Aussie that's right I
agree you should be here
you'll be here everybody should be here
to get your daily dose of kiwawa and
happiness I mean recently it hasn't been
that daily but I'll be back I'll be back
daily soon you know you'll have so much
Chihuahua that you don't want to like
take the excess x-axis excess kiwawa and
throw it into
one of those compost thingy bins you
know what I mean while you're throwing
like banana peels and all that
yeah and then you'll try to make
something out what am I saying
[Music]
compost
um I mean I don't want to like make it
go to waste I mean it's kind of waste
but then it's good waste
you can grow a tree out of my remaining
excess tangents or so
already a trash compactor dough
hi no no no no no
are you saying that because of my butt
I have a butt yes but
I am not a trash compactor that would
that you basically calling me trash
right now
thank you
thank you soon for the red super Chateau
I wish you Happy New Year too another
question oh
oh long enough for a tall person you're
welcome I wanted it to be really really
really big I didn't want it to be like a
shitty
[Music]
black kids
no
okay
um
[Music]
100 of trash can come back to it
yeah it's a big bracket I don't have
mine yet though I mean I don't know
maybe they already sent it while I was
here could have given it to me directly
[Music]
who's asking for the Toy Story
I guess I didn't put it into the wheel
oh oh
that's the team yellow
I have one more extra tangent that I'm
wait let me check my Discord
not sure if I can talk about yet but
oh
yeah the cat reply it should be fine and
fairy but that's not just I mean I can't
do all of them anyway so let's not put
it on here yet anyway and okay I'm not
ready for the tangent yet thank you
Terrace
thank you
he left us hanging last time
the wheel decides what I talk about it's
not my not my fault no
no no hidden
[Music]
and so I'm not familiar and green Wilder
or Wilderness
[Music]
happy New Year you sexy amazing Phoenix
you sexy thing you sexy baby I believe
in miracles big
you turned me on something like that
what was that I'm going to bed but I
hope this stream is fun for everyone oh
I I get worse I think it was hmm
[Music]
it's such a funny voice that guy sings
it in such a funny voice next on
archived oh yeah if I remember
I don't know if I can sing it though I
don't I think I might only know that
part that one part
did you see the new
let's send the boots movie no there's a
new one
foot did you miss since you last lived
in Japan you guys stop making me tangent
hey hirakatsu I ate it right away Ramen
I I already several times Ramen now
um
craps already ate that been there done
that I already like ate everything that
I wanted to eat I would say Yakiniku
even had shabu-shabu
and yeah lots of good stuff you own an
airport now yes I do turn supers off for
the stream no I need to make a living
guys for the whole time where I've been
um you know sick and all that um
uh
and could not only sick but also then in
Japan where I couldn't read Super Chat
that much uh
it turned off the whole time as you can
see I I still wouldn't have been caught
up but at the same time you know I
you know
I I stream I got it yeah I got it yeah
yeah
and my health insurance is [\h__\h]
expensive you know
[\h__\h] health insurance and then I
still pay extra [\h__\h] that anyway
um thank you
Happy New Year to you too maybe maybe
someday I'll sing that you sexy food uh
song uh for you for you specifically one
day
I pray thank you for the pinky clocking
health insurance prices so real so true
I never thought I would complain about
that in as an Austrian living in Austria
I insist you turned off super short but
you're the one
that wants to chat
you're not helping
happy New Year kfb thank you guys for a
lovely year couldn't be happier to have
spent the countdown with y'all once
again congrats on your Freddy
appearances boss and here's to many more
in 2023. thank you Arthur I think there
will be many more yeah yeah looking good
so far
um
please you have to stare around though
all right in order to see all of that
coming to life and happening all those
dreams coming true you know better be
part of that
and celebrate together and then be happy
that we accomplished it together thank
you all for Happy New Year
guys you can stop now
you can stop
I'm not starving
I'm not
and Nathan Colton thank you
maybe I'm starving for your love
maybe I'm just starving for your love
[Music]
no oh stop oh
that's too much love
uh guys guys guys guys guys guys guys
guys guys guys guys guys
[Music]
from my favorite Japanese uh Cafe
chain Cafe and chocolate and some
pineapples
for breakfast but that's like a really
realistic answer that's not really what
you wanted to hear right
you honestly is what I very much
appreciate here's your living foot thank
you but the thing is the more money you
guys give me the more expensive my
health insurance will be
I don't know I don't know if that really
like
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah what
it um yeah but I guess it like
bound no it does no I don't know I don't
know man I don't understand
but I don't want you guys to get a bad
image of Austrian health insurance if
you have a normal job it's totally fine
it's just because I'm like you know
independent
um yeah
just just because of that
and as I'm not even not only just an
independent but I'm also like you know
an independent that is doing
well it's so weird to talk about stuff
like that
so I think there's a if you are an
independent person
with like a more of a normal income than
your health insurance probably isn't
like literally
[Music]
like ripping you another [\h__\h]
anyway two hours 40 minutes left
[Music]
oh man
[\h__\h] short go go go go it's like
imagine like a marathon you guys are on
the sidelines you're glad that guys are
like you should be throwing a lot of
bottles at me okay maybe not not
throwing them at me but instead you're
throwing super chats at me you should
just like not throw them at me should
offer them like kindly yeah don't throw
them at me because then I might stumble
over them as I am and then I can't get
to the [\h__\h] goal
okay okay but in the end it's my fault
it's all my fault look look what I have
done to myself wait what what did you
just say
should be around 550 per month for
independent people
you you're talking about normal earnings
independent people right
not people I you know right Alex
I don't know about the normal like that
doesn't it fully depend on how much you
earn I don't know man maybe not for
normal people
um
what
Vapor Rub
we don't have Vapor Rub I think
um
I guess I'm not normal
I'm not normally anyway stop okay okay
it's so like how to say it like it's so
like raw it feels like a really raw
but that's more like a Japanese that's
what I would say if I was speaking
Japanese
this this this topic feels so raw if you
say that too in English
it's like just too real I guess so let's
not talk about it feels too real
it's awkward
it's [\h__\h] raw put it on the grill put
it on the grill like Emma did
oh I wanted to say one thing no I should
say that in the tangent
but I'm already permanently dancing
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] hell where was I
foreign
no not midlife
I hope I'm far from that
I have a life crisis yeah yeah
stop stop
and day and light night maybe am I there
maybe not Nathan caught the neck let's
just go back and like beep beep beep
keep packing up and then going front
again okay daylight night thanks for the
pinky happy New Year koala I can always
be in chat but I always catch you live
oh what if you always catch me live why
can you not always be in chat
where do you say you always catch my
lips are you here now daylight night I
think it might be a decent time for
America not as bad as like last time I
think
right work podcast mode maybe yeah
podcast daylight night can you write to
me now
working on the road oh I guess so
well if you're hearing this thank you
all the stuff you do here's to another
year of Halloween it's it's here I'm not
missing him right
[Music]
I don't see him another YouTube of holy
and another year to home life and
another year of chasing the idol 3
. you know uh I feel like recently
my motivation as a streamer and my
motivation as an idol
uh or towards Idols I don't know
has been increasing because of all the
things that I've been like
um facing
that I've been up against and yeah
um
so I am I am motivated
motivated
pay you daylight now thank you soon
happy New Year
[Music]
um
foreign
about the neighborhood game oh my God
yeah but even if like I don't know what
I'm supposed to say
it's such a random thing like hey did
you play the neighborhood yes I did ah
okay cool oh that's so old right yeah
it's really old oh yeah cool oh
such an age game that nobody knows right
yeah yeah okay cool
what what
the the
topic doesn't really like
turn into a conversation I don't know
nothing wrong with it being a bit random
no I don't [\h__\h] watch SpongeBob why
would I watch the new SpongeBob episode
I don't even have access to it I don't
know and I don't wanna
hell no
why are you so excited like
how did you watch it as if as if I ever
mentioned me liking or watching
SpongeBob before
as if that's a thing here
[Music]
you should know better
okay
hey
but you know by watching that movie
it really like
you got you guys know how I don't watch
like anime currently that actively at
all
um but that movie was absolutely
absolutely crazy insane so good
and if there's like animes on that like
quality level uh with a with a story
that like deep and moving and like cool
then throw it at me because yeah
I would gladly watch it um don't spoil
it yeah I I wish I could talk about it
but you guys like don't have access to
it yet so it's not very reasonable for
me to ruin it for you and spoil it for
you I don't wanna
um Violet evergarden okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay that is true like
yeah okay
on a level like that yeah
I did watch your name I did I did
I did I watched uh a lot of other Makoto
shinkai movies I think
um
so good
so I think I watched silent voice too
wait watch it together ah yeah we did
what about this point [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] off
with the SpongeBob movie have you seen
that no I want to Bow yeah
and now I think it's not in the cinemas
anymore anyway ah
but I have a double Jones
thank you for the pinky happy New Year
thank you for all the Townsend streams
of music new and Hollow Pro have given
everyone such an amazing such amazing
concert this year and can't wait to see
what's in store next here's to another
year and I'll continue to support you
Michael
thank you thank you thank you soon
I will need your support there's gonna
be lots going on and maybe there will be
ups and downs again and hopefully you'll
be there
all of it thank you Happy New Year to
you hi in the chat now too
have you guys noticed that
um my chat box currently I I stole it
from Ina
because the other day when we did the
sponsored sponsored thingy I was like
yeah I'm in the studio and I like I
don't have like yeah I don't want to
like remake the [\h__\h] code for the
chat box again you give me like your own
and she gave me hers and now I just kept
it
yeah that's why it's purple
[Music]
um
it's only on this I'll be as the studio
OBS that I have now though
um
purple like my beautiful eyes
does this make us all tacos no of course
it doesn't no time to focus okay
you you you're like you pulled on my
sleeve and like you you brought me back
to reality you're like I'm I'm like like
trying to go into another dimension and
you're like
cut it out
[Music]
the game of creed thank you neon sign
thank you thank you PNG
oh wait did I do that in PNG oh [\h__\h] no
I hope I helped that next time we don't
have so many problems and will have a
proper streaming environment and I think
we will I think we will next time I go
to Japan so far from what uh I know uh
things are gonna be
like you know I'll have
something to stream with and all that so
it will be better
you said you get nervous before every
whole talk but how nervous were you for
this happy New Year oh I was pretty
pretty nervous yeah I mean
um
we did have like a lot of fun already
before the stream started but like the
time suddenly started going so fast in
the last hour before the Stream
that uh I barely noticed it
sorry and then suddenly uh
uh yeah suddenly it was like okay
starting in five minutes and I'm like
what the [\h__\h] yeah
uh that was that was
but then you know I didn't even have
time to think like or be I didn't have
time to be nervous I had to like
suddenly be there and then
yeah and then I was in it and then
there's just
you have to
give you all and be part of it fully
but yeah yeah
very very very new situation that I was
thrown into
and I hope there will be more of those
so I can get used to them
you naturally that kind of stream
am I am I like I actually like oh I
don't know did I do well I already
forgot I think I did well I think I
blended in nicely hmm
um
[Music]
when you have all that [\h__\h] that I had
like bronchitis laryngitis Etc is there
like
a path that opens up between your nose
and your throat
that wasn't open before that's just like
casually exchanges fluids like because
I feel like I have a new like path I
don't know
it can
[Music]
it's always been there
nasal what what the drip isn't drip good
post nasal drip
nasal drip
postness of drip is wearing more mucus
than normal cabbage and drips down the
back of your throat you may feel like
you have a tickle on the back of your
face
drip can be bothered some condition that
can lead to chronic cough the glands in
your nose and throat are constantly
making mucus because I I feel like
no I don't know whatever
[Music]
attention knowing Ed do you guys have it
or had
it you sound like you had it
you might just be more conscious of it
now after you were coughing up like him
so much hmm yeah yeah possibly from time
to time sucks put up with it often oh no
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm imagining the tickle and I don't
like it
common oh
there's just like one thing
um that I saw you know when I knew that
I had bronchitis and I was looking up
things uh I read something that if you
don't go to the doctor early enough and
you just like let it happen on its own
for too long there's a chance that it
turns into a
um
[Music]
or something
that sounds so weird
in German there's a word like Cornish
but they didn't use it it was a really
really weird
[Music]
flashlight
s in English is
delayed bronchitis
[Music]
but I guess it's just chronic then I
don't know no but it's not
no no it's just like it said something
like like it can take like weeks months
uh to really fully heal afterwards
chronic means that you didn't have it
forever
this didn't seem to imply that thank you
blue
cat
oh well oh well bird Focus ability is so
real shut up I can focus I can focus
semi-chronic
no chronic means it comes back chronic
means long term oh oh okay okay not
necessarily forever not a hotel okay no
we've had more into Super chats shut up
we're dead
um
thank you neon sign once again happy New
Year to you not slow dancing for the
pinky and happy New Year Buzz thank you
for all your hard work this year thank
you too I did my best and you know even
though there's times where I wonder is
it even worth it uh I've got a lot of
motivation now so I'm gonna do my best
for a while and then if I lose my
motivation again and you guys will
hopefully be there to motivate me Euro
school thank you Happy New Year and I am
a beep can
I'm a beep can
Christopher Rand thank you soon for the
pinky Kiana you are what
amazing made the Super Chat be my token
of appreciation to you as 20-23 rolls in
no matter the time or place my support
for you will always remain you're an
inspiration to Manny keep up all the of
the great work thank you oh very much
that's so sweet one million percent
that's a lot of zeros thank you
thank you soon I am really really
grateful to have your support for such a
long time and then I guess it's safe to
count on you for the future right happy
New Year to you and let's have a great
2020 free okay thanks for being part of
kfb Christopher what sweet words very
very sweet
fried squirrel thank you for the recipe
Chad if you want to thank you so much
for this wonderful year you have done so
much this year and shared so many
stories with us from your travels across
the world to your pretty concert I
really wish the best for you on this new
year my beloved kamikazel lady patola
many nicknames
I don't get cold uh Kami or Kaiser that
much though
that's interesting Lady Lady ladies
understandable because that's an
official title I have yeah
anyway
yeah thank you very much that's Grove
for being part of it yeah we had a great
year
let's hope for and live a great year
yeah yeah and you'll be part of the the
journey Pride screw all right I'll put
you in my luggage I'll take you with me
so say goodbye to your family and thank
you
Happy New Year
[Music]
thank you
uh Happy New Year Dental crazy dance
already the third time two hours remain
oh my God it's like [\h__\h] Majora's
Mask but no two hours and 15 minutes
okay you're too early that's already the
first time celebrating with kfp oh
you're right it's the third happy New
Year that we had so far oh my God
also the anniversary of the day you
crashed into me and Mario Kart 8 and
sent me to the YouTube what you're
saying that I I said I you you crashed
into me even though according to you I
crashed into you well I'm pretty sure if
I sent you to The Newsroom then you
crashed into me not the other way around
gonna come out now I've been in here so
long I forgot my employee number wait
did I send you what for Holier it is a
usual room one year for you were
crashing into me
I don't remember that
I don't remember that valcus where are
you
I don't remember that at all
yeah that's that's a long time huh
yeah I feel like um
you never let me out what did I not give
you a time
oh maybe I didn't give you a time huh
done two year sentences before
hmm okay Bacchus you're out
sorry
uh my what's how to say
um my kankaku my
I don't know what's the right word my
feeling for
time for sentences for the usual room
in in the beginning may have been a
little bit like unbalanced
um
yeah kankaku means plant no K Taco means
plan you don't know [\h__\h] about Japanese
language don't act like you do
[Music]
sense of time yeah maybe it was a joke
really are you sure now you're trying to
make excuses so it's not so embarrassing
by you
think you know Japanese by watching
anime anyway
um
so welcome back out of the usual room
into the real world valcus Happy New
Year
go enjoy yourself
oh
Young
[Music]
uh
Happy new year thank you for being here
I'm happy you're my own Seasons I missed
my birthday when you missed your
birthday
this will also be my birthday supergen
I'm so glad you're a baggage man why
were you not there for your birthday
did you so leave your body
I guess you just mean you forgot to send
the super chat or so but I like what
you're implying it's funny
how do you miss your own birthday I
guess it's just when you forget about
your own birthday that kind of means you
missed your own birthday hmm
well slept through it oh no no that's
you can't do that man that was the best
of us no it shouldn't like that it's
impossible I don't believe people who
forget their birthdays
I don't believe them
[Music]
oh you can't you can't forget your
birthday
it's trying to be funny
how can you forget your birthday
maybe intentionally yeah but then you're
not really forgetting about it you're
aware you're aware it's happening
[Music]
some people are too busy to remember
it's not something you remember it's
like even written in your your password
or whatever I feel like it's like
engraved in your brain it's not not
something you have to remember it's like
it's like right there in your head
anyway you you guys wouldn't get it you
would get it you won't get it
oh I'm so glad you're back in Japan you
say but
um I'm honestly very glad to be back in
Austria very soon
because as much fun as this trip was
um I'm really exhausted my social
batteries are drained to the absolute
over limit
I want to go back to my katos
I want to go back to my bed I wanna like
sleep in
like I noticed like I slept a good
amount of time last night but yeah these
past three days or so
I was so tired
um
so yeah I'm ready to be at her with a
binge five Bloom for eight hours yeah
yeah as long as I can sleep in then I'll
play find one for eight hours so that's
okay
[Music]
not only hold out as long as you have
but also be super entertaining at the
time entire time thank you hmm
um
[Music]
I want to go back to hiki Comedy live
please yeah but even if I go back to it
it won't be for long but yeah for now
I want to go back to it I'm very happy
to go back to it very very happy now
so
you know I originally planned my
schedule with like
one or two open days
uh
each week
hoping to like recharge my social
batteries on those days but I guess I
ended up not having time for that I
don't know also my body I'm so exhausted
like Ugh I'm gonna go to Setai um like I
guess it's like Physical Therapy plus
massage later
[Music]
because
I mean I have obviously really sore
muscles
um
and uh yeah but my body is like
like
I need to recharge my body and my social
batteries both of it
hmm no longer sick from the sound of it
oh yeah I mean I still when I wake up
and I saw
feel like I need to cough up some flag
but there's barely anything coming out
which kind of pisses me off because I I
feel like there's something but it's
hard to get like the last little itsy
bits out I guess yeah but I would say
I'm healthy yeah in terms of
bronchitis yeah
plane ride must have been painful
uh it wasn't so much painful it was more
like
um you know I had I at the time of me
flying to Japan I still had a lot of
like um and cough attacks
so it was hard to hold back because
obviously you don't want to you don't
feel like you can let it all out
in when you're sitting in an airplane
with the same people for 12 hours or so
um
but that was you know I was pissed that
I didn't have a window seat but in
hindsight I I'm really glad I didn't
have a window seat because this way I
could run to the toilet so many times to
like spit out like a month and so on and
because I I drank so much liquid in
order to calm down my throat so yeah I
had to go to I don't meeting many times
I just woke up what the time is good
morning sunshine you missed some
tangents uh that are like trying to
squeeze themselves in between the cracks
of the super chats but I haven't gotten
to the main tangents yet yet
it was terrible
and a traveling sick is that so nice but
which Islands did you meet
that wasn't I was looking in the mirror
and I I saw an idol there I don't know
man
I don't know who it was she didn't talk
to me
you know who she was have you seen this
Idol only one hour left no two
she's stressing me out
black Rich negason mod arcade thank you
sir
oh wait what groups didn't I didn't even
say happy birthday to you girls didn't
have a ballet the birthday even though
now it's already so long ago
but you miss your birthday I don't even
know when your real birthday was
must have been ages ago
happy happy belated birthday
[Music]
next time don't miss your birthday if
you're not gonna come to your own
birthday party who else who else is
Gonna Come
I mean you wouldn't even know if someone
else came if you're not coming you know
so it's important to remember your own
birthday party
I mean I guess it was leaving the party
but next time next time
my birthday is the same week as koalas
so I don't really complain when no one
knows no
so I will notice if you tell me
tell me
Black version one architecture 956
Nico no thank you for the pinky
happy to use my OC Houston have a great
year with lots of wonderful things to
look forward to really enjoyed so many
streams of yours this year your music
and stream con that you've created have
been so amazing never doubt yourself
thank thank you yeah I was it was mostly
song covers though this
past year right only one original
well
[Music]
we're doing song covers too but
hopefully this year we can have about a
couple more original songs you know an
album would be nice if I make an album
though this year I'm not sure if I can
do an also a single if anything I'll do
it like Cali and make music videos for
some album songs maybe favorite night
February was also 2022 oh I guess it was
that felt like 2021 to me
oops
that was 2022 May
whoa
I did I did do two songs
[Music]
okay okay well then it wasn't so bad
then
did pretty well in terms of music
production
thank you Nico no
I'll requested
I was busy in 2022 as well yeah I am I
always I always am
[Music]
okay
your night still feels new to me oh well
that's good
let's listen to it before the stream
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
Happy New Year I received your goods as
well I thought it was a mouse pad but
the blanket arrived I was shocked oh
when you ordered that because in the
picture it looks I guess just like a
square thing you thought it was a like a
mouse bed or like a keyboard pad thingy
but it's sad blanket okay maybe blankets
didn't translate so well into Korean
[Music]
oh
there's no mouse but I'm sorry I think a
blanket is better though
I feel like a blanket is better
this chocolate has massive note fits on
the desk
yeah but it fits on your big bed
I already have a mouse but no we have a
we have a
really mouse pad it's like a desk pad
right
sleepy yes I wish I had the blanket now
that I could lie down and I could sleep
that's why you guys need the blanket
on desk mat yeah
your first birthday oh yeah I'm talking
about that one but it's more like a desk
mat yeah
[Music]
hi uh thank you Ivana Happy New Year to
you too I will do my best to learn
Korean this year so please help me out
okay
mwah Gary ganza thank you for the red
super chat happy New Year attention
thanks for helping me get through this
here uh especially when I was terribly
sick my birthday was a few days ago oh
and I'm glad I can spend the season with
you on kfp I'm looking forward to an
even more eventful 2023
thank you thank you thank you yes I I
hope so I hope I can like keep up with
everyone's expectations and so on and
like I know I I wanna like re
what's the word I wanna I want the hype
to come back but it's hard I don't know
if I can do that alone with my own power
definitely not My Own Strength is not
enough to
you know get the hype going again
um but yeah I'll work hard and we'll see
where it goes reignite yeah reignite
rekind the last one I was thinking about
so listen there
yeah but I'll do what's within my
just um
[\h__\h] English can't speak English
within my
[Music]
um
yeah capabilities yeah yeah
grasp yeah yeah yeah yeah
so please continue support thank you
thank you guys and happy belated
birthday
hope it was a good one for you drag off
th.com just want to say Happy New Year
everyone I'm so proud and glad to be a
member of the community even I if I just
look most of the time my only regret is
not joining sooner oh man you don't have
to regret that but regardless I still
have these memories that help me laugh
and smile on the days I couldn't ah
thank you so much you definitely a
lurker I haven't seen your name much
around but thank you for supporting so
being here after a long time not giving
up on kiwawa believing in koala I wish
you Happy New Year and thank you so much
for the red super chat you're welcome to
show your face more often you know you
don't always have to lurk you you all
welcome to you know
say something in the chat every now and
then I'll gladly have you anytime except
as well have a new year attention Okay
features of fun-filled 2023 hope you can
kick it and kick the sickness and feel
better soon yeah I think I could have
kicked its butt although oh man I feel
like it quickly kicked my butt more than
I could have kicked its butt it was
rough rough I don't want to get that
sick anymore please
[Music]
um
whoever gave me that sickness [\h__\h] you
and if it was the weather then [\h__\h] you
you suck weather you suck
on wood knock knock I won that fight in
the end I did but it was a long long
exhausting battle thank you MVB thank
you
thank you super who I'm Blue
oh
[Music]
got no time to lose
there's a new twice English song
and I liked it
but I don't think it's as good as their
previous English song that one was more
catchy to me but who knows like maybe
maybe it will get to me
when I listen to it again
maybe it will catch me more but yeah
it's I'm right right the fields was
catchier I've got the things for you
yeah yeah
you have stole my heart oh yeah now I
let it go oh oh no now let's go
how can you compete with that oh they
set the bar for themselves to hide
so good [\h__\h] oh man so good so good
twice
[Music]
foreign
have you ever listened to Girls
Generation of course back in the day
yeah
many many Girls Generation songs yeah
they were they were so popular back then
you know Mr Taxi Texas
[Music]
yeah and of course Gigi and I don't know
I don't remember what songs but
I yeah I did listen to them sometimes
[Music]
yeah that was a good one but it wasn't
my favorite aloe group I liked others
more back then hmm
[Music]
I like your your profile picture it's a
chicken give me Chicken in there and
whatever the other thing is it's a ghost
a ghost takodachi something I don't know
isn't it oh what is that toilet paper
donation thank you looking for the top
Danke Schoen Dustin King thank you soon
oh I see the end guys of that stream
super chats which is a big step for us
and then I'll read some uh then I'll
tell you a tangenti Chris thank you for
the pinky happy New Years from PST might
not be able to catch everything live in
the few upcoming weeks but we'll always
support you can't wait to see what the
new year brings us love you and take
care attention well are you here now
because now I think it's a decent time
for you maybe maybe not maybe not I
don't know but tomorrow's tomorrow is a
Sunday so
don't have to go to sleep early right oh
there you are surprising only missed one
stream
[Music]
you know I just wish that I feel like
all the streams I did were like good and
we had big fun and all that but most of
them were like 95 uh Japanese
so
I feel you know it's it's kind of a
waste that you guys can't enjoy all of
that fun
um
I wish I wish there was no language
barrier
tried to you know with Louis and hatama
and Superman
the whole laughing didn't work out this
time but you know I tried to get some
some English cool ABS in there
um
[Music]
there's not many English speaking
members in whole life Japan
um
yeah can't do much about it translated
Clips are godsend yeah but you only get
like Snippets right and I wish you could
get everything
um
so that's that's multi night but maybe
kfp can see it from a different point of
view maybe you can see it as like you
know
um
me just staying or having fun bonding
and getting Japanese Bros to know me
and I don't know
um and it has its good sides definitely
so I'm glad I can I could collab with so
many members and with all of them I made
such fun memories and that's the most
important thing
period
[Music]
didn't bother watching most of the
collabs you should have though they were
hella fun but I guess if you don't
understand Japanese then that's a
problem yeah
[Music]
um the past two and a half years
I don't think I've been that much on
other people's channels right
but yeah these past off collabs have
been on so many different channels
because normally collapse most of the
time I organize them and therefore I put
them on my channel and this time
pretty much all of them were organized
by me anyway but we had a lot of them on
other people's channels because number
one I thought wow they're gonna be
mainly Japanese so having it on my
channel is not the smartest thing to do
and number two
um well I'm traveling with a laptop
without Photoshop and all that so
setting it up is meant and this way my
Japanese friends could make the
thumbnail and set it up and all that in
their usual streaming environment which
saved me some trouble and yeah
logistically yeah yeah yeah
golden stream was pretty good and I
don't know Japanese I can film but for
the corner of the stream I tried to
squeeze in some English here and there
as you may have noticed
um since it was my channel anyway
oh
I was wondering about you guys because I
remember from last year during lunar and
New Year you guys sent so many super
chats but I thought you guys all left me
because nothing happened on New Year's
but now I remember it was a different
date huh
so it's now New Year
Lunar New Year today
well I guess that when was it
or not yet
or tomorrow
whoa
I was like I thought I thought that oh
my lunar fans
just left me
oh he didn't even have new year yet
oh [\h__\h]
hmm
don't be silly
hey
Muna seems like a fact of future
well I don't remember the days why
wouldn't I I don't celebrate it but okay
[Music]
arrival time
what lunar is a game
where was I where was I where was I
where was I where was I think uh here RS
thank you for the pinky happy New Year
not too long ago I reached two years of
membership oh you have an incredibly
positive influence on my life and I'm
happy to see more years of you
oh really I've been a positive influence
in your life oh wow
I'm probably not such a positive
influence on like children because
they'll learn swear words from me but
you already know them so it's not like
I've ruined you thank God
very much so
oh my sweet onion I'm also an onion
sometimes
we are onions
I will keep you safe don't worry onion I
will not put you into a curry anytime
soon yeah layers
onions have layers and you have so many
beautiful layers RS I would love to peel
you but I will not I'll keep that fun
for another time
yeah anyway thank you Happy New Year to
you too
and um
let's have a fun 2020 free
I'm excited too more time together hell
yeah peel me please
about to reach halfway point of like my
total or ah you mean time time
everyone on the clothes thank you for
the rest of the chat happy New Year
Tango I will have to watch the Vlog
because I'm at work but want to drop by
at PST New Year's thank you well you're
probably here right now too right if
you're PST happy New Year belated to you
Happy New Year to you happy new in your
show Happy New Year and pst2 happy New
Year to you
thank you for the support Evie in 2022
and I will see you or I am seeing you in
2023 so
um yeah kfp is very lucky to have
to have happy although I don't see you
in the chat where are you I wonder
thank you soon for the support though
thank you
hopefully this year you don't have to be
vodking so often but well
well well
no two hours remain oh no I guess it
can't even be a three hour stream
wait a second
eh I'm confused I can stream until 5 PM
jst
thank you
simpleton black Richard nugget show and
spice chicken itchy
foreign
[Music]
artists
um
ass
[Music]
a
guys
hi
[Music]
I don't know that
is
[Music]
foreign
thank you
yeah told me to take care of my throat
but like you know in the night this
night again I had the the humidifier on
like a big humidifier right next to me
in the hotel room
um but I woke up so many times with
afraid that felt I was like dry
and I tried that like humidifying mask
but it also didn't really help
so yeah
I know what's going on I want winter to
end now please thank you but
February is still
still winter right I think
until March I'll have to continue
suffering perhaps
any plans for February 14 is that
Valentine's well I guess I'll be
streaming what else should I be doing
what 14
I'll probably be streaming
oh I think I if I have a plan then it's
probably um
um
work but try closing your mouth when you
said well I I am I think I have my mouth
closed when I sleep
I think so I have it closed when I wake
up hmm
[Music]
where was I oh
happy New Year celebrates
[Music]
then why is it dry well because
winter hasn't started yet in Texas is it
going to start
are you gonna have delayed winter in
Texas
it's winter like in Texas Joe
then we saw
the humidifier right yeah I don't know
at all
how does you guys are stupid
why are most of you here in this stuff
spring starts on the 21st of March what
what it's cold
what what
depends on the prior Texas warranted I'm
a real they've already had one too Texas
that big that makes a difference
[Music]
in Texas gonna snow a month or two ago
oh
please don't insult those words
sorry
but I mean can you claim as a chicken
that you have a really really high IQ
[Music]
no
no celebration my favorite sanctioned
for the words of a chat here's some New
Year's money glad you had fun and
connected with Gamers and Subaru minus
okay it's like a
whole equation it's like I'm in math
class Gamers plus Subaru and then in in
the brackets minus
equals what though what does that equal
hope you can have more uh like that this
year oh
but less math please less math that's
already too much
equals cute
isn't there a name for gamers plus
Subaru even if there is what about a
Gamers plus
um
well that doesn't need a name doesn't
happen so often
hmm
honorary Gamers oh I have Fabs
[Music]
that is already game responsible to
minus okay you no no no no
okay Fabs eh okay fams ah
huh
okay okay I'm confused
ah that is I am it too ah ah I forgot
about that oh okay fans
weird
I guess it
is
just the starting letters
and to me I mean I think you guys may
have the same sensation but as an
English-speaking person to me it's like
okay fam
like people say that don't they
yeah oh okay fam
what does that even mean though like I I
see it a lot but what does it actually
mean
[Music]
this is just like okay dude or
it stands for family yeah I guess that
but that's like okay sure right okay I
thought so I thought so
okay fam
okay okay fam
yeah that's that's what I see when I
read that name
and anyway Merry Christmas
thank you for the words of a chat Happy
New Years to you thank you for the
generous donation
I hope you already had a good start of
2023 going good so far for me at least I
hope it's the same for you
[Music]
I know
foreign
[Music]
yeah give me one second there's one more
Super Chat here Patsy thank you for the
Super Chat action and here we go
which was a big hurdle just because
since it's a New Year's stream it had so
many Reds and pinks okay
thank you for bearing with that
is
[Music]
spin spin spin spin spin spin wheel of
tangents where will you go wheel of
tangents let's go
[Music]
laughs
too bad
the winner is
Spin to Win what tangent will fake Jews
it does she wants you
okay okay guys
let me open my memo Joe
um I think I wrote some things down I
think I did
school school school school yeah okay
there's not that much though to be
honest because
um
originally
I had something planned of Subaru Senpai
for the whole day and I preserved that
day with her uh like over a month before
it happened
we can talk later yes
kept on screaming give up a face please
no talking it's so funny
my shoulders
that was funny yeah but I I I
um reserved it long time ago and then
um actually
uh so we were supposed to stream but
before that we were supposed to hang out
together
but there were some
things that kind of like
made the situation a bit difficult so I
said can we just have an off collab
instead
you know not so much of hanging out but
just to off call them
and she said yeah okay
and then it seems like she kind of took
it as the whole thing was canceled
and that was like on the day before or
so
and that's why she then ended up
adding another collab I guess kind of
last minute on her Channel
planned it like last minute and then she
came back to me and was like oh my God
[\h__\h] I misunderstood I thought it was
completely canceled so now I already
have a collab planned
and I'm like oh oh
so then we squeezed this one back in
um but now it was kind of not so much a
priority anymore uh yeah yeah a little
bit awkward but
um we still had uh fun it worked out in
the end yeah
so
uh it was earlier than it was supposed
to be
and yeah but I was like ah thinking so
hard what we should do so we're gonna
stand by told me yeah how about we
um play some like game that oversees
you can do only with pen and paper like
Tic-tac-toe and then I was like trying
to figure out one but the ones that we
came up with because I also asked you
guys I didn't feel like they would be
really entertaining but I I understand
you know I understand you guys want more
um like tattoo dance like chit chatting
streams and I agree like
um especially with members who are so
good at talking I don't mind doing those
but I still wanna take the opportunity
and play a game together anyway so I've
been trying to mix it guys like on
purpose but then both
we know where the collab with coroner
and the collab of Louis and I think also
the collab was supervisor said by all of
them you know I started trying to force
some SATs down and then the comments
they would always becomes like when are
you starting to play the game and I feel
like that's like that was always
Japanese Bros though so I was like I
guess okay I guess let's let's play the
game then okay
yeah but um try to squeeze in some more
that's done in the beginning and the end
and the reason I was trying to tangent
while I was screaming with Subaru it was
just because I know you guys liked the
tensions and I'm trying to have a
conversation while playing but that game
is really difficult to play while
tangenting because you have to focus on
those [\h__\h] stupid controls hmm
oh well
I think it was really funny anyway
though like
often she would yeah scream at me don't
talk
please
we weren't getting anywhere yeah
yeah but yeah her shoulder she even
asked me to open an already opened
bottle where the cap it wasn't even
properly closed it was just really
slightly on top of it and she was like
open and
I
feel like maybe she was
um taking advantage of me
and one time I was so excited I
accidentally like shook her arm not her
shoulder directly but I was shaking her
arm
yeah and then she was like
I'm so sorry yeah moment
what's your favorite thing to do in a
game center and normally I feel like you
would say you would mention like you for
catcher or a certain game like a dance
machine or whatever but she says and I'm
like
that makes me so happy she doesn't even
understand she doesn't understand the
thing is she wouldn't get it she doesn't
understand she doesn't know what kind of
connection we have of purukura yeah she
doesn't know the tangent the copy pasta
yeah
um
then I showed her my other punicula but
yeah my neurons were activated exactly I
couldn't hold back I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry
one day I will take pretty good out with
you bye
goodbye
she wouldn't get it no she didn't get it
um anyway uh one thing
I thought that was really funny
[Music]
um you know I asked her uh if I could
record something work related
um because I don't really have like a
good microphone with me in the hotel so
I asked if I could borrow her PC and her
microphone for a little bit to record
something she said yeah absolutely no
problem so after the stream I was like
ah can I use it now and then she opens
her
she opens her sound recording program
everybody bury yourselves please hold on
to your chairs or whatever you wherever
you are hold on to something
she uses
audacity
I was like
oh my God you're you're out
oh my what how why are you how are you
working with audacity I mean the
audacity to be using audacity I used to
always think it was all the city but
anyway I guess it's audacity right yeah
it's a free product but there's a better
free program that we have been like
recommended by
um Management in case we don't have like
um like a one that you have to pay for
um
and that's called Studio One
which is better uh I learned how to use
it too nowadays I use audition though
Adobe Audition because I realized Adobe
has a audio recording program that I
didn't know about yeah but Studio One is
free and it's better than audacity
and yeah really big recommend I I did
recommend it to her that was actually
was like she was like no audacity
is the best it's great and I love this
one it's the best
I'm is so funny to me because it
reminded me of you know when I was like
I don't know when I was like 12 or 13 or
so and um I had a PC back then right and
there were like I don't know for some
reason I wanted to record my singing so
[Music]
all I had
on on my PC that I was aware of was this
like audio recording maybe is that is it
on even voice recorder
I don't know if it still does the same
but back then unlike Windows XP
yeah the audio recorder I think it only
recorded 60 seconds at a time
or even less
it was like a really tiny window and
then you can record 60 seconds at a time
and then it stops and then you have to
press play again and you know which one
I mean
I I feel like it was shorter than a
minute but I don't know it would be kind
of weird maybe it's like
40 seconds or so yeah so that's all I
had like 11 12 year old quinoa or so
that's all I had and I was I wanted I
wanted to be like those cool YouTubers
or so or like back then there were like
a lot of like Services websites that
where people uploaded their singings
they recorded on their phone or whatever
and they uploaded and then you know I
wanted to be like that so I tried to
record my singing with that but it was
really difficult because I always had to
stop in one minute and I was trying to
time it and then continue and it was
really difficult
yeah long long long time ago like yeah
yeah like those Services yeah yeah I was
looking up to that I wanted to do stuff
like that
um
and I don't think I ever did anything
with those audio recordings
yeah I don't think I did anything with
them
but I was playing around with them
so it reminded me of that because that
is like one step below audacity
also that is a big step up though that
is a big step up
I will give you that and I I did end up
recording with audacity but I had to
record and yeah
does
what do you mean supercharger I'm in the
middle of
a fans and it's still the same tangent
okay it's all in my memos I wrote The
Audacity thing and all that down in my
memo
it will decide when the tangent is over
okay
I've been reading super chats for one
hour 30 okay so I have a right to
tangent
and I will make use of it so anyway what
was I saying yeah I recorded it yes it's
not so bad like you can totally do your
thing with it but the it's just like
surprised me so much because
she's been doing this job for years
and I think she uses Photoshop too
probably
which would mean that she has a dope
subscription which would mean that she
has access to auditions probably doesn't
even know it exists
but because I didn't know either until
recently but it's like it's
a pro when she's comfortable with yeah
you know I I didn't really feel like
changing to a different program either
um
but at some point like my studio one was
like [\h__\h] around I didn't like
something wasn't working the way it
should be working so I eventually I
switched to
um Adobe Audition but yeah yeah yeah I
mean yes it was fine it's like it's like
using [\h__\h] instead of Photoshop
so funny though
continue using Audacity Of course
it's just I was shocked
[Music]
what
hmm
I use Camp imagine using Game Can't Be
Me Yeah it couldn't be me either
attacking us game pieces for no reason
same room
anyway and then oh yeah
when I got to her place I was feeling
kind of hot again so and I thought it
would probably once I started talking
and screaming I'll feel hotter so I
asked her like
actually I didn't ask her directly I
think she authored offered me a T-shirt
and I was like yes actually that would
be great
not the first time I'm changing into
someone's someone else's clothes while
I'm being there for an off collab
and she gave me she like brings out this
non-stop Story Tour not tour but Concert
t-shirts from years ago
and it's so
feels so emoi feels so emotional because
she must have watched a million times
because there's the colors on it are
basically
non-existent at this point and yeah so I
wore that with pride and I was very
happy to wear it because I never saw a
t-shirt before in reality
the Senpai on the t-shirts Costco
but she actually had four of them so I
didn't feel bad to ask if I could keep
it she told me though that everyone only
got one and that the reason she has
Fuller if I understand correctly is
because
somehow even when she stayed at other
members places or when they said at her
place maybe they bring it or she would
wear other members t-shirts and then
bring them home like anyway she got the
other free from other people so
I may have taken a t-shirt that may have
originally not belonged to Super Duty by
anyway
yeah she's been like collecting them
yeah I got to keep it yeah
so I got a t-shirt from Coronet and I
got a t-shirt from Suman Senpai and I
got a coat
from Denmark
can I have this coat I don't wear from
Liz Lisa do you want it
I'm like okay I guess I'll take it it's
not too bad
it's not too bad it's all right but I
can't wear it right now because it's
more like a spring coat
close collector
it's not like I need any more coats I
have like a million coats at home
like really I have way too many coats
my like
um you know in my entrance I have this
rack where I hang up coats
and there's like I would say at least 15
coats and jackets hanging up there
so when someone comes to visit me
and wants to hang up their clothes it's
like every every like hanger is taken I
just have too many this is not even all
of them this is only the ones I hung up
yeah so many
the rock is held together with duct tape
no it's not but speaking of that so when
I walked in I saw something I saw
something that looked like the same
trash can that I sat on
two years ago right I mentioned it on
stream
it was still there but I would like you
I would like to remind you it's not like
a normal trash can it's really not
sturdy to begin with it's basically two
really thin legs and then like a square
um but inside hella Hollow uh ground
that like the legs are connected to but
it's like I don't know how to explain
it's not like a yes it's a flimsy one
it's like if you put a trash bag in it
you see it because there is no
surroundings for the trash can there's
no walls you know there's just two Thin
legs
yeah so when I had no trouble sitting on
it well
okay she may be lighter than me
but I have to say that that doesn't mean
I'm fat
man
I don't like the implications of this
[Music]
I don't like the implications of that
man
[Music]
um
but I also I kind of like challenged it
because when I sat on it I was like
shaking my booty a little bit
you know how I was shaking my booty when
I was sitting on coldness Empire in the
Stream
I was challenging it I was testing to
see how how sturdy it's now yeah but it
wasn't very sturdy after all but she
told me that back then she she drilled
in it and I saw I showed me where she
drilled something like back in or so I
guess screw got loose or so
um
I'm so tired my face and my eyes
everything's so exhausted what's
happening man oh my God I slept like at
least seven hours
wake up koala please wake up
anyway I did manage to give her the
um the iron B thingy I didn't forget
thank God yeah I waited to give it to
her until the stream and she acted as
ish as if she saw it for the first time
she completely forgot about the fact
that I showed it to her before
yeah I had to remind her but
um
yeah she loved it yeah
I mean maybe she'll forget about it
again but for the moment she was happy
about it
I made it if she only knew how long it
took me to make that thing yeah it's all
handmade
um
but I think it's a cute present yeah
and then you know actually
after the Stream
you know I was gonna I wasn't gonna wait
until azuki Senpai comes because she
told me that when asuki senpa is
supposed to come and I was like um
actually I have something important
the next day so I want to practice for
it after this stream
and I was gonna actually leave but then
you know I sat down on her sofa you know
we sat down and we got comfortable and
we just started chit chatting and then
she was like you know giving me advice
because I was like telling her some
worries and we were discussing things
and this and that
and eventually time was passing by and
nazuki Senpai came actually
yeah so I did see aziki Samba for the
first time
and just because Itachi guy just because
we like like exchanging places basically
so I thought it would be weird to leave
like five minutes before she comes so I
just stayed and then we talked a little
bit but the moment the moment she came
uh it was kind of fascinating to me
because apparently it was uh also maybe
the first time Superman azuki Senpai
Matt
and their first collab that's for sure
the first one-on-one collab at least
so
uh yeah they immediately sat down she
wouldn't say if I brought out like a
notepad
like pen and paper and was asking us we
sent by like questions like what what
can I ask you what's not good to ask you
and uh what should we talk about well
this and that isn't that started to
write down things
because uh that stream I guess it's
something regular that sort of senpai
does like uh it's like her
room's room where she brings someone in
like a podcast to talk with them about
you know you guys say it's professional
but it's basically like holotalk in in
that matter like a like a mini hole talk
like a more podcast style uh chill
whole talk um
whole talk light very light light though
I think it's kind of different goal of
what what knowledge you want to gather
than what whole talk is but anyway yeah
um yeah more casual mm-hmm
cool quack
yeah so she was writing down things and
then it was like oh I should probably go
now because they're like getting really
deep into it so uh yeah so what does
that buy it called me a taxi though
I I just asked if she can call me a taxi
and I'll pay for it because I just don't
have a taxi app uh for Japan that works
in Japan apparently they do Uber now but
like the Uber app works in Japan now but
there's like basically like no taxis
available ever
well yeah everyone who calls me attacks
oh she called me a dancer and said it's
okay I'll pay for it though
um so then she said no I know a present
blah blah blah I'll pay for you and I'm
like oh man you're so sweet hmm yeah
so she also paid for it even though she
really didn't have to like I was going
to pay for it hi taxi hi
yeah
and how do you pay taxi before you reach
using it no no no no it wouldn't be paid
beforehand it would like charge from
Super just card once I would arrive
basically yeah
and so
basically because it was really short
that was all all there was to it pretty
much I think
oh you know I arrived we set up the
stream you know did this in the Stream
had fun you saw the stream hopefully if
you didn't then catch up on it it's on
my channel and then I left when azuki
Senpai came and talked a little bit a
little bit about two but the thing is I
already had plans to meet her
yesterday
so I met her again and I was originally
thinking that that would be our first
meeting
so I didn't expect this
and yeah and I thought that would be out
first but you know I don't know
um
[Music]
yeah I'll tell you more about that too I
know it's not on the tangent list but
I'll tell you more about it's um it's uh
something with several people involved
um
I'll tell you that another time
who haven't you met yet
oh
a couple
yeah
I think so I didn't meet Aqua Sam but I
am a senpai uh okay you Senpai for
example
I didn't meet uh
[Music]
um
bye
[Music]
I cannot say that I
didn't meet her
um
[Music]
but I can
uh I don't know
I am
yeah well anyway let's um
[Music]
super chance
yeah yeah uh so after the New Year's
stream we had what
epic seven oh my gosh super transform
Downstream
um
wait didn't I read those early I did
didn't I it's such a genius then maybe I
need to read super chats of the Super
Chat stream
I might need to worry to pretend of the
super jump stream right
now
[Music]
no problem
no problem though yo
let me put up though
thumbnail
there we go
I don't know how many there are uh
oh there's quite a bunch oh dear
okay how much time do I have left one
hour oh [\h__\h] nape thank you for the
pinky nection it's late but let's have
our first Super Chat in the New Year it
was a fun 2020 review I wish you well in
2023 Happy New Year
yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you Nate for
still being here I hope you had a a good
journey into 2023 and as I already
promised before this year
I will do my best okay I will really try
hard to learn at least like com basic
conversation Korean okay Fighter
fighting
[Music]
yeah it's a Super Chat ratings room you
forgot how can you forget
yeah I'm I would be satisfied if it was
just conversation
um or like you know because like uh I
wanna get so good that I have no
problems singing and pronouncing
K-Pop song lyrics
because
you know even when Korean Bros tell me
that pronoun my pronouns pronunciation
is good so far
um
I really have to try hard to like learn
the pronunciations of my
um of the K-pop songs I've sang so far
it's not that easy
so I would like it to come like
naturally I don't want to I want to
leave the read the lyrics and know how
to pronounce it
just by reading it ideally
um
Helen
that goes right
for the pinky High attention since you
might read this within this stream
what gave you that impression
wow you're a really hopeful positive
person aren't you
in Japan and using this old thumbnail
can we get the old loading screen one
more time if you still have I hope you
aren't straining your throat though
oh the really really old one
[Music]
um
I don't wear this
but I could probably like Get It by just
downloading my own stream and like
cutting it
worst case I could probably like get it
again but it's too late now I already
used something else too bad yeah sorry
but yeah that one is really no Styles
because in it
at least I still use the OG
loading screen bgm sometimes currently I
don't because I'm just using whatever I
have here to use
yeah the bucket cat yeah
[Music]
cute cute cute good old times where
where are they good old times they were
very stressful
and
um
[Music]
mean mean old times
well no I'm glad I'm in these times now
yeah yeah I am
important times that is true I have a
hard time so they made us love you thank
you bedtime good night thank you for
coming
[Music]
happy New Year Wawa I finally graduated
from University a couple days ago just
before the new year oh and now I'm
officially a Bachelor of Computer
network engineering yay what do you do
when you are a Bachelor of Computer
network engineering I can kind of like
roughly
but you guys can probably tell me
properly right a useful degree that
sounds useful
he makes computers talk to each other
real good
Engineers can be no that doesn't really
help me
servers hook computers together
[Music]
ISP he designs computer networks
it's kind of still complicated for my
brain but okay it sounds cool and
complicated but useful so I think you
have a great
future ahead of you I wish you good luck
congratulations on graduating
now nice uh good for you
yeah all the hard work you put into it
was worth it
good job for
like holding it together for such a long
time I'm sure it was a long time happy
New Year to you now will you stop at
Bachelor and go find a job or really
trying to get like more degrees or
whatever whatever you do I wish you luck
with it I'm the one thank you for the
pinky and I only wish for 2023 is for
kewa to be happy and healthy yeah I want
to be happy and healthy too and I wish
you the same let's be happy and healthy
together okay
thank you Kevin C thank you for the
pinky hey thanks you're glad your Japan
trip has been going well yesterday I got
two
today I'm not that far in yet but I'm
loving it the gameplay is simple but
draws you in and the bgm is so nice to
listen to oh
tunic I love you Kevin Kevin have you
finished by now are you in the chat
thanks for getting me into this amazing
game you're so [\h__\h] welcome come and
see where are you where are you
where are you oh
I'm so glad that people gave it a chance
you know such a deserving game like it
deserves all the love
yeah maybe you're playing tunic right
now you know what I'll forgive you you
don't have to watch me if you have to
play tunic then that's more important
hope you're having a great time moving
and it's fun I hope that thanks for my
memberships hope it will not make you go
crazy like it made me go crazy around
the end
but yeah that was I feel like you know
if I would have played privately given
it more time
[Music]
then I wouldn't have gone crazy but then
if I would have played privately I
probably would have also relied a little
bit too much on online guides for the
end maybe
ah because I would be so confused
[Music]
please support and let me know what you
what you think of it at the end okay I
mean
I'm assuming you watched my playthrough
too which kind of ruins a lot of the
experience like kind of spoils
everything maybe you didn't though who
knows
we'll have fun Skylight in Phoenix
oh
cool nice World Tour HD thanks guys
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
oh my God that's a lot
it's a lot
wow so generous thank you
[Music]
um
is cute and wonderful just the wishes
you're not just my favorite streamer but
you're the only streamer I watch wow
thank you for all the time and effort
you put in happy New Year enjoy your
time in Japan how hey I wanna know and
I'm the only streamer that you watch
like
why how did you find me if I'm the only
one
how did you find me endless are you here
[Music]
#work yeah
literally saying well for you I I wish
you would watch other people though
[Music]
they were exposed to the truth must have
been destiny
cute yawn I'm sorry like I'm sorry
I watched a few others too that's okay
totally okay
never ever wow you really
you really don't give a [\h__\h] about
what I'm trying to say hmm
value for Tales of ambassadorship oh
wow thank you that means your tails off
fan Maybe
[Music]
well hopefully I can play the ending
soon if you guys are still up for it I
want to play the ending you know
I don't know how much time I have left
in the gameplay but I did you know try
to do all kinds of
um
like side quests recently you know yes
yes
[Music]
apparently you're very close yeah I mean
you haven't seen me doing the Cyclops
but I think I I would I should be very
close I think it should be manageable in
one stream but what do I know
um yeah okay let's do that anyway thank
you endless I'm very very happy to hear
that happy New Year to you too and on
you say hi a bit more often will you if
I'm the only streamer you watch anyway
and I would like to see your face more
often
okay Jake's oh wait endless mwah kiss
Jake's the best ever thank you also for
a recipe it's like everyone says some
days look better upside down oh
stay strong and stay calm I wish you the
best years of your life well then I wish
I could do a handstand man if some days
look better upside down I just don't
have a way of looking at it the other
way around because I can't do a
handstand
um gotta learn how to do it can someone
just
like hold my legs
hold my legs up while I'm trying to push
myself up with my noodle arms
someone rotate me please
now now rad we we're done with that joke
I'm not upside down
I'm not Australian
get rotated
to do a flip
package and Jake's the best ever
[Music]
since you are a real Miko do you have
any Shrine recommend to visit for Osaka
Kyoto who has already been a while maybe
you've already gone Paul John are you
here
well I
Kyoto has that one big famous one right
on like a mountain or so and also I
recommend adasiyama
but in Osaka maybe Osaka 10 mangu
hmm
the big one
ah kill me so that was the name oh yeah
[Music]
Shrine I went to that one before it's a
lot of walking but it's so cool it's a
nice like kind of hiking trip yeah
many many many shrines there's so many
cool ones there's one
um I went to a long time ago I think
it's in shizuka
shizuka prefecture it's
a quite a ride from Tokyo though
um but I think
and I think it's with a train pretty
easily reachable maybe
um I forgot what the shrine was called
but it has this one totally
instagramable really cool
um Toady E Gate you know the red gates
uh in like on the path that like Blends
into the water ocean I think it's an
ocean not a lake
um that's so cool because you can like
take pictures while like kind of being
depends on how high the water is I guess
kind of being a little bit in the water
or not with the with the 20 there's
there's more than one gate like that I
think
in Japan you know there are a couple of
those which are somehow in the water a
little bit
those are really cool though I like that
they have big Instagram potential
that's called itsukushima Shrine eh
let me see
my
oh ah
well that's not the one I meant
but that one's even sicker
[Music]
that one's like even sicker blank so
cool it's a Gorge oh my God
because the one I remember was really
tiny like small like normal size this
one's huge
but this one's so worth to check out
I didn't go to this one before is that
she's local
United
that's that's insane
I don't remember I don't think I went to
this one
wait there's wait there's so many on
Google Maps there's like one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten ten
it's a kushima shrines
[Music]
foreign
I guess they just share names
[Music]
share names
must be a franchise it's like a chain
Trine what so
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
it's confusing
um cool wait where is
[Music]
cool
oh it is in Hiroshima
that's so far that's definitely not the
one I went to
whoa that one's wow
yeah if you want to go there that's
pretty far away from everything else but
uh I've never been to Hiroshima but
Hiroshima is also worth checking out so
when you go to that Shrine you can check
out Hiroshima too while you're at it
um
[Music]
no so
there is some special Foods there
[Music]
uh like um oysters I think cocky is
oyster
pink and Anna go rice
[Music]
a Nago is an eel too like
I think
um
[Music]
oh yeah Super Snake Mario thing for the
pinky how could it happen New Year well
thanks for the membership you guys are
what's going on why are you guys so so
generous today
Happy New Year I wanted to report to you
that I was recently able to receive your
birthday image it's all so cute this is
my first time receiving any of your
merch and I couldn't be happier I'm glad
to finally have some cat in my home
yay that's great oh so maybe I don't
know if you bought the whole set but if
you have the blanket then maybe you're
sleeping with it now oh
oh kiwawa wrapped around you like you're
the sausage and I'm the bacon
well like a piggy in the blanket
together guys cute
yeah big blanket
what's that reaction it's supposed to
mean
aren't you happy
imagine imagine
the blanket is really me
the blanket is me
um
[Music]
you're just nice to me because you're
waiting for the tour attention
wow wow wow
you're welcome
um for the merchandise thank you for
buying it though thank you for
purchasing it and supporting me through
that thank you so sweet
thank you for the red super chat hi
Kiana
oh
happy New Year first super chat here
thanks for coming to Comic Fiesta this
year I wanted to attend but cancer is a
b
I hope the crowd there was fun my oceans
are Central and almond but I love
everyone in the whole life including
yagos wait do you have does that mean
you have cancer
but you seem very I don't know
I know like you like handling it well I
don't understand hmm
[Music]
I don't know how to if I went
If this means I guess what else would it
mean I'm not sure
hmm
that's sad that you couldn't go but I'm
sure there will be more chances to come
to see us and even if not you know
that's the great thing about us being
streamers no matter where you are you
can always watch us anywhere
at any time we're here for you okay so
I'm sad that you had to miss it but
there's there's more opportunities yeah
so thank you for your support to me and
to all of us yeah
thank you and I wish you a Happy New
Year too thank you for your Super Chat
though Happy New Year may all the luck
go to you wow
thank you for the pinky get a blanket
was almost taken away by my parents who
visited after a long time I kept it
you protected it
I read this I feel like I saw the super
chat before
it's a beautiful blanket right yeah but
no no no taxis
no keepsis
protected strawberry but then you need
to protect it with a shield and a sword
and your life
um
[Music]
happy New Year you probably won't read
this until February March hey no no it's
January still but we're planning to do
fan ads in Tokyo oh to celebrate the
best dancing chick I mean Phoenix Idol
Chihuahua and whole myth for second
anniversary of Hall of Fest hope you
like it love thank you
it's so January though
I have
what's the word
[Music]
over your expectations Unica Vision oh I
know unique condition I think
I know it
I've heard of it
[Music]
which which part of the city is that I
wonder
that's so cool though thank you for
planning that even though you're not
even exceeded yet
exceeded your expectations you're not
even in Japan right wait no wait
no you're not you don't live in Japan
right Shinjuku oh you will be there okay
but you like generally don't even live
there and you still like aren't
organizing it thank you so much thank
you
even though you live in I think Korea so
thank you sure that's what's weird guys
gotta take videos I don't know if I can
see it in person but even if I don't you
guys gotta take video of when it's like
airing okay
it's so exciting yeah thank you for
doing that
[Music]
so now that you guys heard about that
maybe they still need help for it or so
so go to pong if pong still needs help
land him a hand
Kid Fury Place official dangshan and
furry Fury
one R I think that's pronounced Fury
right and then two hours is having furry
oopsie closing I I saved it
avian thank you for the pinky
I bet the dances are great too bad I
can't listen right now because in the
middle of my work day oh well at least I
bought to watch and look forward to once
I get home offered to has fish pass
ES
[Music]
oh
I'm exhausted
yeah
um ABBA is call me about it
time slot
machines
thank you foreign
[Music]
you're welcome
tangent Queen I hope this year I'll have
more fun tangents right now I have an
over
um
oh what's what's a good word over
demand no over
abundance whoa I wasn't thinking of that
over capacity all right abundance and
over abundance of tangents but I'm
scared of the times when I ran out of
time run out of tangent so hopefully
that will not happen
yeah but
I wish you a happy New Year too and when
you run out of tangents we just gotta
make more gotta make more memories right
okay
for being part of 2022 and continuing to
watch me in 2023 wow
thank you for the rest of the chat chat
Flynn is a great song just got some sad
memories attached yeah
I'm looking forward to more Phoenix
action this year I'm glad to see that
you're back in Japan I hope you can
enjoy it even with such a full schedule
thank you
yeah
[Music]
I think I enjoyed it very much yeah it
was a very full schedule but I would
have felt like I was wasting time if I
wouldn't fill it up that much yeah
um
I got to do some like work too
oh
oh Airport
especially the day before yesterday you
know when I tweeted it was really
important to me and it went well but it
wrecked me thank you
productivity crime
I think I really made some special
connections with some members so I feel
like especially actually last night with
koyokana
not like we
um
bonded very well
so I will cherish those friendships
[Music]
let's hope that we can Bond too okay
2020 freeze our year hey
[Music]
thank you for the support happy New Year
thank you for the pinky hearts hearts
hearts back to you
there there you go I can still do it
yeah
um profile no wait that code thank you
for the pinky Gilmore Girls episode 11
way to get that date tsuki Paris so mean
again why I feel bad for Max but I
appreciate Laura live being honest it's
a way to dump someone or be damned I
have experienced both but and I guess I
depends on the circumstances
um yeah it depends
but generally I guess it would be dumped
yeah right
[Music]
yeah yeah that's
tough
what hurts those when you have to dump
someone
even though not because you like hate
them or dislike them also lost interest
but because no not not because but you
still love the person but you dump them
anyway that that is pretty painful but
you dump it for your own good or
something like that
sometimes life just gets in the way
chocolate
special kind of rough yeah like it's
like you're
doing
inflicting the pain on your self yeah
but you're doing it in order to have
less pain later on
let's hold a snare oh well they're good
I have a game of girls these last nights
too because
um I only have like I didn't bring a
tablet or anything I've been like
watching on my phone to fall asleep and
so I only have like Netflix on there so
I've been continuing my gamer girls
where you watch grind but I'm excited to
go back to home because then I can
continue watching Tad lasso
so excited for that
now I was in the middle of
binge watching tag lasso before I left
so good
[Music]
oh my little garden yeah okay
thank you very much
hat
dancing
happy New Year almost two years and I'm
here and I had once again thanks to you
such an amazing year can't wait to spend
more time with you and kfb this year too
we love you so much quinoa and we
appreciate everything you do for us
really
thank you very sweet for fall yum yum
yeah
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
no no no no it's it's okay it's okay
it's okay
no it's okay no it's okay
hmm
no let's stop now there's nothing to say
you do you you do you no I have no
problem with anything whatever
no just don't get a third Aussie okay
free is too much
[Music]
I know
tonight
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um well
freeze too much how about for can you
count
challenging me again
[Music]
Super Snake Mario thank you for the
pinky I gotta say it feels really good
to be back at your shrank yada this
place is kind of special to me because I
remember that it was here that I just
decided to join kfbo
and what exactly made you join so being
able to start another year here with you
sorry getting a bit sentimental oh don't
worry about are you here now Super Snake
Mario
are you here what made you decide that I
want to know what was the turning point
I would like to know if you're here has
someone seen super snack Mario my long
chicken hmm
if not then tell me on Twitter
#talk Wawa or kfb can't respond to in
this case because we're streaming right
now
thanks by the way guys for
um making use of the hashtag I mean I'm
still like kind of busy so
um I haven't been uh checking it like
since yesterday
uh but I think later today I'll have
some time to check it again
[Music]
you need to chat thank you for a raise
up a chat
by the way I think I can finish that
stream super chats today
and we have half an hour left and maybe
we can finish and and read some and do
one more tangent okay
I'm really happy that I also hit two
years of supporting you now I won't get
into how you became an ocean because I
already wrote about this in my dopamine
letter ooh but I want to say that I'm
grateful that I found my way here at one
of the two you have become a very
important part of my life and my life is
better for finding your whole life and
the kfp community thank you I will give
my best to always support you Kiana
wow you're so sweet you're so sweet
thank you soon
one of my precious European chickens
thank you for being part of this
Movement we need to get YouTubers out
there in Europe all right let's try to
do that more in 2023 even though
Eurovision song contest turned me down
or like Germany turned me down and they
don't [\h__\h] understand what mistake
they made with that but in any case
we'll find Our Own Way alright
just go on your own way
[Music]
yeah I know there was an article
yeah some some excitement article about
me being turned down by Germany
they don't even have all the whole story
probably I didn't read their article but
no not the big certain one no no no no
that was a different story
the certain one they deleted their
um the Tweet if you're not on Twitter
you miss out on some funny things
because there was some site that um did
like uh what top 10
most watched streamers or whatever
of maybe 2022 I think maybe
and they showed supposedly
uh Miko Senpai and
and by right but then they were replaced
the videos they showed for them were for
other like
Senpai was like IMS and Mikko Senpai was
a random like anime that I guess comes
up when you Google Miko Chan because
they also called everyone Chan and not
Channel
but that that mistake I still understand
but research doko it's not even that
difficult of her research like how can
you use a random anime
yeah anyway that was like funny and then
I I made fun of it a little bit and then
it was like but her drama and then they
deleted the article and I guess they're
remaking it not article the video I
don't know if they're already remain it
but apparently apparently me saying oh
10 out of 10. good job was so hurtful I
don't even don't even get me started
okay back to Super Chat thank you Unity
chat
motion Infinity War reduction you
honestly don't if you can't get take a
little bit of like hahaha then
oh
no okay I'm gonna stop myself motion
action Infinity Warrior dungeon Skyline
Patsy dungus and Felix wolf dungeon oh
man oh man song
[Music]
mini oh okay
you mean TV table training
brick Stanger
it wasn't even like
[Music]
it wasn't even like against like one
person or so I was joking about the
stupid video whatever
for the pinky please give this to Jenna
for spoiling you
hmm well maybe I will
I will I I did I think invite uh okay
for one like proof that we had like
lunch or so maybe but she definitely
deserves more like um because she's also
like she picked me up from the airport
for example
uh
right when I came and you know you know
she's like
um she went to places with me where she
didn't have to go with me so
um
Nash kind of deserves more huh
[Music]
so sweet and she's still like
it's so sweet she's so sweet gentlemen
so sweet yeah okay but I think you know
we've both been very very busy with a
lot of [\h__\h]
and
I don't think I've rotated everybody
I don't think it will calm down anytime
soon though but let's do our best gen I
don't know if you're watching but fight
all
fighter every day every day
every day
everything
[Music]
been tagged oh
okay
my tangent has been released but um I've
have yet to be released from the super
jets the one thing I did yesterday let
me just quickly say yesterday
the one like thing I've said a while ago
that I've been invited to something with
a lot of whole Live members also someone
that I haven't met yet it was uh
invited me to check out
watamerino collab number two
and with her and Bhutan senpai
and azuki senpai
and put it as senpai
and uh
well Avatar my Senpai was obviously
there yeah we were five me
[Music]
um well so for me I thought it would be
the first time to meet vatam and azuki
Senpai but it ended up being the second
time I met both of them because I
already bumped into them in other
occasions because I've been here and
there so much you know I met asuki
Senpai when I uh
what's that soup at this place yeah both
on Senpai already met like a long time
ago when she fixed my uh or like took
apart my PC
is she fluffy how so fluffy how she
looks well I told her
when I saw her I told her
[Music]
you really give me those like fluffy
sheep Vibes I don't know what it is and
then she said that she she understands
like she's been told that before she has
this sheep Aura she really has his sheep
aura
yeah I don't know she has these this
comfy sheepy Vibes I don't know man what
it is but yeah I told her that
a true sheep yeah it just makes sense
yeah
um but yeah I also already have like
bummed into her before but this time you
know it was like a proper meeting but
I'll talk more about that when the
tangent gets chosen if it gets chosen
I'll have to put it into the wheel
um but let me finish your super chats
and then we have not much time left and
[Music]
mm-hmm
um Skye thanks for the pinky send the
super chat see what tangent I will get
in the future oh it's like a
like a like a fortune
but instead of a good fortune or bad
fortune or whatever you get a good
tangent or a bad tangent or no tangent
at all
tangent all right I'll spin the wheel
for you but afterwards okay I need to
there's like not so many there's like
one more red and a couple of mixed ones
okay Skye give me one moment and looking
for the tap back it shouldn't matching
eight thank you soon for the red super
chat Phoenix in Japan there's a Super
Chat stream it lasts over four hours and
despite needing to attend entitled
meaning she refuses and continues
reading them is this her first Super
Chat stream from September 17th 22 2022
or her most recent from January February
2021st try and stay Health attention
what was there like a
same similar occasion
two years ago
I like this trivia
this whole Super Chat is like a trivia
oh my first superchat reading I really
needed to go to an idol meeting and I
didn't go
um
well
I mean if there's so much to read so
hard to
to go yeah go idle meeting I can
um thanks for the trivia muffin
you how do you even how do you do you
even remember these things thank you so
much though mwah you have a good memory
can you share those brain cells with me
please
[Music]
accomplishments guys accomplishments
[\h__\h] yeah
that means
you guys said I read a geoguessr stream
super chat thingy before but not the one
that came after that right you do you
mean the one that kind of no way the
second wait maybe I did where it does
there were two though
I wonder if I read those
did I
[Music]
the short one maybe
I did read both
first one the short one is the one I
read okay
only the short one
[Music]
okay okay well there's not that many I
mean never mind I mean there's
no
not that my knee is super chest left I
think after that
it doesn't look that bad there's a
couple streams yeah but a lot of them
didn't get that many super chats so it
shouldn't be that bad bad for me or not
all right all right all right all right
okay so that one will be replaced with
[Music]
and here we spin
spin what will it be what will it be
chocolate today
[Music]
it's just it's never gonna happen
no no I'm not sorry no I'm not
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
so let me let me tell you the other day
I had if you didn't know and I've collab
with chocolate Sensei and may the same
pie and I asked them to do a Oscar live
with me together because you know they
do a lot of things together so I thought
it would there would be um
they would feel comfortable with each
other and
then I asked them if we could do like a
cooking stream so
um
just say it's a good cook meru Senpai
not so much so we were I guess hoping
for chokosensei to do
um you know to save us from being
poisoned or whatever
um but yeah so that was organized and
originally it was supposed to be held at
Yoko sound buys place but her I guess
one day or two days before the stream
her PC
died
and I think I asked her she said her PC
was only like two years old or so I
think
but it died yeah
um absolutely unusable so we had to do
it at minus Empire's place but you know
why I'm happy about that because
when I entered meru's Empire's place I
was graded by such a cutie patootie
boo Kato I saw
[Music]
huh okay she has this cute cat that
looks like me because it's orange and
white
that's what I am
um
it's so cute and you know you know cats
and their tails right depending on where
their tail is
it it tells you their mood but some cats
they have their tail up so straight like
in TV antenna and they look so happy but
the way they have their tail constantly
straight up like that is kind of
freaking cute especially if they have a
really really fluffy one they look like
that they look like um like a like a
squirrel it's so adorable and her cat
was like that so it looks so cute
happy like I walked in and I you know
there's medicine fire and then there's a
cat and I was like nice to meet you
first time meeting husband but but I
could not hold back immediately all my
attention went to the cat because it was
so adorable she was so cute and the Cat
created me and oh you know I feel like
um cats really notice when a cat owner
pets them because you know you hit the
right spots and all that yeah and I was
already missing my own cats so that was
a great refresher
um yeah I miss my katos you know but
it's so cute
go over but her cat was kind of
energetic too he was running around and
going here and there and I was following
her cat the whole time like middle
standby actually first before we were
setting up you know
um we went we went right back out to buy
groceries
so after that that was like following
the cut around the whole time but yeah
we actually we couldn't find the the
right missile
thing yeah thing but it looked out
anyway
I think I said like chocolate senses
sent Meadow Senpai like a ingredient
list and we were trying to get those
things from the supermarket yeah and but
in the end everything worked out we got
I think more or less the right
ingredients and hey but they sell really
like so different things than what we
were selling our Supermarket so if I
really want to recreate
at home
hmm I hope I can find those ingredients
maybe in an Asian supermarket because we
have those but I need a miso miso paste
and some kind of like katsule flakes
um and and some some other stuff I hope
I can find meeting meeting meeting for
example
[Music]
um
and I'll go to an Asian supermarket
Market hoping to find those things
meaning
the available right and miso I mean miso
me so that's a basic and important
ingredient they should have it too right
they take long to remember everything
um yeah no my Japanese was really rusty
even others told me that and I noticed
too but
um with every day I spend here the
better it gets again so it just kind of
need some refreshing time yeah
yeah
[Music]
anyway yeah so we went back after
shopping and then we were preparing the
whole stream set up and uh since I came
really last minute
and yeah but uh I also met her for the
first time yeah so I was exciting I met
both of them for the first time and and
I I was like inspecting because I was
every time I went to someone's place in
the law school lab I was looking at the
whole like setups and rooms and this and
that I was giving myself a room tour
yeah it was really cool and and then I
saw I saw that uh medicine if I had like
some jewelry on this play and I noticed
one necklace that Cali actually also has
and then it was like oh yeah yeah Kelly
and Kelly has that one too right I'm
like yeah yeah but you know I don't I
don't really virtually myself and if I
would then I probably wouldn't do this
one because this one's too big for my
taste and I'm right next to it she had
the same necklace but in much much
smaller
um It's like a what's it called again
um
nah what's that one again you know they
always have this planet with the with
the ring around it
that that brand what's it called again
the the uh
not so tune I don't mean the planets
[Music]
they've been Fiesta one thank you yeah
it was Vivian Westwood necklaces one
really big one one small one
um well if I had the truth I would take
the small one that one's cute and then
she she points out that she has two of
them and she asked me if I want one of
them and she gifts me one of the Vivian
Westwood the necklace is the small one
yeah it was so sweet because I actually
really liked it and it's kind of like
rose gold
a color
it's really really pretty and now you
know I really don't have much jewelry I
always tell myself I kind of want to
wear my more jewelry but whenever I like
stand in front of like a jewelry display
in a shop there's so many choices and
I'm like I'm not sure what should I get
um even though probably all of it would
be fine but I don't know what to get
[Music]
but necklaces I still have a couple
necklaces but like bracelets and rings
and so on and and earrings I don't even
I don't really even really have arrows
so because they they
grew together again so yeah
um
I need I need more but yeah
so Disney I was really happy about that
present hey yeah and then I kept on
playing until last minute and that was I
was even brushing the cat because holy
[\h__\h] her cat
Megan by the way was really really
shedding a lot not [\h__\h] I mean
shedding okay shedding
um and I wanted to help out my brushing
hmm
yeah yeah just as if it
was
to like being brushed but she was she
kept on walking around while I was
brushing her
um
and then also so often she would just
drop down just like my cat she would
suddenly drop down
and then she seemed to be enjoying my
pets but once you get to like a little
bit too close to the tummy I guess it
would sometimes try to attack me
it seems like she's not that open to
belly rubs as my own cats are
[Music]
trying to munch me but I was like hey
free to eat my hand I will be your food
gladly
um
anyway yeah you guys watch the stream I
hope but we whipped that up so fast like
the oyakudon was like done in an instant
um gladly and then we ate it together on
stream and add some Chit Chat
that was really good it's a simple
really simple food
but it's pretty yummy
I think the the most important uh thing
about it is the Dashi
so when I make it next time I'll pay
close attention to that do not mess it
up
yeah we even made it from scratch so
I'll try that too
I mean we only had like really tiny
portion door and honestly like whenever
I need to eat on like a like a dinner on
stream I especially in the situation
like that where it's like an off collab
or so I I feel way too nervous about it
so I wouldn't really be able to eat a
big portion anyway so it was good that
was it was a small one
um
and then after that we after the stream
we just continued to chill like that and
chit chat and talk and I think uh oh
yeah
it's really good with Google said but I
think so for some reason I don't know
why we got to that point but because
there was it was still early in the day
or in the evening I guess
offered to contact nobleclaw Senpai and
ask if she would come over to hang
because I guess I guess we talked about
which senpas I haven't met yet and which
Senpai had no plans on meeting with yet
and then the book said by his name came
up and then Joko Sensei was like oh yeah
I'm really in good terms with her so
we're good friends and then she called
her
and she calls it and then she's like
what's up but what are you doing and the
book was said but it sounds like she
just woke up she's like ah what I'm not
doing anything
[Music]
or so I don't know I forgot but yeah we
were me and Mary San Ben were behind and
chuckling and then at some point was
like
I have black and then chocolate Sensei
finally explains
wanna come over crazy the Chihuahua is
here and then it didn't seem like there
was enough time because I think she had
a
I had a cool lab or so
I think there was something about the UB
foodie or something like that
she was supposed to participate and I
think Louis sent by us at the same time
yeah and whatever so she couldn't come
but
um
that's okay I told her don't worry there
will be a chance so don't stress
yourself about it eventually and we can
meet for sure yeah
chatting about this and this and that
and and you know it was a good time I
can't really share most of the things
that we talk about
it's top secret classified information
but
um
yeah eventually
I was gonna go home and then I think
choco says they called me a cab
I think what was it male Senpai I think
it was chocolate Sensei actually maybe
oh yeah we watched a little bit of
pickles everybody's birthday live
together yeah because it was happening
after our stream
yeah
[Music]
I was called a cab again
yeah then I I took off but actually oh I
was I think I was riding yeah I was
riding the cab with chocolate Sensei
actually together and she first
um you know had them drive to my place
and then she left yeah so she did pay
for it very very very nice once again
you know the samples keep on calling me
a cab but I'm gonna say I don't mind
I don't mind at all did she fall asleep
that time too no
what why oh
[Music]
the net and she does like writing caps
yeah yeah seems so
anyway that was only sweet like I I feel
like I learned you know it's really
really
precious to learn cooking from another
culture another country I want to learn
more maybe I should take a cooking class
in Japan next time I'm here hmm sounds
good doesn't it
yeah
kind of get more variety variation into
my daily cooking oh once I go back to
Austria I have to start cooking again
huh because like here obviously I don't
have a kitchen so every day I've been
like eating in the restaurant or
convenience store food and yo that takes
up a lot of money man
all the taxi rides and all the outside
food takes up a lot of money just this
this week I already spent
because I remember I
got like
450 bucks or so from the ATM
and I only have like 80 bucks left now
yeah
cause I was also like there when I took
that money from the ATM I was like no
way then I'm gonna use that up on uh
right right until the end of my trip but
taxi rides are especially the one thing
that takes up the most money like one
ride will take like what 50 60 bucks so
expensive because they don't have Uber
as well
just normal taxi ride money and oof you
know
some of them some of my taxi rides of
course have been paid by the senpas very
kindly but the others haven't and I
don't know if I can write them off
I'll try
to write them off but I've been trying
to write more more trains in Japan too
though because holy [\h__\h] like for go
like I could spend 50 60 bucks for a
taxi ride or I could spend like five
bucks for going by train
of course I would prefer to ride the
train so most of the time I try to go by
train it's just insane otherwise yeah
yeah
anyway anyway anyway anyway if you
haven't received you definitely could
well I don't know because it's a
Japanese receipt and it's I don't know
how it works when I paid in Yen because
then my accountant will have to
convert it but like in in what days
a conversion rate is she gonna how does
how does she do that like how what I
know foreign
I hope so
because they are really expensive and it
was work related so
um
that's why I'm speaking of writing off
things you know how my my tax person she
told me I can't write off games even
though it's literally connected to you
know my streams literally like it is my
job to play them Japanese soup senpas
have been telling me that they write off
games no problem
hmm
no man in the US you can write off games
I don't know if that's a tax person
problem or if that's a tax law problem
if it's just my person not wanting to
try or if it's just you know
[Music]
the law like for real like maybe we
really can't do it in Austria I don't
know foreign
[Music]
you telling me to cheat on my tax lady
okay anyway I have to end it now we
still have so many targets left
so I still have
one two three four five six
tangents at least
that I can tell you in my Fire Emblem
streams that are happening soon in any
case thank you guys very much
for being here today listening to my
struggle with the super chats and all
that I have to go now because today I
have only a limited amount of time here
[Music]
is
I think we'll have more than enough time
in Fire Emblem yeah to tangent right so
yeah okay and in Germany guys thank you
very much
love you guys
sorry for busting our eardrums
but have a nice day everyone
this time bye bye I need to go to the
island meeting anyway bye-bye
[Music]
So Long Farewell I'll be dancing goodbye
please don't bust my eardrums
oh there's no there's no music here
anyway uh yeah there really isn't
anything here well that's okay
[Music]
or is there yeah no there isn't I don't
know why it's not running it's an OBS
but it doesn't run
[Music]
bye
don't write public transportation like a
common Pleasant
thank you
um
[Music]