[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
five
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello hello
hello hello hello
[Music]
hello
wow
wow everybody and welcome to Among Us
with whole life English and Indonesia
here today to present to you a new
feature that just was updated in Among
Us for the home alive
thank you
[Applause]
wow
okay let's go wow wow
it is if you'll get the whole life
Cosmic Cube then you can like get
outfits from selective members from all
app en ID and Japan this this are not
sponsored but we just really want to
show you so good look at everything
yeah we're all dressed up yeah
look at my cats
everyone to introduce themselves and
they can also show off their sexy outfit
while they're introducing themselves all
right
sit down oh we might get kicked out of
the room eventually but let's just start
oh let's start with
hello
number one detective I'm naked
um
she will have some sick outfits some
sick drip right yeah yeah yeah
okay below um we have Anya at least in
the prescription
hello everyone I'm shirakamian today
[Music]
okay next we have Kalia primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming
guess what also my mommy hooked up my
Wi-Fi which means I'll be streaming in
480p which to be honest why even why
even [\h__\h] bother why even bother so
I'm here to get some whole swag As a
sheriff let's party
time
[Music]
clips of you guys every once in a while
don't worry about it bro with Amelia one
of the selected people you can get the
outfits of hi gouda hello you know yes
we're officially in the Among Us lore
now we're ready
hi
hello
now you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
I love it there are many sharklings
around
this one's right here right next to you
is cool pool please introduce yourself
who is you what I miss you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God
looking good
[Music]
it's a crazy music
right now
I don't know it seems like an imposter
and then we have Mona who is also part
of the people whose outfit you can get
in the game
[Music]
I'm wearing a scientist outfit right now
I feel like I'm I'm doing a touring love
in the Among Us oh
yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
[Music]
what outfit do you want
whatever is the closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right
yeah
I agree today I'm cosplaying as sexy
lake with money in your area
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
actually actually unlocked a bunch of
other people as well but oh my God yeah
I have my change every single round
it sounds fun at least the organizer of
today's event the special of today's
events oh
[Applause]
oh no
wait okay
all right hold on
okay wait a minute
a new code is in the Discord chat
okay yeah
uh hold on
wait am I in okay okay comedy goals
okay all good nice can you guys hear me
hello
okay awesome okay perfect let's let's re
introduce
thank you thank you thank you
a really sexy combination of marine and
pecora you look at that is so cool
looking good I can also do like a
million I can do so much I can do this
[Music]
I will now change the world settings we
will have everything included we'll have
scientists
if you don't know the scientists can see
the vitals at any time
well there's a countdown but you can see
if someone's dead before finding the
body and then we have the engineer
engineer can is a crewmate who can jump
into the vents so you can maybe no I got
that a lot
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that might be
helping in the lens
yeah
it's spicy for you too you're very spicy
and then we have the guardian angel
which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
[Music]
shifter this one is that that calls for
a lot of uh
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shape shifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think wow oh my God
just so you know all of these rolls are
not 100 so it's not guaranteed that you
that they will be in the coming game but
you know it can't happen to you
let's see
let's go
thank you
it's starting okay so this is my
favorite everybody
[Music]
okay okay
I'm
[Music]
a scientist you are lying
all right
I'm doing records
okay I'm doing it I'm doing things and I
don't know this map where oh I'm sorry
what the heck what the heck where am I
got one left okay I see it records sorry
you guys
okay
please trust you but never mind
uh by the way I'm not gonna be looking
at chess yeah
no looking at chat nobody's looking at
chat honestly
uh cap room
electricity on
CE again
[Music]
wait where was it the um where was the
body Armory yeah
I think or was it Ollie exactly
yikes I mean Phoenix tastes good right
what wait wait
that's very sassy
[Music]
she was pretty busy the whole time
she was pretty busy the whole time I
would say
hello
what are you gonna choose
I can hear you uh it's the the corpse is
in the Armory right yes because like uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the Armory but Night Pool and
that was the beginning I was in the back
room when it was for now well she got
killed fast
wow anybody want to step up and be like
yo um I have no idea though I didn't you
can uh if if you are you were telling me
that um I was in a Armory you can ask a
gura because I saw Guru also in a nearby
there in the kitchen
nine seconds guys I don't know this is a
little tough I'm gonna just inform you
guys
Skip and see how it goes
we're only
[Music]
let's see oh I'm alone no one can vouch
for me
no one can vouch for me now okay that's
okay love is good
okay I'm insecure already upload
[Music]
no no
what
oh okay
it's just
everyday life things you know looking
for signals
okay I don't know pretty oh hello hello
[Music]
um
sussy
any other task
s
yeah
[Music]
but there's a task here why I said hello
hello
your twin
there's really a task there
I wasn't lying
uh
where am I
huh
oh okay I see myself feeling deck
oh hello
me I am together
[Applause]
okay okay okay okay okay but you know
what I mean I mean Senpai saw us
together right
and gura as well so I don't know they
saw us together so maybe
maybe
oh my god
um kitchen
um
so it was
in recording maybe it's her did I say
that last time I saw Zeta they were in
the mail
you know I was searching about global
because uh she she telling me on the
previous one it was me well I definitely
like far away from the kitchen and now
[Music]
um
but to be honest I left
two people saw me alone I think that's
why so any last words music
was like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh
like just what she said and then after
that I go up
herself
[Music]
oh me
you may says
wait so she wasn't an imposter
at the very beginning
who's gone people oh hey
why did you fall for yourself
oh no thank her records babe
um
I just need to finish all of my tasks
you know be easy
I I think the only one dead so far is
just me and Kia
where she I want to First
I should probably haunt my Killers
hello I wanted some people who bought
more
I won't stop you I need to go I don't
think it's Mommy but I and I definitely
don't think it's innocent definitely
I wonder
how does this game work exactly how does
this game
that's completed hi hello
oh no
[Music]
um
that's insane Watson is dead oh I found
the body
oh
um so I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
right after while I was figuring out how
to do the mini game I was like how do
you do this then mume ran in hey and was
like he eats he he and doing things and
then I walk out and Watson's dead body
is there
Watson if you were entering the front of
the ship you would have passed Watson
how did you not say that oh my God I'm
so sorry guys um
yeah I just noticed as well
[Music]
I'm not gonna point fingers
no no I'm not I just want to know what
your Alibi is because I Watson left and
then you came in and I walked past you
and Watson's dead bodies on the ground I
just want to know what that's about I
don't really remember so much Kelly I'm
I'm just surprised
now listen here's the deal so the amount
of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
it was like no time at all you would
have passed her I just I just want to
remind you that we have 10 seconds left
so
I don't know who is it I'm sorry I have
to vote for a roommate I just don't
believe it
what they voted
yes wait who did not vote
um I mean I think I don't know God I
hope I wasn't wrong
I don't know I legit don't know
[Music]
good job everyone good job everyone
congratulations
[Applause]
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately in a month
he's shooting thanks I think I think
Kelly you should go for the Amelia
Watson detective outfit
yeah
[Applause]
you earned a detective outfit let's go
thanks are you guys ready for another
round
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't want to be near you after you
laughing like that
pretty sassy
oh hi oh hello oh hello hello
um I'm an Armory right Armory don't kill
me people stay away stay away stay away
don't touch me
I am innocent
sorry I'm really bad at imposter I'm
sorry I'm saying me too it's okay
[Music]
yeah very bad
posture meeting
okay download okay
okay I think we're all good let's see
what we have here
okay I'm gonna go to electric golden
oh there's still some tasks but then
nobody's gonna vouch for me if I'm too
far away from people
all right let's see what I can do
down down we go oh hello
[Music]
me
I think it's around here what if there's
a dead body here no way no way I'm
insecurities
correct
okay nice too nice nice
so let's see
uh okay electrical I guess
someone probably died
I found Ollie dead where
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower and then I walked off and I
turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone coming down from there so I'm
kind of like well
so like above the shower house above the
shower to the right yeah all right on
the way to the archives
you remember well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she didn't close I think girl was in the
shower as well but she like went down to
the left no I was up in the meeting
[Music]
because because if if it's really if
it's raining if she already killed only
probably she cannot kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like she was trying to tell me a
joke and then I ran away from her oh
yeah Kiara also could have killed me but
didn't so okay I have no idea because I
didn't see Ollie at all and I was like
at the left side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below I have no idea
I don't know I'm just like saying uh so
probably saying that you are nearby the
the place I just like think not true I'm
true you were also there by the way but
I I don't remember I saw moonassemba in
the middle-ish or on the left side
um
[Music]
mom
Spider-Man actors
what oh hello
wanna go together with me
I was just doing a test
oh
yeah
I'm not following you
oh yeah yeah oh hi there's so many
people
yeah put your head on my body and we can
become one
I see
oh I have a task here
too
do I turn the knob what is this okay I
don't want to do columns because I can't
like literally
I can't do this one what is this I will
do it leave it to me
oh thank you
everyone's here oh who's not here then
hey bro
okay so this is like engine room right
okay
okay engine room
yeah bye
uh hello oh
I get scared of rainy
I don't know it seems kind of sauce
[Music]
telling her oh hello
okay here
bang sound you know
a bang sound
bang bang cargo bay
oh I have a task here
oh what is this what is this
what
whatever I'm not doing it I'm gonna find
another task
me
hello hello
hi hello I'm gonna oh how do you open it
no I have to go back I know don't we
have to turn on the wait what the heck
did she shape shift wait who what what
poor who are you talking to nobody you
me oh my God where what no
oh
[Music]
where was she very bottom of the armory
what
I'm already
else Kiara I was with you and we
confirmed each other as Alibi yeah
below the main hall
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room
I saw you I saw you at the right side of
the map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know there's the test oh okay
cool
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part tasks after
the shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so
you're pretty close by yeah
what I also thought that up it was like
way back
inside it's not me
training went past me and it was not
getting his voice it was Santa's voice
and I was like I went like what
[Music]
I didn't even vote
in time
I'm sorry voice
[Music]
very saucy
I don't know guys it might be oh hello
hello you want to go with me then
um what if I go down you know
she would hello hello
why not have stuff here oh I don't have
stuff here oh see
uh hello I'm sorry for sounding awesome
this way uh
uh so they're all in kitchen everyone is
in kitchen
I'm gonna go to main hall then uh okay
you came from this side because like
explain yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no
we were met in here that way
whatever I mean maybe not but it was
kind of weird you came from somewhere
are you guys not doing your tasks
oh it's not here oh
I'm all alone this is not good I'm gonna
die oh I can't do the cargo bay
you know what I'm gonna do cargo bay
six
sorry it's the arrow is pointing to the
right
what am I
huh
all right I can't do this one what is
this uh
I can't do the cargo bay
oh I'm stuck uh I'm gonna go off
[Applause]
okay
somebody's playing with the lights we
oh
somebody's playing around
um
I'm gonna I'm gonna be here in Maine
Hall
oh it's this is not me haul oops hello
you're not gonna kill me
oh hi hi it's the four of us again the
four of us
what
whoa whoa
whoa
whoa I clicked the report button but it
didn't work
what the I clicked the report button but
it didn't work
no way is it
what the heck what the heck
what the heck I literally I was like it
didn't work okay
someone's got it they have something
against cats
yes
technically that's true
yeah
not fairies
[Music]
you know
no
[Music]
why I feel bad what if that wasn't all
right I need to do my test you are kind
of stuck
oh no
oh didn't I just do this I was just the
last round hello oh no it's gonna happen
don't you think
maybe you're lucky I'm on cooldown
she's not kidding I'm gonna do my task
mean Hall
I wasn't kidding she was really on
cooldown
uh-huh
oh dirty I'm dirty she already know I'm
not dirty
hello
hello fellow girls
look at the ears I'm sorry
thank you
Mommy I'm sorry
can anyone please tell
banana
bread
could you
[Music]
then you're not free from this side
two and then five right
yeah
and then what
happened
I definitely wasn't rated then I thought
it was her maybe oh my God these two are
diabolical oh God what's happening again
so yeah
of me
so I didn't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see I'm
running from Moon
[Music]
it was so very clever
but but she didn't kill me neither
[Music]
I wonder why they didn't kill each other
I wonder why and how is no one noticing
the contradiction
I haven't I haven't go I haven't go to
the Armory can anyone vouch for Ahmed
and say like she's safe I was with Gouda
and I didn't know
I did
[Applause]
rejected
I'm gonna be here
[Music]
I'm gonna create an image of herself
okay I'm gonna do more tasks
laughs
okay I got this
sorry five and then four one two
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
um
let's go right so you were like
we're like would hear you and you were
on purpose saying something that only a
crewmate would say again
[Music]
oh my God oh my God right now yeah I'm
back yeah
[Music]
I was about to change
let's go
honey congratulations
the records
um I'm scientist
okay gotta do my test School
how do I do this task I wonder
[Music]
I'm scared I don't want people
hmm nah
decided against it
hi hi
you want to go together I'm scared
yeah all right hi
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
I saw rainy uh yeah uh going to the
Armory and the kitchen when when I want
to go to engine room so I saw you
whether she from cockpit or main hall
in the communications Armory kitchen I
saw viewing deck of all the angura oh no
it was short yeah it was
we kind of passed by each other always
me wasn't it yeah you guys have against
me yeah I'm saying that we were in that
group yeah yeah
I think
she went to the left side so she was
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't uh you
probably weren't that worried since
you're outside
actually right by the body because uh I
was the one who reported it yeah I
couldn't because it was really dark and
then I went out yeah
you went up I went up no I went up you
go up yeah
um
[Music]
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't yeah I don't want anyone
dying yet
why I did not think
okay
hello
[Music]
everybody stay away from me no are you
targeting me because I called you out no
I wanted to know if I killed you now it
would people would be so sure I know you
have a cool down just
[Music]
I'm gonna go down
hi
[Music]
don't kill me no I'm not gonna kill you
hello
always and by sticking a dump in the
next bathroom
we're gonna fix the lights
wait I'm gonna fix the lights and stuff
hold on before you do this
I'm gonna fix the lights and stuff
like
wait what
I would know that right oh my God
there's a lot Anya's dead
What the freaking
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else versus us here okay I was trying to
fix the electric where's the where's the
body uh anybody who knows where's the
body or showers oh no that wait what the
[\h__\h] Lounge Lounge Lounge which one is
dolls are
um so let's we're out that's a day where
um the last time well last time I went
near the shower and main hall is I saw
Ollie
and I think I think did anybody see Anya
with anyone
[Music]
I think is she alone in the
right side then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zeta
what no
[Music]
silence
she's innocent yeah listen to me I'm
always us when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm uh nuts so keep
that in mind now you're saucing me which
means I'm a crewmate it's always like
this it's not gonna work are you sure
about that you always killing me wait
what about your Alibi well then I say
it's almond because why the [\h__\h] why
aren't you providing an alibi instead of
Defending yourself huh
why why is why did Ami found a buddy
twice
with only this included room where like
she would have killed me
[Music]
I'm gonna skip I'm gonna skip because I
don't know
[Music]
a lot of people
records okay
I can't see it's so dark
why is it so dark I can't see
somebody gotta fix the electricals
we're here
scary I'm scared of all man I don't want
to be close
Kiara and Ollie's on the left so I think
if they're together they can vouch for
one another you know
wash it in here
how can it how can it
oh okay
this and this okay that is complete
play with you no I don't want to stay
with you it is here
is here I'm not here I'm gonna go up
scary
wow
I'm gonna go for emergency bro oh okay
it's Zetta for sure I'm voting no it's
not oh really why okay where is okay why
are you the one you you said you you
found a buddy three times in a row now
yeah because I just happen to be a
detective who's really good at SpongeBob
could I have killed you or would I have
uh killed that body if I was with you
and in that room for like over 30
seconds
I don't know uh you want me to be honest
um what you said was oh just kidding I
was just waiting for my cool down too
yeah but I was already in the room doing
the task before you got there should we
make a snake I don't know I don't know I
don't know I think it's self report
it's like three times
can anyone give an alibi to Jada
no no no but nobody can give alibiotics
are they running away from the body
because Reina and I were both up in the
room like in the meeting room and then
as I went down I was with Rayna the
whole time and then we saw data passes
yeah I thought Kobo take the little
elevator yeah I don't know I don't know
I'm voting for a man
when I take the elevator what's in like
near the fan if if I die and it's not me
then it's um okay
together
why why isn't anyone surfing me aren't I
sassy
[Applause]
ten seconds who
I voted for Zeta but maybe it's wrong I
went for Jenna too but
it's not me
oh am I gonna join the course
[Music]
oh
okay now we do sabotage
Kobo could have backed me out a little
bit but it's okay
um if she backed me up she would be
considered so I'm not sure
I'm gonna find out later
could have fought it for
my friend
wow look who's here huh I think this is
so ridiculous
hello
are they in comms
wait wait uh I'll close records then
just in case
uh hello hello
one more over here say hi hi
I'm trying to find my other friend
where is she where's my other friend so
I can help out you know lock the other
person in
where is she
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know how to get up there
[Music]
um
gonna kill me I swear also I'm done with
my cast okay
oh boy you gotta kill now
okay
[Music]
laughs
okay
oh sorry sorry sorry
I keep pressing the wrong buttons
beautiful
[Music]
I'm closing all ends we could win
win
oh my God
[Music]
but why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you
I was just being stupid
oh I'm sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place just because
all right because we wanted to vote you
off yes sir
[Music]
laughs
is that enough that's enough right
huh
it's like uh plenty seeds of gout you
know
planting seeds of doubts
let's do electrical
and what is it it's me hello this is
getting perfect
[Music]
we just finished my task and I will be
okay it's a ruby
can they hear us probably not hello
Mommy
[Music]
I'm
golden
um
yeah we just gotta wait it out until one
of them kills each other
hi Mommy
I'll I'll revenge for you who was it
who dared too
I'm going through you are going to
uh
I'm almost done
oh no
um there's only so much that happens
like I'm gonna I'm gonna lock try
locking them I'm gonna try locking
everything so that they don't get to go
around
but
I don't know man oh man there's only so
much that I can do
the task is almost done right I'm gonna
go electrical
good haircut okay
okay
where is she
I have no idea why Cara is scared let's
just not gonna tell me hello
right about your Cask I done all my
tasks
uh okay wait uh I'll I'll turn off
lights then
there you go
and we should have won right now
oh no
I can't go
she's going after rain ago
[Music]
[Applause]
it was global
um
[Music]
but to be honest was so spot on
that's just her personality it's not
that she's deemed yeah that's just her
personality
and I was like doubting myself
[Music]
um
oh wanna see a magic trick yeah tell me
can we do it do it do it do it oh lights
off oh oh oh okay okay do it do it okay
oh I'm sorry I can't do it with an
audience
no not with an audience
I'm gonna do I'm gonna do this
I can't kill her like she wanted I'm a
disappointment
is this Kiara oh hello
our movie okay I think Kiara is doing
Armory
hello yes hello
foreign
hi are you gonna kill me nope
all right good
what
I'm sorry
excuse me what is that supposed to mean
oh
oh I can't think of like 2 A.M let me
think um
what
huh
else
yeah oh my God
wow
where was the body
watched her die
[Music]
you know beheaded or whatever okay oh
I don't think um left side
[Music]
we'll give you until the next meeting as
many people as you can
[Music]
oh I forgot
votes
is she gone
oh no
it's a battery right now
okay wait till my cool down okay it says
everybody's house
I just need to do this how do I refill
the code I cannot do this task I'm gonna
do another test
yes
I want to be a daughter anymore oh no
I will be your new daughter
I'm dead though hold on
[Music]
what am I supposed to do what's the code
okay okay I see gem okay
so it was Kiana all along huh I was
gonna saw us to be honest
no one has killed me it
yeah you want to be together with me
wait where is it
Kiana
and who
[Music]
can do some electrical when I'm a ghost
where hello
's too good at killing people that's how
you know it's her people died
[Music]
an alibi for for only and gura because I
saw them and we were we were near the
just chill person and go to security and
electrical we haven't go to medical and
cargo bay yet
for a while so
I'll buy
um
not screaming at all let's go yeah
when when she was the crew matches she
always screamed whatever you should have
cut me off and did scream I feel like me
and Kelly soon might always die early
yeah
cool some tasks who is it again
really loves to scream when I ever met
anyone I was scared that's because
her screams I just didn't show that you
are in here
oh
[Music]
you need to show that you're scared
oh no
I'm scared for my life I don't know what
to trust anymore
oh no no why would you do that you are
resting fine
okay
she's floating around
uh I'm gonna do my chat oh you already
did it hi I just saw Ollie and she was
going the Apple
let's go to engine hello
I'm doing my task oh it's so fun am I
here oh
what the heck yeah I couldn't hear you
oh hello is there a way to help us hear
the ghost better I'm sorry
I hear that I'm sorry
Mommy
uh okay I'm gonna do my best to finish
the task
[Music]
okay
intense task
[Music]
hi
uh two more
let's do our task I think I'm almost
done with mine
hi
okay one last task at the cockpit
[Music]
I think I just went to heaven
I'm done with my tasks okay
with my toys
kinda hi what's up it's Bryson and Muna
I shouldn't be typing
everything is close
we need the electrical thing the lights
silver
don't go into the light
I will go into the light and you can't
stop me
people
hello I'm done with my tasks
oh no
[Music]
um
uh where did you go
maybe up here
I'll go find her I have nothing else to
do I'm just gonna
okay
that's over there alone on the left side
I tried to help you
what if I hold this emergency meeting
oh
short wait where's Google now she's here
she's like she's haunted by so many
uh
someone said I'll be very happy
it wasn't yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai
going towards where Ollie was and that
was the last time I saw her
on your way there they're over there
I pressed the emergency button no okay
yeah
it really went to check if anyone's
out
anything shark also not saying anything
yeah I didn't know
what is it called what are they called
imposter
consumer skins
[Music]
I'm done with my task anyways so like
maybe I can just go chat with the girl
so you guys can vote me out if that's
what you guys saw no
ghosts the imposters
will win
[Applause]
[Music]
I've been stuck
oh no
God anyways
[Music]
who killed you
um
nice
[Music]
I think hobo got one kill and then the
rest is ski at all I don't know get us
and fine
oh they're all in
I see uh
ignore your task
do your task I'm done I'm done I'm done
with my test I wonder if we can clutch
okay yeah I'm already done with my task
so just just clutch it please
do your test do your trash
nice too
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
I wish I could jump and come and dance
I'm so happy I want to go what is that
weird who is breathing it's really
strange why are you not the best
yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo she's
so quiet I just love how awesome
she saw the crime scene when goes to the
emergency meeting and then Ahmed Changes
Everything by sussing the innocent ones
yeah yeah
[Music]
right with you Kiara salty
okay next time
all right let's go again okay
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
I'm scared
I'm gonna do my task on the
um
Kelly and gura is on
records I think
oh I'm stuck
[Music]
um
miracles happen
oopsie
then
all right one and a half okay yeah oh
the last one oh what oh I need the
screen what
once again
why no no I thought it was your body I
thought it was uh no Raining Raining is
dead so here's what I found I was
picking up all of the towels and [\h__\h] in
the shower and I said I hope gura
doesn't kill me a girl is fine I don't
think that she did it but I went to the
left okay
um we were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta yeah well let me tell you where
I found the body first before you start
pointing fingers okay listen to me
because I didn't even tell you where I
found the body you just immediately
jumped on me so so
from the left from the left of the
shower walked up and in that photo room
we're all like it's like a dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report Netflix report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there okay
Circle
I was sniffing towels
electrical and I saw no one yeah I saw
Zetta but I was there
where where I was at electrical I have
my I was at the bottom right of
electricity
[Applause]
no I didn't finish picking them up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels I I
whatever I am
in the electrical I saw I was in the
electron I was in the middle I was in
the middle bottom and see that it was in
the bottom but I didn't
problem
s
too much all right
[Music]
okay time to do some tasks
foreign
[Music]
Armory as well and then I have to do
some
um
I didn't finish the towel one
what do I do
um
I I I pass uh on always I pass on
Ollie's uh in the in the electrical
and then after that she's going up and
then I saw I saw
I ran into Ollie after that and she was
saying and I quote ha ha sure hope
nobody sees
the first time the first time all he
said is she was an electrical but I
didn't see it and then the second time
you know we we had to teleport first
right and then after that he said you
know I'm an electrical I find you and
after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie pass by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
I just couldn't resist to him
too delicious
hi I wish your partner good luck whoever
was with you
can do this alone
the next one might be same gen Bond
[Music]
um
what if we got it wrong is it actually
Ollie
[Music]
it wasn't her
yeah
she sounded like sorry I don't know
that's
I feel bad what if it's not her
[Music]
of elimination
I don't know
Senpai being really aggressive
what if it's not her you know
what if it's not her
okay gotta fix gotta fix the lights and
stuff
fix the lights
gotta fix the lights and stuff
you know
oh my God
oh no I gotta do this oh no where yeah
where oh yeah I just saw her like a
second ago running away from the alarm
like as she finished the alarm and then
she walked to the right side towards the
records launch Etc
where's the body
who buddy where's the body
so records I was in main hall going to
showers
Best Buy and then I checked I checked
like around the showers and then I go up
a bit and there's Anya's body there are
you saying Sarah was dead yeah but I was
probably Zetta yeah yeah but I was but I
was assessing me again but I was coming
from the left side
uh-huh
come on come on we need we need fast but
I was like
Shape Shifter accessed here
we don't know for sure we don't know for
sure
I don't know okay but me neither but
she's like she's like uh you know when
she tried to do her alibiotics
no no
[Music]
what if there's
what is
everybody no it's not ourselves I'm is
voting for me again isn't she take it
easy
[Music]
because I was checking the maps
hi
[Music]
I called you amen good job I was
saying I didn't even have like 10
seconds of gameplay holy crap
nice job
you guys figured it out yeah
good job everyone
that was a great job
no no no I'm sorry that was my alarm
sorry
there's anyone who didn't get imposter
every single time
yeah it's always always
I don't want to get imposter anymore
now this game is like never end I feel
like I want to play it until I got a
major imposter
yeah it's addictive I wouldn't mind
playing more but I'm just worried about
the ID members because it's like you
know anyway right yeah it's fine because
I usually sleep at morning
for me it's fine
okay okay
[Music]
I don't want it
one more
oh my God again me again
thank you so much
oh no oh no I want it to be one again
[Music]
do you guys want to see a magic trick
never mind please no I'm not
but I was really going to see the magic
trick
money
what is this why
I can't open the door hello hello hello
[Music]
no no no no no
I can do the magic trick right now
oh my God
can you open the door please because I
can't open the car you mean here here
I'll give you some space open the door
equation
open the door
guys guys
[Music]
it was in the hallways it wasn't a mean
Hall actually I mean yeah okay
um
I was I actually uh saw her through the
showers I went to electrical a little
bit then I went back to the main hall
and guess this I actually met another
Ollie so if you guys said anything like
oh my God no there was actually a
doppelganger and I actually met her she
was chasing me down and no no listen she
was two three down and you know what
even if you get
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah
because I'll do the task easier that way
anyways I can just fly now
you're safe okay
I think
I don't know what do you guys think I
think it's uh Anya
or
rainy
um
hi
do you want to see a magic trick no
thank you
that's so mean
okay okay I'm gonna okay I will
but I don't know
I just want to use my magic trick mans
uh I can't open this
hello anyone here you want to see a
Magic Tree yeah somebody's here Kara
just saw me
yeah you're gonna kill me if you kill me
no I'm not gonna kill you I would just I
just want to show you a magic trick I'm
an engineer do you want to see I'm an
engineer I want to show you a magic
trick please I just
oh hello
I just want to show people my magic real
quick
play
huh no not at all I haven't seen gura
Senpai in a while
oh
that's fairy sauce I'm gonna go in main
hall and then
who else is dead
what
did you find it wasn't good
how Dolly got the pretty name plate I
want it me I mean I have I have an alibi
you know so I was I was on the first I
wasn't security with rainy if if I was
the Imposter I've been I've been with
Renee uh for like a couple of seconds
I'm not killing her at all so if and
then I got maybe you were to come down
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something
and then there was also or something
yeah there was like a bunch of people
there there was a lot of people so I
take a trick I feel like Yeah I wanted
to show a magic trick because I know
like I'm not accusing anybody I'm just
telling what I saw okay
um I feel like this I mean uh Muna okay
I don't know
it's fine I was alone
I think all these fun around Muna a lot
but she never killed me but this can't
be the cool down speed it can be the
coolest down here so I'm vouching for
Ollie I mean
for like a long time yeah but the thing
is I don't know Anya Anya was also there
but Anya's also there but girls also
dead
I don't know
I don't know I think I don't know if
muna's alive and heard always say
anything I don't know because everything
will be used against me so I'll just
check
before I went to the main hall
uh-huh uh I was in the main hall too
I want to go to the right cards to do
another
um okay let's oh
why did you fall with me
why didn't wanna phone me
that's fairy sauce
I don't know I don't even know if I can
trust
what is wrong with you I just saw I'm
just a matter she's just like magic
tricks maybe you know I should look
around
see if anyone is there I'm gonna find
some sassy people
but first my task
[Music]
kinda sauce
and
hobo is not saying a lot
is it possible to get three times
imposter in a row maybe I have
so I don't know all these standby seems
uh
hi hi hello don't kill me no no no no I
would not
okay she's not killing me so that's good
oh where's my oh there's no task here oh
no I have to go back
I have to go back and do all the tests
me
help me I'm scared
yeah right she's below left do you want
to see a magic trick
oh why can't I do this task
wait don't don't uh don't show me magic
again not looking okay now
what wait I can't exit my task
do you want to see a magic trick wait
I'm not looking the time she killed me
and
hello Allison bye
please talk I need to know that you're
not a doppelganger oh yeah yeah I'm zipa
oh no
I don't know I'm pretty
I don't know I'm pretty sorry
I'm pretty I'm pretty source of Cobble I
don't know
are you
I'm super scared are you done with your
task because I am no I have a feeling
I think I don't know
agent
hunch
um find bodies guys guys
so I'm actually an engineer want to see
a magic trick
really bad
okay okay cool okay cool
use that to you to find the goddamn
imposter but they're not anywhere I
can't see them every time I went out
they're not there but I feel like it's
uh
I don't know I'm just gonna be with
Ollie just in case
um
see I think it's moonlight
here will help
longer up there
hello okay
hi so I think it's Mona and Kobo but
yeah hello yeah what happened whenever
it happened
I want to say
it's cool
I think so too
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gouda
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
to the electrical to act as if she's
doing a task but it takes one second and
she waited one minute one minute there
believe me trust me bro I will probably
don't have any I will I will vouch
because the only thing the only thing
that's like for me suspicious is that uh
she's she's being like awfully quiet she
hasn't really said anything up until
like in the discussion at all do you
have a defense for yourself yeah do you
have a defense for yourself like why are
you so quiet or you know I'm always
quiet from the beginning
that is true
a lullaby
what if I really
do my task in electrical I mean why
mommy I'm gonna be so that aggressive
[Music]
I did it right after you too and I know
it takes one seconds
are always together
yes
how was your imposter friend too
rounds ago
as she did I don't know I don't think I
don't think it's raining oh oh hi holy
Shaw of course
I think it's moon now or Amy
I don't think it's Kiara or Ollie so
can we just call an emergency okay
I think it's hello rainy
hello hello
by the way I'm an oh yeah hello she says
when it says
that's what I've been telling you
wanna see a magic trick meeting room
magic tricks with me
okay okay you can accompany wait do we
need power no
um
they don't think we can all go because
there's like a little elevator thingy
okay then
I don't think we can get on at the same
time hello where are we hello okay so
we're all here
nice yeah
I'll fix it okay okay you guys are too
late wanna see a magic trick where are
you going are you going yeah but we
can't go over there with her I
yeah I'm done I think rain is the last
one
okay no I'm not done I'm not done sorry
that's my fault
um showers oh interesting yeah
interesting
hold on
can you help me with the okay thank you
I opened it thank you okay I just have
lounge and showers left sorry
[Music]
is this it no holy crap
what is this
foreign
[Music]
I don't know I think it's Mina oh my God
hello oh my God you scared me wait wait
wait wait wait wait
[Music]
I'm scared it's like so narrow
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna
vent here
bye okay
oh my God oh my God
where was that where was it oh no okay
now I'm okay in the cargo bay and she
was about to vent because she's she
thinks she's cool and then I saw a red
body
don't you see that um I was from the Gap
room and I passed by when you were in
the electricity and I go to the shower
and then I go to records again I wasn't
sure there's earlier
I I saw I saw I saw I think it was Kiara
and then Zeta is from the shower too
yeah
all right okay okay I don't think it's
raining so where is where is the
location of the body
uh I don't know what do you think it's
um in the cargo bay between the door of
medical Bay Reyna and Zeta which way
were you guys going through the showers
like to the left no I was with Kia I was
with you
yeah that was with me we came from the
top to the bottom from like loud could I
go the other way or you saw her going
with you no we I don't saw her I didn't
see her at all which is the problem what
yeah
literally I saw I saw like um
I go down I saw Zeta and then Kiara and
then uh Zeta and Kiara I think there
goes some of them going to the up to go
into the record and then after so after
that I sell okay if it's not Muna again
if it's not and she's just faking being
an engineer no that's your big brain
[Music]
would you say your brain cannot handle
that kind of skill
we will see we'll see if the game ends
now
if it doesn't happen no it's not me I
think you guys are losing
when I said bye
uh
[Music]
oh yay
hey
oh no my stream died
yeah
[Music]
you guys you guys like playing girls
like you guys going to two two groups
which one should I follow me
during the meeting was actually really
scary yeah
yeah yeah
it was pretty good
I'm so proud oh my God okay
a great a great round
excellent
as much as I want to continue playing I
don't wanna you know yeah yeah yeah we
don't even need to play on stream to be
honest just together yeah it would be
fun
yeah I know right I am rich right now I
have like 77. I have 1 600 full Cali
costume though and I'm wearing it so you
have until it's December 20th to get all
the Hall of Life stuff yeah
I have this one too long
[Music]
let's go Gamers Gamers I think I want to
hear a goodbye from everyone if that's
okay
for real goodbye let's start from the
top again I'm there how was it today oh
yeah it was pretty fun I won and it
passed around and then what all the
crewmate rounds or pretty much all of
them so it's you know pretty good day
pretty good game thank you for inviting
me Kiara thank you for setting it up uh
yeah thank you guys for playing thank
you for always sussing me even though
I've almost never with me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I kiss you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I couldn't get impulsive but it's
fine it's cool thank you so much as long
as you have fun right yeah
together thank you
you think knew it was fun
and next we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies yeah so I
think I was born to be crewmate I don't
like playing imposter anyway so I had a
good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your boy that's fine just let it be
and then everyone killed you early
thanks yeah
whenever you like explain something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like yeah it's so convincing and you are
not lying I'm good yeah shooting us I
just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
but I have to do tasks and I love doing
tasks so it was fun thanks for the
invite here
I do
you you didn't get an imposter right I
didn't but I made sure to be the damn
this best teammate that
[Music]
it was a statement about your actions
today how many times were you imposter
three times four
four four
it's like something in these collabs
there's always like one person who gets
it all the time I only got it quite a
bit too right like twice yeah I want to
say sorry for uh those who are
um being posted together with me because
I cannot
um I don't know why but a plane on this
room like uh there's
maybe pressure
um yeah like okay so I'm not that like I
felt that you you seem very important
very pressured it's okay if I if I fall
in for a long time because uh first I I
don't really uh can make a good excuse
or I will buy maybe in Bahasa Indonesia
it's so easy but
um I don't know uh you can always use
that as the excuse yeah I use that with
the JP no English please
you did a good job you're really good
yeah yeah
who gets just so many times
[Laughter]
because I thought the reverse psychology
would work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually access and say oh I'm
actually says
Ah Ali's just messing around but nah but
that's not true I pray I feel like
oh oh
no no no no
all the most utmost respect thank you
for accommodating all of this collab yay
Kiara thank you
[Music]
that was fun after a long long time it
was fun let's skip Luna for a second and
go to oh mama is not here anymore
oh hello yeah I start the stream naked
in the end the street making it even
though I unlocked the outfits
inviting me to the collab was really fun
playing with you guys was fun OT suit to
all the crewmates and also the Imposter
you guys were great
thank you so much it was so much fun I
got a few imposters and then a little
how many
you're afraid uh two or three I don't
remember yeah it was fun thank you for
those who teamed up with me and thank
you Kiara said bye for hosting it and I
want to apologize because my stream died
six times
how did you survive I don't know I just
couldn't apologize anyone watching but
today is good yeah
I think they're pretty good
I think Zeta killed me more than any
other member
[Music]
she can't talk
well we've got Bean said I'm sure she
had fun too yeah
hi
are you able to talk
no please
oh how fast are we trying oh oh Discord
oh yeah
let's go to Discord everybody
[Music]
okay I'm gonna move
hey okay
it's okay uh
you did it
hey congrats
thank you see you next time
[Music]
I have fun uh actually uh the first time
I'm doing uh the to become an imposter
with I mean it's really fun
is the one that I'm I'm usually afraid
of whenever I become an imposter
if I if I make it a list it's probably
and then Kali is the one who can like
talk a lot that make me you know
so that's usually the person
yeah I'm the sheriff hey what was that
surprise there
well anyway we can just talk anything
yeah let's just talk we can talk in here
we're done anyway I think I got to hear
from everybody I'm glad that we all came
together for another big Enid collab I
think the last one was Mario Karts
a year ago yeah it's a long time ago but
maybe since there's a lot of people this
weekend we can try it again sometimes
too
[Music]
thank you so much it was so much fun
thank you I'm having so much fun thank
you yeah and I really don't have
anything else to say besides good job
everybody hope you had fun and yeah see
you again soon sometime
everyone see you soon
[Music]
foreign