[Music]
[Music]
me
n
[Music]
N n
def n
n
me me n n eeeeeeeeeeeeee
[Music] It
was
[Music]
Men
N
[Music]
Ben
N
Hmm,
this kind of revision hurts.Idol
live tour is a folder.Dochipukuhotakke
was in the Ukeido way.This
program is sponsored by the sponsors you are watching.  I
'll send you
DEE
Ah, oh, oh
,oh, oh, a
day GM, and you
'll want to do good morning
way park throat nonno
andere f 4
regclean
menus king
sentiment predater zo
tarp 4 apbs
per  Worker Bad Forechonso It's
okay to do it see
ren Da Da Pu Puu Saa
areas All
rear derailleur
indore This
is actually the second time the leaders have jumped and talked about zorb Talk with Pururusa before the release of that one that I can't pay for.
Yes, I had the pleasure of
having a very deep and deep conversation with Mr. Tomizawa once.If
you are interested, please
come and see the worst 4s before the release.
Yeah,
yeah 9 is a potty boy or a graveyard day
center shop pottery
n
ase monopoly walker mean to
do I'm going to surrender to the vehicle inspection
interview of 4 The
broadcast is gyaa
4 star b The other side of the car And the
senior is that little bit of fun
Masuki, I'm fine. I mean, it's just that loud recording.
Boo-
boo
searc e to
do the author of arc
2Staff and patty
That one bird that did Ne in Undo is
that time in the default phrase.I'm
translating it live, but like the previous Tel Job
talk, the year is a little bit Chiara. Wow, I
didn't have the confidence to convey the content, so
subtitles are fine.  old r fork ios
b up to
acme gathering continue watch oome gyu
girl-chan t
aaaaaa
testis party sauce won ownership
waaaaan
i inside strangers plan
Wow, there's a fish in the eye blind
ok I'll
break out of my shell tomorrow and
renderjre
anc is
terrorizer It's getting cooler and I'm going to 6
5 fufufu
[Music]
Oh, and in addition to 5 door cure 5 acom Tsuboi
Tartasker
There's a trailer I'd like to show you a little while ago, so please check it out  Look at that
[music]
pattern
rester charles jointy
co
hardy screen name place
a clever
mima foretrex so rear
[music]
voodoo
graffiti girls jr edition
bonder 2 s bar
[music] I've
been drinking
baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
booboo
seara ah the whole amateur fukue
mase voodoo m sports e-prize
ya rap hanyu point game
n
ifaw monster web yumu
weber pink don't get better lean naming
amo3 es main vein  Kushiya
Actually, I think this Aisin is quite a sound topic,
but
if you haven't seen it, it
's a pretty rough topic, so I
think it's just barely okay.
So
acore
Gettweet  please enjoy
amebagg sesami roux
de rinon bar &peing
arin pro surfer a star
lever everyone please enjoy and this is
a
4 point job talk with my senior.
ahkah
eroliwangoo even
esp limit store arm birthday
in front of the imperial palace a
howa skin 4
san it's far away apis giant ghost same
report bird chase espa lsdana and
pop person and pepsion we are
chitar
bunch
taso  cesarean
riso
[music]
manen be some name
ermaster ice cream
window asr painting
in
rb zao
boob
ander phone ah soai goo
[music]
do volume osanai
asperge teens were
to
do ri so gd 5 gay bar
walker bow arere n suo
iso has no day of
unpa way beads bas reb
hanyu point game
yeahyeah
ran b 2 dj  ren beats
pro aboard maa piece 4 s
akekno web alanui black
Club member Comet Senpai 2 maisto Key
a
Living Senpai Good evening
to the city Hello,
good morning to Hello Comber
Hello, good morning Good morning, it's
okay to use Japanese from here on, so let's celebrate
Reiji Well, please sign language is Hoshimoni Comet
Thank you for your support Ahano  I would appreciate a
detailed self-introduction from my senior.
Okay, the
raw superdo stone appeared like a pod in a hurry.  I
'm the conservative town comet in the love/hate department. Thank you very much.
ig I want another one.
Thank you for coming to this industry today. It
's my second time. Yes,
it's my second time. That first time was Nemecha.  Me-
chan was feeling sleepy. Parser: I
'm sure it was heavy at that time. ia This is the rice. I'm
sorry for the wallet, but my head has been feeding well since spring. Did it
reach the surface of the water? It's already been today. Today.  It
was nice to have a photo with a badge. That's
right. I'm going to do it.
Thank you for your support. I'm going to show you the
show, and I'm
going to talk a lot about the video and the body damage series today.
But,
before that, uh, before that...  I
'll give the details to everyone in 50% of this broadcast, but the
characters are so
special that Ubebe's medieval name is so
powerful.
Eh, Fufuufuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuo~ Toulouse Orb Arise, a
staff member, Ranko Hane, showed me a
very nice technique. I
was given such an opportunity, so I was very impressed.  How
many times should I say this?
If I don't sleep, I don't know what's going on.It's
still one series, yeah
yeah.I might
not be able to do it yet, but at the end of the year, I
want something and I don't want it.
Seriously, I
want that sword of universal flame.
Reina Tsuusei's Chiara already has the power,
and
I don't have it. Hmm, I think the
Apen-san case is better.
If it were that Geara, then
Phoenix.  That's why it's not painful to hold that flaming sword, but
it's probably been two years since I've had it,
right
?
That's right, that surfer is coming! I was
wondering what this was all about,
and I noticed that, and so did the viewers.
There's a theme to the flames in Haiphong,
but there are other things like the sound they make when they drink, their
personalities,
management,
etc.  It's kinda like that, yeah yeah
Well,
there was a part where she was playing, so I was later in character,
so at first I was more interested in Shion-chan, and I
thought it suited her better, but
in the end I decided to listen to something.  When I got to the end, I
thought, ``I am Alfe.'' Nana,
after all, the cemetery, the
society, and that kind of thing are not now, and I think
it's more like me. A
self-improving character hmm
a
Eran: There's
no book about the characters,
but if you ask me, when I was playing that game, I was
always using Alfe, and I was
always playing Feng with the lane,
so I kind of empathized with the
main character.  It's
big,
but I thought it was me, and I was talking, and I thought it was me,
so please give me a shallow, understandable source, because I was doing it with Alpine in mind, so that's
meat, so that certain Fen is a market.
This is definitely one of the 7 most similar characters to me,
even if I don't have a source.Hmm,
Japan's favorite cap
is Alfe after all.Ah, it's
Law.It's Ross.What's so
surprising about it?  I don't
know, other than karanmiruno,
umm, Rasmurano, I like leaf sudare, and it looks like soul. Hi
, the polyrhythm
was also like Moon Alfen, but
ah, if there's an argument, do you like the sound? I'll do it.
He's a good guy, but I
like his hoodie. I
like the front. I can see him. Why do good seniors
always say things like that during the dance? It
's always Nezu's words, but
the front is...  I love you,
and Law is really a good bookkeeper.
Yo, come on, come on, come on, let's say true. He
's a striker, so it's Law. Also, he
has a cute personality.
Maybe M's is the best.As time
passed, I started to like Michi a little too,
but at first I didn't like it at first,
but I thought it was a bit annoying,
but I don't know what the reason for the split
is.  There was a story about Roan's father. I heard
that Roan's father died, right? So, what
started the whole thing is over, Ro says.
So it's like the fur you suggested.
At the end of Law, I thought he was a foreigner like this remote island where he used his mantra, so
I thought something like that too,
but as the story progressed, I started to wonder
what kind of person Law was, and when Law's true personality
first appeared.  I was already thinking about her, but as I
started to see more and more of her bright personality and her role as someone being teased, I
thought she was cute, and that she was the mood maker at that party.
super  Did you put it in t
?
Ah, I
didn't put it in loose party.
Ah, I see.
Ah, that
's a lie. I'm not here. Wow, my
favorite character is:
Hmm, it's
a bit of a tingling scene, but it's delicious. A
character that basically makes you fall in love with teenagers.
Tower, a woman.  But what, I can
understand being gay. I like cute girls.
But I don't know if I'd say they're cute. I like kids who look like they're cute.
That's why I don't think they're just posing.  I
love Kisara.
Yes, Kisara is a nice place. It's a really Japanese
burger, but it's a restaurant at the door. It's
not just sexy, it's
like they really take care of the house they're heading to.
That's why I like it.  When that part of Kisara that doesn't exist and embraces it
comes out, I thought, "Oh yeah,
that's it," and then I threw it away, but that part
of Kisara that I really fell in love with
was a very serious part.
Hmm, after my death, I'm trying to do my
best to think about the island, and I
wonder how amazing and serious it must be.Also,
this is a little bit about the
appearance part, but
it's
about the basic mother, that video game as a whole.  View It's
always been that way, regardless of the
female character's
equipment, the group is AI, and the
equipment that doesn't protect her body properly is height and eye-fi.That's
how it is in character design.
Acura Design has a proper rose version, and I
thought, ``This is really cool,'' and I
thought, ``Hmm, it's got a shape,'' but then I found out that it
wasn't really hidden, but it was
completely hidden in the middle of the night.  I don't think so,
but Kisara also said that why her back is
so empty is
because she doesn't want to show her back, so
there's a reason for her improvisation.
There's a good reason why
Kisara
has a really big shield,
and up until now, she's fought standing upright.In the
games in the Away series, it's
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa For sure, the
sound mirror is really good, isn't it?  Yeah, that's true, I
really dislike Tsuru Tsubasa's fighting style that revolves around that.Actually,
I actually came back with the character to use in that battle,
but
that wooden plate...  It's
a bit slow, I don't know, but that
speed feels a bit slow.However
, compared to a certain Fen, it
has a very stiff wind,
and yes, it's surprisingly easy to fight.Oh
yeah, and of course there's only that wooden plate.
In that battle,
a, I wonder
how they would say it in Japan, that
opponent's
a,
rather than opening up the opponent's attack, he
completely accepted it and took it on stage.Hmm, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, the
school doctor is interesting, it's really cool,
and a.
Actually, I've come to really like Shion too. That's right
. That girl is a
little bit nyan no Tezo blog
a
Song parent, Xillia's umm mirror, she
's definitely a strong woman. She has some kind of curly
hair.  I remember something about the color,
but somehow I thought it was worth more than that.At
first, I thought it was so similar.It was so
cold.I
don't really want to interact with people.
Yeah, I can't push people, it's accurate,
but as the story progresses, it
becomes warmer and more accurate, and I wonder why it
starts to look like a human being.It's
true that Miller also became more sensitive and human-like.
That's right, that
's right, that's why wooden plates and salt are the best for ski days at home.  I
thought maybe it was fate,
so I met him and showed him the review.Heheheheheh, there was a suicide note from Kisara.Well, I
want to give birth to a child, and I want to go to America.  That's
great. I don't
think I can compete with Uso, but in Papauchi's mind,
he's the one. I'll make it come true in my path, too.
Thank you Hiko. Yes,
then Root.
Tails of Arise
Eight
Hmm, it was my favorite out of all the games.
Is it poop? Yeah, I
guess that's it. Hmm, graphics. Phone. The graphics are really beautiful. Dane. I thought it was a little different from the usual Tales.  It's
not 3D or Starbucks' CG, but it's
textures that give you a sense of the world, and it's
watercolor-like or something.  The
water repellency is weak and it looks like watercolor,
and the CG has a kind of analog-like
feel to it, and the fact that
it's
expressed in the cc
doesn't really make you feel like him, which is
amazing.  I've always thought that, and
thought how beautiful the graphics were.I
remember games like Egg Syria and the
graphics being so beautiful.  It
had a digital feel to it. It was free. It
was really good, but it felt like it was the latest technology, and it was so beautiful. Hmm, Arise feels more
like an ancient civilization. It really
felt amazing.
That's what I thought was the
best part about Washing Your Head.I see, that's
the story.  It's a
story from the Tales of series.
All of them are very satisfying.I wonder how
to say Pa's amazing Inspy Ring in Japanese.I
had it written with subtitles.  I
was thinking, hmmm, and
when I'm choosing a game, I'll
definitely look at the graphics of the house
.  I don't have much
interest in games that aren't 3D, or maybe I'm really into them.I
really like the style of the anime A, which has a Japanese style, and I really like the illustrations.
Like the recommended senior,
I really liked the graphics
of Todo of the Angry Wave and
Aru Njare Sai's Maa Mobile Zo Rise.The
character designs of Mokamikami are amazing!  I was
just lucky when I first saw the final specs.The
character
design is very girly,
but it also has a
bit of equipment.It looks
strong, but when I
touch it, it's so weird.  I
wonder if it's just the cliff that's going to scatter, but it's a fleeting patient.That's right, I
drew a dog that saw a beautiful kamikami, right at the very beginning.That's
when the new trailer was released.
When I saw the Chance Wave, I saw Isaan al-
Sion turn into a cow coming down from the stairs. I
was so moved when I saw him walking. There
was something so new about that. I could
feel it. I
couldn't stop my heart pounding when I saw it, and the chicken bones were all messed up.  It was the
scene where she was standing -
Elegant's
Shion-chan had left her there.Hmmm...I really feel like
this Tales Handwashing
Arise is really
in charge of the character design as well.  I'm
sure it's different, so I really
thought it was a new Tales.Even
above, it seems like it's the same Tales.Please, there's
nothing left.There's nothing left.  I
want you to say, ``That's my favorite scene.'' I'm a child who loves music, Momo, who can't pay for that Tills. Oh, ah, the
old man sitting in the strange chair, Nishion,
was taken away, wasn't he?
Yes, it's fast Fujin r It's pretty good at the beginning The
first one is
Ah, what kind of things are you talking about?
That guy has been stalking us all the time, or that weird guy.
This is Borage, but Ponpon-tei
Wienska number That person is that one.  I wanted to
take Sheen away and then we'd all go somewhere, so my
sister and I
wanted to go help her, but
Alpen
brought back that pain, so we said no.
Even though I was in pain, I
decided to help Sheen,
so I went deeper, and Shion had already
fallen into a dark place,
and Hahn came closer to me and started to feel like it was you.  It wasn't
like that, it was really painful,
but there was
nothing I could do about Alfon being in that pain
anymore, but now that the tide is out, I'm suffering from that familiar pain.  It
hurts, but I held onto Sheen
and said, ``Caramel Nuts.'' I
thought that Sheen was a man who never made a mistake, and I
wanted to have a big spare, and he
always asked me for the correct answer.I've done that already.  I
thought that the main character was really doing what I wanted him to do, and that
was a really great scene.On the other hand, when I
walked up to him and it definitely stayed in my memory,
it was one of his wives.
Well, there are
two. Actually, there are
three in Gaan, but I
can't get enough of my mother, but it's sad and angry. I
talked about it a little bit earlier, and that
hard-working envelope guy died a quick death. There
's one scene, but hmmm, there's another one.  On the other hand,
there are too many children who die like a good Salah, and I wonder why they died in the first place.
People won't believe me, so I
have to introduce something to everyone and put up a front.
So instead of delusions, I want all the women
to understand, and
I sacrifice myself to save everyone else.
In Toyonaka, where I had to go to
A, I burst into tears when Kisara saw it and
cried like that.I was
already in my heart.From the
lines.  There aren't too many reporters at home.  I
was playing with an English voice, and
Mr. Kisara's 8 voice actors
were really good.
[Music]
My heart is so sick,
but it must have been a bad thing. Japanese Grandma.
I was in
Japanese.  The version was already very emotional.
Yes, that's right. No, I don't
dare.
Still, even the half-damaged rim
has been traumatized. Let's put
it out there. Behind the scenes,
everyone understands, but
no, but...
Well, there wasn't anything
else that could have been done depending on the store.I'm
thinking about it a lot.Well,
well, it seems
like it's inside.It
's a total shame, but thanks to that, I was
able to show off a really great performance.  Taichi left and right Nishiosu is unique
Haito a
Hey hey yeah
Next
thing I want to ask is
Yes,
there's a lot of those shakes.
Kako's sister-in-law is fast, huh?
Did you find them all? Ah,
actually.  Ah, I
cheered when I found them all.
Hahahaha, I
haven't found them at all. No jamin. I guess it's just the moon
a.
I can't go back. I have to go back and look for them. There's
one Frill and two Cars,
but...  I loved shaking it,
and what I liked the most was touching it, and what I liked the most was
touching it. There was a full ball that Kou was hitting. He looked like it was going to be
rough, and then
he hit the oil filler and it was full all the time.  is in my head  It
's cute and cute, but I thought I'd add a little more. I
added it to the selling l.
[Laughs] I really
like the Boober. Did it have an
attachment?
Actually, it's Comet-senpai. The attachment was
n't running before, so it looks awful.  As for how many years ago,
in the full game, I
would catch as many Oto as I could find them,
but,
well, back in the day, when I played Tales, I
had my own rules.
Oh, I decided to play that first round
without changing any attachments or costumes,
and I decided to play from 20 a onwards.That
's southwest.The
reason is that in the first round,
there was a really serious scene.  I'll do it.I'm
wearing a bathing suit as a lie.The
words are written on my face and I'm dealing with it.Already, the
ring of angels is going at the same rate.It
's one of the top mano cars, isn't it?  I'm going to
lose consciousness. Let's hold it.
Um,
in that state, I wanted to enjoy Tales in that neutral state
first,
so I tried not to touch the ground and the stone grains. You
know what happened after the attack.  It's been a long time since I've had a Negiya
I also got a little scolded by the viewers during the stream
Sasa Sa Onyau listener support For example, it's
so big
a
Honey Girl Ranson, that ground, that
TLG downloadable content, etc.
If you put it
on
, you'll be able to make the screen almost completely from scratch, and you won't be able to
see the character's face.
Let's
smile
8 It's cute
Yeah,
no, I'm sure I don't know what's going on, but yeah, it
's that Fang,
right? Then the goal doesn't look serious anymore, and I wonder who it is.
There were 7 heels that the director could not enter,
but even if it is not, even if you do not have that
patience, you will have a variety of decorations.  A
pond full of water 6 It's probably in a self-propelled car.
I think everyone will understand.
There are probably people who look like Chara,
there are people who do things like me, and others.
There may be other people who think otherwise, and there are
many ways to play with it,
but there's one thing that
Chiara did, and the other thing that she did was
break the eyeliner, and if she did the same hairstyle for each of the 4-style costumes, it would
be
blue.  That mask on your cheeks will come off quickly. There
's an
air trip,
so it'll disappear quickly, so I looked at it first.
Uhoho.  I
heard that it was that real story that turned that opposition party out of line, but I did
n't watch it, so it's weakened.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah, the
emotion of that moment has faded.Even
so.  It's my fault. I
couldn't make the ball, so if I had hair, I wouldn't have it all. It's
all the fault of Mr. Barndam, who is cool and has a cool haircut in his prime. No, no, it's actually me, 4 strokes behind.  It's
my fault that the eggs aren't coming anymore.
Well, putting aside the winter story, it's full. I personally think
that finding the old door is the first mission of this game.  It
's full.
Ah,
duffle bus.
Next question is,
uh,
which one was the one you hated the most
?
To the boss enemy you hated the most,
why that house?  Matching
eyes dollar
Oh, those witches, please, Soma, the higher ranked lab. It's
not a ball run because there's no launcher. Ume. She
said she didn't like Dora, and she didn't like that.
And that story has a really bad personality. And it's
not because she has a bad personality. It's not because she has a bad personality. It's not because she has a bad personality.
Well, during the boss battle, you fought with a long bird and then a hatching. It was
really difficult and far. It was
amazing to defeat flying enemies, but Anchor
was difficult. That's true, but it was really difficult. It was
because there was a voice.
Kirifuhaha
is also Amedora, but
it's not anyone's good problem, the
problem of phrase personality is
very sexy and
Usuki, but that's the boss in each of them.  I do
n't know how to say it in Japanese, but
a That's the
cheerful contest. Hmm. The contest that
all the bosses are participating in.
Ah.
Yes, yes, it's early, yes, yes,
everyone has their own
a-
instruments to win, and the guards and others have their own a-a strategies
to gather that energy.That
blue girl, I
feel like it was the worst.  Ah,
Mach, that woman was terrible, wasn't she?
ee There wasn't a 3 difference.
First of all, I wonder
what it is.
How should I explain it? I
don't want to spoil it too much, but it's
possible.  In
44th Day, the Blue-Eyed Ones were
called to defeat the Blue-Eyed Ones, but in the end, that was the most
important banner,
and everyone gathered together and died there. That's a completely
surprising Doll de Breligar, isn't it
? Clown.  I'm a fan,
and that's the story. I
thought that Aomemedora was the best, and then there was
Rin Archer,
Blue Mirror, and another CI, which was great.  I
got emotional, but it
was Murou-kun, and I was trying to stop the a ring router there, but
from the point of view of the end, I was thinking, ``Just keep doing it,'' and then I was
thinking, ``Wiener Cola'', but I
thought, ``I'm going to kill you.'' Give me these clothes.  I was
seriously thinking about it when we fought each other at Goro's,
but
Furo-kun said it was too expensive,
so I stopped going there myself.  There's
a lot of stuff that
goes on and on, and I
think there was that anime about Ume Dora no Kami, right? I think there was an anime about that, and
at the beginning there
was that scene where they almost got burned like that.
Please stop teasing me in the club.I
said, ``Hey, Ume Dora is in the third layer of the zone, and the other
batting lineup is...''
After I said that, when I saw him, I thought, ``Oh, he's such a nice guy.''
Even in the middle of the soil, it's like a half-damaged
rim. Ohno: I thought it was going to be different, but it's going to be different, but it's the one that I hate the most because it's like
that.  I chose number Kira,
right?
moumoon
a
Hmm,
what is the Japanese sound called? From the trend
Nellis launches anon Mysterious black in
Fukuoka hit
a It
also appeared in the trailer a  Is
n't that man a color? Ah, I can't help but wonder about that mysterious riddle that appeared so often from the beginning. Oh
yeah, after that, I think I'll be able to find out more and more about who this person is,
but I
still don't know.  Sending out this character of myself back in the day
What kind of person is this
?
Creating an image of myself Wow, what was that
? Well, I
fought hard. That's
right, I am.  I
thought that Ryuk in Tales of Vesperia was the person from 81.
Ah, I see. I don't know what to say. He's neither
a target
nor an ally, but in the end he
becomes a target and becomes the final boss.  I
thought he was the type of person who would say something like, `
`Well, I guess it wasn't like that.''
Harlau's...
well, Kiara-han,
un-go,
how many levels are there?  I
thought it might be a battle that took place in the future or in the past, and I thought about it, trying to find a good day and thinking about it.  I
had a notebook where I was coloring various sizes, and
ah, I was trying to process the past or future evil [ __ ], and it
was wrong. The
slider was so annoying.
Well, that's just what I wanted to ask
. a
8Next question is,
if you live in the world of rising market prices,
what part of the world would you live in?
Where would you live? After all, the place where the Nakaharim ruled was the place where the
Nakaharim ruled.
There's an area that's full of hot water, and it's very clean,
even if there's not one head there.
Hmm, am I
messing up?
After visiting that quiet and calming place, I love snow, so I
thought it would be a good idea to go there and go skiing.
But yeah, the
people who live in the sushi area are too strong, so
who's on the 4th floor?  We don't trust each other or the people around us anymore. I
thought, ``This is going to make life difficult,
'' so I thought, ``What if it was Sysrodia after those security people
saved me?''  I'm
sure you're the type of person who doesn't want to do that, right?
Well, the people who live there are the
only ones in the world where people are expelling terrorism,
and
where everyone is from.  It
's so peaceful because we're all together, and I'm
also thinking about hand-clawing, and I'll take good care of
you for 2 minutes.
I'm a liquor thief who lives there, and
when I first
walked in, I thought, ``Wow, it's so beautiful.'' I
went there for a while, and there were parts like this, and I was
running it, and I felt like it was so
comfortable.  - Hmm, when
there is a beautiful fruit, it has a very familiar feeling.It
was a design that seems familiar.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa,
today's type a
You
can also do a lot of fishing without rolling or paying.Resale
Wow, I've been doing a lot of things, Khan.Actually, I've
been to Lid's cheek fights, and I like someone,
but my favorite hobby is fishing.I
love it, so I told the other
characters, ``
A, that fishing is great.''  It's my duty to press the button, follow me,
and follow me.The village is so
cool and cute when you see it lying at a distance.But
normally, I'm not interested in it, but
in this game, I'd rather just do fishing.  Well,
I've
caught a lot of them. Have I caught them all yet? That's
true. Well, I always catch the same fish, and when I
'm in a relationship, I sometimes catch one. I was
wondering how I could do this, and I
kept on catching them all.  There's a trick,
but you know what's wrong with that rainy mountain,
that fishing thing, the
middle town,
and that brain for fishing,
that's right, that
fish,
that special one, that's what I don't have.  They
don't come to me, but that's because
even after that game, I have to slow down a little to get them,
so at first it was all about the same Yusa,
but I was a
carrier,
and I liked water, but this...
Even in the game, I thought Arthur was a bit gloomy because he was so bad at it,
so I
couldn't remember the buttons on that controller at all, and when I
didn't see them directly, I couldn't figure out where the buttons were,
for example, where the egg type x was.  I
can't remember if it's a big deal, so I made a lot of mistakes in the part where I
had to press that button in Fear Fishing.  It's
good that there isn't that darkness in southern Hokkaido with ltrt.Even
though it's small, something is going to happen.Well, it's
good.It's not just the house.I'm
glad that I have a lot of things too.
someone told me
In fact, there was a long pattern,
and now that I think about it, there is a pattern that is easy to catch and a bit
like that.If you look at the way the fish fly, it seems like it's Baikal.Yes, it seems like it's a
fishing master.Ah, now that I think about
it, all the viewers are fishing masters.
I'm amazing. I'm
a little bad at taking pictures of
that one, but if I try really hard, I think the
more I look at the movements of the fish, the more and more they'll
disappear, so next time I'll get them to pay attention to it a little,
and I'll take the house back as well.  Mr. Miss.  It
seems like there aren't any.EighterThe next question I want to ask is, do you have a favorite costume of all kinds?My favorite one is, why is it Genesic, King Orlan?Wow, that's such a crazy name.  But,
ah, I wonder which one it was.
Maybe I don't think it's the English pronunciation in English. That's nice. evernote. What is it?
Let's eat like a deaf person.
Guaaaaaaaaaaaaaaand the cause is the fence.
Philippi.  dba dnj child,
uh, welt
Hey, it's a Boost Strike Day of 6 with influence. It's
basically like a negative gate. It's like an evolved version of a negative gate. Oh, it looks like it's a splash, and I love it for that reason.
That
gigantic Harim
Toriuel is a good
thing on its own terms, but I'm pretty sure those two hated each other the most.  I
couldn't really understand such a huge amount of things,
but in the middle of 7 or so, we
both approached each other and looked at
each other as if we were people from different countries, but we had a lot of dual characteristics.
There's also the fact that they accept it properly and it's constant, and the fact that
these two are doing that trick together
makes it a great meeting, and
today, Ha Rim's eyes
are shining brightly.
In Ram, the scene where that
woman turns blue and turns into
a certain 6 is so cool.
Ah, yes, I'm in the overwork zone, and that Liberl dares to
say the words that make me angry. She flies
in the sky, like a witch. It's so true.  It's
impressively cool and I love it,
and since I like Negative Gate, I
thought that the Tax Enforcement Ordinance, which feels like an evolved version of Negative Gate, was really cool and I loved it.I see.
When I was editing the video, I
lost the case, but everyone knows that
there is something about a father and son in the station,
but even if it doesn't involve cowweed, I
like that one.  Booth Slyko is the
best at stealing Phoenix. I
don't know the title of Japan, but I can
unravel it. Also,
Kisara and a certain side of the West are like Fire and
Tornado's angry guy.
Edgarmoo
is amazing. He's gotten so powerful. But I don't like any of the booth strikes that Kisara participates in. They're all powerful.
Oh yeah, and the
festival that moved after that has a technique with Phoenix's name on it,
but that's the number one line.
There are a lot of thunder jeans feet, Nicks, and there are some
techs that jump up, and then they come out and
jump off.That's
right.
Sasa is cool.
That's
right. People were bumping into each other.
Everyone used it.
Ah, it's so easy to use. Hmm, it
shined. It's something that's been around for a long time. Let's
leave it alone.
Some girl, I
decided to do that, but I'm not moving Ah, I'm sure It's
been around for a long time, so I remember thinking it was Mars
a I
see,
ok ok
a Let's
move on to the next person
Next
a
Kihara: I'm a little curious about this, but what is it?
A terre, Raizo,
Hiraga, and I noticed one thing as I continued to play.  My
play style has
completely changed. Up
until now, I've been paying too much attention to the story, and I've
decided to go ahead with the battle.
After laying an egg, I was supposed to be the boss anyway.  There are
quite a few times when I'm fighting that I don't have enough to sell, and I end up getting sold out and failing over and over again.Riser: When it comes to bar rises, there are
a lot of things that are shocking, for
example.  After the battle, you can quickly return to the map. It's
really fast, isn't
it? It's smooth, isn't it? Well,
it takes a lot of time compared to before, so I hope
Kiara doesn't get tired of fighting at all. It's so much
fun.  Go on and on.
Even if you raise your level and fight bosses, you can
usually defeat them in one go without any problem.But it
may have been a benefit of the DLC, but I just told you about this.
For that recommendation senior, I
want to play my own at Rise, so has
anything changed?I
said earlier that I only use Alpen when I sing, so I
guess that's true.Hmm,
Alpine is often in April, isn't it?
Well, it's
okay. Pharynx Originally, I used to use the magician to attack from a long distance, but Ramon: Yes, that's right, it's been like that for a long time.  I've been using it a lot, and
I've been doing that for a long time,
and I've been doing it, and I'm using Harold, and I'm
going to use the demon king, and it's been a long time since I've been using melee.  It's been
almost a year since I've used magic, and I've
started using it quite a bit, and I
used to think it was difficult, but
now that I
try it, I feel like I used to have a hard time with it.  I
thought it might not be as good as I imagined it to be, so I
thought there was an avant-garde model that said it was easy, but I thought it was fun and fun, so I just used Bun-Bun Alfen.I
thought it was really interesting, but now that thin senior is doing it.
Did I mention that
I
always had a wizard character on my team in the Tales of the North series of games,
but I've never had the chance to do it myself
?
When I tried it out, I
thought it was a little more flashy with things like Rinbel, and I
think Shihyun was able to do it a bit more, but when I
tried playing around with it, I
found it to be much easier to use than before.  It's okay to  Now
that I think about it, it's really fun to do the tricks twice at
such a fast speed, so
I thought, Wow, it's amazing and easy to use.Um, let's
use the water.Well
, the next question is, yeah,
pay the teruzo.
Why do you recommend it to those who are researching it? What
is the best part of it that you would like to recommend to viewers?
And
what about the other Teru Kakuboto Top series games?  et
al.
Uh, please tell me in a promotional manner.
Okay, so I'd
like to give a presentation on Tizbu Arise. It's cancer.
Well, speaking of Ad Tales,
this person's character has a chest shape of about
23 people.  Since you haven't been here, that
girl has really been completely redesigned,
and
now has a different character and shape than before.And there's
also that
[ __ ], isn't it?  I was
wondering why they decided to use the same type of screw because they thought it would be used for lung cancer, but
this is a new departure for Fields.  I wonder if it's a point, because
Hahn has always been the same, so the
good parts of Tales so far are still there, and the
anime is sandwiched in the middle, and there
are skit chats like that.
But it's a classic picture up to that point, and while still retaining the Tales feel, I
thought it was really new, and conveyed that feeling to everyone,
especially
in Arise.  What I thought was new was,
well, as I said earlier, it
was skit chat. It
's completely different from before, it's different from before the war,
and to be honest, Chiara is better here.  I
like guides, so it's interesting, isn't it? I
never get tired of listening to the stories, and it
makes me want to do them. That's
right. It's even more elaborate. Up until now, it's been like
that anime-like Last Day. It's
like an anime.  Overdoing it and
chatting, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right,
the face has some expressions, wheeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeh up chatting out there, out there I
killed the middle icon point on my face.  It
's 4 people, but the construction this time
is 3D at the Harbor Rye place, and it's a chain, isn't this money? Is
skit chat really? Up
until now, I thought it was pretty much a running part with extras.
But Louis already has
that mini-story, it's
dark, it feels careless, it's like a foreign Japanese item, but it's not that,
so I'm a
fan of the till's off series.  It's a
work that retains many of the elements of the new Tales, while also retaining some of the elements of the Tales up to m, so
it's a work that I would recommend to people who are playing Nails for the first time.  I
thought it was amazing.Of course, I would
recommend it to people who have played Tales before,
but
to people who want to play Tales but don't know where to start, it seems like it's a
game I'd like to recommend.
Hey,
if I were to choose one of them now, I'd
probably recommend it, but I'd
say that I recommend it.The story
of Real Server Rise is
quite dark, and
even if the story is muddy, it still has that
sensitivity.  Soriona story 0 I highly
recommend it, and the battles are super
fun.As I said before, Chiara
usually doesn't like it, but this shape
makes me want to do more and more battles.  It's
fun and smooth, and it's
really fun.It's
not just the main character who eats, but also the other
characters.It's
very easy to play and easy to remember, so I
highly recommend it to everyone.Aso  I would
definitely like to tell my seniors of the opposite sex that I should
try playing other characters.I want to
do ecoo.It's amazing how it
works properly.If you learn how to do that, you'll have a lot of
fun doing it.That
door rim.
Well, because of the speed of the heels, it would be nice if they
were included in the video.The dog's heels
don't need that much, so I
think it would be fun to fight by dropping the tide yourself.Please
use the official clothing at the same time.  And Mahler, other than that, I think the water-based
version has summarized it very well.I'd
like to ask you a few general questions about the series.
yeah
How did I get started on that expansion series
called Sitter's Ga
?The
reason: My older
sister's friend got into Tales, and
she was able to progress with the Boo Boo minutes, so we
met and said Tales was interesting.  But it
was Tales of Destiny 2,
but
goo,
it's a sound that
my sister can't do.
Yes,
management I could
n't defeat that boss, sis.
Oh yeah, so
I said I wanted to do it too, so I
connected two controllers, and the two of us
defeated it together, making it the boss of Da. Let's
defeat it. Bye. Great work, you
two.  It was fun to play with them,
and I
started following that series all the time, and it was a fun game for two people to play together.
[Music] It's
new, is
n't it? It's a new toy for the two of us, or
rather, it's fun to play with.  Hey
Kisai grew up painting abroad, so the
afterlife was 6 stitches, and the
score of the series was quite different from that of Japan, and she was
n't well-known in the rain,
right? That character was also a child.  At the time, it
was luck, or rather, it wasn't well known at all, and the
first game that became a bit popular was
Tail Increase Suspicious 4 Urine,
then High Rider Progress Meow, and it
spread overseas more and more.
When I was a kid, I didn't know about the city motels, and I didn't
know anything about Japan's first-year junior high school families.I
still didn't know anything about Japan, and I hadn't really
developed an interest in Japan, and my
mom told me about that ignorant brother
for Christmas.  I received a European-style symphony as a gift,
and I loved
it.That's right.At first, I played it all the time as a 22-year-old brother, and
I liked watching it at home,
so I'm still enjoying it.  I
don't understand the game a bit, so I'm going to
accept the Grandpa's new option even if it's difficult.
Pony is already a game that can be played by two people,
so the freshness of it
makes me want to participate eventually.
It's cute, so it's
cute, and it's fun.It's because I'm just
trying to remind myself.Sometimes I get
to hang out by myself, so I'll write a report, but
when it's hard, I'll call you big brother and we'll be together.
That's how I played it,
and from there I started to wonder if there
were more games like this,
so I looked it up and found out that
there was an increasing series, so I started playing
from there.
Hey, I'm
addicted to it. Yes, I get it.
That's why I'm such a lowlife Shunpo. All I can do is
thank you for your guidance. I love this
game. That's the
best
game in the series. Which game is it from the Eyes Off series?  It's a
6-cut Zorbsiabyss.
4 points ahead of the direction peak I mentioned that a little bit more.
That's certainly a very popular run. There are some
scammers. I was
really worried about Vesperia and Vesperia.
Ah, he loved Vesperia and the house.What I
like about Bis is that the
stories are so painful.I love that the stories are so painful.
After giving birth, each and every one of us has that something,
or rather, our own thoughts, and we
have to do it ourselves, because we
all don't have a party, and our
souls are
deceived.  It was really like the
party in Tales C. It
's said locally that it was the party that got along the least,
but that party in the middle was a little gray at the end. It
felt like how many parties had it been or should I say
6 Actually, it was about Luke.  I didn't particularly dislike it.
However,
I feel like that. It's
really m. It's so delicious that I can cry, and
everyone is different, so when I go there, I
find out the true meaning behind it. It
's called an RPG, but it's
kind of my
thing.  Or rather,
thinking, I
learned one of the works that encouraged my child's growth.
Well, that's okay. I'm
playing an RPG that's really deep and worth the over-the-top
[laughter]  It's
definitely one of the best games I've ever played.Kitani,
by the way, my favorites
are Zone Songs, Xillia 1, and Flow, but there
wasn't anything special about that one.Well,
I understand.  I think it's a
laundry share game,
so let's select a tile once and make that
choice.The whole game changes depending on the choice.It's a
very, very dark question.It's a
very dark and painful game
in the Teruzuof series.  I
think it's the
only game where you can choose a lot of options like that, but it's the only one that really has any effect.Also, there
were some parts that seemed like the lower route without Posk,
but that Xillia.  I don't know what it is because the main character
doesn't talk, so it doesn't really matter.The main character doesn't speak, so it doesn't really matter.The main character doesn't speak, so it's centered
around being made into a character.It's the choice
you make.Hmmm, the
choice is the most important thing.That
feeling really
struck me.The trajectory of the wind.  I
like it when the route of a series or game is already decided,
but this one was really fresh and I
thought, oh hey, it's fun.As I
was playing it, I also found my favorite
character.
Mirror max l o xo
hey maxwell ni hody se
again oh yeah soo I
love a so much and so
much a and a and a and a and a A and a and a and a and a a and a and a and a and a a and a and a and a and a a and a and a and a of Magiruu-chan is no wonder but
Gil-chan is so funny I like who's my favorite  I think the
support team-like girl I wanted as a character would be Ritter.
Wow,
Ribogaeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
stills heyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
When I looked at the IC that was supposed to come out, I definitely
liked Dayner and Akane's fighting style, and it wasn't very innovative. It
looked like a middle scroll, so I made it carefully.
Why aren't there any boys here? I
used to not really like approval.
Hmm, I've recently realized that I
like boys. I don't notice my age. I really
like that female character.
o
That's why I'm going to do an assignment with Anise.I'm
not even Arietta, but I
loved Harold's evaluation.I really
like the older sister who has a cool 4.Parita-
chan, I love her too, and she has a really crazy personality.That's
right.  I
really like Washisu and even Nacchan wants to be my friend.
Fortunately, the girl is cute, so I
just can't help but fall in love with her. I wonder if I can
understand this even in the game.
For some reason, I like the wizard character every time. I
understand Ushiki that I like her.  I wonder if Natsunenon's name is
Magilou's so-and-so, and he's really number one.
He's a rotten guy with the power to quit.
He said he likes that and likes Ing Syria 2,
hmm, I'm the best.  My
favorite scene in Xillia 2 is that
one,
that big brother's
car is
stretched out later, and
when Asaki quits, it ends with a dream, and then opens.  I do
n't want to kick you out. I do
n't want it to just be that older brother's singing voice. It's
raining neon lights. What's the point of the lines? What's the next question?
If you were to become a character in the Jizobu series of games in El's Off Game Do,
what kind of weapon and character do you
think you would have?a
But
hey, if you're someone who fights up close, I'd go with a halberd.  Even though there are many outsiders, I
have quite a bit of an image of that,
so I thought I'd like to use it in the future.I
see,
but I want to use magic, so it's a little difficult.Of
course, I want to become a wizard, so if that's the case, then of
course.  Tsuneyaga  I'll
tell you about the cane too. I'm sure I
want to have something like a book or something for a night out. I have a
dream.
Chiara also uses the cat's tall clock.
No, she basically uses it.
Well, I don't know, but I wonder
what it would be like if I were to join in. Hey, I kind of
like wizards, but yeah,
to be
honest, I want to hit the ruling party.
oe  It's nice, it's nice, it's like Natalia-chan in the middle of the night.
Natalia I
might want a weapon like that. It's
a bit of a love affair in the past. In the Middle Ages, it's a bit far away. To be
honest, I'd like to fight the enemy.
Armor, to be honest.  Hey, haha, I'm
sure that share of Radiant My Solo
G is
always doing 7, it's my own thing, but I'm
happy to hear from people who have a lot of love overseas.  I
was doing it,
half
Hey, that's right, it says that I'm going to type it now.Teamachi
Ouji is about zoom, that picture is 8th place, 3 is
warm, 3, 3,
that's right, that's right, that's my own character.I
can make it.Loan, Soka Noteru.  The illustration uses a fixed protagonist,
but the
special thing about A is that you create your own benefactor.That's
right, you can't do something like Day, so there are a lot of characters.That's right.  After
all, if you change the dream, Stan is in the same place,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, it
's hot as a fan of a child who stands with you. It's so
good. There is a dream.
I've
been asking some basic questions about the Tezuo Off series, but I'm
getting close to the end of the series, and there
was just one more question I wanted to ask.  The
food at Nadai Arise looks
really delicious, doesn't it?
There are a lot of recipes, and each recipe
has a variety of effects, but
no, that game at that restaurant...  I
think I'm going to make some of those dishes,
right? Out of all of them, I liked the
most delicious dish or the one with the best effect. I wonder if it was a
good
day. The one
with the best effect was you, Kanaoka.  Y  Wasn't there something
like that
? Ah, there was a surprise. I see.
[Music] I wonder if that was the case.
After the battle ended, the experience points increased.
Bash.
There are some experiences that increase after the battle.  There is,
but that's why things
like Uchigara Brain are also dishes that increase experience points,
but it's true that the two that increase the most are the ones that
Ibii Yasushi got from
Fruit Sandwich and that EXB
Boost L.  I think it's great that the preparation 1 is big, isn't it
? You should be excited about the fruit.
You can't get it, so there's no recipe at all.
Yeah,
both of you are
close to experience. That
increases the experience points you get. That's something like b. So it's been
a long time. A
a man is dead, isn't he?  Yoshika Fruit
Sandwich The one that grows all over the house, I
think it's cracked. That's the
writer Parker who had 4 dozen contents in the DLC. Oh
yeah
[laughing]
No, really.  It
's Shirley, so I
got them to buy the DLC content, and I wonder
if it's a red maple leaf bank. Was it because the
effect was exp?
This is so written that it gave birth to a Ketchup VIP series.Also,
that character has a good appearance.  I'm not in Nishio-chan's
pancake game,
but the 4-ordered cake
looks delicious, and I can't help but think the
apple pie looks delicious, too.  It's a
losing streak
rme Well, it's definitely delicious. It's delicious. I
eat it with Hydrophobic Lois. There's not
a bit of pyorrhea.
Everyone must have
thought it looked delicious while looking at this picture. She's already a
child, right?
Skin,
etc. Wow, what's going on here?  Is there something you'd like to talk about about having a stepmother in the Middle Ages?
Well, I'm going to use a little English from here,
but I
wonder if I can wipe it off if I can hear it.Movement-based
4-way
[Music]
reverend 4 badge dig dig
yasai
web menus peace aogei over
attached da rua nnu game
give away
5 face 4 pre-healing automatic part
attached cup less carrying hall nyain
desu green spy page is like shoes
is the best presentation minute  EU outside
speed law See Enza's
really beat realism Regional width part Osu Kiura shitty
recipe book
Recipe burger  Let's
make it together in the cage
No, seriously, it looks delicious.
Yeah, I'm sure Chiara is addicted to that new dish,
but there aren't any recipes for it in the book,
so I definitely want to use it as a reference.
That's what I personally think, but
please make it in a bread mold.So I
'll tell you how to participate now.Ah,
campsite space
a
char ustr per impal
trente
regenerate
hommes  Wish Fundis is
good, ore fa, part a moment, form this, no
, no
, finger spar, the key word is 1cm of contact item.
5 Ines Pipe Pack Come on, 1st Ward I'm a
pretty media reverse one-two & size fan
Oh no, that girl's Negoho  I will
give one to each of the 5 3255 chicks and
finish them.Hi, please come
and join me.I
am from the applife armee group and will star in the cap as planned.S
renda some
elf full seg to
donda
rendered to do for
body name bos pains 4 seus
ugh
ore to
do Actually, when I make this dish in real life and
eat it, I get that experience point.
No, goodbye, well, it's sour. Well, that's it, my
mother. I'm going to close the c1000 plae.
Well, I'm just saying hello, just in my head,
but I think it's definitely delicious, so I hope you all
enjoy it.
So,
yeah, yeah, I've
reached the last book, so sma-senpai, if you
have any final comments, please do so. I
want to eat mapo curry.  It
comes up a lot, but what did he eat? The
content of the octopus is real, and there's
no such thing as that girl. I heard that there was a boy who was at that festival during Tales.
Well, CDA.  I tried to shut up. I'm a
fan. I'm
sure I'm a little more concerned about my ovaries. Hey, it
sure looks spicy and I want to eat spicy
food. I don't like
wash food. That's why I don't eat funky
food. It's better than him not eating.
Well, thank you very much for talking to me so much today about Neon Teruzo. The
9 schools you created were so fun. I've
never had anyone to talk to me about my love for Fields with me.  So, it
was fun. Thank you, Hoshi was also fun. Let's
talk about the Tataman Nantan Buildings. Let's talk about the Nantan Buildings,
Gakusawara City, Yasuya. Well, when the new work
comes out, let's do something together. I'm looking forward to
10 Dial
a
favor  It seems to fit
anode degree is fashion unknown seed hair
but winter is s 5 genuine
gupper water saving senior so aop safe and
say so you
do for s copy you do
Cure Wing Smile Scoop Bird
Weiwu 5 get match brb  phil
wood
ah
as check
ehren sweep chain
4 a
light bulb smoking woman pass mahjong tile aizu and matter
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Money
rain ni bar
yeah
it's ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
game play in the picture
[music]
standing
Awayama Hachin business department oil painting s 2nd candidate Luna is
a bar s wrapping aboism makeup
technique Char work towa and Finn Weiner Boda
To
ah Ayaka fortune seasar es is paro
spray meter and 4 berejaan number 4
hall ah
Well, I can
tell you a lot, and there's a little more information from here,
so please stay.
Okay, soarn, it's a
hassle. I have an iPhone.
This point b,
Appelthorpe, ok, Skewer, Nyan de Rossi, Herbert
Padyo
code, male japan.  2 is Che.
When I found out that Kessler existed, I went to Japan.  I
said that I was disappointed that I couldn't go and see it,
but now I
have to move
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
me
aim
ni
dare
[music]
[applause]
ni se patch
parte f 2 re
releases day is chain
surfcast completed
anatano ash ie
esther vienna spec ii junsu arm ryukin
chekebetube fuyasui urine with
asain dx 2 p 2 e  4 e
Avatar Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu Phaneuf's anti-
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa knew now was concept's original bar
now I don't buy Lydia like that Ozasa
art putter option ah
no ah
oh
my gosh
goose pants pink pansuiters
ferrocene funny ah ah ah
Starry heavens,
Dish's thoughts are threatening the truth,
so many nostalgic songs are
playing, and a beautiful version of that one is coming out.  I don't want to
flowing, oh, oh, it's
time to see it
sometimes I can see it.
Ya
Minister
ES 04 Love is a Branch 4
5 Passboa Moe
Umm
a
Sonota King and Dry 2
Musaw
Denso.  real shop ask web application
minute device ios so fa color
dondon 4 days bye
wither rough backpack nets aaa
won go for x ga
to do
sasoon  Moon's baldy
fixspim nf 4 min
open [ __ ] 2 e 0
gold chain download betsey
42 minutes device sss soccer
teyozo sushi soccer game and web
wow smart mu character
sah rotation mortal good
a yeah
big detail  The story is true, it's
a lot,
Uuuuuun, it's a
battle story, no, no,
it's a flurry of thoughts.
Jaaa wipe for me
Watch Masunai to do After sound and branches
so our story Lampard
teruzo
a office shop iometer
Laughing uniform goods my truth
i feel fine editors
bower an eye where
wso catchphrase
case alea
boreal
pou
dou
dou Kosame Awesome Yami Daiginpu Power
Game Wing Scopia Challenging
Parfait Knee Kut Mine funny usb Kita
32nd place Nets Pat Gyaa already cooking Is it
one thing to stream since I was doing Anshin Raku? I
thought I'd make a recipe for Taser life
Taiishitemasuyaume darshan
op Goods cosmetics Suan price
Chain  Oh oh oh
oh oh oh yeah, wigen's shavings in the shrine
Can Do Do Me
Qui Wife's Wife IS NEED YOU SO A
FUNNY Oh, it's a
dart punch.
pekodayda s enjoy It's polite and
Fenkubelcho 4 is Chen Yong,
public sounds and stationary Goto-kun are more than this,
but I feel like they enjoyed it.
big c
please refer martial king moss throne
terrence
correa and pro glide power
birdy scarface i scenery 1 pt
scoop
bought
nonbe
good rimi r 4 n d  e
x Plain Dinner Show Window
[Music]
render armor web plain
sa bar to do my bag
That's where I studied par as i can
see voice ono zu local web
press ntp 6 s 10th
Bryce Large Pension
Twings Good Reardonfu
Geh tareas
retro opc piece for
peace fife ft s 1
tik tox
sx xbox
sender
dynamic makeup change 1
ana b zaku s  Female Spy Dimension 2
Surf  It's like
Shimomurago,
Soncha, that rice turn the
warlord Urabuide,
blame it on
Enju, ahhh feeder's winter
was also a hindrance to strengthening in low.See you tomorrow.
oh baby
Hihara-chan's side
asg Hurray! I'll be there this year on 6 e-fair p 2
[Applause]
[Music]
Mmm
men
[Music]
[Music] N-
no-me
[Music]
N-
n-
n
Hmm
boohoo
huh
[music]
voodoo hmm
min
hmm
[music]
boohoo
hmm
me
boohoo woo
me yeah
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
me
voodoo
uuuuuuunuuuuuu
nun
dog dolly bonnie onbase 4 avc
nneku3
inui mon sawabe which one is better n
[music]
yeah
me meuuuuun
[music]
hoop
uuuuuun
Hmm
me
[Music]
Woouuuuu
Uuuuuuuun Yuinyan
pre to your needs
ani
me
technique n
buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuun
us career woman's tar e to
do
[music]