[Music]
thank you
oh my they are here again
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh my God how
why
[Music]
I'm embarrassed to show my sketch
I don't wanna
hmm
[Music]
okay
hello okay
[Music]
I don't know good morning
once again we're being uh greeted by a
lot of Korean people thank you
[Music]
wait my brain is I'm I'm a bit slow
today
uh
um
wait let me do a pool again
where are you from
or Korea
[Music]
please please take part in this poll
o school
oh
oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh the percentage is
higher than before even last time we had
25 percent
right now it's 48 what the [\h__\h] 47 okay
okay it's going down a bit one percent
welcome to Whole Life Korea
I am now a member of Hello Life Korea 37
percent
what the [\h__\h]
well 36 percent
that's insane insane what are you doing
what what
also 3 400 votes YouTube can you keep up
can you keep up with with the account
huh
oh for oh 47 it went up one percent oh
oh my God oh my God
[Music]
I feel more and more
um the pressure of needing to learn
Korean
motivation I am motivated let's go well
today we'll have a comfy hopefully comfy
uh drawing stream somewhere in between
um I will have to get up to uh open the
door for some groceries 4 000 votes
okay YouTube is really [\h__\h] 4 200
votes at the beginning of the stream you
know they say that people come and go
okay but this is the beginning of the
stream like everybody's here
nobody's just like coming and leaving
immediately huh
YouTube what's wrong with you what's
wrong with you
what four thousand three hundred damn
huh okay what anyway
um so I'm I'm gonna drown myself in
today like a French girl no I just said
that because Titanic and so on uh and
I'm gonna drown myself in this outfit
that I'm currently wearing
[Music]
um
mature adult cool sexy way
and uh it's been a while uh I I have
eaten two kiwis for breakfast so I'm
kind of hungry I'll be snacking on some
stuff today
uh and when my groceries come because
I'm waiting for groceries
I'll eat some bananas potassium
oh my God
I need to show this poll to my manager
Jenna are you seeing this Jenna are you
seeing this
we'll get this poemer 5000
5200 what the [\h__\h] votes and 37 percent
manager son janma look at this can we
like get Kiana to a convention in Korea
too
like the one in Germany
go go go go go
okay oh my god oh oh it's oh I'll keep
on uh
should I I think I can close this the
percentage isn't really changing
so going on
oh my God
[Music]
okay
I closed it thank you everybody for
coming I don't know uh I don't know if I
can really Entertain You well today this
will be a comfy stream
I know
um
do for a bgm man I I'll I'll look around
in my in my uh audio stock Library
maybe some Lo-Fi Lo-Fi is always good
for drawing right
uh Lo-Fi chill here absolutely
Lo-Fi who doesn't love oh doesn't love
Lo-Fi
oh that was loud
five
[Music]
is it good volume right now
we have also Christmas Lo-Fi why the
hell not
[Music]
okay and when we get sick of it a bit
loud okay when you get sick of it I'm
gonna go grab some more from audio stock
how do you suck
audio song recently I haven't been doing
uh many
streams like this where I can talk a lot
to you guys right so I'm sorry about
that a lot of a lot has been going on
like a Christmas and New Years and then
collaborations and all that
um and but here we are today I will
today be able to talk a bit more with
you guys
um
[Music]
yeah busy times it's gonna go back to
normal I hope my my cintiq in front of
me
um
it's getting like the my ceiling light
reflects on it I don't like it it's kind
of
um
[Music]
okay this angle works
okay do I need to show you my Arch
in an art stream is it necessary to show
you my art it is
[Music]
maybe I can blur it
it would help
and
[Music]
they're close enough in the art right
now so I'm naked
right now
foreign
[Music]
bye
open
[Music]
bye
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys
wait we should Loop some of those it's
not yeah let's Loop them
Loop
Loop that look okay
hello hello
no I'll just be drawing in this corner
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
and bear with me
but it's still too loud isn't it
okay I turned it down a bit more okay I
need to need to look at myself so let's
throw my clothes I don't know them by
heart
bear with you
not like that uh also I will probably be
looking
all over my screens today
um
so sorry if I like stop
moving a lot
[Music]
we haven't drawn in such a long time the
last time I drew something was like
uh
when was that was it for like birthday
and I knew I know I drew you know but it
wasn't for her birthday it was just as a
thank you I guess for her drawing me for
the birthday
I suppose
okay now the one with me not that one
I'm not really counting that one for
some reason
[Music]
but yeah I guess I drove last week okay
okay but that one was with a shitty ass
art program where you can't even do more
than two layers and you can't go back
you can't see TRL uh what's what's it
normally I usually
um since I'm not used to drawing anymore
I always like do it manually I don't
press the buttons I think it's that that
yeah
would you come to jackbox I don't count
any of that you know what the Raffles on
my dress up there they're kind of weird
like I don't I don't I'm not quite sure
how they are supposed to look like
probably not like the Ruffles that I
just drew more like maybe like a bottom
ruffle additional to that and then make
it so that it goes like this
I mean that still looks different but
that's how I want to draw it yeah
they're not Momo Ruffles
um
no that's not it's not fur it's not fur
and then we have like a like a ribbon
but the ribbon is also not exactly like
a traditional ribbon but it's like kind
of like
[Music]
you don't see the the knot of the ribbon
either
I don't I don't I don't see enough we
need to go a bit higher oh yeah and then
we have
you're around under the buba we have
some fabric here and then
okay okay so at least now I'm wearing
like a little bit but I need to work
some more on the body too here that's
the transparent part and then we have
dessert okay and the wings are already
kind of layered on top now let me record
this I think yeah the hand was supposed
to be a bit higher I think
uh uh uh boobies boobies
yay Justice for boobies and I need to do
my hair properly oh wait now I'm kind of
cut off at the top huh
difficult
I need my mirror my mirror
difficult to control let me make myself
smaller
okay
uh
okay okay this is what we're looking at
this is what we're working with
oh
okay I want to do the hair
so we have something
here
[Music]
and then yeah I like how fluffy the hair
is in this outfit I really really like
it
that one's there
a little bit of a Sideburn
here's the hardest thing to draw not for
me I think it's one of the things that I
enjoy the most and then here it's kind
of slicked back there
okay we'll draw probably a second layer
of sketch though probably I usually
um
wait how was I trying to do that I
usually
when I draw I I don't really do many
layers of sketches I just do one layer
of sketch and then and then I just do
the outline on top of it but I started
really messy because I didn't have much
time
uh wait what is the shape of my
uh the top one is a bit different than
the lower one isn't it from my veil
[Music]
I think the the top layer is kind of
straight almost but like it's definitely
a different shape
like
I love drawing Ruffles like that man
no no no no
and then this one goes like that well
this should it be that long I think the
length is okay
okay
oh I can't read
50 of the comments yeah
[Music]
and translator
okay yeah definitely need a second layer
cause I'm only drawing very very roughly
also I don't know if I'll finish the
whole piece today I'm a very slow driver
drawer especially when I'm thank you for
the membership especially when I'm uh
distracted by the Stream
[Music]
feathers feathers feathers sweaters oh
guys tonight
um I was also thinking of like streaming
very long and then reading super chats
uh but we can't go too long because uh
maybe you have seen I will be
um on the mid Corona 24 hour stream
they're currently doing Migos
they're currently doing uh 24-hour
stream and I will be there for a segment
of one and a half hours
oh
come Sunny now
one and a half hours and that will start
for me at I think 1am that's in
eight eight and a half hours from now
is it
I think I think it's an eight in eight
and a half hours
[Music]
uh maybe schedule a Super Chat stream
next week it looks like oh it doesn't
matter
[Music]
it looks like I might need to do it yeah
because from the New Year's uh stuff we
have a lot of super chats oh this is too
messy can I already do a second layer
it's too messy
I'm gonna do a second one
um gosh
this program okay then we'll lower the
opacity here and then we'll
um do a different color maybe maybe
I don't know this one
[Music]
what program you use I'm using Club
Studio
clip Studio paint
[Music]
which I'm still not used to because I um
when I was actively drawing in the past
I used to draw
um
on a program called Psy
wait let's do a smaller brush now
um
and I'm really used to that one so now
it's like what the hell am I doing
special
I didn't get much chance to get used to
this program
yes I I really liked Psy but nowadays
um clip Studio paint has many more
options and stuff
so after watching Inna draw I was like I
guess I'll I guess I'll change
the program that I use I guess
[Music]
you see you see the look in my eyes
there I'm like kind of like huh
[Music]
I know what happened to me I'm I'm
either embarrassed or sad or
um scared or everything at the same time
[Music]
um
okay let's try to be speed but yeah as I
said I don't think we can finish it and
uh
uh I have no idea how far we'll get
drawing the outlines bores me to death
and uh it will bore you guys to death as
well
so probably maybe should even yeah I
have to do the outlines on stream
because uh otherwise uh we'll end it
after the scratch is done and that's
like nothing
[Music]
everybody I didn't think I thought that
would be a one-time thing you know I
thought they would you know on the same
fourth stream there were so many of them
and I thought that was like a one-time
thing
uh it turns out it wasn't
yeah
happy
although we right now there it's like
past midnight I think
so a little bit later they might go to
sleep
but don't worry guys
don't worry guys I'm still here for you
for all of you
[Music]
I I will speak English because I don't
know how to speak any other language
just that's that's not true I can speak
the Glorious nihongo
same time as Japan right
can I go to sleep that's too bad
too fast oh wait can I eat a snack
already
[Music]
I'm like really really hungry because
that didn't I mean not really I two
kiwis but that's all I ate
thanks so my snack of choice is
[Music]
it I love making it down
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
yeah most of you guys probably don't
know what that is um
foreign
[Music]
oh this is fun it feels like my hand
is oils today
[Music]
oh I'm not moving properly sorry
thank you for the Super Chat
I felt like I just saw something but I
didn't I imagined it
[Music]
yum yum yum
[Laughter]
I'm happy you like my German accent but
I am sure that I have an accent
[Music]
are you sure
do you want to go to the usual room
that has no such thing I speak perfectly
fine
[Music]
no no
I I take pride in
the game
really good English compared to my other
countrymen
I mean okay I I understand there is some
some
some wrong intonations maybe here and
there
maybe a little bit maybe
well I need to go closer to the mother
what does that look like
oh
don't move so much
[Music]
oh wait
don't move oh maybe I can look at this
one
[Music]
oh okay stand still still still
okay good good good she stopped moving
she's dead
now I can no stop moving stop stop
oh God
okay okay okay uh
[Music]
details gotta get them right it's a
drawing of myself after all
something like that
[Music]
something like that roughly
um
oh while we're at it
while we're at it need to look at that
stuff but I can make myself a bit
smaller
um
[Music]
oh that's a bit complicated that's a bit
complicated
come on
oh
phew okay so it starts with a gold line
here
and then
go around the neck and then the second
Gold Line okay this is easy this is
still no problem
[Music]
huh
okay uh
okay
we don't have to be too accurately
people want to zoom in too much into my
art will they
do
[Music]
I have also as a different snack I have
some milka chocolate but I have some
special milk of chocolate that's like
winter time limited only time Limited
it's winter time because the oh oh let
me tell you it is it is
snow Miracle milk cream with uh crispy
cookie pieces and then I have some
others too that are like different
tastes like of roasted almonds or
something like that
so I will test this one today and see if
it really tastes like winter oops I
realized it needs to go be a bit more uh
angled
[Music]
because
like this
[Music]
okay oh wait
uh
oh I should just cover all of this up
with something oh no
oh
[Music]
stop moving Kiana how big is this
uh pretty much to the edge
and then some wings oh God I'm getting
dizzy
[Music]
oh my God
oh
[Laughter]
ah
[Music]
sure
okay this part is getting easier again
so we have the tail oh the burp it looks
like a burp and then little stones
[Music]
oh that would have been smart
you say put myself there
[Music]
the idea uh
um
snippety Snipping tool
[Music]
s
you know
cheers
in the drawing program oh yes here it is
okay okay
while I was smart chat thank you very
smart people you are
okay
get good now I can make myself smile
again
although don't tell me you didn't enjoy
being able to be so close to me
right
[Music]
um 100 IQ chat
okay well this makes it a lot easier
so two pieces of Tails and then
[Music]
um
something like that
still kind of messy but okay
[Music]
a little little piece of pink
detailed a little Stone
no
interesting shape
[Music]
oh oh by the way the clip from the clip
review stream from yesterday uh is
processing right now I have to edit
something out and
um I might have to do the processing
process twice because when I was
in the editing window you know that
the the editing option that YouTube
gives you is really
uh not that good and uh
uh
when I selected a portion to cut out
it like wouldn't let me like it started
bugging around and lagging and wouldn't
let me select the second push portion uh
so anyway I tried saving that one for
now I was like oh maybe I can go back to
that but no you can't once you click
okay once it will go into a processing
process and you won't be able to edit
anything anymore and update it you also
can't undo it anymore so
um now it's processing one edit and that
will take over 24 hours and then we'll
see to be honest I'm considering just
keeping it like that afterwards
yeah so at least some of you guys can
watch the archive as soon as possible
hopefully
YouTube oh
yeah let's go I'm drawing on the wrong
way
um why
[Music]
there we go
now not anymore okay
[Music]
thank you
your dry skill is very dedicated
can you mute portions of the stream ah
no I don't think so the only things you
can do is uh cutting uh
uh pieces out completely or blurring
people's faces I think
I know that YouTube sometimes itself
mutes portions when there is like a
copyright problem
oh man this doesn't work so long
[Music]
whatever uh you know what I can cover uh
part of this up with the with the with
the feathers uh
um
social
[Music]
yeah
I mean it was gonna be pretty close
anyway so
hey
my feelings are so long in this outfit
they've grown so much by the way those
are not earrings I will repeat it again
because people always think they're
they're earrings
they are not
[Music]
um
oh my God
scary face
when I'm not completing
everything properly
there we go
get yourself some hair girl
um
[Music]
don't what just got my apron and
slippers oh
nice so you got
you guys yay thank you for getting that
Annie got all
we got a deserter what does that mean
a deserter what someone
in the super chats
I'm giving someone a toothache
Korean living in Germany cool
[Music]
someone who leaves you mean someone went
to sleep how
oh
what is the name of the museum I got it
from audio stock it has no name to be
honest it's I called it sweet Lo-Fi
I'm changing it now
[Music]
inconceivable
oh man last night
um I I re-watched uh you know the the
clip
um
the clip review
um a little bit because I wanted I
wasn't able to look at your comments
much
um because I was watching the Clips so I
looked back on it in order to watch your
guys's uh reactions
um and then I watched the part where I
laugh at myself laughing at myself
laughing at myself
and I laughed at myself
I don't know man there's something about
that that moment where
where I love so in controllably yeah it
gets me all the time
in the beginning where where the
original Kiana starts laughing it's like
it's not funny what's funny about that
but then she starts laughing more and
more and more and then I'm like oh oh
God it did it again
you got me again
love section
yep that's what it is
[Music]
oh pretty hair
you missed out on another giggling Kiana
yeah
I wish I could read Korean man
but don't worry I want to say that I
don't mind you guys uh writing Korean in
the chat I mean if you can write in
English that would be helpful but it's
not like I'm saying hey you're not
allowed to speak Korean in my stream I
really appreciate you guys being here so
don't worry about it
about it
okay
[Music]
how big is this thing somewhere around
here
[Music]
okay
oh thank you for the super chance I I
was thinking maybe if
um I can multitask I could start reading
some super chats while drawing today
perhaps
I will I'll try because uh we're once
again behind even though I was just I
just
I just come for the New Year's stream
but here we are again
here we are again
here we are again not that I'm
complaining but I'm sorry guys that I am
multitasking yeah
I can't multitask about even my brain
can multitask I'm sorry that I am behind
again that's what I wanted to say
grades a comment that says multitask
while talking and says multitask instead
of the other word I wanted to say blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah foreign
[Music]
myself in my casual outfit this one is
way more detailed
maybe I should just keep it simple
I see some other artists throwing this
outfit and then keeping of course like
some of the parts a bit more simple and
that's that's totally cool
maybe they were as as uh scared
as I currently am of my outfits
foreign
[Music]
and I insisted on getting something like
this so it's my fault
[Music]
where are we now uh yeah yeah yeah and
then it meets like there should be one
more here I hope I'm drawing this
correctly
foreign
I go through
[Music]
um
kind of like that oh man I love the
hairpiece too y'all
hmm
and then
[Music]
so by the way I will be uh posting my
schedule tomorrow probably I'm taking
tomorrow off to do some
necessary things like uh doctor stuff
and all that
uh
so I'll I'll be quite busy and I
probably will be also taking off Tuesday
so you know
[Music]
but
was that next week when when I'm
planning to do it I I can't I can give
you some hints what will happen next
week as far as I currently have have it
planned so uh
um on Tuesday however I I want to call
in to Ina's Mario Kart stream and then
uh on Wednesday I'm thinking about
this could still change but I'm thinking
about playing death loop on Wednesday
and then first day Mario Kart
and then Friday is the Mario Kart
tournament
uh I am not sure yet if I'll be
streaming anything else on that day
a Saturday
who knows what I'll be doing there
uh there will be a full mythical lab on
my channel uh but it will be after
midnight for me but it won't it will be
before midnight for anyone who's like in
an a time zone or so we'll be playing
worms but I'll also be doing something
doing a short stream before that on my
channel as well
[Music]
on Monday after a good night's sleep
I'll be doing
some kind of New Year's related stream
uh like a like a talking about New
Year's resolutions and um stuff like
that
it may be doing something like omikuchi
if I can yeah worms worms worms worms of
all the movements it will start at I
think 1am
which is pretty late but we're gonna
play for two hours and not more yeah
so I'll be done at 3am it's okay it's
okay it's okay it's gonna be fun because
Mario Kart is [\h__\h] up my sleep
schedule anyway so yeah
hi guys
[Music]
oh yeah for Mario Kart tournament hear
me out I'm thinking about
um it seems to be like uh free to choose
whether or not you want to stream it or
not
and I'm thinking about
not streaming it
because
you guys know how distracted I get and
how I want to be entertaining whenever I
stream
um and also that will bring bro probably
one more
um
one more help with it that I uh you know
if I stream then I'll be playing through
a capture card which apparently has a
little bit of a delay but
if I don't stream then I can play
straight from the switch
[Music]
so I won't have any any dealing at all
supposedly
you aren't gonna win either way
[Music]
she a much better driver I can 100 focus
on just driving and not entertaining
which I I'm pretty sure otherwise I
would
do
now you will definitely win yeah
I know I know I won't but um
why is my where are my groceries coming
well my grocery should be coming like
now
can I not hear like uh I usually hear it
don't don't I
usually hear the Bell
my order go through
did my order go through
no idea
[Music]
yeah
so in case I won't be streaming that
then I I'm thinking about well uh doing
something something some something else
for you guys then on that day a short
stream
maybe maybe if I feel good
that might be a gorilla day because I
don't know how well I would sleep after
the tournament how long I'll be awake to
begin with for the tournament
so it might be a gorilla day where I
decide
spontaneously what to do okay I think
I'm finally done with the outline of
that uh
maybe just dressed yeah but I'm already
taking Monday Tuesday off
I think it's okay to take a few more
days off in the first two weeks of you
know the first the new year because you
know you know New Year's you can chill
right yeah
but no I think I will keep it at two
days
um
[Music]
I'm doing it again where I keep on
looking at my moving self even though I
could just take a screenshot
smart kiwawa
oh no I'm gonna take a screenshot
Snipping tool
[Music]
well maybe from this angle let me
perform
[Music]
okay you'll see my background there a
little bit it's just my my Kathy Kathy
playmat
that I love
from my birthday merchandise
my birthday merchandise they're so
beautiful the baby
[Music]
bubble
bubble up
[Music]
milk milk
YouTube
[Music]
Mama this is where that phrase in Korean
comes in handy Boba milk please please
[Music]
wait did the baby just send that members
message now
W is laughing in Japanese it's laughing
oh baby's love is the cutest love
no it's not like that
maybe doesn't talk baby still hasn't
learned how to talk can someone teach
the baby how to talk for God's sake it's
gonna grow up into the into an adult and
then wait no it's dead so
it says what look at the name it says
two days after birth
[Music]
but it's not dead anymore it's reborn
Like a Phoenix
[Music]
oh God
it's reincarnated okay
um uh explanation time once again
um
uh uh over a year ago this baby
character super chatted uh only stickers
like like milk stickers or crying baby
stickers or whatever
um every day with a countdown uh of like
uh how many days until its own death
like it was like 30 days to go and 39
days to go 28 days to go and we were
kind of worried like what would happen
if it's dead and then the the day of its
death came but
um
yeah I think the baby also was just like
time limited but I'm planning to be time
limited but then after its death it
changed its name to one day after its
death crying baby at night and then two
days after it's death crying baby at
nine and three days three days after
instead of crying baby at that and so on
and that went on for how long one year
or so but then eventually it said I'm
I'm leaving I'm out of here baby no more
and we were without the baby for a while
and I was sad
but recently it's come back to me and
now now the name says two days after
birth
[Music]
it's so stupid but I I like having like
kfp kind of has all kinds of like
characters
in our community and this baby character
is one that reminds me of you know the
good old times
the good old times so I want to cherish
that
I'm so happy to see it back
okay
so
[Music]
hmm
whatever okay at this point I'm like
whatever I'm still gonna do it my way
[Music]
yeah whatever
clinky just get the get the overall Vibe
of it
uh
yeah
okay whatever that's fine
oh it looks so straight though why did
it end up looking so straight where's
the okay lasso selection tool
give me that give me that headpiece
chill
the angle of it bothers me so I'm gonna
change it
[Music]
it should be more like no I'm on the
wrong way again
[Music]
oh wait
ah wait so take this and then put it
here and then do this and then do this
and then on it
yeah that worked okay and now we should
be able to move it on I was drawing the
wrong way yeah
[Music]
okay
oops
back on track
are you drying my back no I have an iPad
but I'm always like I got I got this
iPad for
dad's tails off uh stream right uh
Bandai Namco thank you very much
and then I was like oh I've heard so
much about people drawing on iPads like
oh it must be super uh
must be super good idea logging the
layer
must be super good for drawing right
I would heard so much about it so I
opened it up and I realized oh
it doesn't really come with a good
drawing program though I thought that
was
that wasn't it
[Music]
creates the the one that everybody uses
right
I was bamboozled
foreign
[Music]
so I ended up not drawing to
because I also didn't know how to pay
for it because like my iPad I don't know
what I did wrong but I uh it's
complicated I
I registered it with some
email address that is like on the
account that's kind of like made in
Japan
and now it I can't change it anymore uh
even though I bought the I bought the uh
the iPad in Austria but the email I
registered it with is Japanese and now I
can't I can't oh my question right let's
go BRB my groceries
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I got a free bottle of water let's go
every bottle of water pimple
Free bottle of water
I don't know why
yay I ordered groceries normally I don't
do that but I did it today because I
needed some more breakfast and food and
something to cook for dinner today and I
know I didn't have time to go out to buy
it
the supermarket also is a Sunday so
nothing's open so yeah that is how it is
in Austria nothing's freaking open on
Sundays
no I didn't order the bottle of water
that came extra I ordered bananas and I
wanted potatoes you know what I was
thinking of making today uh because it
has like this this page where I ordered
it has like some packages that you can
order to make yourself dinner and
um it's not much choice but uh one
choice was uh often cut off it which is
um basically a potato in aluminum
aluminum aluminum Illuminati foil that
you put into the oven and then you get
it out and then you put sour cream with
like
um bacon and stuff inside of it yeah
baked potatoes yeah so I'm making that
tonight I never made it myself but I ate
one at the Christmas Market the other
day and it was so yummy so I felt like
eating it
Illuminati foil
baked potato so now I'm gonna eat banana
potassium
vitamins yeah vitamins
[Music]
oh canned hairs yay
it's super cold
[Music]
oh
Illuminati phone makes a lot of sense
because
aluminum tin foil hat right and then you
make you make um conspiracy theories and
then an Illuminati
don't eat the foil again okay
okay
oh did you guys see it
on Twitter I posted it late at night
because I remembered my mom sent me
um
oh I dropped some banana my mom sent me
that that greeting card that you made
for you guys in Photoshop I like how
like how intended for it to
split I think because of her
being from the old days saying she's a
boomer uh maybe that's why um it kind of
looks like a [\h__\h] post
kind of look I don't think she intended
it to be a [\h__\h] post but it looks the
the way it's like
made it looks a little bit like a [\h__\h]
Post
Yeah was mama to be trending after that
crazy what the [\h__\h]
why is anyone else called Mama Tony in
this world or okay for everybody who
doesn't have Twitter let me show you my
mom originally said she wanted to make a
video like a like no not a video but
like a voice message I guess
um
but then she just ended up making a New
Year's greeting card for you guys
and where did it go
thank you
there it is
a lot of oh maybe I shouldn't even show
this there's a lot of references here
um
so it says all you have to do is to
decide what to do with the time that is
given to you Happy New Year
which is a quote from Gandalf uh she
loves
um
uh Lord of the Rings as I do
or more than I do perhaps and in the
background is apparently the Phoenix
fireworks that they did and was it in
The Hobbit do I know Lord of the Rings
in The Hobbit I guess
um and then in the front is you guys but
I didn't realize this the first time uh
when I I looked at it but your guys's
comments made me realize that
it sounds kind of threatening doesn't it
well I don't know it sounds um very deep
I'm not sure if she also realized how
deep this is because
me as the Eternal Phoenix and you guys
as the immortal chickens I guess I and
me being your employer and me deciding
when you get fried I guess it is me who
decides how much time you will be given
and then you have to decide what to do
with that time that it's given to you I
think that's indeed ironic after you
guys pointed it out
wait did I say Immortal word you're
mortal sorry
you are mortal
um mortal plus one
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
I wonder did you think that deeply about
it
foreign
[Music]
will be very chill and
um
Challenge and chill
yes yes
don't play God With Us
um
[Music]
banana in my right hand pen in my left
hand
we need to
we need to be quick
[Music]
Jenny banana
you don't need any pen
[Music]
you
take the banana and throw a photograph
no no
um
no no no need to provoke me
foreign
[Music]
I watched a new video from not a new one
it's an old one but a new one for me
um
from a Lonely Island
[Music]
it was it was the one with Rihanna and
Shy Ronnie
Mommy I love Rihanna and oh I like
so cool and and uh like you know she's
her user usual self although the lyrics
are kind of you know obviously uh
um like what are you doing
I speak louder
I can't hear you
[Music]
funny
and then whenever she leaves
he like wraps properly so it's like I
guess he's intimidated by her because
she's so gorgeous
I love how Rihanna was in there so funny
[Music]
oh I have like free spikes there don't I
everyone just like uh-huh
yeah when he opened you and then one
that goes like to the inside
okay we're getting somewhere maybe
which one did you watch there's two of
them there's two I want to watch the
other one too then hmm in Korea banana
and iron love pronunciation similar oh
are you in love with me after eating
bananas there's a meme called that oh
banana banana
banana banana is banana when I say
banana does it mean are you in love with
me
banana
[Music]
oppa banana
banana Moco banana banana
[Music]
wait okay to do it right now that I
think about what I just said
[Music]
uh never mind never mind
moment
I need to focus on Art okay shut up
[Music]
I like this curl I like this curl I like
this one
[Music]
all right the color color color color
colorable
supposed to be higher than that okay
uh why did I decide to make a second
sketch it takes so much time
as fast as in yeah
okay no more banana
[Music]
huh fluttering sentence it would really
help if you would ride the romaji
wrote Roman letter uh writing with that
but okay let me let me figure it out
Google translate Korean I I hope for you
that you didn't write something
different than what I think is oh no it
seems it seems legit
um
no no wait actually no that kind of
[Music]
kind of mean
Google says it says I'm in love with
bananas
it's like something a minion would say
if you ask me
I'm not a minion
but look like a Minion's here
wait I kind of closed all my windows um
yeah
[Music]
where the hell did my windows go
foreign
[Music]
don't you dare pick it oh I see a minion
fan art in coming Kiara X minions
oh no
yeah
wow
changing again
this is the Christmas lullaby that I got
for Christmas season need to get more
use out of it
should we do like a little you know here
you see that
[Music]
see what I'm doing there because that's
where the fabric will
the
sheer fabric will like squeeze the skin
a little bit
[Music]
I don't know what I'm drawing it's so
messy maybe lower this one a little bit
yeah that's better that is better
okay
here we go everybody
here we go
Kiana X-Men is more like Kiana X Kiana
what does that mean
[Music]
why and I'm not a minion
okay now this hand I haven't really
decided what to do with it but
[Music]
she's gonna be in I don't know squeezing
itself
how many fingers one two three four
[Music]
I kind of want to give her something to
hold maybe like a ribbon but who knows
what what the story behind that ribbon
is
[Music]
but I will give her that ribbon
you guys can decide for yourself
what it is
[Music]
foreign
yes
everyone like in the moment which one
[Music]
is River no this one is too small for
that
[Music]
something like this that's what I was
imagining
[Music]
I wonder if that arm length is okay
maybe like
done
does that look wrong should it be longer
should be more down here
[Music]
horizontal flip let's go oh
looks weird everything looks weird to me
you know I don't know
ah the hand is big
okay and then
[Music]
get a good look at it
an overview
but the hand really looks so big also
the the head shape looks weird to me now
oh my god oh everything
[Music]
so
okay but we're far from done okay
oh
I'll turn it back I don't want to look
at this no
oh did you see Connor's rap video I did
it was cool and once again that was
included
[Music]
yeah it was like a big Rap Contest
pretty cool
didn't know Kiana could draw I can't
that's why you didn't know
hmm
[Music]
the hair here the ear is too low or the
hair is too high
[Music]
we'll get nowhere with this today
we need a live performance of that oh
yeah right because that rap I I did
listen to that uh full version I think
before I think it's the same one uh it's
like
someone made
a rap out of little itsy bitsy pieces of
my voice
like not even sentences but just like
single
um
single tiny bits have you seen that guys
and then they what was it Kiana talking
takanasi aggressively
[Music]
laughs
syllables vowels yeah yeah yeah yeah
and and made me say whatever they wanted
put a rap song
[Music]
where is this a good question what was
it called I'm not gonna um
[Music]
um
I can't find it
doesn't show up right away
I saw it on Twitter I think
[Music]
yeah the point in Canada's rap radio is
just really really short there's like a
full version of it
ah here it is
kfb Rap featuring takanasikara from Dan
dungeon
[Music]
oh I'm not sure I should probably not
hmm it would probably be okay to to play
it but I better not
I'll send it to you guys
[Music]
okay
it sounded funny
there were some parts that sounded quite
funny to me
[Music]
oh but yeah very interesting
that must have been a lot of work
I think
[Music]
um
is the hand still too big what do you
think guys I mean compared to the face
like a hand if you look at your own hand
it will it will cover up a big portion
of your face so
uh maybe it's a bit too big still
and looks good it thinks I think maybe a
tiny tiny bit smaller it could be
[Music]
like so
you know to make it more feminine as
well
small tiny hands versus big big yowie
hands
oh
you know those
imagine me with that
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no inconceivable
impossible
[Music]
not chicken feet no
okay now the wing piece is there they're
really pretty uh one two three it's
three layers huh
but the first layer kind of
oh throws together with the first one
and then the wings are pretty round
shaped
okay okay
oh okay something like that and then
[Music]
these ones are a little bit more spiky
and they get kind of bigger
oh a little bit
[Music]
um
you actually sound really good in that
rap you think so maybe I should cover it
one day in my karaoke stream
although I feel a bit embarrassed about
the lyrics here and there
[Music]
a bob
feel like I should
um I should get more into a rapping huh
[Music]
I'm a I have a secret talent and skill
for it
so here we wanna do
we want to show some side view if
possible is that possible
the dress is like oh now my wings are
kind of in the way but it would it will
go down like that and then the boop boop
is here though oh cycle
pie
ah only all these here
and there she is
let's do a rap battle together Ollie
Ollie hello my stream is currently being
uh invaded since uh two days ago from
very nice Korean fans that watched my
clips
epicola rap battle hell yeah you know
what we should like to do that for real
with Cali being the judge oh my God my
brain I'm in the brainstorming phase
again uh Cali being a judge and who else
could be the judge maybe or do we want
her as a participant
who else could be a judge
maybe just Callie Kelly and and maybe
and then it could be a uh with Japanese
Indonesian and English members
whoever wants to participate everyone
writes a rap to like a like a track from
audio stock because we have a
subscription with audio stock yeah yeah
yeah yeah and then everyone presents
their their rap
and then we grow I don't I don't think
I don't think we're like
we have the skills to do like a
spontaneous like freestyle rap battle
even Cali usually says she can't do it
but yeah I would like to actually
prepare it a little bit maybe oh you
know what oh you know what would be
interesting oh we could give like the
the people who prepare the the contest
well like maybe partially me we could
choose a few tracks from audio stock
um and then uh the participants will not
know which track they will get and then
they we give them the track and then we
give them like uh five minutes to write
a wrap for it so we're getting the time
limit so it's still kind of freestyle
it's still kind of like spontaneous oh
[\h__\h] here she goes oh and then everyone
uh presents their five minute uh rap
that they wrote in five minutes for a
short track of like maybe one minute or
two minutes or so and I will see what
they got and maybe we could even have we
could give like oh we're cooking like
the same track to two people and and
then we would say yeah you actually have
to maybe partially this one another and
battle against one another one another
so in those five minutes where you read
the lyrics you kind of have to try to
also I'm rapping already kind of have to
try to to diss the other so you
implement that into your lyrics as well
are you in are you now
let's go
oh oh my idea
oh and then because they both using the
same audio stock track we can kind of
like compare well because it's the same
track with different lyrics and
different different performers
okay I'm gonna gonna write to Cali
afterwards it's actually I think a
pretty good idea
Galaxy brain
I already
um presented my rap just now it's the
brainstorm rap brainstorm rap let's go
[Music]
oh I'm a genius
M genius
wait how do we do this booby part
kind of like that okay
but that's better
yeah okay okay okay here we go let's go
here we go
thank you
will you still do that yeah I will
definitely do that but uh who
um
2022 has just started let's
get into it slowly
but
yeah I haven't I haven't uh
um I I like wrote up a little bit of a
concept and sent it to uh Ahmed and uh
and her manager and my manager
to see what they say about it and yeah
I'm gonna
angle the hand here downwards so that I
don't have to draw a hand
no second hand please no no
[Music]
there was a second layer
okay so far there's still some weird
Parts but I'm mostly happy with it in VR
chat now but like I wanted what do we
want maybe Ian ID only because then we
can have English wraps
um
[Music]
if it's Enid only but an ID also doesn't
have no I don't think we can do it in VR
chat
because the ID and Japanese members
don't have VR models
[Music]
I'll discuss what's better it could only
be Enid and we only have English wraps
or we could try to
do it more International
we'll see we'll see we'll see
hachama could be if we only do it Ian ID
and hajima could be one of the judges
um
we can get subs later
but okay if we include Japanese talents
then we need a Japanese judge as well
[Music]
should I be a judge or a participant
guys
it's my idea so now I kind of
want to work on it as an organizer
but I also want to participate
I can still participate even if I
organize most of it I just shouldn't
listen to the audio stock tracks I can
have someone else I can have someone
else choose the audio stock tracks and
then be surprised okay you guys want me
to do the participants okay okay okay
okay okay okay
um
foreign
[Music]
um hollow life rap battle Holo Holo rap
Holo rap
whole rap battle
Holo rap turn around hold her up
tournament has a nice sound polar rap
tournament I can already I'll experience
there are you here I need a logo
my collection the next logo
time to commission the next logo for at
Spirit snares
yeah let's go oh I'm excited that sounds
like a lot of fun
hmm like even if you don't wrap well I
think it will be very entertaining
yeah sponsored by kfb once again
[Music]
looking forward to it already give it
some time though stuff like that doesn't
like
happen in one day Rome wasn't built in
one day
right so it takes some time to organize
stuff like that let me look at myself
again
[Music]
oh
yeah
a month or two yeah something like that
maybe
but the question is what do I want to do
first to hold a rap battle or my my
other big VR idea
that I had
[Music]
um
Holo rap is definitely easier to like it
could be much faster
[Music]
to organize because for the for the
other idea that I had the VR thing
um I also want to
um get like new outfits for the wealthy
models
and yeah it generally needs more
preparation I think this and it's a
little world modeled for it as well
[Music]
according to the theme that I'm choosing
the other idea that I have is doing like
a
um a VR
uh Pro program show
like kind of like a comedy show inspired
by
um downtown's music
um
the the comedy program that they have in
Japan
where you're not allowed to laugh for 24
hours or 48 24 hours while you're being
presented by a lot of funny jokes and uh
skits
and if they love then they'll be called
out and they will be slapped on their
butt with a bat but since we can't do
that I was thinking of sending everyone
or like having everyone purchase like an
electric shock thingy and they'll get
Electric
yeah no they'll get a tiny electric
shock whenever they laugh
I think they will have to activate it
themselves
um so I hope they will really do it but
yeah we need a little bit of pain and uh
um so far I think I presented the idea
to gouda as well and she was like yeah
let's do it she didn't seem
against
the pain you know
yeah we need some pain otherwise they'll
be laughing all the time there needs to
be some some you know backlash for them
laughing they need to know it's not okay
to laugh
but but not so much pain that they are
like terrified of it either
and then whoever laughs the least
um
will be the winner and uh the the people
who will make us laugh will be
um
will be Hollow did I say hello Council
or his whole comes to one of I think
yeah myth the five myth members are the
ones who are being made like to laugh
and then cancel plus some ID and
Japanese members that I want to invite
will be the yeah the funny ones to
prepare some jokes and stuff
yeah yeah
that was that was that that was that
another great idea why do my boobs look
so big in this picture
[Music]
so much fun to draw that would be so
much fun to color I think
[Music]
uh wait where
foreign
[Music]
did I tell you something fun let me read
do you know what it's called for the
videotape of kfb employee going into The
Newsroom it's Usual Suspects
I'll tell you something do you know what
it's called for the videotape of kfp
employee going into the usual room
it's usual suspect
I don't get it I don't get it I don't
get it
foreign
[Music]
it's a movie
oh
don't get it
maybe that pun works better in Korean
Maybe
[Music]
sorry
okay how's it looking what did I not
redraw yet
I feel my face looks too chubby
[Music]
yeah definitely looks too chubby
hmm
[Music]
I kind of maybe should be bend a little
bit
[Music]
I usually don't draw like the actual
nose but
mmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
that looks like Tengu
thank you for the pinky
thank you
[Music]
now that I look at the neck looks kind
of thick to me as well but maybe that's
just no that's just me no that's no no
that's that was fine that was probably
fine
hmm
now some things just look weird to me
[Music]
um
okay let's just let's do some of this it
will look better
[Music]
I forgot the other eyebrow
I think
it could be like somewhere I it is I
guess it is there it's overlapping with
the hair
Crest on the collar is off center
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
let me try to fix it
I will try
to fix you
whatever whatever
[Music]
that's a that's a bit better maybe
Korean Bros like a flight to attention
please why I don't know what it's
looking for a tool in this application
is is there a Lego photo
I will go to sleep no no
[Music]
don't
know nope
nope
since the last update oh did I update
does it automatically upload there's
there's a Lego find tool
distort
Ed
pinch twirl
sharpen
[Music]
I don't see it but what would we need
that for it's okay we don't need it
looks amazing thank you
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
oh yeah I am
about the the New Year's relay that I
organized
it ended up being quite a success huh
[Music]
pretty proud I gotta say
I'm glad that I did it so even even
though it was last minute I'm glad I
decided to do something like that
wait now the shoulder looks like really
thick and fat but I thought it was like
too too small like too much ins in words
Maybe
it was okay
maybe it was okay
in the chicken
mummy was the only casualty what did she
do because she was a little bit sick
that looks better wait the one where it
was bigger or the one was not so fake
[Music]
uh she was a bit sick yeah I kind of
heard about it but I'm glad she still
participated yeah
she had a bit of a hard time oh no I
didn't get to watch her part I watched
um
I watched a little bit of crony and Sana
doesn't need more whiff you think so
okay
a tiny tiny tiny mount
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
I still feel like in reality the
shoulder should be like
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll have to fix everything else ah wait
now
lower arm looks very wrong to me yeah I
started it so low
[Music]
maybe that's better
I mean look at the flipped image
the shoulder looks really round to me it
should be like here
[Music]
uh maybe it should be like more rounds
then around
it is pretty flat on my head like if you
look at it from this side too
the part that you see here is very flat
shading will solve it
wait the problem with the shoulder or
the problem is
the headpiece
thank you for the membership welcome it
does it does look flat yeah and right in
reality look here as well what do you
think about the lower arm does it look
very wrong we can also just cut off the
whole image like here
to run away from our problems
hmm
the change in the arm works better
you're kind of kind of uh
if I do that and then
in order to make the arm not look that
fat
we can move this thing
but more to the sign which will also
make my buba even bigger let's go
like this
mm-hmm
[Music]
so what do you think about this
boobs enhancing
but somehow
somehow I feel like the arm should
already start below the wings
now I keep on fixing things
[Music]
I want this to look good decent
because like my
like mine's like my elbow is at my at my
waist
and the waist here
is like
here so the elbow now
[Music]
it's okay
uh yeah but that looks that looks good
that looks good
which means that here the elbow is a
little bit too too
for the first time everybody
anyway
ah wait was there more I wanted to say
about the relay
um
I'm just glad it went well everybody had
fun I think except moving
and uh I think mine in my karaoke I I
tried really high to practice my songs
in the short time that I had and I think
we not only me but also you guys agree
this time that I nailed my karaoke I
think some people said that was my the
best karaoke
ever from my archived August
I did nail quite some songs there didn't
I
don't know
[Music]
I'm pretty proud of that
all of the karaoke's were fun
that's important too that not only the
audience but also the the singer the
talent enjoys it so I'm glad everybody
had fun with it Divine Exquisite was
unbelievable thank you
[Music]
it was a huge surprise I was if I had
more time I was planning on learning
um 24
hours Cinderella
as well
but I didn't have enough time so I'm
keeping that for another time
the oppai looks weird to me now [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
it should be like here
it will be like a camp
wanted to be squeezing
oh my God
[Music]
my butt whip shading yeah shading I
think you can do a lot of stuff here
[Music]
foreign
I think I got everything down
they had this job that one is a bit too
tiny
the kindness
foreign
[Music]
guys just don't really notice it but
they are pretty big
uh I need would not need a line for what
behind the people ah
maybe you know what
I have this is his hair
foreign
are really like pushed upwards though
[Music]
they're kind of heading to Luna maybe
yeah maybe
maybe but it's kind of I don't want to I
don't wanna I like them I like them the
way I drew them
foreign
like if you look at the oh that that
looks nice
the line that I just drew
[Music]
in theory like this
oh nice shape
but I want to go back to the face
because the face I don't like it I wanna
do something about this face
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah during the yam relay
was announced
and uh did you guys watch it
the whole life English
actually it should have been out
also a long time ago
but then it was like yeah it ended up
coming out now but this time now with
everybody with all the end members
I got one of the quick parts
yeah I think the
um that the you know the the sink is
much better than it was in like a
country roads for example
because this time yeah some things were
improved
and uh now I think we're all happy with
how it ended up how it sounds
I'm satisfied as well
I guess
but I don't want to sing in the next
karaoke we're doing I'm gonna sing my
own rendition of ultramakino like a full
version
[Music]
because you only hurt me for like uh
five seconds or so singing alone
[Music]
and I can I have known this song for
such a long time I know it by heart
[Music]
s
are you ready
because I quickly threw it in there in
case I didn't have enough songs but it
turned out I had more than enough songs
for that short time slots um I thought I
had to
add some songs
it was not the case
[Music]
a song that everybody knows I think
was that supposed to be
here well did I was I supposed to was
that supposed to be hair or what was I
doing there
anyway it's hair now
I think we're done with the sketch
I think
um
[Music]
I think
Eyes On Point you think so
I'm not not happy with the eyes
ah
now
let me actually
a little bit like
[Music]
oh
I want to make it worse
[Music]
first way was okay
did that make it worse
[Music]
the worst
yeah the hair is pressed down because of
the accessories yeah that is true
foreign
[Music]
mm-hmm
must be huge
[Music]
that looks better to me
it was better that looks better
foreign
[Music]
going to the outlines I just want to
make sure that I'm I'm happy with it
now a perfect really
[Music]
foreign
so many dreams tonight that I wanted to
tell you guys about because they were so
crazy and I was like I'm gonna remember
this because this is so crazy but now I
forgot
[\h__\h]
I was like I don't need to write this
down I don't remember this
those are some really good dreams
[Music]
I need a dream diary
I wanted to tell you guys
[Music]
um
oh my dream content man ah what was it
what was that
[Music]
meditation helps to remember really
meditation well I'm not really a
big meditation fan
[Music]
but I can proudly announce that after a
break of me not doing my my daily
stretches for a while I yesterday did it
I told myself it's a new year
I have to get back into it
and I did feel like I was low-key
meditating
while doing the stretches it was kind of
relaxing I didn't I didn't even use the
the guide video anymore that I always
was using
I just did uh try to remember some of
the things that I learned
in the physical therapy
and I just went with it and added the
things that I remembered from the video
um
yes yes yes
[Music]
okay
does something look after you maybe not
now this shoulder looks off to me again
does something look weird to you guys
[Music]
looks good
oh I found some things
because this line implies that it should
be higher the football
[Music]
compare
hmm
[Music]
it will you look it will look cute of a
smile but she looks so maybe maybe a
little crazy
but then we have to change up her whole
expression
ah
should I do it on the top layer
we can give it a try
it's a pacifier
sad look is good because I have I have a
lot of people usually draw me with a
smile I was sometimes I'm like when I
when I want to do certain like for
certain thumbnails I'm like oh if only I
had like a good piece of art with like
an angry expression or if a sad
expression and then I can often not find
anything
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
then we shall do we shall do
a new layer
uh I guess we're keeping the space now
you know what I could do I could
afterwards add another expression I have
like two versions one with a happy face
and a little bit of a sad face that's
not so difficult to change
mmm okay let me name this outline
outline layer and I usually do a little
two outline layers so this will be
outlined
um extra
and I will probably mess up a lot
this
and now yes
okay well with this one okay
oh yeah run away
my uh there was a a package that I
received
uh with letters from you guys
from ages Agoda
some of the letters are apparently like
someone was sent me for example like a
Valentine's Day card
oh
[Music]
oh thank you Phillip thank you oh thank
you for the counter for the membership
come Sunny down
um like from Valentine's and I think
somewhere maybe even from before
Valentine's Day which I don't don't
quite understand because I did get a
batch after Valentine's day as well but
I guess at that point they even didn't
arrive yet or they just kind of slipped
through or something I'm not sure
um I didn't read for all of them yet I I
started reading because it's quite a big
batch
I started reading and some of you guys
write really long letters
there are still people who are right
really short letters
and then and then
and then there's the ones who write like
uh
uh three five six pages
[Laughter]
or even more I mean I've had the letters
with or let her before that was uh 30
pages or or more it felt like 100 pages
fascinating okay outline time
[Music]
yeah which
um it's fine uh you can write as much as
you want in the letters
I'm happy that you write me letters at
all guys and if you are not wondering
how do I how do I send Kiana a letter
well well well
and if you go to the whole live homepage
there will be an address
that tells you where to send letters to
now you cannot send any presents
unfortunately
but
um
but you can always at any given time
send me a letter however you will have
to think about the fact that it will
probably not arrive until
much much later
um but please go ahead also the Korean
people prefer to write me a letter but
please don't write it in Korean if you
can because
I am not that good yet by far
foreign
if you want to tease me
and if you're wondering should I ride it
with my handle with the computer
shouldn't you always write a letter by
hand is it not kind of
weird to ride it with the computer I say
no
both is fine I've had some letters that
were really hard to read because of the
handwriting so I actually kind of
appreciate it when it's
um
uh by my computer when it's printed
that is actually kind of helpful
in those cases well what I also had
before is someone sent me both versions
like a printed out version and the and
the handwritten version but the same
text
just in case I can't read
the handwritten one I was sent a a
printed out version as well that's
pretty smart
foreign
also you can since I saw that on Twitter
you can write a letter in German of
course I've had a couple of German
letters already some Japanese some
English most English doesn't matter but
as long as it's a language that I
understand
then it's fine
[Music]
foreign
my birthday is in July so if you write a
letter now it might not even make it for
my birthday
think about that guys if you're if you
feel like oh perhaps I would like to
send one in for her birthday you should
probably send and write it right and
send it now
[Music]
I think if I were to live in Japan then
the letters would arrive faster
it's just because I live far away
[Music]
well uh you know what was cute someone
sent me these these uh postcards with
some really really really cute like cat
images on top of it oh those were the
prettiest postcards I've ever seen
[Music]
cute cat images
and the other side was covered in like
cute stickers
[Music]
they know what I like
okay
[Music]
that looks good really
thank you
[Music]
very right let us agenda sure
if you if you feel the need to
do that I guess so
go ahead
you're not really gonna do that are you
I mean okay if it's like honestly if
it's like an appreciation letter you
guys don't even know half of
what she does behind the scenes so she
she should really be appreciated
definitely deserves it
lots of love
always working hard always uh ruining
her sleep schedule as well for us
[Music]
tenshi
Jen my real angel
so should we write her an appreciation
oh wait oh James he really did put up a
pinned comment ah
well do you want to receive a fan
lettuce
well I I I say this you can send her a
letter but only if you send me one too
[Music]
both of us won you're a kfb member after
all
[Music]
who's your boss huh
tell me who's your boss
here Kiana please give this I'll show
you wait that I think that did happen
before
there was already someone who sent the
letter to me into general what be the
first I'm pretty sure that happened
before
[Music]
um
I'm your boss she's my manager she's not
your boss though
she's not your guys's boss no
[Music]
don't get it twisted go
oh
I also heard just reminded me because of
the goth I heard that some of the omocat
merch has been arriving but I feel like
for most people it still takes a while
who who got their omocat merchandise
raise your hands
like we should still wait to do the
thing that I wanted to do the
I didn't my pins
only pins
only buttons
seems like that you shipped the pins
earlier than the cloves huh
mine sets to arrive next week yeah I
think we should still wait I think maybe
in February
we should do that stream I wanted to do
a stream of Cali where we um review
everybody's
[Music]
um outfit
um
yeah outfits with the omo cap
merchandise
with the super cool clothes
Korean Bros do you know about the omo
cat merch do you know about the alma cat
merch
[Music]
omocat minus shop.com
minus shop.com
did you know that there's some super
cool Kiana sweaters and oh they're sold
out right now
the pixel camera pocket t-shirt is uh
not sold out at the moment maybe they
restocked it or something
certain sizes s m l oh they're all
available ah Excel is not available you
can you can get the piano pixel let me
show you
[Music]
let me show you snipping too
oh there he is
[Music]
I I put him into a clip clip Studio
look at him look at him styling
oh
yeah
Kiana shirt
[Music]
where are we here
see that you see that that's a pixel
shirt
it's almost shop.com there's some others
too and also not only from Kiara but the
other Holo and members
well the
uh these ones are currently sold out
the other way around
I think y'all would look really cool in
these clothes
[Music]
FP uniform
almost cat minus shop.com oh my cat
minus wait I'll send you the link guys
you can also click something that will
notify you if it's restocked oh oh Jen
man me both centered at the same time
[Music]
nice in sync
Eminem
[Music]
hmm
okay back to work back to work back to
work
um so whenever whenever I see that a lot
of people are getting the merchandise I
want to do a stream of Cali
where we judge how you guys how well you
guys are putting them together
yeah
that'll be fun
[Music]
foreign
they're going to restock
this was uh this was just started uh
like what what about now
has it been a month
in April
um that's quite something
[Music]
okay then you have to wait
are you going to Kelly's tea party what
a tea party
if you mean that stream that she does
it's usually at a shitty time for me in
the middle of the night
can we always streams in the middle of
the night for me
not always sometimes she does uh stream
at like 1pm or so but it's pretty rare
I thought these outlines are gonna take
me forever
[Music]
actually I've noticed there a lot like
um like for example like good as new
year's stream she was like asking hey
I'm doing a part where I want to play
with you guys something or where you
guys can call in and the other day she
was like I want to play Uno with you
guys who wants to join but like for good
as stream starts for me at 2AM so I also
have to always like turn that down like
everybody
they they asked like hey who wants to
Club but this time it's never a good
time for me that's why I um am now
planning so many other things like the
Disney collab and the Disney Minecraft
collab and and uh what was the other
thing I was planning
ah the collab of crony
um and also collab with Japanese members
are
a different story
yeah I I kind of
I I kind of need to be the one to ask
for the collabs because they usually
plan it like in their time zone
and and then I usually have to sit it
out
so I'm I'm going in on my own
[Music]
yeah but I'm looking forward to the
Disney Minecraft collab I'm actually you
guys know how that one works is it true
do I need to like put up like a server
or something
actually not 100 sure how it works but I
still have time it's like two weeks to
go until we're doing that one something
like two weeks
yeah I think that one will be great
that that will be great I'm already
looking forward to the moment because I
spoiled Myself by watching the other
girls Stream So I think the other ones
the other participants are not uh aware
of it yet but there will be this
attraction that we will ride and and
only three people can go into the
attraction
so one of us will be left out and I'm
wondering who it will be
full body so I'm gonna get into it
quickly
yeah as far as I know it's not Java
it's bedrock
uh but do I need a server I don't know
If someone knows
feel free to let me know otherwise I'll
sometime soon when I find some time I'll
look into it closer oops wait this is
the wrong layer ah
foreign
[Music]
so all I need to do is buy myself
another version of Minecraft
and this time Bedrock Bedrock is uh
oh it's just a
you can play it on Windows right
can I go and sleep now no no no no no no
it's on Game Pass oh I don't have the
game pass
it's on Windows okay Bedrock is the
window ah but didn't it didn't the Java
version also get bought like don't you
have to like now use your windows
account for that
I feel like I heard something about that
too
foreign
[Music]
you should come by more often new year
new motivation to come to my streams
right
[Music]
rock is also the console version aha
think of the console version I do want
to eventually play that
um that Minecraft game that's like a
like an RPG
not really like is that like an armpit
chance like you get some quests
what was it called again
Minecraft dungeons yeah yeah
it looks like fun
[Music]
Minecraft yeah it's like Diablo somehow
Minecraft Diablo
[Music]
Terraria ah
I bought Terraria ages ago I mentioned
this also before
oh
I didn't mention who it was back to that
thing but my name's Empire was like
thinking about getting some people into
Terraria
and therefore I bought it back then
because she was like do you want to like
Play This Together
that was when I still lived in Japan
and then me and me and Martin played
Terraria for like an hour or two
privately
to check it out but
um yeah we ended up not going for it I
guess because I don't know why but I
personally have to say I'm I'm not very
interested in it like
hmm
I don't really it doesn't speak to me
it doesn't pique my interest
unfortunately
at least not as a streaming game
I'm sure that it's a great game and many
people enjoy it very much but I I need
to look at games from a perspective of
you know streaming it
and that's a different story
[Music]
foreign
although I do often just choose you know
the jrpg games that don't get views and
all that but I still I still believe in
them like I feel like I feel in general
they are good streaming games but it's
just not many people give them a chance
like Tales of our eyes I think was a
great streaming game it was very
entertaining
very entertaining very much fun
it had it all it had a good story it had
a good battle
had good characters good visuals very
good visuals for me visuals are very
important
don't want to watch those that much and
like for ryza it was the same I feel
like ryza
um had a lot of time for for chit chat
and still have cute visuals
[Music]
so I thought it was a good decent
streaming game
but uh Atelier franchise is just not
it's just not very well known overseas
so when people see uh piano streams rise
and what the hell is that they just
don't click on it often but we got a lot
of Great Moments out of my rise of
streams
that was some good times
[Music]
I feel like back then when I was playing
rhizome
I feel like
KFC was really shaping itself into the
community it is now
like my my core audience we all grew
together so closely I feel like back
then
foreign
[Music]
got some good ties
indeed
sakuna
sakuna streams they were um they were
good too I feel like for like one or two
streams it was great but that's why I
dropped it because after that as a as a
streaming game it was a bit too
repetitive
but I really like that game
[Music]
we did
yeah I haven't played jrpgs in a while
recently I've I've been
taking a little bit of a break
and playing mostly like random games for
games and we had that Pokemon face the
new Pokemon is coming out soon too
wow at the end of this month
[Music]
I hope I hope we can stream it
no
[Music]
feels over eyes not yet
um I did see that's what Tales of arise
now you can move it over to PS5 from PS4
to PS5 your save file
you can move transfer USA file
[Music]
um I wanna do that I guess
but I'm not sure how yet I need to look
into that
to get at least a few moments with my
PS5
um
a little bit
can't you what genre of games do you
like
um well I mean you must have heard it a
little bit now but I am my favorite game
genre is jrpgs
Japanese RPG games
but they are not so popular
sadly
so my stream is also when I do a jfpgs
we don't have so many viewers but we we
have fun and we make nice memories and I
enjoy it and that's the important thing
that I enjoyed the games that I'm
playing like I I don't really play
shooters or horror games
hmm
[Music]
because I don't want to force myself
into a genre that I'm not interested in
but we are trying death Loop
next week which is uh which is an FPS
game
so I like those kind of games I like
games like
um I like games like like Minecraft
where we can just do whatever we want
and party games like Super Mario
um Mario Mario Party or like Mario games
like like Super Mario 64 and Mario
Sunshine even though I dropped both of
them but I still love them
it doesn't change a thing
change anything
[Music]
I should go back to pick it up again I
wanna I feel everything like I could use
a bit of that Super Mario 64 Nostalgia
again
I wouldn't mind that
um
[Music]
oh oh yeah games like Sims as well yeah
yeah
so I would say I do play a lot of like
Niche games
recently I got a little bit into
uh metroidvania thanks to Ori
made me a bit more open about playing
more games like that
oh yeah small games like papers please
that was fun
yeah papers place was
simple but very fun
uh what was I about to do
my childhood
the jail played so far was uh Fire
Emblem although there was also strategy
game Fire Emblem free houses
that was that was great that was one of
our first games and it was very very
long but the first series that I started
and it went on and on and on and on and
on and on
um but I have very fond memories of it
and it was my first Fire Emblem game and
I wanna I kind of want to play it again
like a different one maybe or a
different route wow my chocolate is so
soft what the hell
time for some chocolate Fire Emblem was
quite a journey
it was
I'm so glad we went all the way to the
end with it though because obviously
there were times you know in the
beginning I also still
didn't have much confidence and and I
didn't know like ah if I was like what I
was doing 100
um so I was worried about the village
but I didn't want to give up
um I didn't want to give up just because
just because other games are more
popular or just because other games
bring in a bigger audience
[Music]
so I kept on going what am I doing here
foreign
[Music]
fans out there that I played and
finished fire emblem on my stream on my
channel
and I don't know that some fire emblem
fans found me for those streams
and maybe are still here up until this
day and they at least were there for a
while even if they're not here anymore
today
I got my final fence for that
[Music]
um
hmm
[Music]
if a new one would come out
I would play it
it would be another very long
uh game series but
if a new one comes out I would be very
open to playing it
[Music]
I wonder when a new one would come out
I think people were hoping for something
to be announced in the last uh Nintendo
Direct
that's where it would get announced
right if anywhere it would get announced
there right
in the Nintendo Direct right I'm not
Nintendo
yeah but nothing came and that was the
last one for that year
when when will there be the next
Nintendo Direct no one knows right
how often do they release Fire Emblem
games the big ones
should we have a new one by now
January usually has one probably
February okay
hmm
[Music]
they are due for a new one really
people are expecting celebrate
Chronicles free
ah
[Music]
I thought they decided to not make any
more F Eagles what
[Music]
was there something like that talked
about
[Music]
no it's not true of course not what okay
I just got into the game series
you can't take it away from me now I
just got into it
[Music]
it's like you know the you know saying
there will be no more particular anime
and then they of course continued
[Music]
I need my stabilizer where's the
stabilizer how does this stabilizer work
again here
stabilize on him
[Music]
nice stabilization
instead realizing stabilization
[Music]
the world cannot survive
I've sung quite a few pretty cool songs
in my karaoke before
you make me happy
birthday
[Music]
foreign good times
good times
[Music]
magical girl anime
how to catch was a good one
[Music]
I wanted to do now that I'm singing
reminds me of I wanted to do a K-pop
Only karaoke sometime soon but I need to
find some like
instrumentals that are okay to use
but I really want to do a Kpop Only
karaoke
yeah I want to sing like a million twice
songs
and some others some other some others
what is this pattern I don't understand
it
[Music]
um
I like them two of those really
difficult they sing so low
I want to sing soon me and jungka
[Music]
and red velvet yeah
uh
[Music]
wait I forgot the name what the hell
they're they're gone now the group that
was time limited uh oh yeah I know you
I loved sister and Wonder Girls
[Music]
his own songs
on me
is one
they were so good
I was watching the whole like uh show of
how they were created
and
um you guys know that I love hello
project right
and they did a thing where that show oh
let me explain for the people who maybe
don't understand
um I I zoned that idle group they were
created in like an audition program like
a survival Idol show and
um uh
[Music]
uh and it was normally they only do like
uh Korean talents they get like all
kinds of Korean girls from like all
these managements and then they like try
to build a group together
yeah they're already disbanded now but
in this show they wanted to create like
a Korean Japanese group
and they uh had like a collaboration
with this huge AKB show it could be
group um it could be 48 and they got all
kinds of members from there this is like
it could be 48 was like the biggest
Idol agency in Japan
um kind of like next to hello project
and but like AKB has like millions of
of members
um yeah and millions of groups well
hello project kind of keeps themselves
more small a little bit yeah
um
[Music]
I wouldn't say something but I'm gonna
not say that
uh anyways I'm a huge I have a project
fan and I kind of I wished I wished that
instead of AKB it would be a hell of a
project that would be cool but oh well
so I watched the show anyway and um
did make me like her
a bunch of these AKB members as well I
did find a liking in the ones that got
into the group in the end
pretty pretty cool what was that one
girl called the the one that was a
really small knuckle knuckle knuckle
she got really popular as well because
she learned Korean so quickly and she
spoke Korean so yeah
spoke Korean so well and her singing is
so cute and she's so tiny I like her
if I had to choose one of the Japanese
members as my Oshi I would choose
knuckle but then
for the Korean members I'm not sure I
like them I like them all hmm
yeah and two two of the eyes one members
recently uh created or joined like a new
group from their management what was it
called again uh those were like really
really popular members they're in a new
group now where the where are the Korean
fans I I've even I've how do you
pronounce it I've
I like Eugene a lot
cute
[Music]
this is now our topic K-pop
foreign
was my bias she's very pretty
[Music]
she is very pretty isn't she a gamer
girl too I know she likes to play games
doesn't she have a YouTube channel where
she plays games
I think I saw it
game girl suck it up
she's a gamer maybe she should join her
life we have a lot of gamers in her life
we have a lot of them here
[Music]
why am I taking like a million
yeah we I don't even know if we'll start
coloring this today honestly
we might not
yeah
[Music]
the positioning of that uh eyebrow is so
awkward it's like partially in the hair
partially not
whatever whatever
black pink oh I like some of their songs
boombayah
[Music]
I like their song with Dua Lipa a lot
they had a song of Dua Lipa it was
really good because I also like Dua lipo
yeah
really
really dope
[Music]
foreign
come on
Girls Generation did I still make songs
I know I know some of the old songs
[Music]
oh I know a lot of the old K-pop songs
don't call me Boomer what's the Korean
word for Boomer don't call me that
[Music]
um oops wrong layer
that was the so was this um free member
unit that did like really cute songs
which were more like j-pop-ish but
what's it called again something was it
[Music]
the way I described that won't help you
at all will it Orange Caramel yeah
Orange Caramel oh that was so cute I
like them too
Orange Caramel what was their song like
again
ah
once again after school I liked after
school too
a lipstick ah how did it go again
[Music]
wait a second now I want to look it up
muting my desktop audio so you guys
don't hear it lipstick orange camera ah
audio muted right yeah yeah
boom
[Music]
down
they look so hot too oh they're so cute
oh
[Music]
oh another old one
brown eyed girls abracadabra
like the dance
[Music]
now I'm just listening to K-pop here
go go
um
[Music]
Wonder Girls be my baby is also one of
my faves
Papa
[Music]
don't change
I can only sing the English parts
[Music]
hey
um
please be my baby please be my baby
[Music]
I can only sing to English
oh
oh oh this one was good too
[Music]
Japanese that was actually uh
mister
yeah
[Music]
foreign
oh let's go
number nine
hey
[Music]
I don't know this once
oh yeah
[Music]
oh this one was so good wasn't this one
so good I think this one was so good
oh I remember this one I was first thing
for Hyuna
oh
da da
Hai
is the same link
that's the right one
[Music]
I haven't heard this in so long oh
raps
I can't even I can't even imitate it
[Music]
I like this one
touch my body
I touch my body
touch my body down oh I know you want it
dude
[Music]
oh wow
Papa
[Music]
touch my body baby
so nice
to go sick on step two step
oh yeah I love that song
K-pop fans are probably so pissed off
right now
oh man
oh
oh I love all these songs
[Music]
oh
papa papa
[Music]
well bye
bye to turn my hey boy
that's in Miami
[Music]
yes
I'm sorry there are just too many
bangers out there how can I help myself
it's impossible
yeah Hyuna was really really attractive
really oh but one of my favorite groups
was exid
eggs ID
we we on it we at it we we add it we add
it we we at it
we've added we we add it we added we got
it we I we we I mean
[Music]
Twerk it girls so twerkable
shut your monster
oh baby
[Music]
why don't you know don't you know don't
you know
[Music]
why don't you know don't you know don't
you know
yeah we added we we added we added we we
added we added we we added I don't even
know that means it's like up down up
down up down up down
um
that I really liked was AOA
oh
oh I like all of their songs
foreign
oh heart attack was so good
[Music]
I know Congo is like Doki Doki right
oh
hey
[Music]
why am I so knowledgeable
I don't know
[Music]
foreign
okay I'll stop now I'm sorry
this is so awkward probably because you
guys don't even hear the music at the
same time again as I do
what does Goya mean again
uh yeah I was quite into Kpop for quite
some time and I'd stream doco
too
[Laughter]
yeah I know you don't hear the music
because I'm not allowed to play it of
course I will bring back my Lo-Fi again
oh I just want to Vibe too okay
yeah
it's good stuff
[Music]
ah but but nothing's better than uh
spikes stream Fox
[Music]
going your own way but you may have
noticed that all my selections were
female groups
have you noticed a pattern there
yeah I only have an interest for
female artists
you have noticed
um
[Music]
you look so cute they are so pretty
although I don't know some like
uh
boy groups songs as well but my jam was
the girl Gramps definitely
[Music]
so okay back to drawing everybody
now it feels like it feels like a core
now a corn
but I gotta do it
I have to do it I have to get at least I
want to get the outlines done can I do
that
but we also have to read some make some
time to read some super chats eventually
otherwise I'll fall behind way too much
[Music]
not of course
yeah right right that's how you say it
oopsie doodles
[Music]
is it nice to jam to music though
man I usually I I never like I used to
listen to the music so much but nowadays
it's I never do I never do
[Music]
I usually never do
no you're cute no you're cute no you're
cute
uh
we'll see you
[Music]
I'm in a good mood now thanks to that
K-pop I mean I was already in a good
mood before that but that hyped me up
just now
same only whole life music I only have a
life of only whole life music
but I hope you're listening to my music
of course you are of course you are
honestly for streams like this before
the Streamline was already considering
of us like listening to some radio
together
like Amit does
but when Amma does it it still has a
delay right the audience doesn't hear it
like exactly like accurately like in
sync as AMA does right
like you could then choose either to
listen to the radio or just to listen to
whatever you want to listen to
and I guess you know if I'm only gonna
do the outlines today we could do a part
two but I I didn't plan on doing another
art stream next week maybe I I will have
to
maybe I will have to
we all hear it on Twitch it's not much
of a delay
um but still like one or two three five
seconds no
I see I would have just used some kind
of YouTube Radio
there are like some channels that do
24-hour music right
Lo-Fi or whatever you want Christmas
music
I mean I can I can go into the depths of
audio stuff because as often as you guys
want but we can also try to check out
this radio function
let's see if that looks for us
with twitch we can pick the songs I play
I mean ah you mean you guys like give
suggestions and then the bot chooses
[Music]
I see I see
I see I say I know how that works
I mean I wouldn't know how to set it up
but I know how the principle of it works
all the attackers I think we could name
it after my cats
oh
my kitty cats
my cute kitty patooties
[Music]
I by the way I finished the Spanish
princess I finished watching that and
um I already let you guys know on
Twitter well I'm now watching uh
something from before that timeline
because I realized the makers of the
Spanish princess years before started
out by making the white princess
and then they made the White Queen and
then they made the Spanish princess it's
like free free shows and you should
actually watch them chronologically
but I didn't I watched the last one
um but now I'm watching the lead
princess which is very interesting
uh it's before before Henry Tudor the
eighth was even born I guess
and I'm getting into that now
starts where like one king was just
overthrown and a different dude called
Edward took the throne
uh and after that I will watch the White
Queen and I'm very curious to see how it
will all connect and make sense in the
end
connect to the Spanish princess now
[Music]
and that's why I tweet it out like I'm
so confused because
in between the show I keep on opening
Wikipedia and I keep on looking up these
people and I'm like which Henry is that
I'm like what this what what how is this
is this person related to that person or
or do they just have the same name and
all that it's so confusing like I'm not
sure in which year I am and then I
looked up this Elizabeth and I'm not
sure if that was the right Wikipedia
article article because there's so many
[\h__\h] Elizabeth's am I looking at the
right one or am I looking at the wrong
one I'm so confused
[Music]
foreign
it gets very confusing
[Music]
but but I like it so far although I have
to say uh
they didn't seem to have as much budget
for the white princes as they had for
the Spanish princess
because the dresses are kind of lame one
reason why I love watching these shows
is because those oh beautiful medieval
dresses they look so beautiful with the
corsets and all the fabrics and all the
cuts and everything is so beautiful and
the white princess is just like cheap
that's how they dress but the queen like
the queen even the queen wears like the
cheapest not cool [\h__\h] at all
where is my Gucci where's my Versace huh
thank you
but it's quite the eye candy to look at
all these beautiful dresses from the
ladies
[Music]
yeah really eye candy
what are you doing
[Music]
what am I doing
what am I doing what am I doing
[Music]
okay
something stuffing Kiana is also eye
candy oh no you
Kiana history fashion Ruby let's go
but now I'm honestly wondering maybe it
is what they were wearing back then but
does 50 years make so much difference in
in that I don't know it's supposed to be
realistic did they or maybe they didn't
have much money
maybe the crown didn't have that much
money in 14 uh yeah 14.50
and that's why they were dressed in such
lame dresses nah no way
15 years can change a lot
Maybe
what I did notice and what I do believe
in is
um in in the in the white princess or in
the 1450s
um the women don't really wear any
corsets they wear uh which is way better
for their health too uh and then in the
Spanish princess
which plays like about 50 years later a
bit Yeah in 1500
um they were like everybody wears
corsets I guess that was probably a real
real thing
that change that difference
I believe that
[Music]
this look really pretty they really
shouldn't have won that many corsets all
the time because
as far as I know that really affected
their health
and that might be one of the reasons why
so many ladies were losing their
children
um very sad
that and of course I mean the lack of
lack of uh
Health stuff obviously
obviously but still I think the the
corsets really
um affected it too
like even during pregnancy
Catherine of Aragon even during
what nine months pregnancy she was still
wearing those uh those corsets what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
what that's crazy you guys gotta you
guys don't even know of course it starts
so tight
foreign
but still I I think I would still affect
it quite a bit
the like wearing it for your whole
[\h__\h] life man
what
[Music]
if somebody asks you to expose your
Google history on Livestream right now
for 1000 would you do it this sounds
looks like a Spam comment
my Google history
hmm
[Music]
for a thousand
no no I'm not that desperate no
maybe four million
would you guys steal it for a thousand I
mean you guys don't have much to lose do
you
you don't have a YouTube channel
[Music]
play everyone judges you partially you
would do it
power to you power to you
[Music]
we're going into the details
no
[Music]
I know
um
[Music]
I'm really interested in
specifically especially especially
English history but now I'm like kind of
branching out
foreign
[Music]
I want to learn more now that I'm out of
school I have no choice but to teach
myself
with the materials that I'm being given
which are obviously I understand that
not everything or a lot of the things
are made up in these shows uh and I
often wonder like how how the hell do
you know that lady Margaret was alone in
the church and at that time talking to
herself how
know that I really question it a lot
um so don't worry I don't take it all
that like that serious and wordful word
but
um it's it's an easy way to get a an
overall idea of what roughly has
happened back then
even when there are historical sources
they can be very biased yeah I I believe
that too there's also like uh what I
found was interesting is
um the difference in how the tutor is
portrayed Catherine of Aragon and how
the Spanish princess portrayed Catherine
of Aragon the same historical person
um like
the cheers
like portrayed her like for example
there's this one argument that she uh
uh uh was
um not uh
that she didn't have her maidenhead
anymore when
um uh she married Henry VII
um and in in the tutors like when
there's the prosecution
um where not the prosecution but like
they have this this this scene in court
where Henry tries to you know argument
that
he shouldn't have married Catherine by
The Eyes Of God because she was married
to his brother first
uh and according to the Bible that's a
No-No
and then she said yeah yeah but you know
for what one thing I can say for sure
Henry is that I was a true maid when I
married you and Henry in the tutors seem
to believe it
but in the Spanish princess
um by the end of the show
like for for most of the show he
believed it but by the end of the show
he really doesn't believe it anymore and
he's really mad and and and and just
doesn't believe in Catherine anymore and
he's so sick of her
yeah
so one show believes in the maiden head
and one show doesn't believe so this is
this is where it also shows that their
biased like well we will never know and
I mean but to be honest like if I had to
if I had to guess I would say she
probably was not a virgin anymore
probably wasn't she how long was she
married to Arthur hmm
a little bit a little while
they had to at least try and offer
needed an air
sorry this is history nerd talk oh my
god do I sound like a nerd now does it
sound like a nerd oh yeah
[Music]
gossiping
oh man
and I when I watched the tutors I was
rooting for Angeline
but when I watched the Spanish princes
obviously because Catherine was in the
focus I was rooting for her so much more
um like now that I think back even when
watching tutors it's it's kind of lame
to root for end because even there it's
like
so unfair to Catherine she's she hasn't
done anything anything bad in the tutors
either but I think yeah the power of the
script writing but also the power of the
choice and actors because in the tutors
Catherine is played by a pretty old
actress which is visually not as
appealing
as the actress that Anne Berlin is
played by who is my absolute bias I
stand
Natalie Dormer my beautiful wife
of course I of course I didn't prefer
Anne Boleyn because she's so sexy
but in the Spanish princess the actress
that plays Catherine is very young and
doesn't get much older throughout the
show either even though she should
should have gotten much older and she's
so beautiful she's really stunning and
oh my God I wanted to talk about this
with you guys hear more nerd talk
um
so uh someone pointed out to me on
Twitter
that the actress from Catherine in the
Spanish princess
is the same actress as the crazy
girlfriend in Game of Thrones from
what's his name
the one that tortured his uh
brother uh
yeah Ramsay Ramsay had a girlfriend that
was just as Massachusetts
sadistic as him right
um yeah yeah Ramsay tortured fiance
sorry spoiler
and and he had a girlfriend who was
helping him torturing him
mm-hmm
Charlotte Hope was that her name her
real name
and I didn't realize that
even though I watched Game of Thrones
twice I didn't see like when I watched
the Spanish princess I maybe felt like a
tiny bit like
she felt familiar to me but not in a way
that I I really was like oh I've seen
her somewhere like not at all like I
didn't feel like I saw her before at all
and and then someone pointed out on
Twitter to me and I was like oh oh my
God she she has a
totally different aura
around her
in the Spanish princess which I mean
could have many reasons such as that
although my Game of Thrones is like kind
of medieval too it's like just more open
more fantasy but they're kind of
medieval too
but she had the Majestic Aura and and
man she I thought that this is not the
fact that I didn't recognize her is not
only due to
um her looks being different because
they're not that different
I think it's more because her acting is
so good
oh my God she has that
Aura and that attitude
and I think her accent too she has a
completely different she really has a
Spanish accent uh in in the Spanish
princess but I don't think she had an
accent that in Game of Thrones did she
I don't recall that girl having an
accent
I played a big role too like she has a
really
really believable accent oh
and you might say hey Cleo of course
because she's an actress but
uh who was it wait I wrote that down I
think uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
now there's Gianna I I really want to
praise that actress there's the other
thing there's
um another comparison that I have
noticed in the Spanish princess there
was another actress that was 100
familiar to me that I immediately
recognized and it's
um it's an actress that also played in
um Downtown Abbey
you guys know that show
acting tangent yes
and the thing is in the when I watched I
binge watched the hell out of Downtown
Abbey
but I really disliked the character that
that actress played
I don't know if I disliked her because
of the character or because of the
actress
but down to a Downton not downtown
Downton downtown
Evie no
um but now that I've seen her in the
Spanish princess the same actress
[Music]
I don't know if they she was supposed to
have literally the same character as in
Downtown Abbey or if that's just the
only way that person can act but she
acts the same way and it annoys me I she
was like in every freaking episode and
it was so annoying because
[Music]
she's I really don't like the character
the way she acts
and here as I said I noticed immediately
that it was her because she acts the
same
happy
Maggie Smith yeah
I'm talking about Max Smith I think oh
wait wait
[Music]
um Spanish princess
Maggie Paul Maggie Paul is the character
and the actress was Laura Carr Michael
or so
[Music]
uh Maggie Paul was the character in the
Spanish person I forgot what her name
was in Downtown Abbey
[Music]
huh Maggie Smith McGonagall from Harry
Potter no no no no no not talking about
that person I think whatever
doesn't matter how to pronounce it
as if crawly yeah eat it eat it eat it
eat it yeah yeah yeah
yeah
if you guys watch both shows you will
understand she like literally acts the
same way
and I really don't like it because she
gives you this feeling that
you really have to feel pitiful for her
in both shows like
she really makes you feel like oh oh I'm
so sorry for you every time you see her
God
not in a good way though
I'm sorry but I don't like it at all
[Music]
excuse me
she's like a very whiny character
in both shows like why why
was Maggie pole really such a whiny weak
person
I mean she went for a lot of [\h__\h] okay
and by the end of the show it's kind of
like she's going like almost crazy
understandable because of all the [\h__\h]
you entered
she's typecasted I think so yeah that's
that's something I wanted to talk about
like some some actors really get
typecasted don't they like they they
kind of act the same way in every show
that they are acting in
and then there's other amazing actresses
like the the Catherine actress of the
Spanish princess who is so different in
Game of Thrones that I have absolutely
not recognized her and I really respect
her for that
what a glow up
glow up
yes
[Music]
can I go to bed now
um you guys if you I don't wanna I don't
want to force you guys if you guys want
to sleep now you're sure but if you want
to stay and stay I would be happy
if you stained
because I got a lot of work ahead of me
or you could go to sleep and then wake
up for
at 24 hours
uh thing that I'll be part of
onions
24 hour stream
[Music]
because that is when in
five and a half hours I think or not
four and a half maybe
[Music]
wait then you won't even get much sleep
haha how about you should stay up the
whole day
[Music]
no but for real don't don't force
yourselves guys I always stream at this
weird time so
um if you can't be awake for this time
please just watch the archive although
I'm very happy to have everybody here
who can be here
the sea viewers always have a tough in
my in my streams I know
I know I know what am I on what this was
what is all this
[Music]
foreign
that's very early
[Music]
yeah you can always watch the Vlog later
unless I have to make a private again
though this time no this time should be
fine
sorry I've had to
oopsies in a row
with my streams it's been a while
I didn't I just recently say oh it's
been a while since I last had an oopsie
and then bam I have an oopsie
sounds like
sounds like I jinxed myself
[Music]
what was the oops oh yesterday it was uh
that the clip review because I wanted to
give you guys you know uh genuine
reactions I only went roughly for the
clips like I I checked what each clip is
about and I kind of understood what that
would entail and and then it was like
okay I'll include this this must be fun
and for some of them I I zoomed through
the clip a little bit to check what's in
it but then some of them had some
copyrighted music that I didn't even
recognize until you guys told me about
it so even if I would have checked I
wouldn't really have known but yeah it's
okay I'm editing it out and it will be
and we'll be back soon but YouTube takes
a long time
for it to go through
[Music]
okay
looking good so far the outlines
it's so so much though
also
[Music]
how do you get smooth lines um I use
like I think for for small blinds
one thing that is important is for like
long lines to use the stabilizer or to
stabilize their option in many drawing
programs
it makes you like like like it the the
if you draw like it goes really slowly
with you
hmm yeah I don't think we can finish it
today and I should probably end it some
what early two to read super chance
oh but for now we'll continue a little
bit longer
[Music]
I'll add a hair here
oh by the way I didn't tell you guys
what I did for my New Year's Eve home
besides the New Year's uh the relay
[Music]
um after the relay
um while partially watching over the
other relay streams
uh I was like [\h__\h] what should I get to
eat
because I kind of ran out of things to
eat at home and shops were closed kind
of or I also didn't want to go outside
anymore
I think it was too late
to get something from outside too
and uh
I couldn't order I looked on the online
order thingy and all the shops were
closed it was like what 10 pm 11 p.m
and they all closed early because of the
you know New Year's fireworks and stuff
that they wanted to go out to party it
was just understandable with nothing
nothing was open not a single shitty
pizza place
so I got the last thing out of my
freezer that I had which was a
Pizza uh pasta bolognese sauce that I
made like a long time ago
um
and I warmed it up and I ate that
[Music]
and then
uh around like half an hour before the
uh before midnight
the fireworks started going off
and then uh
I actually had called my BFF after the
stream I tried calling my BFF I was like
maybe I should spontaneously go and hang
out with her but I couldn't reach her
and then have an hour or so before I
finally was able to reach her and she
told me that yeah she was like
like somewhere with her friends from
work I'm gonna she was gonna go check
out if she can find the roof to be on to
look at the fireworks and she was like
you want to come too and I'm like no no
it's too late and I wanted to be with
you
so I gave up on that too the last minute
idea of hanging out with someone
so I just uh I have I have a little bit
of a review from my balcony I saw a
little bit of the fireworks
better than nothing I guess
[Music]
so I went out of my balcony
about five minutes before
the before midnight and I was
immediately insanely intimidated
um because
there were
so many other people out on their
balconies
from on the other side
and and and they were all kind of like
partying and drunk and they the moment I
came out I think they noticed me and I
think they yelled I tried to ignore it
and not look at them but they yelled at
me like oh get naked take off your
clothes and I was like I was like [\h__\h]
you I was so close to showing them the
middle finger but I didn't want to let
them know that I know that they're
saying it at me
I just thought it was so rude it was so
rude they were probably making fun of me
because I was alone on my balcony for
the New Years while they were partying
for rude though they kept on yelling at
me and I just I was just acting as if I
was looking somewhere else and looking
at my phone
so I wrote that kind of ruined it for me
um but I didn't give them the power over
me I didn't look at them
um they found you attractive I I doubt
that they even like saw me well because
it was really dark and yeah
I don't think they really saw me well I
didn't see their faces either even if I
tried to
but they saw that there's a girl on a
balcony alone so what do you say get
naked
[\h__\h] you
kill [\h__\h]
your own [\h__\h] business
oh made me pretty mad and then so I
tried to not get bothered by that and
look at the little glimpse of fireworks
that I was able to see foreign
[Music]
which I did see a little bit and it was
cool that was cool and I also saw like
the reflections of more fireworks in in
like Windows that looked really cool
um but next year
next year I might want to go somewhere
for real like even if I have to stream
if I'm even if I stream like before that
it'll last like one hour before midnight
I want to go somewhere and see the
fireworks
no matter what who knows though maybe
next year for New Year's that will be in
Japan for whatever reason maybe like it
could be
which then means there will be no
fireworks or not at all because in Japan
they don't do fireworks
at midnight for New Year's
do they do it in Korea
like I feel like almost everywhere in
the world they do fireworks for midnight
but do they do it in Korea they don't do
it in Japan they keep it quiet
um
because they like to keep their neighbor
and in neighborhoods quiet I guess
foreign
Bell
no fireworks yes they do
there's a show
[Music]
oh they ring a big Bell okay that sounds
like no not really
the same tradition as we have it um
I guess maybe maybe the Asian countries
like to be quiet during midnight which I
mean it is very noisy
so I get it it was very noisy oh yeah I
wanted to say that my cats were really
Brave
[Music]
um it wasn't the first time that they
heard the fireworks anyway must have
been the
third time by now
Maybe
but I had the balcony door open and my
cats while I was standing outside
after a little while of having the door
open and then like sitting inside and
looking at me they even came outside to
me on the balcony
well it was like really loud like
the balcony where it was insanely noisy
yeah both chunkers and smoothie but
mostly a smoothie
smoothie is a bit more Brave than
chunkers
but I was like almost movie thank you
for keeping me company at least those
[\h__\h] over there on the other balcony
can get jealous because I have cute cats
and you don't all you have is a it's a
ridiculously sad life
where the only thing you can do is get
drunk and then yell at girls on the
other side of of the roads to get naked
foreign
I have cats and you don't maybe you do
have cats but mine are cuter
you get them get them
get them roasted
stuff like that is the reason one of the
reasons why I don't I don't like like
really drunk people and why I don't
drink either like if I were to drink I
would probably not be bothered by it but
I'm not going I'm not going there
not going there
[Music]
and like some people get really really
aggressive when they're drunk and I
don't like them
[Music]
um
so yeah after being kind of insulted by
those people on the balcony and looking
at a lame firework I went back inside
and I ate my my warmed up the pasta
in my bed which all in all sounds very
sad doesn't it but it's okay I was still
um happy thanks to you guys so it's a
happy thanks to a successful event that
I organized and all the sweet messages
from you guys I kept on updating uh I
kept on refreshing my Twitter and
reading everybody's messages yeah yes
[Music]
oops
so all is good all is good it's not the
first time that I spent
New Year's
alone at home
it's not the first time
[Music]
where I didn't really do anything
so
it's okay there will be many more New
Year's Eaves to come when where I can do
whatever the hell I want to do
hmm oops
[Music]
did you tell the other ends what
happened what do you mean why would I
tell them
[Music]
spend my news at home too for the first
time in four years oh
nothing bad about that
thank you
for the membership
foreign
I peeked into a couple of them
crony was singing something really
nicely I forgot which song it was but it
was really pretty
some calm song
I thought they were all gonna go for
party songs because of New Year's but I
guess a lot of them chose like calm sad
songs yeah
[Music]
yeah they were singing really sad songs
I've heard but Sana Sana was like she
started out with
YMCA that was nice Santa knows how to
party huh
[Music]
why does outlining take so much time man
foreign
with the speed hands it's like she's a
Superhero and her power is Speedy hands
[Music]
I really enjoyed days I couldn't catch
that one
wasn't here
's archived
I also didn't catch the actual
announcement of ojamikino with Guna
because it was really late I was I think
I was um
half asleep if if not already asleep
no
[Music]
she covered oh
I thought I heard your voice me I wasn't
there yeah because gooda opened voice
chat right she had some girls who were
awake
come for the announcement who was there
I actually don't know who was there
foreign
about me
I could have sworn I heard you won I was
not there
Kelly San Antonio
Bay crony and fauna
Cali Bay Foundation
okay okay
you've got some of you guys are
forgetting someone so can we found a
crony I mean
okay so there were quite a few people
missing
yes sir yes
um someone was available because she was
doing her own stream at the same time
right
[Music]
so are you guys excited about that
what's up were you guys excited
I think you guys expected something else
didn't you I know some of you guys were
like oh pretty pretty
I hope you guys weren't disappointed
[Music]
so you guys are getting your own hopes
up with thinking it was 3D or something
like that
or a new gen or something
well at least it wasn't merchandise
because you guys have all your hands
full and empty Pockets don't you
with all the other merchandise that
dropped recently
[Music]
um
is something that is not time limited so
don't you worry don't you worry
oh my God it's starting to look like
something here
[Music]
oh that was also announcement yeah the
pop-up parade figures I have no idea
when they will come
was that the first time they announced
that I'm getting things mixed up in my
head
because I feel like it was announced
before but maybe not
was that the first time
they announced them a long time back
we already announced it okay okay so
that was not just an internal thing
that really got me confused because it's
been so long
it's like hey did we did you really say
something about that or was that just
like
within our own
like internal chat
[Music]
no idea what's going on anymore
I have no idea about lead poses or
whatever so no I can't give you any info
on that
and really I know nothing I don't even
know if they'll be like
stale figures or if you can move their
body I know nothing but what I do know
is that I need some more water and I
need to go out and I don't mean
foreign
BRB
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
got myself a new jug of water what
you can only get off work by overworks
real expired them
I never watched that movie by the way
it's part time
but I know it's like
I am
[Music]
all I wanted
oh this is spider
ah 300 oh 300 is the name of the movie
that's a weird weird name
300 is it because of
the year 300
oh
oh 301 ah
300 patterns oh
[Music]
and cat hair let's go
an army of 300 that's nothing they would
be 100 losing against us
kfp we have over a million
oh we're almost at we almost had a new
Milestone guys
I I think
with the help of the Koreans we can get
there soon
[Music]
oh my God
we are about you guys don't see the the
exact number do you
we are about 5 000 away from 1.3 million
oh
you know I'm gonna party for that you
know it you know it
foreign
[Music]
I Believe in Us I believe in our power
let's go for 2 million this year
I I
should have my my goals high right but
I'm not sure if we can make it I don't
want to disappoint myself
that is very that is ambitious there's
maybe too ambitious unless I suddenly
[Music]
um become
the most popular member ever
[Music]
okay we'll do an endurance this time but
just maybe a celebration perhaps
I don't know
[Music]
um
I don't know at all yet what I want to
do
but in some way we will we will
celebrate
yeah okay
[Music]
back to drawing everybody
I don't mind going pretty long today
because taking tomorrow off something
good thank you for renewing your
membership
we need to open Cafe locations to spread
the word yes and you know what would be
cool to have something like
um
[Music]
um like you know like like a like a big
sponsorship like the like the Taco Bell
one something like that where
it's
also it's not only me promoting
something but also someone's promoting
me that's what we need
where I also get something out of it
that's what we need
yeah I mean KFC is like uh
so cool but ah
seems so
Out Of Reach if I was if I was good at
maybe yeah but I'm a monkey out but
that's my theme no
hi I mean I will hope and I will pray
for it that if I if I am able to prove
my worth I will do it
I'll do what it takes whatever it takes
maybe I should do streams where I eat a
lot of fried chicken
Fried Chicken eating endurance streams
it'll be the potential cognit one day
Believe It Believe It Believe It
something like the Eurovision song
contest would have worked wonders in
promoting
um
but
that's not happening
because no 3D yet and the applications
by now are uh it's I I've read up and
it's already been decided to it seems
like it's been it's a choice between two
people or so by now I think for Austria
the participant for Austria
[Music]
maybe next year I can try
I mean we do the thing is as you guys
know we do have the 3D already but
I feel like as long as I don't have an
official debut where I can show you guys
properly I don't want to spoil it like
that
I also will never know when when I'll be
able to
show it off to you guys
so I can't just already like throw it
out there
well if you're a vision
have you seen your 3D model of course of
course of course I have
it's cute
oh and don't worry some people were
worried about the the skirt size
everything is accurate everything is 100
accurate guys as it as it should be
[Laughter]
um
no nerfing
would have not accepted it if they made
my skirt longer trust me
no freaking way that would look so
stupid if my mini skirt was like five
centimeters longer hell no hell no
hell no here
well I will not say more than that I
will just say it's accurate
that's all I can say
[Music]
melon
toys
[Music]
don't you guys worry
will you be able to do 3D at home well I
mean Japanese members are able to do it
so I expect us to be able to do it as
well once we are finally like able to do
a 3DW stream once that hurdle is
overcome I think we can do whatever the
hell we want and you guys know Ahmed you
guys know amen she will lead us to
success
I I can already imagine all the things
that we'll be doing with the models with
the help of Amen
foreign
[Music]
she knows it
Sasuke detective yeah
we'll find the way we'll find a way
like it we it would be really cool to be
able to use it even when we're not in
Japan and then
maybe because it is so difficult and
long and complicated to get to the
picture to Japan even when the borders
are at some point open
um it would be nice to just have the
possibility to
use it like as a full body too
one day one day
which will never be studio quality I
suppose
but that's okay I mean we love our scoff
in the end don't leave me love our
scuffed Wolfie models the VR models
the movement of the VR models
that has its charm
but I think with proper like
proportionalized models
it will be a bit less scuff looking
still don't worry scuff is always there
oh I have English AKA whole life scuff
gang
[Music]
we were born in scuff it molded us
take me to the r
a amen
amen
take me to Japan
I'm back welcome back oh another
membership thank you
we're doing this detailed part right now
I wish I could just I should just drop
one side and then copy paste it no
should
[Music]
um
but does that mean does that even work
because it's kind of curved
but I think I can
adjust that later on
mmm
I'll give it a try
because otherwise it would be super
difficult to make it look the same way
[Music]
that I use the tools that I have been
given
this point I'm just raffling trying to
recreate it recreate it I don't care if
it's accurate or not
foreign
no one will look that close except for
you guys
my back hurts man I wanna you know what
I'm gonna do on Tuesday
I'm gonna get a massage hell yeah
maybe even not Monday I don't have a
time
and then Tuesday
let's go
foreign
[Music]
too much too much uh fresh paneling
have built up I'm too tense too tense
[Music]
I have that I have that massage device
for the shoulders that you wrap around
your arms your upper arms but
even with that
[Music]
it helps a little bit
you know what doesn't help me at all is
hot baths people say when your tents
take a hot bath it doesn't help with any
anything at all for me like even when I
put like there's like these stones that
you can put in that supposedly help
uh but nope the bath salts nope they
don't do the trick
for me at least
it's just how it looks like
[Music]
okay let's try to copy this
it's kind of tilted though
[Music]
maybe just part part of the part if I do
it one by one then it should work well
thank you
this and then flip horizontally
[Music]
I'm cheating on it
huh
[Music]
laughs
okay I need a little bit of fixing
foreign
[Music]
exactly I agree in this case you can't
go in cheating
wait for the foreign game
uh so it's you know the one where uh
you tell someone the phrase it's like
like you say something and then that
person Whispers it into the next
person's ear and it's gonna be chaotic
because
they don't speak English well so they're
gonna totally butcher the sentences and
it'll be funny to see what it ends up as
at the end
yeah
oh especially no both of them have
a really cute funny English
I am looking forward to it
I'm really glad I was invited
even though it's a shitty time I didn't
want to turn it down because like when
when the lion when do I get invited to
these things I have to say yes yes see
this doesn't work at all uh
is there like a
wait can I like
like free transform there must be a free
transform tool have a free transform in
in uh
[Music]
does someone know that someone know
right here okay okay got it got it got
it got it got it
ah there we go okay
[Music]
where should it be over here
no does that look weird it's gonna be
covered by feathers partially so not so
important
foreign
let's try it like this and then
we'll take we'll take a
this part
[Music]
copy paste holds until we flip
turn in some more oh I didn't need the
balls with it but okay
free transform
[Music]
ER
sorry I'm like really really calm too
calm am I too boring I'm sorry
all good really really really really
really
[Music]
we're chilling
we are killing
[Music]
um
it works it works
it kind of works
yeah do I need them that little left
part there I don't think I need is
covered up by the
it's covered up anyway
okay now let me just fix this part
and then we're good to go
[Music]
using it
this is the cheese Strat
oh welcome back
I don't know
using Clips so what would you want me to
looking for it looks okay it looks okay
it's fine it's fine it's fine
[Music]
are we getting there sometime how much
more do we have left let me take uh
I don't want to take a look
how much is left
the arm the wings a part of the hair
oh but it's not that much
[Music]
we can do it fighting
we can do it
oh okay that was eraser
let's get that stabilization going again
and swoosh no no
oh it's a bit bigger brush again
[Music]
I'll need more
what else was there what I wanted to
talk about
what do you guys want to talk about is
there something you guys want to talk
about
when did your sketches oh five minutes
before the Stream
and partially industry
[Music]
ah Corona didn't reply to the message
yeah
[Music]
good question
they charged me for another month for
his children received the first one
[Music]
crony was like
low why
did you learn it from this time chat on
Google
[Music]
he wanted to know who the culprit was
my bus got no no that's not canceled
even but I think I'm Gonna Keep It
foreign
there are many animated Clips which ones
do they mean
what are you hoping for whole lives
audition you mean whole life Ian Edition
[Music]
um
go ahead
you know said yesterday
um
I personally don't think that
that it will immediately result in more
new members
[Music]
um so I'm for now I'm not that worried
but
what I don't want and I said this the
last time when auditions for a council
were happening
all I want is members
who love
um btubing and who live
who have an interest in her life
itself
um
and and are not in it for the money who
are in it for
um you know expanding their Horizons and
become being
um creative and and
being productive
and wanting to do their best people who
are really motivated about it
um
but I also need everyone who auditions
to be prepared for what's to come to
think to look at it realistically to
look at it from a mature angle and
um
don't don't wear the rose tinted glasses
too much I guess is that is that the
right word I think it is
um because
you know maybe if you think back of the
things recently that you've heard you
know like the karaoke stuff
stuff like that you don't have
unlimited Freedom when you're in a
company so you need to consider that
before joining not that afterwards
you're like me me but you I thought I
could do whatever I wanted
well
within its limits you can do whatever
you want within its limits
there are some things that
maybe will not be able to do and then
there's other things that you [\h__\h] you
could never do but you are able to do
things that oh will blow your mind like
being a guest at Taco mean
having a huge audience to support you
make your dreams come true if your
dreams are within the limits
within the rules within the guidelines
within the possibilities of whole life
they are
um I think there are many things that
you won't know until you are in
[Music]
but I I hope that the people who will
join why not one other thing that I hope
is for professional people
[Music]
professional wisdom
is I think very important especially
when you work with so many other people
and with like you know when it comes to
sponsorships for example
I think professionality professionalism
is important very important
and you also have to consider that
you're working with a Japanese company
and they take professionalism
to a whole other level
um
and I mean I'm I I'm totally okay with
that I enjoy working with Japanese
companies I appreciate it I appreciate
how
professional they are and um
in some I think if you're used to the
culture of different countries it can
get uh difficult and you might have some
difficulties understanding certain
reasonings or
you know
whatever
certain choices that a Japanese company
makes like any any Japanese company
[Music]
so keep an open mind gotta be
open-minded
[Music]
bureaucratic
I'm not sure
not sure how to use that word
[Music]
yeah I mean of course I would say if you
want to go for it go for it but you
should still consider it
what you're getting yourself into
you know it's all I will say
otherwise look back on the other Clips
talking about Whole Life auditions or
something like that
or giving advice for all Evolutions I'm
sure there's clubs like that I talked
about it before
[Music]
but yeah I don't think I don't think you
need to worry too much if you are
passionate and talented let's go live
out your talents live out your skills
[Music]
foreign
Ty Korean Bros so flirty
[Music]
my back
chickens I wish you had stronger feet
and stronger wings
can you guys start lifting so you can
guys give me some good massages
I need your wings to be muscles
pure muscles
[Music]
please
oh did you guys did I did I tell you
guys about uh I think I mentioned it
before I mentioned that there was this
this Dogo this husky baby
[Music]
that I saw
um
in my neighborhood and then recently I
met the Husky baby again
I I told the owners I was like Oh I
thought he's already so big he grows so
fast and they were like oh everybody
tells us I guess they probably don't
know this
but oh my God so cute
really makes me want to get a double too
an husky baby was so cute
now he's like a husky teenager
dog
o they grow so fast
it just all grown so fast I sound like a
mom talking about her child they grew up
so fast
[Music]
but I can't get a dog
I'm too lazy to welcome and I wouldn't
wanna have them suffer
because I'm not walking them oh
it is
a
um
yeah it's quite the responsibility
[Music]
would you kids get along with a dog that
is also a question that I
have no idea what the answer would be to
I don't even know if they would get
along with another cat
hmm
[Music]
because I don't want to get another cat
at least
I don't know when though when is the
right time to do that
my cats don't really get along what with
who with a dog or with them with one
another
some dogs get along with cats no
definitely I mean I know but like how do
you how know beforehand maybe you can if
you get a dog is there a chance you can
also give him back again
like after a week of testing trial trial
run a poor doggle
[Music]
like what I mean what are you supposed
to do if it doesn't work out
you can
Foster
I mean it's not the same as getting uh
being a child asking for a dog on
Christmas and then two months later
we've been like
no it's not like that
[Music]
it's
ugly now
[Music]
hmm
that was your reaction to people well
that's a Pokemon it doesn't matter
Pokemons
they don't
they don't have feelings
[Music]
should we change the video again
let's change it
[Music]
that's harsh
what's that
damn
[Music]
um
you guys sometimes seem to forgore
oh by the way I did talk
ume
about doing a history stream
and um I understand her concerns but
I said I said that
I said listen to your sample what you
gotta do is do it like me
first of all Eva just talk about history
out of nowhere
or
[Music]
or do I do talk about
history shows like the tutors
where you only indirectly talking about
history
yeah I I like me I'm like talking about
the Spanish Princess and the tutors and
the light princess
[Music]
and I'm saying nothing of this is
guaranteed to be true I don't know even
[Music]
I don't know
we also I asked mama if she knows some
things about like the tutors like the
English English royal families and all
that she doesn't
he doesn't know uh really anything about
them apparently
the things that she wanted to do were
in a different
different topic and all that
um
[Music]
but she was very up for
um having like learning some of the
basics
and then having me teach her more and
then having a discussion around that's
kind of what I wanted to do
oh
[Music]
yum yum yum
but don't don't worry
Senpai will make it happen somehow
somehow
leave it to your birds Empire leave it
to me
foreign
[Music]
that's not really a history that we want
to talk about
[Music]
that's way too recent I want to talk
about about old stuff
stuff that happened million years ago
I want to talk about the plague I wanna
talk
absolutely fascinating back in the day
they called it the sweating sickness
yeah I am
and they thought that
I don't know if this is actually true if
this really helps probably not
but
Henry VIII
he was trying to battle and combat it by
making him already making himself sweat
in advance
I'm probably makes absolutely no sense
that doesn't help does it
that's it like I said I wonder
I guess like by making yourself sweat
when you sweat you sweat out like
the toxic stuff in your body right that
is actually proven to be scientifically
true no
that is true though
[Music]
so while I don't think it would really
fend off the plague it was a good start
I guess no no no no no really no the
[\h__\h] I heard that somewhere
[Music]
yeah but what about him aren't you
supposed to sweat out of the flu exactly
what about that
[Music]
and what about that
trust me bro
[Laughter]
it only helps with fevers huh
um
[Music]
all right
hold on
I'm in a constant fever
because I'm always hot as [\h__\h]
shut up shut up
do us all a favor and shut up
[Music]
um
chocolate is so good oh
oh man um
[Music]
what the hell
too way too far away
[Music]
okay
I'm almost done with the outlines I
think once we're done we're gonna switch
to Super chances
can you share it with us oh I can't but
you can get you can try to get the same
chocolate as me
I'm eating milk or chocolate although I
don't think you'll be able to get the
same version as I am eating right now
because I'm eating a winter limited
version
[Music]
but from what I've seen milk or
chocolate when I was living in Japan I
found it in Japan so
I think if you go to like stores that
have
um like overseas food
[Music]
you I think you should be able to find
it
like lint chocolate
mocha chocolate
I like a lot too
I've seen a video spot in Japan as well
I was very surprised about that look at
this one is the one that my rats
was eaten
and for some reason didn't die even
after eating through the plastic and
fruited chocolate fascinating
fascinating cat must be a cat rat must
be a mutant or something
[Music]
up to this day I question
that rats
health and
state of
I don't know
everything
Casper yeah Casper
Casper that crazy rat I need to do this
part
[Music]
sorry microphone is kind of in the way
um what's your favorite this one flavor
[Music]
and the one side
that's the best one and the only one I
will ever buy the other ones are fine
too but that one just overpowers
everything so much that I don't ever
want to eat any other forget the point
look at the pot with the spot chocolate
ever again
mm-hmm
oh by the way that's skiing trip that I
was talking about
uh I talked a little bit with rmt about
it and she's very busy in January
so and me too
already
um so we'll be doing it probably in
February most likely in February
[Music]
guys I'm excited I want to mix it with
some
uh like not I don't want it to be only
skiing I want it to be a partially
partially a spa experience too so I want
to go somewhere where there's also
saunas
and apparently now I like going into
Sonos not really but you know sauna and
massages
stuff like that would be nice to have
um
so after going to ski before dinner
imagine imagine skiing all day and then
going back to the hotel and then going
into a sauna and then getting a massage
and then taking dinner and then falling
asleep like a stone
yeah that's why that says toxins exactly
Anna that's also a place where you get
rid of those toxics toxins by
sweating huh
[Music]
now you make it sound to me like as if
that all makes no sense at all but
sweating is okay well Sana Asana I guess
is also good for you know the heart I
guess
I guess that was one thing one reason
why they were healthy
[Music]
hold on
I love how you draw thank you
I am
not good but
try
um
according to labor law you think label
law
works at kfp no no no
[Music]
you cannot
just leave your shift here just because
labor law says so
[Music]
you must be new
um
[Music]
you seem to have misunderstood something
have you read your contract have you
read the small lines in your contract at
the bottom hmm
you should maybe read your contract
again
[Music]
I will let you go only if you watch the
archive
hashtag
you know but honestly thank you thank
you guys you guys are here at the crazy
time anyway the Korean fans so
it's already more than enough
even showing up I was really surprised I
didn't think you guys would be here
again
[Music]
maybe I should always leave a comment on
their bodies
uh clips
because I left one today again maybe
that's why they came again even though I
didn't even ask them to come this time I
just said thank you
love the comments saying thank you
[Music]
maybe or maybe they will come all the
time now
oh new friends new friends you are
training training on Twitter you mean
Kiana Kiana often friends and it's often
not really about me
[Music]
so don't don't don't
think it's about me I see a Kiara music
9 000. that's probably not about me
most likely
[Music]
foreign
no
probably not
okay with some of these sweets are about
me but
[Music]
hey a lot of the recent ones are about
me
yo
skies for tweeting about Kiana
thank you thank you
[Music]
Echo search
you know I said I I wanted to Ego search
in Korean but it's not possible they
don't really use Twitter and uh
I guess it's a good thing though
I guess it's probably a good thing
because if I ego search
um if I find out where to Ego search in
Korean then
I would also say it probably some some
mean people
it's better to stay away from that
better to not know what people are
saying about me and just stay
stay um
naive
internet is evil
[Music]
but that what I do do though is I try to
uh translate the comments the Korean
comments in the clip of booty but it
makes no sense so you know how YouTube
has that automatic uh translation
function but only on the phone only on
mobile
it makes no sense like
you do that too yeah but nothing nothing
makes sense when you use that tool
like what does any of that even mean
[Music]
so useless man they should Implement
deep l or something
in
um in in YouTube
although I have yet to use deep L by
myself when I translate names I still
use Google Translate
[Music]
um
messy
to message
[Music]
the trick is to understand the words by
themselves and then try to piece it
together yeah
but that is asking for me to actually
learn some basic vocabulary which don't
worry
um
try to do that
on my own
and with some help of crony
I'll use poppable to translate Korean
stuff Papago
did you see how Google translate uh
to be honest even for someone who
understands Japanese it sounds like it
could have two meanings uh so who knows
what she meant by that
she did mean
both meanings
[Music]
the problem is that that word in
Japanese
means
it's it's a way to describe something
sensitive and it's a way to describe the
act as well so it's a bit problematic
misleading to use it
[Music]
oh oh
I'm using a razor too
[Music]
watching Tango broadcast while working
oh
working now
fighting
ah already working so early in the
morning
[Music]
that's that sounds tough we're pretty
much done I think I only have to finish
the hair
oh yeah
um
[Music]
oh hell yeah
how does my hair look there uh oh my
hair looks like clouds at the bottom did
you guys notice that
[Music]
this hair will be so much fun to color
hmm
foreign
[Music]
looks like that you guys get deceived
too easily by the silhouette
foreign
[Music]
oh I'm actually really looking forward
to coloring that and shading and shading
and highlighting that uh
can we get this on a shirt oh this
unfortunately I can't just randomly pull
out merchandise like that but uh
I already Drew something for my last
birthday uh merchandise for that little
sticker card now maybe maybe in the
future I feel more confident to you know
drawing up a shirt
would be the the first time after
um after the Holo myth t-shirt
um
[Music]
only for my for my own merchandise
I feel
maybe more okay with that but if it's
like for for all of them if then oh the
pressure is too strong because not only
kfp has to like it but also all of the
other fandoms
quite
pressuring
foreign
[Music]
it's always a difficult choice to make
when it comes to designing merchandise
if when it comes to designing like
wearable merchandise if we should go all
out and like put our huge face up there
because people like that too or stay
simple keep it simple keep it decent so
that people would maybe not even
recognize what is on your shirt like
just like a tiny and Tiny logo or a tiny
font or whatever
um
yeah
and for almost cats I think my things
are on on the more decent
side and decent it's not the right word
uh what am I looking for what is the
word I'm looking for a saddle subtle
yeah my my stuff
it might have a bright color but the
design itself is not so much like in
your face uh I love takanashikiara
unless you know about it unless you know
about the merchandise if you know where
it's from then you know
analyze
[Music]
the hoodie the hoodie for example with
that little house that that uh at kfp
thingy in the front
the mobile can you move no mobile no the
kfp on wheels
[Music]
I said cute cute sweater
for sure
[Music]
so what do you guys prefer
what do you guys prefer
[Music]
do you prefer subtle or
bam in your face stuff
[Music]
everyone says subtle hey
yeah
[Music]
I'm right now under distress I'm wearing
my pickled t-shirt and it's not very
subtle it's great for pajamas though
I noticed though it's kind of starting
to lose its color I washed it too often
no
and then that pick when I showed I'm
wearing is in your face and I'm proud of
it I like it although yeah I wouldn't
really be able to wear it outside
especially me
hahaha
it's like telling people people like oh
I am
yeah I can't can't really do that
um
[Music]
like I when I was
when I was an idol fan I used to buy
um like for every concert they had
t-shirts for each group when sometimes
even for each member they had t-shirts
what I did like is
um the way they designed like birthday
t-shirts uh
because it was really cute like the the
idols would design their own birthday
t-shirts
I still have a lot of those
let me let me show you a sample uh I
won't show it on screen but I'll send
you a sample link
um
[Music]
let's see if I can find something
oh yeah that is that I had that one I
don't know where it is now oh this one
I definitely had that one
why is there no nothing
not a bigger image of that
um
it's so tiny
[Music]
there's someone reselling it no sad well
understandable she's not active anymore
oh
[Music]
yeah
uh how to show you
this one doesn't really
this one doesn't really show it well
[Music]
okay it does it does so if I show I show
you a link now
and then tell me if something like this
would
this is really subtle I think it's it's
cute but so subtle
and the idol threw it herself you gotta
scroll down a little bit
uh
it's just like some scribbles on top of
a big colored t-shirt
[Music]
and that works something like that
their t-shirts usually look like that
like the birthday t-shirts and they
would always be in the image color of
the idol so her image color was red
um
and I used to wear those to the concerts
and then now for pajamas
[Music]
oh cute cute
but I also like both stuff thank you at
least someone oh
[Music]
maybe
t-shirts
well hers was a bit lower on the cute
side
oh
[Music]
oh cute
foreign
[Music]
here this is one of her birthday
t-shirts her 17th birthday t-shirt so
cute that one is really cute
they would also make wristbands to go
with it usually
and her image color was Pink as you can
see
but that's so simple like I would also
love like a badass really bold t-shirt
as well ah it's hard
to make these choices it doesn't show
page count we thought oh no why I see it
[Music]
um I don't even know what this website
is
[Music]
this a fan
okay never mind then just imagine a cute
T-shirt with a cute drawing from a girl
who's not good at drawing on it
[Music]
works for me oh it works for some people
oh
imagine imagine
[Music]
it's too girly well of course it's a
little bit girly
some of these were growing but you gotta
wear them with pride with pride
don't perish
but I don't think anyone's expecting you
guys to to wear these kind of like
merchandise things uh outside in the
real world unless you really want it
unless it's like a cool cool one
you don't have to it's just about
it's just about
um
fighting and having something to
remember someone by I guess
[Music]
uh actually I had these I had these
juicer juicer t-shirts that were really
nice
[Music]
can I find them again
no they're too old
foreign
[Music]
oh I still have time I guess
yeah I'm a little bit she's not on
stream yeah probably not on stream
but I don't know would you be happy
about that I wanna give her something
that she would be excited about
should I ride a ukulele song for her too
Maker's song
[Music]
I mean I'm in she would be happy about
anything for sure because she's a sweet
girl
but still
I mean
you guys better make sure to celebrate
with her on her birthday okay
otherwise I will come
to your room and pick you up and I'll
bring you to her birthday party with my
with my own hands if it must be which
you guys are now gonna be asking for I
dare you I dare you
[Music]
foreign
I know you guys are gonna be there
anyway
and even if it's at a shitty time for me
I want to be there too I wanna be there
too don't threaten us with a good time
hey the good time is on this celebration
I'm in our innovator
done
[Music]
something here
huh
well we will we will we will we're here
oh yeah it's um
is it kind of like on the same day as
the tournament for her
tournament
for her I mean the tournament is still
on the same day right
[Music]
foreign
happened to be kind of on the same day
it's a little bit weird timing
[Music]
thank you of all the membership I
renewal you're an adult chicken damn
[Music]
gaze upon your beauty
oh look it looks so proper now
looks it looks
proper whoa
did my hair
um
[Music]
I so usually like right now I'm on the
extra outline right so that extra
outline layer so that uh when I select
the layers to input the colors later on
this layer you see that it won't be like
disturbing the selection I like to have
these separate so that yeah it won't be
in the way if you know what I mean
[Music]
that's why also I
I put the whole eyes on a separate layer
so that I can select the skin easily
later on
yep
[Music]
and so on this layer I don't have to
draw the lines that cleanly I can just
like
mess around with them because I won't be
using those for selecting each area
[Music]
okay
oh it's the color
[Music]
foreign
a little bit of the hair underneath okay
[Music]
uh
line art let me take a look without the
sketch
I think I
uh some details on over here I missed
[Music]
no problem knows something I can fix
recently
[Music]
okay
you look short in the yard
would you know it's only my upper body
has an ISO portal
looks really good yeah great job thank
you thank you
oh I think now let's go nowhere
good I don't think I missed any details
pretty looks pretty good though
[Music]
oh wait you know what I was wondering
like what that part of the sketch was
but I guess it is supposed to be
um looks like I should be thicker down
here
let me fix it one more time maybe around
[Music]
okay
okay that
uh
[Music]
-huh how about that now will that look
and atomically correct
holy [\h__\h] my boobies turned out so big
yeah
[Music]
foreign
looks a little bit too straight for me
[Music]
I think before I start the colors I'll
be like
[Music]
um cleaning up some lines here and there
but
I don't even know maybe I'll even color
it privately that's some kind of
meditation method but I I don't enjoy
the coloring process way more than any
of what I just did today so I do kind of
want to share that with you guys
[Music]
I'll think about it you guys want to see
a second art stream like this bro you're
gonna say yes you say yes to everything
anyway
you guys are too nice to me
are you saying yesterday
ah wait I forgot did you guys not see
this you guys not seen us
[Music]
oh wait
that was not supposed to
be done like outside of the neck
found a little piece that needed to be
fixed
we could now
follow Upstream of penalty game where
you have to do something silly every
time you're mean about your art
and then I would just hold back
foreign
[Music]
on the left side than it is on the right
side what the [\h__\h] did I do
I was just following sketch
[Music]
I was just following what the sketch
looked like
okay not so tragic
how long is it pretty low
how was it how low is it really it does
go up
because it goes all the way to my butt
actually
okay
[Music]
here we are
long hair Kiana is nice isn't she
[Music]
one day I'll give you guys a short hair
Kiana too one day or or maybe like an
instead of short hair maybe like an updo
up to Kiana
I think that would be nice
[Music]
like a like braided up to or something
like that I feel like that would be so
pretty I'll do my best to get it to you
guys ponytail too or like twin tail
[Music]
what do you want to see more ponytail or
twin tail Kiana
[Music]
you guys probably can't imagine me while
I love twin Tails can you yeah you guys
say mostly ponytail you guys think twin
Tails wouldn't fit me huh because it's
too cute and too too childish huh you
think it wouldn't fit me huh
but I want to be cute too
[Music]
Oh I wanna have twins
but like the twin tails look so
different depending on like where you
place them if it's placed on on a high
part of your head or like really low
that completely changes it too
[Music]
you gotta consider that as well
would you turn into it soon that it
looked into that twin Tails who knows
maybe I would give you guys a huh
and speak German to you
[Music]
perhaps you would like that wouldn't you
okay
today is a
um
I finished the
uh
outlines so I might still change
something if I find something wrong
again with it but for now this is where
we are at
yeah ponytail and little twin tail in
the front what
left biceps Kiara huh
well I don't see anything
left where is the bicep the season in
the upper arm
[Music]
s
little below the shoulder
what did I miss a line I feel like
everything's there
upper arm
huh wait are you saying which one here
something here
[Music]
your arms look too musculine huh
you guys say I have no lives well maybe
I don't lower arm is the muscle that
everyone
he wants more muscle
here
now this was fun what bothers me maybe
is this is uh this this this this line
maybe a little bit
[Music]
because my arm looks so wide here but it
would look probably better and when it's
colored in
[Music]
I think
it doesn't line up after the Bubba
I'm like are we talking which charm are
you talking about left from our point of
view I love from Kiana's point of view
also now the eyebrows
[Music]
and left from right from Kiara
the armhole oh that's a good question
this is the arm holding holding the
ribbon
[Music]
the left elbow might not line up of the
arm
[Music]
y
art backseaters
I mean I did ask you guys if something
if you see something wrong with the left
[Music]
the line of the right elbow doesn't line
up with the line of the upper
are you do you mean
do you mean like
this one I think it does
I think it does
uh what do you mean here that's just a
little bit bent it's a little bit bent
you know what that's actually I mean
I've seen arms like that before
mean that one maybe they mean that one
you know what maybe you do maybe you do
okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay okay
oh the other arm yay
thank you for your help everybody we're
done here
[Music]
how do armpits look like
what does my armpit look like oh
[Music]
huh
it's missing armpit head no Kiana has no
armpit hair and you guys you would know
that if you listen to my story of me
permanently removing my armpit hair and
it being absolutely painful
how painful that I cried and I hated
going there but no armpit hair
non-existent
[Music]
it's legit it's not even lore it's like
truth
armpit feathers that is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard
[Music]
nasal removal isn't it I know I didn't
get laser removal
I got something that's permanent and
that exists yes you just don't know
about it
but it does exist it's just extremely
painful
at least for me apparently it's not
painful for everyone
um
I'm pretty funny
Downy armpit feathers speaking of downs
my my cats
it's really smoothy I feel like she's
losing her winter coat already because
she's like oh my God she's losing so
much hair every time I I like
pet her when I pet her even once when I
stroke over her body oh so much hair
everywhere
she's yeah I feel like she's already
losing it but she's kind of losing it
the whole year
they're always losing hair throughout
the whole year so I guess maybe it's
just Dad but it feels like she's losing
an insane amount of hair whenever I
stroke her as if she's
um yeah losing her winter coat
it's barely became winter yes she's not
alone early early bird even though she's
a cat but she's owned by a bird so she
becomes an early bird rather than an
early cat
but that doesn't exist on the coat yeah
maybe just undercoat oh
no it doesn't really look like undercoat
to be honest undercoat is more thin
right no it looks like the top top layer
[Music]
um
the early cat gets the lasagna okay guys
we have um we have some time to read
super chats foreign
[Music]
anytime soon so
let's start I want to make him a little
bit less round
here she goes again correcting herself
once again
[Music]
I like big big eyes and adding my eyes
there's many different ways to draw many
different ways to draw eyes
can you post your sketch
and I can post all of the olive lines
and sketch
I guess if you want to see that
foreign
[Music]
thank you also someone said Vampire
Knight Vampire Knight I does that look
like vampire National to you I did like
Vampire Knight a lot when I was
um younger I was you can read the Manga
I even write the manga I normally never
write manga
[Music]
but that was one of the few ones that I
read because this was one of the few
ones that they had translated to German
in the bookstores
yeah we didn't have much choice in uh
translated manga and back then I
couldn't read Japanese yet and English
was
uh not uh on sale either
in the basic ass bookstores no
Vampire Knight I love that one back then
but when I think back of it now
it's so tacky
but it's very nostalgic to me
[Music]
let's go to my office
oh is everything fine here in my office
world
is celebrating New Year's now
wow we have so many time zones all over
the world huh
damn
[Music]
pickle Lambs Mars
Florida
I want to keep you know I have these
fireworks I don't want to use them only
for one day
I'm gonna keep them for a little bit
longer maybe only this stream okay one
more also I gotta take my tree down
eventually and all that man nah
I want to keep want to keep training
everything a bit longer maybe until the
end of January we're gonna keep the
winter office
until the end of January
[Music]
I feel like a lot of people leave up
their Christmas decorations
until the end of January it definitely
is not only me
[Music]
okay uh where do we have to start
reading is it from the
ah ah wait
[Music]
do you guys know
I want to change the bgm
[Music]
this one
karaoke
the relay
is that the
is that the one I have to start reading
I'm scrolling I'm scrolling
[Music]
yeah a bit more cheerful
wait I'm squalling
[Music]
mmm
it's bgm not new I think I used it at
least once once before
it's really good
[Music]
I named it electronic chill cute
when I saved the audio stock files they
only get saved with numbers so I I named
them roughly
and this one is electronic chill cute
[Music]
yeah yeah
ready for another four hours I will go
as long as I can definitely
I have still like cool three and a half
hours I think until the Mi Corona thing
but it would be nice to get a little
break and ahead of that before that
[Music]
clip review super chats are
partially mixed uh yeah partially before
the
okay
for the karaoke ones we have to start
with those
[Music]
okay soon
as
I'm only gonna read that one once
I received your letter thank you
finally finally huh
it only took us a year or so for me to
receive your letter only only over a
year
uh
[Music]
so it says uh here we are preparing to
take that New Year's ball and throw it
on the ground let's go seriously though
it's hard to believe this is the second
New Year of kfbl
when I started watching your debut I
wasn't sure how long I'd stick around
but now I can't think of anywhere else I
would rather be ah I would rather be
for all the ups and downs you've
constantly been able to make me smile I
can never express how much I admire you
see in your struggle and push on is an
inspiration that has made me want to do
the same in my life I know
[Music]
you are an inspiration and a star seeing
you grow and improve this past year has
been beautiful I'm so proud to be able
to call you my attention oh
you make every second of my time that I
spent watching you worth it
I have never regretted a second of time
I spent did I just read it no I look
forward to every stream song and
whatever else you decide to bring to us
this next year thank you Kiana you are
truly the single best potential we could
have asked for and have made our lives
better in so many ways however long we
have with you I'm sure every second will
be worth it
thank you what a sweet message thank you
thank you thank you typhen
I'm glad I can Inspire and help you like
that I never thought I would be able to
have such an effect on people
[Music]
I don't think I'm really doing anything
that inspirational but
but here we are
well I'm really really glad
thank you so much Tyson for all the love
and support thank you for staying a
loyal supporter kfp member hashtag
vocational
every day thank you so much and I wish
you a happy New Year a successful New
Year where you can Thrive and have a
great time not only at kfb but also in
real life at work yeah
I read I read about an in your letter
and I am not gonna go into detail
obviously but that definitely sounds
like oof that sounds very tough like I I
can imagine like when you when you look
at uh like like media like Netflix shows
and whatever that are about lawyers
[Music]
um okay it seems like kind of like a
dream job doesn't it but
yeah then you gotta get into some deep
[\h__\h] every now and then I can imagine
[Music]
always wonder how
how lawyers can seem so
come across so
so like cold in those shows you know
like as if nothing can hurt them as if
nothing touches their emotions like as
as if you know they're just really built
out of steel but but that's how the
media portrays them and of course uh it
must be a really tough job
where you you have to stay strong and I
I believe in you you can do it
it's it's as you said you have to think
about you know
the good size about it being able to
help people
um
[Music]
and don't blame yourself when it doesn't
go that way once or twice or Thrice
doesn't matter
you just know in your own conscience
that you did you did what was in your
power
and I'm sure that any client would be so
so grateful to have you
so thank you for your
subscribe here feeling illegal counting
on you when those people try to sue me
those employ those ex-employe is no no
we don't have ex-employees we just have
dead chickens
[Music]
Happy New Year
to be a second here let's go
thank you
thank you for your love and support in
2021 yeah
and now I think it looks like now it's
karaoke and then it will be back to clip
super chat later
foreign
[Music]
to our face for being guiding star for
us lost in the world whoever our beloved
potential kinds of in Kiana that's a
nice ring to it doesn't it
uh happy [\h__\h] New Year to you what
can be let's make 2022 a better year
together I made my New Year resolution
to start saving money so I can live on
my own that means I won't be super
traveling as much but that won't mean
I'll be gone oh I want this I won't be
disappearing as long as you are here
with us oh okay no problem I mean saving
money is a very smart thing you gotta
you gotta save for yourself but for your
future maybe for I don't know a house or
something or a car hmm
it's okay don't worry about it thank you
though
[Music]
thank you for all the support you have
given so far
[Music]
I wish you all the best in 2022
hmm
thank you
for two pinkies that's one case
look because you're Phoenix okay anyway
I joined this family at the start of
this year and I think it was the best
decision I've made oh it gives me joy to
support a wonderful and very talented
Phoenix like you so to keep this amazing
feeling I'll definitely continue to
support you my OC thank you for this
exciting year and for the many others to
come for us
yes sorry
sorry I try to adjust my camera
[Music]
what was that
thank you foreign
[Music]
it's been foreign
foreign
[Music]
yeah I um I just just uh last night I
was telling you guys about this song
that I want to cover
um but I think like I can't just do it
immediately this year because it would
need art and that takes some time so I
don't want to do it in February though
because in February the thing with Ahmed
will be happening and I don't want two
things in one month you know I try to
spread it out at least to have a month
in between
so it probably will have to wait until
March even though I'm like really into
the song right now
[Music]
unfortunately but I will be bringing you
guys
you guys again I hopefully we'll also be
bringing you guys more Adventures um
thank you
[Music]
I've grown a lot
of Celebration so I cannot wait to see
what 2022 has to bring in terms of
Kiana's streams thanks for making the
past year so enjoyable for me and the
rest of these chickens
welcome YouTube for making my hair so
much fun every day almost every day I
played some games unless I was doing
some other things watching concerts we
did watch a lot of uh concerts didn't we
made some nice memories of you guys I
will never forget
never forgot
[Music]
thank you Patrick
for the pinky to thank you believe peeps
wouldn't support you even for one year
now we are taking 2020 and 2021 off the
list girl you're not even making it hard
to stand on your side in 2022 you can
try to stop being a cutie with giggle
with a giggle that mounts my heart who's
always working on being a better version
of itself with a turbo weep dorky side
but who gives her all for the brother
she's passionate about and maybe that
will make it a challenge
ah
[Music]
oh no okay
no thank you Happy New Year working for
the job thank you for still being here
thank you
glad to still see your name pop up
next one is a Korean name
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I will try so that it reaches all of you
yeah representing all of you guys
[Music]
yeah about you know meeting other whole
life Girls huh
sometimes I see that like uh uh certain
members of En go to tea with other or
not even only tea but like generally
anything really with other Japanese
members and it makes me think of the
time when that was possible for me
um to meet all of them living in Japan
whenever I want it um
I should have made even more use out of
that
yeah but back then I was still new so it
was also kind of like difficult to be
like hey I wanna hang out well I never
talk to you before but you want to hang
out
well now it would be so much easier I
kind of have um
more connections um
but now whenever I collab with a
Japanese Senpai so often after the
collab it's like oh I wish we could hang
out yeah I want to take you shopping or
to Disneyland and all that let's do it
when you're in Japan and that just makes
me think like oh man the the mo the
moment I go to Japan for a 3DW my
schedule will be so packed I I wonder if
we would even have time to hang out with
all these people we need like a big meet
up honestly that would probably be the
smartest thing to have like all of em
meets up with as many Japanese members
as possible who can make a Time who can
make some time for us
have it be like 20 girls all in one spot
going together to Disneyland or so
the biggest sleepover ever
so that we can meet as many people as
possible in a short amount of time
whole life Supreme off collab
yeah the Disney thing that would
probably stand out if we were there with
20 people
um
[Music]
but somewhere somewhere we would have to
you know gather together
um maybe maybe rent out a whole Onsen
and I'll get naked together
[Music]
huh but that does sound cool like
renting out a whole Onsen I think we
could do that
for like two days or so um
that would be so cool sounds like
Marian's dream
Naka sauce on
hush Kitty
is
[Music]
we have to act smart guys be uh uh
effective productive
[Music]
I would be pretty shy about it but what
else could we rent out besides an Onsen
[Music]
um
I'm not sure I can't think of anything
[Music]
oh I mean with something something where
you could sleep a little would be nice
but otherwise we could rent out like
like a big a big uh karaoke place
and a big big ass restaurant and all
that
a private beach yo that would be so cool
an arcade oh an arcade
whoa we're all Gamers after all so
an arcade
that would that sounds like fun like
playing arcades together
oh and beautiful ketchup
cute
that would be sick yeah
thank you for the recipe
thank you so much for spending the new
year with me and still being here to
support me you always so so generous
thank you always happy to see a familiar
face thank you so much
we hope that you will have a successful
and happy
2022. all your dreams and wishes come
true
yes Paulie thank you as well for a red
Super Chat mwah happy New Year 10
challenge 2022 here
glory to Cafe wish everyone in the chat
has wonderful days in this year
thank you CS Polly I wish the same to
you
a wonderful wonderful 2022 yeah thank
you for still supporting me
throughout all these times real bad
times and Good Times
thank you for thinking of me
huh
thank you for the pinky happy New Year
Kiara and everyone 2021 uh foreign
[Music]
foreign
thank you very much I wish you all the
best as well thank you for spending your
precious time with me and for finding me
for in the middle of uh so many many
many many YouTubers you decided to
support me thank you
for always organizing these kinds of
special events you should be very proud
of yourself I'm very excited for this
and especially okay it's gonna be
amazing what a great way to end 2021
love your best friend thank you
oh yeah I uh
I'm I'm not doing as much as amazing
work as I'm trying to make my like a
contribution in my way in in like how
much I can provide I as as long as I can
do something I'm happy to be there thank
you for the membership come send me down
and and I was I was very happy to see uh
the relay going so well and everyone
being so excited about it and you guys
as well like I I didn't think
um that for such a short uh karaoke so
many people would come thank you for
showing up guys
[Music]
yeah thank you for the uh membership
thank you
I'm actually surprised that more people
showed up to that karaoke than to my VR
karaoke which
ah the VR in my opinion was very special
I don't do that all the time okay next
time everybody come come
[Music]
and was it 11 hours long well I mean but
one by one it was very short
yeah you were there you were there
um
maybe it was a shitty time
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
happy New Year utensil I want you to
know that you are the reason why 2021
was such an amazing year for me thank
you so much for everything looking
forward to spend even more time with you
in 2022 I will continue to support you
forever you are the best love you always
my Empress thank you
I I really really hope that I can be
with you guys as long as possible
[Music]
it's it makes me like you guys make me
feel wanted
[Music]
um thank you for that
thank you unknown for making me feel
special and needed and appreciated
Happy New Year to you and all my love
back to you
thank you so much
Happy New Year my Empress my 2021 was
great because of you thank you for
entertaining content and wish you have a
great year in 2022 with KFC
um
[Music]
thank you for the red circle chat wow
wow thank you
Happy New Year my attention and my
Phoenix Empress I have so many titles
but
and cheers to all kfb employees although
I am not able to catch all streams live
I am still lurking around still finding
your stream most enjoyable okay that's
good to know looking forward to another
game of kfb P.S I'm ready to fight
takodashi with these slippers oh wait I
see the flippers in your profile picture
nice you got the slippers
[Music]
thank you please keep them safe and and
uh even if they fit you don't don't
outwear them because otherwise one day
they will be falling apart we don't want
that
you gotta take good care of those
slippers please
thank you
thank you for the love and support thank
you I'm glad you got them safely and I
wish you a happy happy wonderful new
year let's go 2022. let's rock it thank
you Anton and for also sending a red
Super Chat mwah
happy New Year Kiana this year has been
very eventful for me but the real fun
started when I joined kfb no it's only
been 2.5 months what only but I've made
a lot of pleasant memories in such a
short time
thank you
I'm very grateful for all you do for us
and I hope we continue to have a great
time in 2022 consider it an annual bonus
boss oh I'm so glad that there's like
still some new people here like
um I mean especially now with all the
new Korean views of course but like also
like people like you who joined like two
or three months ago thank you I'm I'm
glad to see my community grow oh yeah
[Music]
thank you for finding me
and choosing to stay
yeah since you've only been around for a
short time I hope you don't grow sick of
me anytime soon we still have so much
more to do together okay thank you
[Music]
yeah someday you will be fried to look
forward to that day
now puts you into that hot oil
you hear that frizzling sound
uh Jim Tracy thank you for the pinky
happy New Year thank you this year has
been so much fun and full of so many
great memories thank you for all your
hard work and for making this community
special can't wait to see what 2022 has
in store for kfb Viva La Canada yeah I
can't wait to see Uber to be honest at
this point I really don't know much of
what's to come like for I know some
things for like the first couple of
months but for summer and and spring uh
summer end up
uh fall and all that I mostly know
nothing
they mostly know nothing I have some
plans like I want to put out at least
like maybe free Originals this year or
or one single and on an album Maybe
maybe an album is a lot of work
um
yeah I definitely want to make some
music and uh if the 3DW happens then I I
really hope it happens before my
birthday because I really want to do
like a 3D stream for my birthday as well
I think we can make it happen
[Music]
I think 2022 my birthday must be in 3D
to be honest um
I was hoping and planning for it to be
already for the last year
um it was already ready at that time so
I just couldn't show you guys yeah uh I
was hoping for it I wanted to like
perform for you guys in 3D
but maybe next year then yeah I still
made my 3D and my my birthday
like enjoyable anyway my birthday stream
but I I wanna if possible I wanted to be
like a concert or even maybe maybe the
birthday stream shouldn't be much of a
concert but then it's like separately to
Dad I won the concert like like
Senpai like like their concerts I want
something like that
um
but it would probably be online only
which I think is fine
[Music]
because like I I wouldn't know where the
venue would be
I won a concert like that that you all
can watch
um
a big contact with lots of work behind
it
and an idol outfit
an idol outfit please I want an idol on
fit to perform in
the lion is
[Music]
Idol outfit please
I really really love Idols so I have
like so many ideas for an idol outfit
I have so many ideas in my brain
uh
thank you for the pinky the memories
I've made this year with you and kfb
have been some of the best of my adult
life oh
foreign
family meeting Randall getting teased
about my username oh wait there's more
and this in your bag uh getting to meet
you and Kelly and Yuma Khan and talk to
you that was yeah really cool to be an
all these American conventions and
Canadian conventions
and I'm meeting other kfp as well it's
been such a fun year and I can't thank
you enough Kiara if I may I wish to blow
you a kiss for New Years I hope it
reaches you Happy New Year
ah oh what was that was that the
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
never mind it was not your case it was
my cat that was flying at me
[Music]
hi you're beautiful you're so beautiful
oh my God
you're so beautiful I know you don't
like sitting on my lap but I love you
[Music]
um
you're more beautiful than I am are you
aware of that cat
you're so gorgeous
[Music]
you want to sit next to me hear the
chairs free it's open for you
no okay maybe you change your mind later
[Music]
so one red
you can do something like that again
with the convention
yeah a world tour this time how about
that not only not not only American
conventions
yeah but but I need you guys to let the
conventions know that you want us
let's make YouTubers even more popular
all over the world huh how about that
uh oh how do I read this name
[Music]
ah Valera well
Super Chat and we're
thank you for the pinky spending my
birthday watching Kiana
oh man so many people will have their
birthday on the 31st or maybe it was the
yeah no that was the 31st for you damn
you're kind funny and far more talented
than your you give yourself credit for
I've been here before hold on oh I mean
oh you you mean uh
you would you you liked whole life
before whole again but you and kfb are
what got me to stop lurking oh let's
kick this next year off with sparks
flying
[Music]
happy belated birthday
oh I hope you were able to celebrate oh
my God that's actually you know what
first I thought it was like a thing like
with Christmas but having a birthday on
New Year's means that you get freaking
fireworks celebrating you you could
think it's about you and then it's
freaking dope bad so high if everyone's
in party mood like oh and everyone oh
wait if your birthday is on the 31st and
high chances are that uh like your
friends aren't working and you will be
able to invite them to a birthday slash
New Year's party oh my God that's
actually a pretty good way uh a pretty
good day for a birthday
you always get like an insane birthday
party
[Music]
guys
it used to be I got older oh but you
used to get the most out of it and enjoy
it that's nice I hope so well Happy New
Year to you
now
you can let me out sounded weird to me
you're good
you
[Music]
it kind of sounded weird to me but I
think they're fun
sometimes they meow like something is
really weird
47 I'll thank you for the pinky
and 2021 was a transition year in many
ways moving across an ocean and then
settling down twice wait for you for me
for me that definitely is true but all
things considered is when you handled
very well okay I think you mean me I
can't say what 22 2022 holds still I
have some hopes as I'm sure you do but
I'll be there for it thank you
yeah I I I do agree um
I I moved a lot and uh I wasn't a very
unstable position
for a lot of it and uh I am really happy
that things finally settled down and
calmed down
and it's been fun moving into this new
apartment and even though it takes a
long time and it's also very costly I
enjoy like putting together my dream
apartment finally because up until now I
was always just like
living in shitty ass Apartments
they're really dirty and hat and and I
really had only second hand and really
cheap furniture
yeah well now now I have a great
apartment that I'm really happy with I
have great cats I have great friends and
I have a great job so yeah it's oh nice
movement it really stabilized so I I
appreciate that
thin skin thin walls yeah that's what I
started out with in her life in the
beginning
I remember that oh man I I couldn't
stream for too long because the first
apartment that I lived in when I just
started out yeah it had really really
thin walls and I had to get out of there
as soon as possible
um I can't believe that I even streamed
in that apartment like I literally heard
The Whispers of
the room next to me
and they heard mine
I heard everything
that's why I still felt like I couldn't
stream for too long and I couldn't
stream for it to wait and I couldn't be
too loud and I had to be quiet back then
I didn't feel very very comfortable at
all
[Music]
I can't imagine how I even went through
that
we're streaming as my job
[Music]
oh I don't know I never really spoke to
them uh they sometimes banged against my
wall but I never had a conversation with
them so I don't know they they hopefully
don't know what I did and who I was but
even if they did then whatever at this
point it doesn't matter
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
she keeps on like rubbing herself
against my legs so cute so cute oh now
you're gonna join oh she's sitting down
on the seat next to me oh oh she wants
belly rubs
horse movie
[Music]
oh she's lifting her leg so that I can
reach her belly better
cute awesome
are you purring let me take off my
headphones
[Music]
foreign
she's so sweet right now so everything
[Music]
um
wait let me try to move the microfilter
so you can hear the purse you want to
hear it I know you do is the most
soothing thing ever
[Music]
mm-hmm
hmm
it's a yawned
no no
hmm
[Music]
your cat is looking everywhere
that's cute
oh baby
you're enjoying being petted and getting
belly rubs you love it don't you yeah
oh
so we'll be in your right ear now so
um
[Music]
belly rubs oh I know bunny kicking she's
a low-key um kneading my hand right now
oh my God it's so cute oh but then she
kicks me again like slightly
she's very picky there's some
some spots that I guess she doesn't like
oh oh no she's stretching her belly oh
yeah yeah I'm getting I know where you
want me to pet you
I know
no
hey baby
oh the knitting paw is always like opens
them up and you see her claws and then
she
like makes a fist again oh okay
cute baby
[Music]
are you cute baby
sorry I love my cat way too much
foreign
okay
okay let's go
sorry
ah
is it back to normal I feel like it's
still a bit too quiet
[Music]
okay I I
will do
so where was I uh
[Music]
uh
yeah Aker thank you for the right Super
Chat donkey
hi Kara this year I learned so much from
you just wanted to say thank you and
happy New Year Happy New Year to you too
thank you so much I'm glad you could
learn something from me I'm not sure
what it was
was it was it how to uh be the head of a
company of a successful fast food
franchise yeah I think you guys learned
a lot from me in that regard
one of the rules is no mercy um
thank you very much
thank you for the rest of the chat of
course the kinds of learn Happy New Year
to you and yours
hope you you mean what what just answer
to you and yours hope you're well uh
thank you for being you and for all you
do I have not been part of this
community proper for long but I do not
regret a moment since oh please keep on
being amazing being you ever said oh wow
that German sounds pretty convincing to
me
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you well oh
you seem to be new here to you and your
family I see
ah oh I learned something new
well welcome welcome a new face a KFC is
always welcome I hope you had a
wonderful 2021 and if not then let's
just make 2022 even better a million
times better
thank you for the support I'm looking
forward to having you around for many
many more streams this year thank you oh
you're here in the chat too everyone is
here
everybody's here
[Music]
oh my God her paw I'm holding her paw
and squeezing it's so cute
for the pinky well look at that it's the
New Year I hope that we can all continue
to enjoy the things we love this year
for me this includes all the fun content
you have been working hard at here's an
excellent 2022. yeah yeah I hope it will
be successful till I want this year to
be a great one where we can you know
do anything we want to do now live to
our fullest potential so I hope the best
for you counting chickens
let's make it a great one shall we thank
you for your support happy New Year
Chase workbook thank you for the pinky
as well I'm really glad I joined all the
kfps in watching you in 2021 yeah it's
been a lot of fun we have really great
ups and sometimes down it's just the
time I've spent watching your streams
was definitely worth it so here's to
2022. thank you okay swap work I'm glad
that you feel that way that you feel
happy being here thank you for joining
us
glad you don't regret it
yeah thank you here's to a wonderful
2022 Happy New Year to you thank you for
the love and support you give me thank
you from the bottom of my heart thank
you I appreciate it
J1 thank you for the pinky
happy New Year attention and kfps I'm so
thankful to be able to know you and
spend time with you in 2021 2021 I'll
pray that we can make only happy
memories together next year as well love
you
[Music]
yes
I think I think
I think we will make only happy memories
yes and I will try my best to impress
you guys with my Korean skills
throughout the year
so please look forward to that cheer for
me J1 I will do my best so please keep
on supporting me and following me
Jackson FB thank you for the red super
chat mwah
it says
Hannah I wanted to thank you for
brightening these last few months for me
even when I was at my lowest it's always
a blast of you and kfp also I never
forgot about you hashtag broken Viva La
quesada yeah yes broke gang must be
appreciated as well thank you everybody
who is always here no matter if they're
sending super chats or not thank you so
much oh my
mama
and uh
oh Jackson of course I'm here when
you're at Eloise because whole life
literally came to me and when I was at
my lowest so it's my way of giving back
to you that's the least I can do being
there for you guys
in the great great humans um thank you
polar night time Vic
um
[Music]
donkey oh
do you guys hear that I still hear the
feedback picking up my cat's purse a
little bit in the background
flaming pants
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat yeah
over the bgm you probably don't hear it
yeah thank you
thank you
foreign
[Music]
um
thank you
Apple thank you for the word Super Chat
thank you Happy New Year thanks for
making 2021 and a great year whether it
was a game Stream karaoke song Premiere
Super Chat reading collab Etc he always
brought a smile to my face can't wait to
see what my Oshi does for 20 times too
love your Kiana thank you ever
your OC will hopefully do many things
that will make you happy as a viewer
that is always the goal so
I will work hard
to provide entertainment to you ifo
thank you so so much for staying here
and watching all of my streams
thank you for the love and support
on to another wonderful year let's go
Doom sweet
I don't know how to read that is
[Music]
hold up
foreign
[Music]
celebrating your birthday on the 31st oh
my God
that sounds like fun see that's what I
mean you get a whole party for your
birthday no matter what
it's also a very difficult day to forget
see that's maybe also one of the good
things to have a birthday on on a date
where something else big is happening at
least people are less likely to forget
your birthday
um
happy belated birthday
I hope you celebrated well hope you're
healthy hope you're happy
and hope that 2021 was great for you
yeah
let's enjoy another wonderful year on
this Earth 2020 let's go thank you
thank you that'll start Duncan
so I have to let you oh she just did the
thing oh my God
she's just a fan you know when cats
press their paws against your face when
they're like like kind of
because they're doing the opposite of
stretching but you know what I mean
when they pressed it she just did that
while having my hand squeezing her paw
so she squeezed my hand into her face as
well she does that often
oh yeah when she kind of hides her face
no not knitting no no and it's like
oh when she presses her both of her paws
against her face so cute so cute and you
put on my head
for the pinky
[Music]
was nice because I discovered
2022 will be even better because I can
start it with you and KFA yes
that is a great start isn't it
thank you thank you for finding me this
year it's not it's not that easy to find
me
no there's so many other YouTubers
and even within her life
um I feel like you know when you find
out about YouTubers and you start like
looking through YouTubers I feel like a
lot of people they go through the most
popular ones because they're like oh
those must be popular for a reason and
they are of course they are but I think
there's a lot of people who don't really
go like to though to the bottom you know
to the less popular one so thank you for
finding me yeah this is this is this is
a miracle no this is Destiny
yeah
it's Destiny that we found each other
all of us
thank you
yeah I mean overall we're very popular
yes yes yes
overall of course
popular
and popular
look at all my Korean fans foreign
yeah
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat mwah
happy New Year just a message from an
old chicken and kfp nothing special you
are special happy to be here with you at
the first of January 2022 a whole new
year with our lovely attention what a
nice day thank you you guys are in the
future you had 2022 before me and I'm
kind of jealous but but I strong
accepted thank you for waiting for me
for me to arrive in 2022. I'm here now
let's have a great time together
we see all the best
thank you Bruno thank you for the red
super chat oh boy God
and greetings to Brazil thanks for
another great year dental and KFC it's
been a lot of fun and I already can't
wait to see you soar even higher next
year I can't wait either I wanna see
what's above the sky
maybe Santa can show me some pictures
thank you Bruno
I hope you can keep up with me little
chimpkin you gotta practice flying Bruno
so that you can fly with me up there hmm
[Music]
for your support thank you Happy New
Year
of London for the red super chat happy
New Year Kiana you've already done so
much for us but you keep offering to do
more so thank you for everything every
day is like a dream with you your story
has uplifted me more than you know and
I'm happy to have someone special like
you in my life oh it does one part
there's another one you're easily my
highlight this year you funny cute
incredibly incredible and multi-talented
boob you're my Aussie and I won't be
happier than with anyone else I love you
so much
I love you too thank you
so sweet
thank you yeah you're saying um
Irreplaceable oh
um
go get your kisses thank you for letting
me be your Aussie
oh I'm happy to have such sweet people
sweet and kind-hearted people Oshi in me
thank you very much for your kindness
and your generosity giving me all your
love
hope I can give it back as much as
possible
and here's one from today for some
reason
asd19875 a Korean superchat thank you
zero Pandora
MK zero thank you for the pinky
just wanted to report that I managed to
successfully stay awake for 40 hours to
watch all of your streams
you mean starting from the the official
stream and then wait why did you stay
away before the hours you should have
slept in between it's not like I
streamed for 40 hours I'm now able to
hear colors and taste sound and now I
have to return to my shift at kfp I love
you and stay spicy ggs oh I'm sorry no
you didn't have to do that with your
shifts do you mean no a real job oh my
God I hope not I hope you didn't watch
my streams for 40 hours and then have to
go to work
that sounds like hell
yeah take care of yourself
[Music]
but that was that those sound like some
pretty dope ass skills you know
but thank you thank you for your
dedication and really I I do I do
appreciate it that you tried to watch
all of my streams but just take care of
yourself okay it's always important to
get some sleep I love sleeping you
should do too
thank you for everything you've done
this year we are such a fantastic and
joyous personality that it makes every
stream a ton of fun to watch here's to
another year with you and kfp yay
[Music]
thank you thank you for being here
tonight and every other day thank you so
much my lovey my lovely Canadian
champion thank you
[Music]
love you
so we have to let your paw go I have to
translate something kitty cat
[Music]
thank you for the membership I'm
grateful and glad that I could spend the
last year with you and kfp I will hold
on to many precious memories I hope that
in 2022 we'll make many more I will do
my best to be a loyal on Dependable
Chicken in 2022. thank you I hope I can
count on you to stay here until I
personally end your shift okay please
stay here until the end I'm counting on
you
thank you for your love and support
Happy New Year
dance
for the pinky yeah
even good is yeah
[Music]
thank you song
um
it means Health in German
it's not only me saying uh bless you no
Jack plays
Ravenwood Duncan wave
I know you sent that Super Chat when I
was singing
I love being dramatic about that one
water
[Music]
health
or worship at 72 Duncan thank you nibor
thank you for Pinky happy New Year kiawa
oh did you guys see I changed my name on
Twitter
I just had a lot of guests around and
they plan to leave around 10 pm luckily
they left earlier so I'm happy that I
can still catch your karaoke nice
that's interesting though on on New
Year's they plan to leave at 10 pm why
wouldn't they stay until like the
fireworks and all that it's kind of
weird but all right I see that I see it
thank you for spending your time with me
I'm glad you came to my karaoke slot
thank you so much for making memories
with me throughout 2021 and let's do the
same in 2022
hmm
abilities
G web gaming thank you for the pinky
awesome as always Kiara thank you I do
agree I think I think I nailed my cut
off there
a lot I practiced hard for it um
although I do want to give North from
crafts another try
at some point because I I literally
learned that song in one day
and how are you in two places at once
why
why am I there oh
become a message are they playing the
message
are you guys watching the me Corona
stream right now but let me see
Toko
foreign
[Music]
that's that's the thing that we recorded
I think after
some collab or so recently where we had
to all be together
it's just a it doesn't matter if you
missed it it was just like a cycle do
your best yeah yeah we're supporting you
thingy because they're doing the 24 hour
stream and we were asked to send them a
message like uh yeah we're supporting
you
I think it was after jackbox soon or
maybe this stream is pre-recorded no no
no no no no no stupid I just read your
comments
unless you are planted it is real
[Music]
oh they have rewind on oh one of that's
on purpose
you can rewind huh
[Music]
a special does just a quick message
we did have some trouble though
recording now
so it was not only a five minute thing I
was a little bit Troublesome
anyway
Sean R thank you for the right Super
Chat uh thanks for awesome year Kiara
here's to another cheers that
gingerbread wrap was fine if you haven't
listened to other Lonely Island songs I
highly recommend Jack Sparrow the creep
and Boombox uh I think I listened to
Jack Sparrow I didn't listen to the
other ones shall we listen to one of
those which one is better the creep or a
boombox
we can listen to one song quickly
[Music]
Blue Max
creep boombox
Boombox oh yeah looks like more boom
boxes
okay
um
[Music]
shuttle await
wait what is this Laura Marano Boombox
no that's probably not in here uh
Boombox from The Lonely Island with
Julian Casablancas who is that am I
supposed to know that dude
[Music]
must be some famous person though
okay we'll watch it together two and a
half minutes
okay here's the URL
here's the URL
foreign
oh dear
um
sauerkraut
they're kicking you out
oh no they're liking it
nice haircuts
foreign
to the ground throw the goose to the
ground
oh let's go
nice moves
the ghosts
ew
hahaha
I like fingerless gloves
where's everyone why
is everyone eating boiled goose
turbo base
oh
ah
a bull box is not a toy let's go
[Music]
foreign
enough
soon enough
they need loving too I guess so well
thanks to the Boombox for bringing love
back into their lives there's a song
called YOLO with Adam
and YOLO you know that's my life model
not really it's your life model
is that one good it has Adam Levine in
it
I wanna watch that one
watch it okay let's go quit I'll give
you the link I'll give you like Michael
Michael should we really be wasting time
like this probably not
all good
on zero okay on zero I'll give you a
moment I'll give you a moment
am I Adam Levine
three
two one zero
um
foreign
who's he again
what a banger
yes
oh
thank you
um
oh I guess so
you only live once they'll be extra
careful
I mean it makes sense
we didn't hear that
ew
this is so good
oh
is this the Kendrick guy I've seen him
before I think
yeah yeah that's him
I thought the other guy was conflict
this is real talk guys
no no
isolate yourself and watch YouTubers
laughs
he's wearing a tin foil hat
oh my God
oh
what so you can't find your tongue
oh my
[Laughter]
God
they are really scared of death
um hmm I don't know if I recommend you
guys the same thing
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know I guess
thank you
[Music]
okay back to Super chats quick quick
quick quick thank you Sean I for that
recommendation
thank you so much for being a bright
spot for me during some tough times
happy New Year Happy New Year
I'm glad I could be there for you when
you needed me thank you Miss Ori I hope
that in 2022 the year will be nicer to
you you deserve it you do happy new year
take care of yourself
thank you for the pinky
and this year was wonderful with you
Kiana thank you so much thank you too it
was wonderful to have you around too
thank you I hope that you made some good
memories in 2021 I hope it was a good
one for
one point well okay I wish you Happy New
Year you soda thank you soon okay of
penguin thank you soon
I need to let go of your cute paw one
moment smoothie
[Music]
one moment
chocolate
again
um
the worm super Superior the worm
Superior thank you for the pinky and
happy New Year Kiana I just discovered
whole life a few months ago but your
drive and passion are inspiring me to
keep moving forward in these crazy times
wish you all the best for 2022. thank
you very much thank you welcome to the
fandom welcome to the rabbit hole
I hope you're having a great time here
as you have heard so far it only brings
happiness so yeah please stay around and
continue to support me and my Endeavors
I will do my best Euro school wish you
all the best as well please let's have
fun at kfp it's your guy Claire
Doncaster
you look like a snail baby you look like
a snail you are a snail aren't you she's
like M snail
thank you
thank you thank you Andreas thank you
thank you put this noise
happy New Year it's been a wonderful and
fun year Watching and cheering for you
and I'm sure next year will be great as
this year your streams always bring me
joy and inspiration thank you for being
my OC this year and the years to come
love you I love you too oh thank you for
[Music]
eign
I'm glad I am somewhat likable thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you for making me feel loved
I hope that you will stay around until
The Bitter End
[Music]
thank you
for a long time and I I understand
understand but I'm so happy about it
every time you say it um
black person dancing
for the pinky kind of singing membership
is the best thing ever thank you for
finishing 2021 like this I am the
happiest chicken right now you're
welcome I'm glad I can uh sing some cool
old songs for you that you guys enjoy
even if you don't know them there's one
more song that I love from Golden bomber
I think it was called Dance my
generation
I'm gonna learn that one for you guys
they have quite some bangers
Kiana we love you a lot to the point
where it's weird and uncomfortable no no
nothing's weird about that
no
it's nice to hear it vocalized it really
is
but yeah visual case fan no but my BFF
during uh doing art school the one I
told you about the cute one
the cute girl who's now in Japan she was
a visual cave fan and she was like also
dressing that way the the shy girl
and then through her I found out about
some groups uh like golden bomber
um
yeah yeah
um the one that
um when I joined this school I had like
no friends but I saw her in the bus in
the amidst of so many other students and
she stood out to me because she dressed
like someone who likes Japan a lot would
dress her like a weeb and I was like oh
I'm not the only one and she's my Senpai
I want to talk to her
and then it took me a lot of courage and
quite some time to actually
talk to Herb took us some time but we
became friends forever for the rest of
our life even though nowadays we live in
different countries and we don't have
much contact anymore but we still check
up on each other every once in a while I
did actually meet her in 2021 and that
was a miracle
yeah I met her at the start of 2021
in Japan we went on a little trip
together hmm
I hope maybe in 2022 if she's still in
Japan I could meet her there but she did
say to me last time I talked to her that
she is considering of coming back to
Austria she's been in Japan for a long
time by now so I understand I would
actually be happy if she comes back
because then I would have one more
friend here
um
um that's when you made in frog well did
I was that then
[Music]
yeah I went on another vacation at the
start of last year didn't I mm-hmm
I visited her
back then
[Music]
I want my friend to share your keys with
yeah yeah
and frog past 1 million I know I know I
know I know yeah yeah yeah
uh okay uh
um where was I where was I here muffin
ain't dancing for the red super chat
happy New Year Kiana 2022 will be that
year of myth 3D and I will continue to
wait for it and an orange 3D life yeah
also your new outfit is amazing and your
cover with Inna was great looking
forward to the one with Amir thank you
yes uh I need to start working on that
ASAP
um yeah although I think yeah it will be
fine it will be fine I'll I'm planning
to release something with Ahmed on
Valentine's Day
and it should be kind of I think the
song I chose I chose it like a while
back I think it was kind of Valentine's
Day themed
uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I forgot which song
was it I forgot but oh well I wouldn't
share it with you guys with you guys yet
anyway it's a secret
oh orange and yellow Heights look nice
next to one another it's like almost as
if we're becoming one
it's gonna be super cute
foreign
[Music]
I will try to bring out a lot of things
every month if possible I want to be
productive
even more productive than last year if
possible
um
thank you for the pinky it's a blessing
and a pleasure to usher in 2022 with the
Divine empress and kfp happy New Years
everybody and best wishes for the future
to you too Happy New Year I hope you
celebrated yourself at the end of your
at the end of the year for your
accomplishments let's accomplish many
more things next year okay okay
Odyssey I mean yeah is that a hint what
do you mean what you guys say hintin
what did I hint at what do you guys
think is the hint
that we're melting together
I don't know how that is a hint to
anything
what did I say
are you guys are so paranoid you need a
doctor
hmm
dance is that this year is going to be
the best one yeah
two hearts joining
I don't see wow anything was a hint
[Music]
was Cheryl your fave huh huh you're
welcome I I know people wanted me to
sing more Macross so I decided to sing
some more and learn one for you yeah
yeah
it's cute turtle yeah foreign
[Music]
thank you three months already wow
was that yet another hint when what what
what what
my love was maybe a hint but maybe what
what what what what
[Music]
no anyway you're welcome
um thank you thank you I'm glad you
enjoyed that no friend Chris cover but I
will sing it again at some point and
then I'll nail it better okay please
wait for that don't take this as the
final one
I want to learn that song Too the
diamond one leave it to me
favendor thank you for the lyrics
I've been working since February also
enjoyed the membership on your birthday
you might also aren't the only one whose
merch I've actually bought wow thank you
thanks for the year of streams and look
forward to see what you have in store
for 2022. well I hope you won't learn
that much this year then come out come
out
chicken soft to me don't be such a
chicken don't be such a chicken
thank you for joining I feel very
honored to be so special to you thank
you so so so so much yeah I hope it
arrived by now
thank you for watching my streams and
all the love
and drugs and Red Riot Danke Schoen
Slayer said thank you for the right
Super Chat mwah happy New Year Channel
Happy New Year to you too thank you for
your support in the past year please
continue supporting me in 2022 yes
as well Happy New Year Daisy my love
thank you so much
[Music]
oh I like the the number in your recipe
chat it's 3939 which is
thank you thank you yeah happy New Year
dear Tanto and everyone hope you'll
continue doing what you like the most in
2022. I hope so too I hope we all can do
the things that we like and enjoy
ourselves
thank you for your love and I say that
secret code I thank you thank you i3939
you too
[Music]
oh yeah I guess it's also Miko Miku
that's true that's true it is
it is there's two ways to read it um
smart smart cookie
you need some chassis your lips must be
getting tired from all the cases to be
honest like for real though my my lips
are very dry at the moment because of
the stupid winter air uh you're like
falling apart man
I'm reading these from if you look at
the top right I'm always putting the
thumbnail of what I'm reading at the
moment up there
[Music]
that's it's from the New Year's stream
still kiss your cats more than you kiss
us oh that's a close one to be honest
[Music]
your vocals are in points today I can
tell how much you've practiced in recent
karaoke streams I hope to be able to
attend a live concert of yours one day
Kiara here's a down payment on the
ticket
thank you I really hope I can deliver
that to you as I said I I don't want to
do like a proper concert and I want to
do a 3D birthday stream
I really really hope we can make it
happen I want a proper concert yo
with like effects and Stage a stage and
maybe like a middle stage it moves up
whoa yeah
that would be so cool let's work hard
towards that so we get that yeah
otherwise I guess we could also yeah do
concerts at conventions again but I I
don't want I don't want the proper
concept where I can design everything
like I can I can put input into like how
I want the stage design to look like and
um yeah make a longer set list maybe
call some guests
Cheryl worthy concert hell yeah
a 3D concept
I would run the Winston okay
should not be the nopon merchant dankest
and winterhandan
thank you
um
[Music]
for the pinky happy New Year employees
and Kiara yeah Happy New Year to all of
you too thank you for the pinky
[Music]
that was only close because my my go XLR
is currently covered up by my tablet
like I moved it to the front and now I
can't really reach the button the beep
button
so I said it differently
Feliz and
is oh
see that mm-hmm
maybe this year be even more amazing
than the last I pray for all of kfp to
have a happy New Year and Viva La Quiana
praise praise kaiza Kiara thank you
oh it's funny how you guys still come up
with new names for me but I mean that
was personally because of my new outfit
so it's my my my fault or thanks to me
that we have a new name for me
[Music]
what do you mean you're sad that I
didn't mention those I I mentioned the
artist and listen I can't I couldn't
listen to all of their songs and if I
needed to stop somewhere
oh but I do you guys know I've I did
like kind of sing or like uh
uh hum Lucifer from shiny before
25th attempt oh because of shiny
[Music]
um
that's a good song I don't listen much
to male Kpop groups but back then that
was a good song Lucifer Lucifer
[Music]
yeah yeah one of my best friends really
is like a huge
shiny fan she loves shiny so
such a
cake fan
just crazy about them so cute
Ginger Ranger 13.
for the pinky amazing singing
hoping that 2022 will be great for you
and the KF peeps love you mate love you
too you know what Judy maybe in 2022 I
can finally perfectionize my Australian
accent mate am I am a British accent
which are all the same as my Scottish
accent my wife can make them perfect
issue I mean already perfect let's be
honest
let's go
there's no hope for that shut up
go to the room oh yes Santa could teach
me yeah
Santa and fails could teach me
Australian accent
not that I would need their help I mean
I mean
let's go to makas
you sound just like a Scottish friend of
mine oh thank you I know my Scottish
accent is so accurate it's not and and
it's and it's
uh
felt like you got a potato in the mouth
I will have a potato in my mouth soon
once I enter stream and figure out how
to make an oven potato do you have to
boil them before putting them into the
aluminum foil or do you put them into
the into the oven Raw
serious question
no boiling okay so I wash them and I put
them into the foil and then put them in
and then I put them out and then I cut
them open and then I put the [\h__\h] in
that I want to eat I love
[Music]
microwave and then oven oh
okay okay remember Olive okay I look up
a recipe it's ridiculous that I have to
look up a recipe for that but hey you
gotta you gotta do everything correctly
even the simplest things like making
eggs
oh
Hulk either side of her fork oh here
comes the the pro advice from your guys
poke a few holes into the into the
aluminum foil or into the potato or into
both
[Music]
you can microwave them what
both oh okay okay I'm excited
potato I'm gonna end the stream in uh 25
minutes so that I have one and a half
hours to bake and eat a potato you think
that's enough time to bake a potato
foreign
[Music]
and for the last greeting in 2021
it takes one hour to bake potato what
if it's only one it should be it takes
about 40 minutes
already put it in maybe I should warm my
oven already preheated already uh
wolf
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah I probably have to do it now then
because I need some time to eat it too
okay uh okay okay let me let me let me
preheat the oven
open schedule
please
[Music]
you can stay here smoothie I'm just
gonna turn on the oven you can stay
there
[Music]
okay I'm back which you States movie oh
and Kathy you're here too okay
okay let's go uh uh this one is from the
clip review
[Music]
thank you soon are you more confident
that I'll read your name correctly if
it's in Japanese is that why you changed
it and kept it
we know where to stand don't say it like
that I love you guys I love you guys
[Music]
cat's hair in my face oh just too lazy
okay
hello
Lord
I think that stream was really good I'm
glad we did it like watching those clips
was a lot of fun for me and I think for
you guys as well
looking back back on those moments was a
great great way to look back on 2021
because we all have burp brains we
wouldn't be able to do it without those
clips I think like if someone were to
ask us what happened in 2021 I would be
like oh
I don't know
I need something to guide me brilliant
[Music]
I I I do want to say
um before I forget to say it
um in the actual in the New Year's
resolution stream although I don't know
how much more of a New Year's resolution
stream that will be but anyway I I don't
want to say that for me personally my
biggest accomplishments in 2021 are
moving from Japan to Austria and
settling in
and being at tokomi as the first whole
Lab English member to be at a convention
like that in person and representing
whole life English like that
and having it like be so special it was
really special having my concert there
and becoming the tales of the rice
ambassador
that was huge for me I had so many
things at so many streams related to
that to do for them
um
[Music]
and putting out
a high Challenger and spikes yeah
my original songs from this year
those are I would say unless I'm
forgetting something my biggest
accomplishments this year last year
of course it was more but these are the
ones that definitely made me proud and
and yeah
um stayed in my memory
um
still waiting for the unboxing of your
goods from Monday
ah
you mean what the collector's edition I
purchased myself and it's been standing
around there
for quite some time we could open it up
next time I do a cooking the origami
stream I'm planning on the origami
stream or the jacket yeah weren't they
gonna send me a jacket I wonder I wonder
about the truth they also weren't they
gonna send me like this little ball
thing
the cord of the thingy
it didn't come yet I only have at least
a PS5
what happened to the snack yeah I don't
know man
oh man you're the [\h__\h] snack box I'm
gonna write them a strongly worded
letter soon
I mean for a while it was also partially
my fault apparently because of my my
payment my payment apparently didn't go
through for a while for whatever reason
[Music]
but it did a while ago and I still
didn't get my snacks
my man are we going for war again hell
yeah
[Music]
I was supposed to get a
snack box at least for December
in December
I think it was supposed to be a Korean
snack box even or or Canadian
uh celebrate speech thank you for
sending a rainbow super Superman thank
you
wishing a wonderful and happy New Year
to you Kiana and all kfp had primarily
been a clip Watcher and lurk until a
fateful day when I learned that being at
Medical in Orlando oh really that was
the thing that got you to be a proper
Watcher I remember you going there in
your apron and all that the whole get up
I decided to make myself a catfish chef
uniform make a Twitter and join the
community I'm so glad you did I thought
you were already a part of it like
before that but
since that day I've made so many good
memories antagonizing hot summer with my
fried chicken video if you've been out
there yeah meeting Sarah didn't and so
let's keep late and seeing you and Kelly
at yomakon sharing along with all of kfp
to your performances and streams I've
also gotten to encounter a lot of
amazing and talented people online from
all over the world tell them that
creators like Manzanita and barcadi
content creators like cads as and body
and project creators like Dominica
so thank you for introducing me to a
brand new world thank you for being
amused to the new Creator to new
creative Endeavors both for me and
others thank you for your beautiful
singing and creative streams I hope the
coming year sees all your wishes come
true and that good times continue to
come for you your family friends and
pets and to all of kfb oh thank you that
is a lovely message I'm really really
glad that you are that you decided to
start watching my streams properly
instead of only um lurking with the
clips yeah that's a good decision as you
can see yeah really wonderful to hear
that and to be honest when I first saw
you
uh during that whole convention season
you know those conventions obviously
like there's so many like gouda cosplays
and and also a lot of Cali cosplays and
many many other whole life members
cosplays and it was just really nice to
see uh amidst that you know seeing
someone like you're representing the kfp
fandom it made me feel very very happy
and and you know yeah I was just happy
to see some kid proud kfp proudly
representing where are they are from
seeing it there made me
feel very honored thank you soon for the
love that you spread and for being part
of kfp let's enjoy 2022 together thank
you
detective
charity thank you for the red super chat
wow happy New Year Kiana besides normal
thanks to you for always being awesome
lovely and you I really want to give a
big thanks for organizing the karaoke
Reliance bearing the details I had a
final day at work if it wasn't for the
Relay I'd have gone Louie so again thank
you Arigato thank you and I appreciate
your hard work and tactful planning you
always make my days brighter but you
really helped make this one better I'm
rooking forward to 2022 with my Aussie
thank you
um
the you know what was the difficult part
about planning that it was the
scheduling
um because it had to be decided very
quickly but uh yeah um first I thought
not everyone would participate that only
like maybe five six seven girls would
participate
uh haven't I tried to cover as many time
zones as possible and then more and more
Jordan had to move things around and
like oh maybe they put you there and
then they put you there but now I can
only do this time and now I'm having a
string of the line so I need to be there
and I'm okay then I'll move you here or
is this time for you okay then because
I'm moving you here I'm switching you
and you
yeah uh organizing the whole time
schedule is difficult also because last
minute uh good at was like I want to
join too and I'm like yay that's really
cool I thought I already finalized the
schedule but I'm glad you're joining too
now I'm gonna let you go after I made us
do it this way
[Laughter]
now that was very last minute um but I'm
happy that it ended up having everyone
joining I did not think everyone would
take their time in their busy busy
schedules and between their own
um streams that they already had planned
to still participate in this little
event I I really really am glad that
um even if it's last minute you know it
was the last minute organized event too
and gouda usually takes a little bit of
time
to get that info through to her so yeah
it's not her fault it's not her fault at
all I'm glad she joined
so thank you thank you thank you
yeah
on to a wonderful new year together
Felix salvation for the red super chat
let me get a a cough drop it's getting
rough now it's getting rough
no chat no
no no no no
[Music]
um
all right it's understandable like
honestly like there is so much going on
in our Discord every day there's so many
pings
[Music]
and that and this and that
um
uh would you like to participate in this
and that in this net and I need your
feedback on this net and this and that
so
um I also get overwhelmed and I think
gouda also gets overwhelmed by that and
it's it's I I can relate to it
[Music]
I often like when I wake up
I look at my phone and I have so many
notifications so I go through them but
I'm too tired to reply to them so I also
need some reminders as well sometimes
like Kiana could you please answer uh
about this this is quite urgent I'm like
okay sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry I
didn't mean to be so late
um
foreign
you think it's already the heat I need
to I needed to be let me check to the
oven to the oven
uh
196. okay let's go
[Music]
over here
thank you
[Music]
this is now a cooking stream
um uh
wait let me see my
um
[Music]
should it be like only one layer of foil
right my recipe doesn't say it I'm
guessing it's just like one layer and
then fork and then I put it in okay
okay the potatoes are super tiny though
[Music]
foreign
which side of the foil is up uh like
outside like there's a shiny side and
the matte side
does it matter
no okay
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
still here I'm surprised movie usually
follows me wherever I go but you want it
to sleep huh oh yeah I put the oh she's
smelling my hand I put the potatoes into
the oven I hope I did it right I stabbed
it with a knife several times
I stabbed the potato with a knife and
then I Threw It To The Ground no I threw
it into the oven
smoothie kept you guys company yeah I
did not use the glue gun should I have
used my glue gun
uh question why is it not okay to put
aluminum foil into a microwave but it's
okay to put it into the oven huh
it's kind of a weird logic I'm not
poisoning myself am I right here at the
episode
client because microwave was because
science okay
okay
I see yeah they have microwaves okay the
microwave has microwaves okay
okay
radiation or something cool story bro
cool story bro okay wait so uh in one
hour
okay so
and in uh 23 minutes after midnight my
potatoes should be done
how do I know it's done
did I poke it again
[Music]
I just rely on it
Small Potatoes should come out sooner
okay cool maybe at midnight then
okay let me try to read as many super
chats as possible until then uh Felix
Alvin thank you for the red super chat
mwah happy New Year Dental yeah my
chicken brain is blank due to really
messed up sleeping schedule yesterday
I will throw garlic in there I will
um so I have no idea what to say other
than please keep being our attention for
the next year and so so many years to
come I I hope I can do it as long as
possible Felix
um as long as also my own
Mental Health
who gives it and
um as long as it seems like you know I
wouldn't want to end it to add like a
really low point you know right so I
think you're supposed to end things when
there's still someone
successful I guess which is kind of
weird because but but still you wouldn't
want to end it when it's like going down
everything that is just kind of
depressing
um but yeah on the high notes but not
too high I want to enjoy it while it's
high
difficult but for now I'm fine and for
now I'm I'm I'm
looking into the future with a positive
mindset and with
um a motivated
heart
and with many many more plans you guys
know I need some I need to do some
things like concert at least once
um
there's many things that I still want to
do and but I just really hope that
you guys won't leave me until I get to
do those things you guys you guys need
to stay too
I need you guys I need someone to watch
my concert hmm
[Music]
so I feel like so I'm counting on
YouTube please thank you for your
support so you were so supportive thank
you so much for being so generous please
take care of yourself and have a Happy
New Year
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
happy New Year Kiana thank you for all
your hard work over the past year and
all the wonderful memories you and kfp
have given me like the Majestic Phoenix
you are you've read my life with your
kind and energetic personality your
laughter and even your fake angry tone
when you call us a little shits why
would you assume that's fake here's to
an amazing 2022 and plenty of years to
follow glory to kfbi yeah thank you
thank you
yeah but but but but don't underestimate
me and my anger so I realize 100 real
was not acting no no no no no
you thinking that way could get you into
the usual room again soon be careful be
careful
it's funny how people like it when they
say little [\h__\h]
it takes a special moment for me to say
it
yeah yeah
not everyone can be a little [\h__\h]
not everyone
happy New Year decibel thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you for the pinky thank
you so much
thank you for the right support
happy New Year attention and all of kfp
I wish everyone a peaceful Year and that
those of us that need to get our [\h__\h]
together
find a way to achieve the things we want
and let's go to the gym chickens
yes yes I guess I will join you guys to
motivate you guys today
[Music]
I that is that is one of the things I
need to do this year going to the gym
at least once and that would already be
an accomplishment
okay let's work hard hirona
oh also I'm surprised you didn't say
let's go to Brazil you said let's go to
the gym or maybe we could go to a gym in
Brazil
foreign
two birds of one stone
[Music]
College
thank you for the pinky yeah how willing
are you to try new foods that you find
strange let's say you're visiting Bay
and she tells you that she's taking you
out to have some kangaroo steak would
you eat it to see if you liked it
interesting question
um
I heard it's like chicken I think or was
that was that crocodile
um
why did she asking me to do that
[Music]
um
I'm genuinely someone who doesn't really
like to try things that I haven't tried
yet in German we say
that's listening uh what the farmer
doesn't know he won't eat
because apparently people on the
countryside are very picky about it also
no no no no no no we should stay up with
us in soon
[Music]
um
but oh man if Bales insists on it and
really says it's really really good I
guess I could give it a try but under
the high risk that by me already feeling
weird about it my brain telling myself
it's not tasty even even if it would be
like sometimes I I sabotage myself
uh yeah and then it tastes disgusting to
me even though it's probably good
it tastes good actually I I guess so
foreign
[Music]
for example like in Austria
um some people eat like labica SEMA with
horse meat libertad salmon is like a
snack that I like to eat a lot but not
with horse meat I eat the different
version of it
um but I can't really I don't really
like the thought of eating horse meat
because it's just to me horses are for
me personally not something that I like
like people should eat like from from
like I was raised uh in a way that horse
meat was not considered something to eat
but I know in many other countries it's
pretty normal and also in Japan like
horse Sashimi which is a basashi is
something very um
fancy and I tried it before
um
but yeah I just I just something that I
consider as a pet or or it's not
something to be eaten I feel really bad
about eating and my I think my brain
will automatically sabotage my taste
buds to tell me it's disgusting
[Music]
foreign
so with a kangaroo it's like I mean I
don't really have a close connection
with kangaroos because there are no
kangaroos in Austria it's our t-shirts
say that you can get in tourist shops
like for real
uh I'll have much of a connection with
them but still I would feel weird about
eating them
um
yeah I don't know
yeah we have like if you go to a tourist
shop
that sells like any kind of souvenirs in
Austria there's always t-shirts that say
there's like uh there's t-shirts that
have like a a kangaroo on it a
silhouette of a kangaroo and then it's
like crossed out it's like no kangaroos
yeah
yep yep
all right Ghana thank you for the pinky
happy New Years Tanger love you Happy
New Year
I love you too thank you please continue
supporting me in the new year as well
Dominique Duncan
and there's a Korean one
[Music]
um
happy New Year to you good and Advent uh
uh
[Music]
I think it means you are always cheering
for me thank you
Happy New Year to you um
[Music]
I said that before I think
thank you
soon thank you thank you for the pinky
thank you Happy New Year Tai Chi Happy
New Year I think that means uh was it
something koala
um
uh uh
I recognize that thanks to the kanji
and thank you for the pinky hey boom
thank you for the red super chat happy
New Year oh comes I need a Happy New
Year to you too yay
thank you for supporting me and thank
you for joining kfp bong thank you I
hope you're having a great time and
enjoying yourself here yes have lots of
fun next year too okay
night star dancing but I forgot to keep
on a kiss
thank you
soon
you see them dying because it was too
cute
no way that was the wrong language no no
no no no
oh in Korean please
[Music]
red brick Oh
yeah everyone watch out there's a
there's a brick falling from the sky
affiana
[Music]
thank you
I think
I think is that cool thank you for the
pinky pinky Ohio because I must tend to
happy New Year Happy New Year to you too
welcome to the future thank you for the
support I appreciate it
[Music]
enjoyed at the workplace
foreign
[Music]
I think
thank you thank you
thank you for the memberships guys thank
you thank you thank you
[Music]
do it now
what was it the membership thingy was
about the membership that might have
been about my member the memberships
when the memberships kept flooding in
thank you Daisy my love to you
thank you for being so sweet and loyal
back soon
foreign
[Music]
for this
oh what did I do
[Music]
yeah the one from the clip review or the
one from the clip in the clip reveal
I am confused
but thank you
was it again about the green tide oh
well maybe it was again dead
yeah that was funny
that was a day that went into the
history books of KFC
and Counting chickens
happy circuits
and great human dance
is
random collusion thank you for the pinky
am I doing it right
you are definitely not doing it wrong
I'll tell you that
[Music]
for the pinky and your love and support
brother
con thank you for the red super chat oh
hello ostrich
I'm a phoenix for okay
[Music]
um
thanks for a great year full of happy
and emotional memories I'm looking
forward to the next one cheers to your
continued success and happiness thanks
for all you do for us and have fun for
all your hard work see after seven and a
half hours I am losing my ability to
speak I probably need a pork
I wonder how much more we have left
I hope you will subscribe
your dreams come true the way you want
them to um
I wish you all the best happy New Year
thank you for all the support thank you
soon never call me ostrich again though
if you want to stay out of the usual
room
[Music]
rifle bucket thank you for the pinky
there goes AMA being a supportive Hiram
protagonist seriously though you all
have done wonderfully so far and looking
forward to what the future holds if that
was when I played the Army Club I think
she's like that for Lindy but yeah
everyone in home if is necessary to make
myth to one of these now
thank you for everybody who protects Us
by watching our streams and supports us
thank you so much for the love
the Sinister eyes
with a pinky we all know you didn't
really burn your finger the glue gun had
low self-esteem that is how it is Tanaka
you get me of course I didn't burn my
finger on such a ridiculous
thing now
inconceivable
that is so true
you get me
you know me too long
thank you
for the pink Y and there's a long Korean
text to it
um
here yay so cute
I'm I'm really um getting
uh how to say this Korean Google
translate voice is really growing on me
thank you so much no no one comes at me
now please watch my streams anytime you
feel like it which is every day please
thank you five hours ago no that was
from yesterday
that was actually from yesterday
um not today yesterday on this this
stream
thank you thank you thank you please
continue supporting me okay
nice Gordon ramsayan Erebus thank you
for the pinky thanks for organizing the
karaoke relay welcome in 2022 with all
of Ian in American felt really special
um events like this have done a lot to
make following holy and such a wonderful
experience and your contribution can't
be overstated let's go 2022. yes I feel
like you know we might have lost out on
the more like a special alone time with
you guys and me but I think that's okay
I mean look at now now we have a lot of
alone time so what the hell in exchange
for some special moments with all of the
Yen members I think it was worth it and
[Music]
um
and without that what would we have had
nothing like only solo streams nothing
special from uh like organized by
the the management but ultimate Kingo
would have just been released like that
so I think it was good that we did that
last minute we celebrated as a community
yeah yeah yeah yeah I felt that too
um
[Music]
okay
cruise I will end it here I'll read your
stupid chat uh ASAP
next wait no wait almost done with the
clip review let me finish those I see
the end I see the end it's only a couple
more
then we can be done with those so Chris
says in a red Super Chat first bread of
the year I really admire all all your
hard work and endless entertainment
you've been giving us this last year
you've given us this last year may this
new year be even better I know you'll
get uh to do another life performance
like you didn't Google me and I want to
be there to cheerful you love you thank
you well you sent an USC so I'm I'm
guessing you're probably from
somewhere in n a
well I think there's a high chance that
will be at some conventions again in the
following year so make sure to be there
yeah you should be there I think it was
really a special experience to have a
whole life at these conventions and it's
also a great opportunity to meet other
reachable fans and connect with them as
we've heard other people greatly
benefited from that so I think you
should do that too you will okay nice so
it's a promise then
um
mwah thank you for your support
let's have lots of special memories
thank you for the red super chat
happy New Year
um
[Music]
this time
one more
time questions
foreign
[Music]
yeah it sounds like a fun time so it's
like a fun group
I'm at me crony and yeah
um
also that that crunchy noise was my um
the remains of my cough drop
um
where can we watch um
uh I wonder if it's gonna still be the
uh same no they keep on Switching the
audit
wait let me see him
[Music]
oh this should be it
this should be it uh yeah they have a
they seem to have a
um
a slot for every different segment so
it's not like 12 hours 12 hours but it's
like a different stream for each segment
um this is the one that I'll be in the
one that I just posted
it's in wait what does it say
[Music]
oh wait they did something in the whole
live schedule website
it is not
it is only like two streams or so
but in the whole life schedule website
the official one
it's several different streams I think
the management must have like put that
those on there manually then
okay okay well I'm not on there in 11
minutes I'm gonna be there a little bit
later
I say okay now okay now I see it it was
confusing because in in the schedule
it's like so many different streams
um
two 12-hour streams apparently yeah
apparently the new one is starting in a
little bit so okay then I'll finish my
potatoes and I pray to God that they
turn out good I'm gonna cut some
schnitzel now
um
for my sauce for my sour cream sauce I
guess yeah thank you everybody
I hope everyone had some fun watching me
draw a little piece of art now through
myself as a French girl wee-wee bucket
oh see that's what I should have put him
to my hand a baguette
[Laughter]
chives chives
chives
yeah hope it was so open with someone
entertaining I'll see you guys next week
with uh some exciting things
and my schedule will come out tomorrow
um
oh
hmm
watch that wink and quotes that wink
next week
no stream tomorrow no no no no no no no
no no no no wait today's Sunday right
yeah no stranger
free record holder oh not yet no no no
no we're working on that
um
I'm
we we need to prepare some special it
will be this this uh one will be
pre-recorded because the person that I'm
getting into my studio uh I don't want
to keep that person up for so long uh
because it starts the stream usually
starts at 11 PM jst we don't want that
we are pre-recording it but that has
nothing to do with my wink that has
nothing to do with that
anyway and Jose Alfredo thank you
oh I see myself
oh yeah and uh look out for the Revival
of the clip review stream archive should
be
sometime soon
bye bye bye bye
[Music]
no I won't edit it again I will risk it
and see what happens
uh I think it should be fine I'll I'll I
might edit it again after I gave some
people the chance to watch the archive
and then maybe I'll after one or two
days I'll edit it again
it's waiting for too long
I noticed some people waiting for the
archive so oh wait there's no bgm here
oops
I decided like
um like I can already see if it got like
like marked by anything
and uh nope there's
so far uh
let me check again
foreign
[Music]
this stream seems to have some issues
though for whatever reason
[Music]
what did I do was it the boobs
that well I'll check up on that bye bye
[Music]