he
[music]
JA
T
DET
[music]
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Tawa
Congratulations
The white team is all there, so it's displayed.
Are you in the display room?
Sleep
Yes, it's fine, my niece is fine.
Good, good, good
Oh, I wonder if everyone is here, let's gather together.
Ah, let's gather, let's gather, let's gather, let's gather, let's gather, let's gather
Hahaha, yeah, teacher, no teacher, teacher
I'm not a teacher at all.
Yes, I just happened to be here.
Is everyone here? Is everyone there?
It's fine properly
I'm fine, thank you for attending.
Please take it, okay, I'll go then.
Eiroha-chan, I’m going from A of the white group.
I'm hungry. Please.
Masuhai Hellobo Imamasu
Thank you very much for your support.
Kanata-san, who is here most of the time?
Yes, it's good.
Well done Mui-chan yesaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Lume-chan
Yeah yeah yeah
[music]
Nainai tomeyou
Kaikai ne Kisoku Sou Ame
Chanmeamechan will be here. Thank you.
Please
Yes, I'm here. Let's go home.
[music]
Yes, thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you, this member is on the phone.
These are the people who break up and become A. Yes, yes.
Then B's Weather Choco Sensei Wow!
Azusa is Kokiyaki
I want to eat Suzuki, please.
Captain, hello, I'm the captain. Hello halo ha.
Hello it fight yay yay
Yeah yeah
circle
Darrin yes yes yes
[music]
Yes yes yes
Yes, yes, let's work hard on the flow-up
Look at me
I was like, uh, can I do this here too?
I wonder if I should go.I should go.
I thought
First of all, today I'm going to talk to Nee-chan.
I'm sorry that I fell into the tracks a little.
Sorry for the inconvenience, but I'm sorry.
Did you come to let me know?
Nema Raden-chan said yes.
We also want to cover the text a little bit.
I think so, thank you very much.
I beg of you
I have no choice but to try harder. I feel like I'm going to have a hard time.
So, let's go Holomen hunting.
Raden-chan appears, but that's me.
I'll just take your place.
I look forward to your continued support as a hunter.
And then, what will happen in the match against Maki?
By the way, I guess that's right. What happens when you're in a hurry?
I'm looking forward to seeing you wandering around alone.
I guess it's all a battle to see if someone will come.
No, I want to see him working hard alone.
Maybe he's wandering around and taking everyone's cameras.
I can't help but hit and hit
There's a spy here, a spy.
What's the truth? It looks like it's so sweet
Teru
or
I have a baby, go away
This is in the waiting room of the white team.This is the classroom.
So now everyone is waiting. Yes, I like competitions.
I wonder who is here
But it looks like everyone is gathered together.
It was good, it was good, it was good, it was good
It's good, it's good, I'm glad everyone gathered together
Oh, there's a signboard, there's a signboard.
I'm not sure where to put this.
I can't put it there to use it for support.
I can't leave a space to use for support.
[music]
Things like this and things like this
Is it there?
How to use it
It's like holding a sign with both hands.
What to do
The raft
Everyone who came to play polo came.
[music]
A little spot where the scout group is coming.
Shall we go?
etc.
What does redness look like?
now
[music]
Become
I can hear the sounds of hitting and hitting from everywhere.
of practice
[music]
The main jump practice was also done by Rigro.
They were having a pretty rough time with each other.
All
ah
You're holding a signboard in your left hand.
I can't take it anymore, but all day today
There may be a sign
I can't take something that isn't there.
I really can't take it anymore, I can't take it anymore
It's not just good, it's true, it's bad
But no matter what you look at, everyone's a signboard
Fixed too seriously
I wonder if it's okay to hold it in a competition?
It's probably easy to reset your inventory.
I think
Maybe all the time you're infected
The knowledge of the left hand
As expected of one of the creators of Minecraft
It really is like that again I'll do my best to back it up
hand
I'll do my best as a ma-baku.
As expected, he can teach you anything.
I wonder if the author didn't attack me.
No, no, no, it's true.
It's so true, it's so true
Is it true that it was made by Minecraft?
mosquito
[music]
That's amazing, what's next?
Ru
tree
But you know, but I don't understand.
Well, we don't know much about cameras.
But I can hear it.
[music]
Sounds like a senior to me
well
I can't hear it
I thought I'd call you Tajaso.
I ask all of you to
[music]
Masumija
It's red from
Yo
Hey buddy, over there, over there
Rumasu is here, it's Chantora
dodge
Yo Mel fell directly
Now fall directly
It seems like it's okay to say it because of it.
le sa le
Sa-san is a genius again this year. He really stands out.
Out
In line
white
Come and do your best. Come with me here with your mom.
Let's go here. What's next?
Is that what you were doing? So yes.
Next, everyone from the white group, please enter.
It came, it came, it came, it came.
Ta
[music]
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here
yes
[music]
Yes, it's the white group of unity, that's good.
Finally, that yellow group called me.
May I
Do your best, it's okay Kashiri-chan
I'm hiding, and you're doing it, too.
Let's mix it up, there's something wrong here, wait.
Self
Length This Ruto camera must have been prepared for what
They're fighting so hard
They are fighting.
hey
white
It's like I have a little bit and a half.
[music]
But only Nanakashi-chan has a pink sign
I have
The yellow board is a book, so it was put together over there.
yellow
It's a board book. I wish there wasn't a white signboard.
Don't even hold a sign
Well, first of all, Hololive Dai.
I would like Mr. Inosa of the Sports Festival to give a greeting for the tournament.
That's all, everyone.
hello
Hello, it's amazing everyone gathered here.
Thank you very much for your busy work.
Seniors and juniors really helped each other until today.
I think he encouraged me in practice as well.
Well, today is the actual day, so everyone's strength is needed.
Let's give it our all and get the victory.
I hope to receive it first.
Everyone should have fun and aim to win.
So, everyone, please enjoy!
Thank you very much for your help today.
I wish you all the best
Masu
Please yes thank you yes
Next, from Mr. Yago, president of Cover Co., Ltd.
I have received a message
As always, please see here
Please, please watch the live movie.
Thank you everyone for your hard work. Kaba Company
I am the representative of the athletic meet.For example,
It's the neck
hey
Until today
Thank you very much for your hard work in preparing
At today's sports day, we cooperated with each other.
Encourage each other and fight bravely until the end
Thank you very much.
Thank you to all our practice members till today.
Please pay attention to and support his efforts.
I would appreciate it if you could give me this gig.
All members, be careful not to get injured.
Please put it on.That's it for my opening remarks.
I will take it as
Mecho-sensei, no, I didn't even get injured.
That was a wonderful message, Yuu.
It was good, it was good
hey
Mite sensei is leaving. See you later.
Good luck! Good luck!
Pleasezaka is a good player
teacher's house
Please, please, please
Please do it now
[laughter]
keep it up
No, please please
vinegar
Thank you very much.
My ears are weird at the end
Become
difference
Mr. White
It's okay, it's okay
Please reach the top of
[applause]
[music]
[laughter]
A lotus flower, a lotus flower, a lotus flower, a lotus flower,
It's so good, it's so good
Nete-sensei, I hope you can do your best.
keep it up
Good luck, then you can ask the players to do it.
Is that okay?
Yes, please
Mr. Masu, all of us players are Hololive
Sportsmanship as a member
I use Hijack Sensei Dodo Fighting.
Kaikaie April 4, 2023 Red team representative virtue
What is the white team representative ah yellow team white spells yay
Yeah
[applause]
Thank you.
It's okay thank you
I'll post it here from here.
No, thank you from here.
I got it
of
in
Well then, everyone
[music]
Mr. Miss.
Excuse me for asking, white group member 7
Voice of the white group fugitive is group member channel contestant
Thank you for your channel.
Sound quality of real sports day
and Realme's
The sound quality is a bit beaty, but it feels real.
Not yet because of that
Is there a contestant contestant channel?
Chara-tai-ni-net-mei-hunting
Only the first round of Hunting
Only those who enter are like that, right? Well, it's the white group.
I'm going to the contestant's channel, so uh...
chan kaela nelisa yes
Okay
[music]
Good luck! Good luck!
Please pre team fight player
Channel Yai Let's Gogba
Oh, try your best, try your best, try your best
Good Luck Good Luck Good Luck
completely
That
It's gray
[music]
In Japanese, that's the third character, right?
Yes, it's Kara.
Good and cool
I speak English well
We were able to go. Were all three of us able to go too?
Is it okay to be a fugitive? This is no good, so what do you think?
I wonder if we're infected or if we're the white group.
The White group will be the first to see Hunter.
I look like a hunter, so I'll support you like a hunter.
Are you going to go see it? Everything is fine except for that meba.
It's okay to support others, not to be runaways.
It's okay, what group will the fugitives start from now on?
I'm sure there will be an announcement
Is there an announcement?
Check whether it is kana or not
Everyone except now degozaru hunter team?2
So maybe we're different too.
Since it's not the hunter team, it's hunter team.
Does Mu refer to the three hunters?
Or I'm sure he'll stab that white group.
Which frame are you pointing at? This is me.
At the beginning of the game, write red.
Red Other than that, I am a fugitive once.
This is the entry
It's great that you can go to the other side without it.
You can press this.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
Nevermind yeah yeah
Entry possible
I'm not sure if I can catch anything.
Well, I had already entered.
There's no me
I have already entered this.
Maybe it's better to enter
I don't care.
I see.In the beginning, it was the power of God.
It's okay if you don't press Ruppai Aja.
Yeah, okay.
Sorry for interrupting Sade's announcement.
Itadakimasukaiha-san Roboco-sanki
Rain, Heaven, Pear, Yuchoko
San Azuki San Hae White group contestant
Please to the channel person on the contrary.
This is the opposite of life moving.
Oh, maybe it's the other way around. Everyone is running away now.
It seems that the runner who is not from the sky is moving.
The person has now moved to my channel.
Is it okay?
I wonder if this is what it is.
Hello hello hello hello aekocchi
That's right. It's a competition where everyone is right.
This is probably the white group.
A competition
The fugitive running away is here.
I guess it's a channel
It's difficult, it's difficult today.
It's difficult today. I wanted to do this difficult exercise.
Number 1
It looks like this is the lowest one.
The flow of movement is
I don't understand
The thing I couldn't do was the one I couldn't do the most.
It's true that if you overcome this and that, you can do it.
Okay, I see, I understand perfectly now.
If anything
Please wait.
The thing is, at first the red team was the hunter and the white team was the hunter.
Everyone runs away yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to everyone
Yes, yes, that means we're all competitors.
It looks like it's sleeping
When it was time for the remaining white group to hunt,
Could it be possible that he is an infected person? Probably so.
is
hey
difficult
[music]
this
Eri is only a hunter
It's fine
[music]
It seems like it's only Hunter who seems to be the best.
Gozaru yeah yeah
[music]
[laughter]
O
[music]
picture
Which one should I play?
In this case, we are the ones chasing and running away.
The one who runs away, the one who runs away, running away, oh oh oh
Well, I don't mind, I'm a fugitive from another team.
Fugitive is probably set automatically.
It's so cool that it's so funny
That question comes up, for example.
The people in the red team were the hunters, and the people in the white team were the hunters.
We're being targeted so we run away
Oh, ok, oh, it's like clicking.
I'm going to get caught with a rope, so even if I get caught, I'll give it my all.
I feel like I want to run away and it's okay.
That's right, you'll be punished.
I'm going to Korea because I'm going to be thrown in.
Yeah, I'm going to South Korea and I can't leave.
Surprisingly, behind the cage is a hiding place.
Yes, I'm a bit anti.
There's a hole you can go through, on the contrary.
I'm going to go to the wide side opposite the cage on my cat's side.
There's no one behind it
I see it.
I wonder if it's the same behind this?
It's easy to become a staff member.
I wonder what that text is?
I'm watching the channel and it's the 7th white group fugitive.
I'm a contestant, so I'm in the second tier.
I guess I should go, Esaka-chan.
Well, my name wasn't called and I was a contestant.
That's right, that's why it's a hunting battle.
The one where both people in the second game went over there.
I was wondering if it might be okay.
Yes, there is that guy.
I was called, but I probably didn't get it through.
That's how it is for you, right?
Oh, I see. Yes, yes, yes, something like that.
I think it's a bit like that.
Let's try it, please tell the announcer.
Thank you for this Yes Asoka Ramen
I have my share of it, so that's true.
That's why he was called earlier, I guess.
There is still a chance that Laden will join.
I wonder if it's progressing, maybe that's it
I feel that way.
Is it really that kind of thing?
Only non-hunters can use this channel now.
I have to be there
Kanokoto Poie was flying around.
road
A god who has the power of a real god.
You have power, God.
Let's just listen to it first
Thank you very much.
Is it okay?
I wonder what it will be like this time.
I wasn't listening to what was going on, now that I think about it...
I've been practicing how to play some competitions.
That's right, that's the flow of the whole episode.
Apparently there isn't any material. Come to think of it, there wasn't any.
I'm probably reading materials like that right now.
I think you can probably assemble either Gozaru.
Other teams other than the players are listed.
Competitors
Write ahdochidadochhi confusion
pounding pounding
[laughter]
But the staff is inputting information.
I wonder if my stomach will come back exhausted?
Clack clack
I wonder which one it will be.Today, everyone.
It's a bit of a long road, so I haven't quite planned it yet.
It's around 9 o'clock, but maybe I'll press it.
There is also an atmosphere of
There's an atmosphere. There's a bit of an atmosphere.
The atmosphere is a little timid and I'm saving up for a break.
But I'm also hungry, so let's eat
Yes, let's take it easy. Yes, it's long.
Karanekara
This is also the real pleasure of sports day, right?
That's right, the main point of garbage is difficult garbage.
It's trash like that.
No difference
I think it's a book called Darouten.
There's no real thrill, it's a real thrill
That's why it's called Real Thrill.
Ah, the answer came in this book.
real real thrill real
Thrill, thrill, great words
In the first place, it's a channel, so now
It looks like it's in its current form.
No, it's true. When this happens for the second time, next time.
The more the three challengers are facing me, the better.
Does diagonal mean that insects are fine?
No, no, no, no, there aren't 7 people.
We are 1, right? There are 9 people who are not around 88 people.
9 people
It's not that big of a deal.
Thank you, no, thank you
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your reply.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, okay, but the first game, the first game is red.
At first, everyone has to run away.
I'm sure it's certain, yeah yeah
That’s true, that’s true, what will happen?
We're on separate channels, but we're doing it together.
rutte voice
Just starting
suddenly
Coming day
Run away, run away, run away, run away
Look around the English members
Let's protect it
Let's protect the English members, wait.
Let's protect the English members!
Hide at the back where you can't be seen
I can't wait
Fa
[music]
If you don't protect me, it's a prison where I'm being pushed back.
I'm not an anti either.
I hate to protect my comrades
[music]
Kachan
Chachan will change, change
14 That kind of thing
be
in
Mistake
Who is the perfect person to go with a score of 9 or less?
Because the perfect person is a squid
I'm not going in, I'm a squid, so I'm going in. I'm going in.
Fits 149cm.
say
I'm 149cm tall
[music]
On the other hand, some small people have already run away.
Be confident without
I'll walk freely, I'll protect you when there's no one around
hand
[music]
I don't know.
But I don't know, but I got caught instead.
Is it okay to be a little disappointed?
No one will come, so it's a good thing.
I'm looking forward to it, but someone please catch me.
Chan
At that moment, I said I could go.Who said I could go?
Or I can go.Who is it that I can go, Chan-chan, me?
I can go, you can catch me, hey
Too many points
do not have
No, it was murder, but go here.
Before I look, please help me, who's talking about me?
Catch me too
Yo it's over
I was like, I wonder who it was.
It's true that Anya was different in some way.
Like
That's an incredibly awkward noise.
Awkward crackling
Nedadede Hunter White Group Hunter is voice
Please move to chat
There are 6 people in total, so there are 6 people in total.
It says, ``It's true, so go ahead.''
Hey there, I'm going.
Wait a minute, that's not the name here, sorry.
I will do it
The 6th group is now talking to all the fugitives of Konia-gumi.
Everyone, please join the white group AB voice chat.
Please move
Masu
[music]
Harimasu
I feel like I'm rooting for you, okay?
I wonder if Kaela-san was there too.
It's so blue and nice
I've done it without fail.
So I guess I should just sit in my seat.
That's right, let's do this.
Is it okay for people who have been arrested to be like this?
No, he was arrested. He's still under arrest. Yes, he's still under arrest.
I can't get out, I can't get out, it's true
I'm getting arrested, it's a lie, it's a game
After it's over, there's probably someone in the middle of the game.
Korea becomes
It's a failure. It's true. I haven't been able to break out of jail.
You can't jailbreak
Okay, I can't do it. I can't do it. It's Korea.
Yoyoyoyoyoyo
Yoyoyo
Oh and Kia-chan are there too.
I might not be able to get out until it starts.
Is it okay if I watch it? Shall I take a photo? Country
It's a country, it's a country, it's a country, it's Korea.
Yo
Thank you, Korea, where you can take photos of Korea.
It's hell, your face is chained to the grass.
Niremechaa here here here here here here
That's pretty good That's good That's good
is
I'll take it, I'll take it.
The reset jailbreak was successful and I finally escaped the jailbreak.
The white hunter finally came out.
Time to work hard
Let's support Wanka, let's support it, let's support it
I'll put it on white then, it's Korea.
picture
Thank you, I'll paste it properly.
It feels so gentle
I feel like I should show it to Na-san, it's the best.
It's a shot, wait a minute.
Wait a moment before downloading
Where are the Korean photos?
Yes, it's true
It's really, really sill
But it's so close that I really love it
It's a distance
It became
Yes, it's Korea, it's prison.
I read it. I escaped from jail.
Wow, the escape was a success, yo everyone.
I'm entering. Yeah, I'm entering.
It's infected, it's infected, it's infected.
It's spacious, isn't it?
The infection was actually created by this infection seat mat.
But apparently it's like that.
Okay, but in the end, I want to think about it now, there are only 6 people.
Look at Ndogabatte.
Human beings are too wide. 1 person 1 block 1
There's a block
It's really big here.
There's plenty of room! It's so spacious.
I'm sure you can see the whole thing
feels good
Yay!
[music]
Ta
I wanted to make this ruins near Korea.
Yes, it is true in Korea.
No, it's definitely dangerous so I made it myself.
Now that I'm in danger of going to the yellow team.
It's been kind of fluffy for a while now.
Are you okay? I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
I'm back, welcome home
I went back and had an interview.
Yes, it seems like he went to the second game as well.
I see, I see.
I have interviewed
tea
[laughter]
[music]
Are you okay
I'm just confused, it's okay
It's okay, it'll be okay, it'll be okay
It's okay, somehow it's okay. Yeah, I was worried.
But judging from the way you're talking now, how much longer?
I thought you were talking so funny.
But seriously, it was blowing a lot, it was blurry.
It was blowing, it was blowing
Let's do something with our seniors who are walking around.
Let's go let's go let's go
[music]
team white team white team
We are team white, white, and team pigeon.
Does that mean he's not a fugitive? Yes, that's right.
Dekotoza
Yeah, I want to run away, I want to run away, I want to run away.
It's okay, I can run away next time, so yeah, that's right.
Please wait a moment until the next escape.The next escape.
to
[music]
You look so well behaved, you look so well behaved.
I guess that's because they're a good team.
That's right, everyone was happy, and the White team was the best.
This one was lined up the most beautifully.
Looks like they were lined up beautifully like our colors.
Yes, it's as clear as our white color
Clear, clear, clear, white
In Kura White Kura
White clear is definitely clear.
But still, resident toy
There is a gathering
karawhitewhitea
Do your best and keep your heart pounding
Good luck, what's coming? What's the theme?
Debut from 2
222 This is quite recent.
Don't put phlox in, just barely put in lock.
That's right, 21 years.
Is it winter?
Even the phlox was caught though.
I was really running away from that live show.
There are English 2nd and 3rd generation students too.
3rd season of Oasoaja ID
2020 different Pol I see, a bit
It's 2020, yes, it's the summer of 2020.
This is a name that's easy to pick.
Even if you know it's useless to stop, it's hard to find
It's tough, you have to prepare yourself.
Hey, do your best, do your best, Mouko Daiko-san.
The Hachamato Festival is being conveyed with ease.
Let's see you
You will feel regretful.
But what did you want to catch?
I feel like I'm being chased.
No, I'm happy. It's a little bouncy.
Bob, I'm sure there's someone else at all.
It's not going away, it's not guaranteed, it's getting cheaper
Come on, are you okay? Is this or that okay? It's okay.
Capture everyone regardless.
If you catch 3 people, you'll probably get at least 1 bob.
I have a short bob
There's another hair there, go, go, go, where is it?
It's not really quiet all of a sudden
He's gone. Why is it so quiet?
That's what everyone did just now
Even though we were chatting, Gura-chan caught a fish too.
I'm saying that
Nice, maybe this will stick in one place
I think Holo is planning a strategy.
What kids think of holo kids
I'm saying it was good, but I can't go in.
Well, I'm not a kid, Hoki.
Even if I don't want to, I feel like I'm going to go in there, so I don't want kids.
I'm not going to get into one, it's me, Akuo.
I'm sure that's not the case.
I'm telling you it's true Anya's scratches
ah
No, it's not my sister. It was my sister.
Hey there, I'm curious about this. I'm curious about this.
I'll see, but I wonder if he'll enter the slope.
Janai-chan isn't tough.
It's a frame for women with big breasts and scratches.
That's what I meant when I said that.
If you say so, I'll put flowers in it.
I'm sorry, I have no choice but to run away. I have no choice but to run away.
It's okay if we all run away, right? Let's run away.
That me and the group
Let's catch it, catch it, catch it.
Please catch them all already, everyone already.
If you don't know what to put in, just put them all in.
If you ask me
Good, good, good
Conclusion
Quite
subject
[music]
Funny so-and-so who is not a common knowledge
think
[music]
Sorry for the inconvenience. Thank you for explaining.
So Gura-chan might be angry, but
Because it was in there.
Enter
What will happen to everyone when it comes to kids?
It's definitely Todoroki, not Kakonokasan or anything.
It looks like it's going to get in. I think it's a scratch.
It's probably tough for Michan.
I can see a lot of girls who look like cats
Hello, I definitely want to know the answer.
Only the senior from earlier
At the end of the seaweed, it's time for a bar.
It was Tayo or it was the fastest.
Me-senpai was totally in it, and he was totally taken in by it.
That's right. That's right.
Nanakarisa-chan looks like that same family member.
I feel like something is wrong.
I couldn't get it, so I was able to secure it that way.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I guess that's why you care, cute.
It's okay, I'm glad. It was difficult.
It was a bit more difficult than practice, at all.
There's not enough practice, there's no problem, there's no problem, there's no practice
That's because the table is too easy.
Who's with that leader?
It's okay, Chiara will cover it for you.
Are you okay
I'm looking forward to it, but you're also going to have a hard time.
It's okay for you, everyone, I'll let everyone in.
I'm going to put it in because it's going from one side to the other.
All the people who found it
I'll put it in, so please use your grip strength.
It seems like it's moving, it's moving, it's moving.
I will
mosquito
Welcome everyone.
Please go to the competition voice chat.
Two people who are not runaways
It became clear
Hey guys, yeah
Yeah, Senpai, for some reason we're just the two of us.
Natteame-senpai is probably a fugitive who ran away, so this is it.
Is it okay to use the contestant channel from earlier?
Yeah yeah yeah o
It's so relaxing
hey
[music]
The shift was off, the shift was off, the shift was off, the shift was off, the shift was off.
Okay, it's done, it's not a problem.
Shokakatan is my 5th favorite at first sight.
REM A BLEM Look, look, look.
Please, look, look at this poor person.
This is how I feel now
Dee
What is this? Amazing.
Amazing, I couldn't find it, it was buried.
So what kind of situation do you want to go to?
Just open the door and say hello
When I close it, the door is closed inside.
If you do this right in front of the door, it will be very easy to enter.
That's great, that's amazing.
I'm in over my head
It has a nice earthy scent.
It smells like earth, of course.
It stinks
Rudo
say
Hurry, get angry
I'm sorry, Kire-chan and Yaba-kun.
A little girl who is trying to protect me
Go against it, go against it, go against it
too close contact
Eh, just now you're on the side.
It was so cute. So cute.
Stand up, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it.
That's it, that's it
So cute, so cute
Neiko will continue to sell cushions as is.
Yes, I can do it. This is really good.
I'm not saying it's cute, either.
Very cute head
Kuru Hunter was forcibly terminated.
Yellow Yellow Yellow
Yellow, just run away.
Let's run away. Let's run away. Do your best.
Come on, I'll do my best, try my best to run away.
Do your best and run away, Ranran.
Yoshi, I want to go to Korea, but I can't.
No, no, only fugitives, only fugitives.
touch
Oh, touch the fugitive, touch the fugitive, touch the fugitive.
Please enter even if you are in the tree.
Maybe it's already entered.
That's not true
Run away, run away, run away
Why don't you run away?
202 This is already
[music]
This is so hard, so hard.
nice nice
Very
Something like that
I did it
He's fresh, let's go to his side.
is
If you want to appeal to your motivation,
Even if you just made a fushide, keep your eyes open.
Hey, don't even look at me, I'm a newbie
is
terrible
[music]
16 Escape
More
Hmm
Sweet potato
If you're over 40, catch me.
I was totally fooled.
Tanaka waited a moment and caught it.
Butte
158 I'm sorry
Lay it down and hide it
hand
Chu
[applause]
[laughter]
in charge
What do you mean by that?
Jako
Catch Namo
[music]
Tateru
Well then, I'll give it to you about three times.
It's not crazy, it's fun, but it's neat.
It's not that it didn't happen, it's Chu.
do
people who have failed a lot
I'm sorry
Kanoiga-san, who is awfully neat, is not neat.
Even the cries of waddlers are clear now.
Monna
Re
It's clear that there are complaints in various places.
I'm getting more and more dissatisfied.
Nice nice, I didn't catch it, I caught it.
There wasn't.
I don't want to be so arrogant, but A-chan is definitely
I'm a member, I'm a member, I'm a member.
I ran away.
I have it. What should I do with it? It's cute.
It's scary, it's pure, you'll never do it
Well, it's definitely neat, that's great, just run away
You are so cute, Iroha-chan
You have to run away, right?
Don't think it'll bother you
It was a really strong yellow color.
Apesu was amazing, this was great too.
The leader wasn't neat, he ran away again.
Run away one more time, you've made an entry.
Everyone did this.
[music]
Lala is running away
Let's go escape
Wow
When I was a Jo-onee-san, I was called the leader.
That's right, the older sister is a sexy woman.
I wanted to be chosen no matter what.
Don't say anything lonely
It's true that my height wasn't even selected.
That's true, but please don't misunderstand me.
Tako is wrong because Polka misunderstood me.
Because I was doing it, I was able to go a little closer.
The cage is really small, that's for sure.
Go back, it's already been caught.
Then you can't run away during the game.
The cat
Hunter Yeah, I'll have to wait until the next game starts.
The rest such as Yanesou
You have to do your best and run away, next Mio-senpai.
No, who thinks it's going to be Jimio next?
I wonder if it's like that.
Is that so? Even if it's true, change it.
Kururu, there's a possibility that it's completely different. Please protect me.
I want it though
Please protect me.
If you do it like this because I want it, it'll be fine.
I want to be protected.
[music]
hey
O shoes
shoes
All my shoes are tight
Wow, this is disgusting. This is definitely the place.
Let's have a little drink next to Xiontepa
It's disgusting
But somehow
And everyone is buried
circle
It's so cute that I can't help but stare at it.
It's so cute standing side by side
Cute, someone please come stand next to me
I've become a [ __ ].
Start again, start again, start again
Oh yeah yeah okay
O
Okay okay okay okay okay
Ok ok ok ok
Oh, it doesn't matter at all, but Subaru-senpai.
My nipples are gone, how disgusting
Tel
Yeah, it's gone, why bother chatting with me?
Words like how many nipples does Subaru-senpai have?
I heard that there are 2. As expected, there are other than 2.
No, I don't think birds are eggs.
It's not a story, so I haven't gotten that kind of thing.
It came, it came, it came, it came, it came.
It has become something of a specialty.
I wonder what it is, I feel lonely. What's the matter?
2 years since debut in 2019
Oh no, no, I'm not here
What is not
Year of the year
year old
Please run away, run away
hand
tea
It's a shame that I came here when I wanted it, but look at it.
That's not the leader, it's leader Nol and leader.
2000 I'm not moving, it's been 29 years as leader.
No way
Mina, why? No, no, no, no.
More than the station I saw cut off
From now on
bad
[music]
Okay, I'm sorry, but I'm missing something now.
Run away, run away, run away, terrifying speed
Well, artists are gathering now.
Very artist here
country
[music]
It seems like there are 3 games.
I had an image of her showing off quite a bit.
[music]
[applause]
Na
I was arrested and interrogated.
People are that fat, even if they're already fat.
It's not Korea, it's not Claw, who is it?
I'm sure I've been arrested before.
Well, I haven't been arrested yet.
No, I got caught
It's never happened, Mie, that's a complete surprise.
totori
It's a lie. He hasn't been arrested yet. It's a shame.
I guess it's not
[music]
Looks like there's some slime
It's me
Yo
Nanao nice nice nice
I barely answered all the questions.
I want to run away, great
[music]
It's cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's cool
Thank you for your hard work, Deoka is moving.
Only three hunters remain here, the rest
Please understand
is
Hello, something suddenly moved.
Is this okay? Maybe it's here.
Masu
Hey, I got caught again. I got caught. I got caught again.
It's too late. I'm going to Korea again. I got arrested.
It's Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea, it's Korea.
I'm sure it'll make you crawl
I'll give you this too.
Which is Korea?
I don't know where you're looking again.
I'm at a loss when I'm caught
I'm at a loss, I'm lost
I'm going to put this out, I'm giving you this here, here, here.
The snack food given by the group leader and Yoisho Choco-sensei.
of
The whole country of Tshot is so amazingly surreal.
But
[laughter]
This Noel-senpai has a great sense of lighting and photography.
picture
I understand, it's a really messed up camera meal.
What are you doing?
But it's a pass, it's a pass.
I want you to do your best in the second race. Good luck, Nechi support.
Let's go to our seats and support each other.
Do your best, wait, wait, I accidentally sprayed you with deodorant.
Please wait a moment.The mouse is
Why am I soaked now?
I was spraying deodorant.
Yo, the dangerous mouse that accidentally fired
Yoishioishi Sukiro that got all wet
Oh no, I was just petting you
That's what I was stroking.
I was stroking him, but he hit me.
Hey
So cute! Looking down!
Come on, you're so cute! It moved! It moved!
Oh, it's moving, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute, it's cute
Chana glass glass pa
I wonder if Gura-chan will appear.
Are you sure it's okay to be here? It's true. Eyes
When I woke up, I was a contestant. Maybe so.
It says I'm currently entering an entry for the fugitive.
I'm probably being taken away right now, so take this with you.
The disappearing guy
stubborn
Do your best, a dangerous brawl has begun.
It's true, I didn't realize it was a Subaru statue
Did that get stolen from YouTube?
I wonder if it was a specific sound.It's a sensitive sound.
I thought I'd do it
Auchichichi
My hand slipped
Yoma
[music]
Yoo it's coming, it's starting, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
It's starting, it's starting, it's starting, it's starting, it's starting, it's starting.
In addition
1509 There are quite a lot of them.
It looks like it's small, so let's start from one end.
You can use this in a colander, right?
So, do your best. Who's the first to enter?
I'm not going in, that's okay, that's okay.
Ice iris-chan is expensive.
Cha-senpai is hiding here. Toa-senpai is hiding here.
Although he is hiding, A-senpai is probably about the same age.
He's really in the corner.
I'm hiding my thoughts
Terue is surprisingly different, I'm failing so much.
Sui-chan looks expensive, Asu-chan looks expensive.
Yes, certainly
Yes, but it was done
It's nice, it's finally here, it's finally here
No, there's someone hiding behind Korea. Who's behind it?
Is it hidden?
Catch it. It's easy to understand. Who is that?
It's too early, it's too early.
Who is Moko-san being arrested for?
I don't have a name
Noekari-chan is tall, isn't she? She's tall.
I agree
Yes, I can catch cotton.
I was told to go to my ears.
I wish I could say that Kebo Emi people have ears.
Is there anything included? Oh yeah, surprisingly there isn't.
I wonder which one it is, the one in my ear or the one in my ear.
I'm sure, right? Right now, I'm just listening.
That's right, that's right, Fana-senpai.
Are the horns not square ears?
It doesn't look like there are a lot of corners, it's pretty dangerous.
This is quite a lot
Yes, this is very blurry.
It feels good, it feels good, it's pretty good, it's pretty good
Everyone is finally getting into it.
It's so scary that you finally got caught.
Even that senior who is catching me, really catching me
Bokeh
11 people are amazing, no, really
early
Quick, go away!
There's no way Merle is going to disappear.
No, Mel-chan is nothing but an idiot.
I'm just a blur, Mel-senpai is hiding a lot.
Mizu-senpai is on the right, he's right here.
It's in the red room.
keep it up
I'm looking at you, you're so nice, so nice.
nice nice nice
That's really me, that's the best record
This is the best record ever, maybe the best record ever.
I was so [ __ ] up
Huh, that's great, you won't run away next time, right?
Kara yoshi yoshi nice nice ah nice nice
Nice nice nice nice nice nice
Nice nice
nice
a
Oh, that's amazing.
[music]
The staff is
a
What's going on? Wait a minute, Choco-sensei.
This photo is so good, isn't it?
Wow, this looks so good!
It's so good, the candy I just took is so good
Let's get along well and put this in this place.
This is so good, so Subaru.
This is good
Too bad this is so cool I'm back
Welcome back, welcome back, [ __ ] me
Tane everyone, welcome home.
It was a lot of work, it was a great job, beast.
It's so cute, I want to get caught in the end
Yeah, the last part was mostly blurry.
large
The face you're looking at is really old.
There are surprisingly few furry ears like this.
I'm a bit worried about Monebame-senpai having animal ears.
I don't have an image of being surprised.
I'm pretty sure this is what I heard.
Everyone's in charge of blurring, so there's not much intrusion.
I wonder if it's that blur, maybe that blur
I don't like it, but if I judge Mio-senpai, she's a pretty dumb person.
It's not too much, but it's a zarukan.
That's right, Mio-chan Kamio
Looks like it's someone other than chan
nemi orlando
Mirandola is a bonus stage in a sense.
I'm sure there's an escape and the [ __ ] is coming.
It would be helpful if you could help us all together.
Run away, run away, try your best, try your best
Soooo
Come, come, come
Ta
After all, Ranran gathers in one place.
It was a little hard to catch
terrible
Where should I hide it?
[music]
Senpai, someone has been arrested.
was arrested, but
As expected, I've been hiding it since 0.
I feel like I'm about 2 years old, and I'm 4 years old too.
Even if I get caught for a moment, I'll hide in prison and get caught.
You can catch me, I'll catch you
[music]
Did you know about Uwateruteru-chan?
I got caught
Hey, I got caught.
Necha
Looks pretty good
[music]
with silver hair
silver hair
[music]
hair
a
Riuwa true
It's not just dangerous, silver-haired, silver-haired.
It was
[music]
Wow.
It's okay
It's the same as Yandata
It was the same, sorry, sorry, it was the same.
Ta
[music]
I did it, but
It's such a shame, I have so much free time.
Hey, I'm bored. I'm in trouble.
Sexy girl caught is a bad sexy girl
It's a little bad
Naneso, hold on, you can catch me.
Dodge or dodge
picture
How about me? What about me?
Completely ignored
why why why
ri senpai senpai festival senpai I'm here
Senior
No one is coming
Saka is sexy
do not have
It's sexy but it's cute
Wa Mosa
I didn't get caught, I didn't get caught.
Nice, nice, anyway, these are 144 people.
He was a real person
Daiya, that was a close call, nice, nice Ceci slot
Nice, just barely dangerous or dangerous
Ta
Hey, the sexy frame was dangerous, sexy escape.
I wanted to get a book, but I was worried about it.
Ta
[music]
Well then
I've lost a lot of weight.
I was surprised
[music]
It wasn't touched.
I've been sleeping too long
White people are being taken away more and more.
Teru
Where did everyone go? Are you here?
Masu
It was moved without permission. It's back. It's back.
enemy
It moved randomly.
drop down
Chiru
After all, who is winning now?
I guess I don't know, I wonder what's going on.
I don't know how things have passed.
I wonder what it's like
Where was this ceremony judgment, Enu-senpai?
Sexy ah yes ah yes no no
this is this is nono
Sexy guy number one
Sexy number one, sexy number one, sexy no no no
Nonononononono sexy no sexy here
Sexy isn't here. Maybe it's not here.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait
Kaela-san is here Oh Kaela-chan
sexy kaela-chan sexy sexy
Kara No No Kaela's sexy self
The person who says is
Noko is cool, looks cool
I'm sure it's going to look cool Rokoshi
It's not advert
Rocco says it must have been shiny.
My senior had that nice butt.
I saw your butt earlier.
But I was already in Korea.
It's not sexy because I couldn't lie to you
No, no, no, don't make me sexy
Yo
That's a little weird
Sexy was better, sexy
I wanted to be caught, but unfortunately there were too many details.
I didn't understand it at the beginning of the sports day.
That's true. I wonder what will happen until the end.
I don't understand, so it's yellow. Let's all do our best.
I want everyone on the other teams to finish as well.
I want you to run until I say yes.
So, let's aim for the next competitive white.
Let's move to the follow-up venue.
Please
Please 15 middle or 2 or middle?
enliven
There are plenty of exciting moments too.
Seconds Go to the next venue or the venue of the next venue
Rare follow-up.
Be follow up follow up I want to fall
I don't want to fall
Raaaaaa up
First of all, I speak English because Kia-senpai is not there.
but
Dangerous English English
Topseka is here, let's go, senpai, senpai.
Let's go home. High schoolers say Eiden.
I guess school school school
school school school school high
school class floor up floor school
Flow assay follow-up stage
5 Follow-up Stages Follow-up
It's stage 5, right? It's called rooftop.
I guess it's high ground, hira
Don't say you don't understand High Ground.
I guess it's high ground up earl.
Lulf Top is all about passion
roof top roof top top hee
Luftgolf Top Golf
GO Luftorft Ieio is here.
Oh, I see. I guess it's the upper body.
I see
All the contestants, now this or that.
It's interview time
I see, I see, I see
Do your best Noko Senpai Character Senpai
stubborn
Do your best, try your best, do your best, right?
I feel like I can even call A and B together at all.
Yeah, I'm not that serious about it.
I didn't feel like I was doing it.
In fact, Chiara's presence really helps.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Passion Inn I looked up English today.
That's the one. Only the one that seems to be used a lot.
I've been looking up English, so let's take a look.
I'm so embarrassed, I haven't used it even once.
Why? Let's use it.
Yoedemo explains Mu-chan during a break.
I heard people asking me about how hard I worked.
Apparently he was listening to it while eating the pastry he was listening to.
What is that? Steak
How do you say chicken and pork in English?
I discussed this with Mu-senpai and
What did you do when you got it grilled?
That's what Asoka told me.
Beef fork worked hard
Chicken Afu Poku Chicken Loco's Etori
If you forget, you'll forget
That's why I have to shout to his senior.
So beef, pork or chicken?
beef pork
It's like chicken steak steak steak
Steak Tekifa Beef Beef Fire
beef beef fire beef fire
I want to eat steak steak gogo steak
I guess I'm hungry
Someone said earlier that they were hungry.
Hmm, I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
I'm hungry
It's just around 7:30.
It's dinner time. It looks like there's no food.
Well, I guess it's different for overseas groups.
Ewatimenownosenpai
A33am
Well, it's not 3 o'clock in the morning. Ah, morning, morning.
You guessed it, it's not 3 in the morning, it's in the middle of the night.
It's hard to be lazy at night
It's okay, good morning, sleep. It's raining, isn't it?
Thank you very much for coming this late at night.
Thank you, Senkyu, Senkyu, it’s okay.
coffee coffee drinker
Nice caffeine, nice coffee
Coffee Nice Coffee Yeah Caffeine
Caffeine is important, no caffeine
Caffeine Caffeine Power Let's Go
Hi
What is the origin of English?
Just say let's go and you'll be fine
Because a great person really said that.
I believe in great people and I'm okay with average.
chan was throwing a trident.
Only Sui-chan has creative authority
Apparently that's what makes it popular.
Apparently he's throwing a trident.
That's right, maybe that's it.
It's Tara, but I'm not here.
The Holomen hunting I did earlier
Try editing in creative mode
Even when I practice, there are traces of that left behind.
Do it and fly
I was throwing a javelin by myself about 3 days ago.
It's so cunning, I'm holding it in one hand.
Trident is cunning, isn't it? Trident
What are you doing, my senior?
What are you doing? It's okay. It's okay.
You can get better because you're creative.
Yes, what are you doing?
Mizuo-senpai has it now.
Tode says he can do this.
Is that true?
It's a book, I can't pick this up, right?
Pick it up
No, I took a photo of what was left of my senior.
Toko
I can read the stars
Hey Hoshide
Teruhiha-chan's star reading is now available.
It's so expensive, it's a little scary for me.
Please don't say it, it's really okay.
Even Channan is clearly visible with this camera.
A little bit of trident hand dirt
I put it in a ziplock bag.
I smelled the trident
I was checking it out and taking pictures.
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone
Even the shock that disappeared
Please keep it a secret, ah yes.
What should I do? What should I do?
Shall we do it?
It depends on how things turn out in the future.
Well, today, the rest of the show will be
cormorant
I'll lick my real shoes. Please lick my real shoes.
So what about that?
Why don't you lick it? Lick it.
It's not Kuren's
I'm so happy
Naja cookies will be delivered Cookie Horaku
Oh Cookie Cookie Ah Cookie Neiori
I want to deliver cookies to everyone.
I want everyone at overseas stores to eat it too.
Tell the world that it looks like it
I want to tell you what I want to do.
I took a break from streaming for about a month.
So let's go to training. Let's go to training. Let's go to training.
But it will come out
Or I'll give it to Callum Iame-chan.
cookie present cookie present color
It's supposed to be a cookie, so the cookie color is coming.
It's coming, 5 more until the start
seconds
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, Pachilets Go Roboco
Roboko, do your best, do your best, Roboko, do your best
keep it up
Fight, I like it!
That's true, but I'm sure he was good at it.
Practice is so fast.
Sobi-chan is really good at it, isn't she?
Mi-chan is so good! Good luck Robo-chan!
Nokotepa is good, finally, finally, finally
Okay, number two now, nice nice nice nice now.
It's all right, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Wow, I just started and fixed it. What's going on now?
Touched a checkpoint, died and returned
I feel so stupid
Checkpoints are important, okay?
It's true that I'm really competing with Sui-chan.
It's true, it's amazing, it's amazing
Wow, that's good, that's good, that's okay, that's okay.
Degozaru has a pretty good route.
It's delicious, it's delicious, everyone
Oh, it's not good, it's not good, it's amazing
Hayaa is really good, really good, really good
It's not good, it's really good, this is the remaining time
The middle yellow color is really Sui-chan.
Sui-chan is doing her best, Eve is amazing
1st place is also very fast
Biuma
Too much blue checkpoint nice
Sapoko
Well, there's something steadily going on here.
Can you go all the way to the top?
I'm doing this. I can go and see it.
I can't go, I can't go, I can't go
Yes, I'm looking at it from below.Yes, it looks like it's from below.
I just look at it, I guess it's around here
I'm looking at a board infection signboard like that.
They say it's like if you touch it, you can go.
It's the first time I've heard of such a lie, and I'm on the right side with an infected person.
This is not the one that says Lee.
It's true that it's going to go up, it's going to go up, it's going to go up
Awesome, amazing, chasing after me
I didn't know you were chasing me, I know now
I didn't have it, but even now I feel like I've gotten into it quite a bit.
It's amazing how true it is, everyone.
Everyone knew it was really floating.
Everyone's head is floating
Only the sound is floating
It hurts, but I'm honestly going to wear it.
Don't look at how nice you are being polite.
It's okay, it's true, I'm almost at the goal
It's true, I've reached the goal. Calm down.
You can do it, do your best, Roboko-san.
Good luck, that pink one is sleepy.
Yo, this, this, this, this, these three.
The guy who works
No, it's progressing steadily.
I can't hear it
Good luck
Nice, nice, nice
Nice nice, nice.
That's so nice, go for it
Nice-chan, do your best, Ichiban-chan is so expensive
Tokosui-chan, Sui-chan, do your best
Do your best, do your best, where is Sui-chan?
He's so cute even when he's playing with Raiden
Please come out.
You can become a great photographer
I'll do my best. I wonder if I can make it. I'm a fan.
I'm looking at you, so it's okay.
Wow, that's cool, it's finally honest
It's not rising, it's rising, it's rising
Terunai is good, good, keep up the good work
Good luck, you're taking shortcuts now.
I went there, right? I'm talking to you upstairs.
Oh Taegu, can you go? Go, go, go!
Yeah, just a little bit more, just a little bit more effort.
Good luck!
That's right, nice, nice eggplant, that's good
Finisher nice nice nice jijiji
Good
The game is good game good game already
I applaud this with all my might
This is good, everyone clears it
It's amazing, something strange has come out.
What is this?
Oh Kia, you must be nervous, huh?
Are you okay? Is there something on the screen?
Something strange has come out. What is this?
Controller if there are chat settings etc.
I often wonder if something has come out.
I don't know what came out.What came out?
Wait, I can't get down.
It's a shift, a shift, a shift.
I can get off with a shift. Is there a shift anyway?
yes
It's a little surreal to see a severed head flying around.
I'm sure it will come back due to this and that infection.
I'm back, I'm back, oh, oh, that's good.
Tae is amazing, he only accepts heads like that.
I didn't know about spectator mode.
It's amazing that there is such a mode.
These ordinary people can't see our heads.
Yes, it's true that you can see it when you look from below.
It wasn't there, I couldn't see it, did you notice?
It didn't happen, I thought it wasn't a lie.
It's so good that it doesn't get in the way.
It's done, I'm forced to come back
Everyone came back one after another.
I wish I was infected after the game started.
I wonder if something will fall from the sky after I die
It looked like it was dead when I was looking at it.
Do you mean an out-of-body project?
It's like, ``Next Kiara''
I support my seniors, but I have to support them in return.
When you support Let's Going Squirrel
How do I do it? How do I do it in English?
I'll support you, fight fight fight
fight fight fight fighter
fight here
Go go go go go go go go
Go go go
Go go go Chiara, do your best, do your best Chiara
Chan
Good luck, it feels good
Yo, Chiara-senpai, you were so amazing!
It's so fast, it's the fastest.
I was practicing really hard, so that's nice.
Hey, you've reached the checkpoint!
early
I was practicing something until the last minute.
No, it's delicious, it's really delicious, it's really delicious
It's delicious, it's delicious, it's delicious
It's so good, so good, so good.
Amazing Kia senior Kia, just one more person
I went 70m, it's already too fast
The checkpoint has arrived, wow, wow!
The checkpoints are so smooth too.
I can't go there, it's so smooth
I'm going to go crazy with shortcuts
Can you go up? Wow, I'm going up.
Let's go, this is amazing, senpai
Super, birds are fast after all. Birds are fast.
It's fast, after all, it's definitely time to practice flying.
I must have been really nervous.
You said yes, what should I do?
I didn't make any mistakes.
It looks like it's not there even if it's sprouting
I don't know, I honestly don't understand this.
I don't know
No, I'm going up again.
If you like it, don't carve it and go upstairs.
do not have
I'm going to go. It's amazing. It's amazing.
Wow, a genius? Wow, that's amazing!
There are no mistakes, seriously, nice mistakes.
I've come this far
Hey, that's great. I wonder where this is going.
I'm going that way, I'm going that way.
I have no doubts about the route.
Even at that speed, as if he had already decided
I can go, it's amazing, it's really fast
Too fast, too good to be true
This is no longer the absolute number one, even the bottom
I think I'm going to fall down here.
There are quite a few checkpoints.
No, I won't fall, it's Kia-chan so I won't fall
It's difficult to fall, so here too
Do you want to do it?
[music]
big bold
It's so amazing, it's really scary
Chiara, do your best and make it in the end
[applause]
Amazing a
This demon is so cool
That's amazing
That's nice, Kia.
[music]
You're the best, you're so good
I was nervous, but I was nervous at all.
It seemed like an innocent move, but I made a mistake and got RTA.
Climb up like
I couldn't stop, nice nice nice
That's nice. It was so good.
I haven't finished 2nd or 3rd place yet.
It's not even half yet, it's not 150 yet.
Because it's there
Hey, the winner has about 90 seconds to spare.
Let's take a look below. That Kira seems obvious.
Early the next morning
Hey, Genius
ah
Oh sorry, I like Annie and Chloe.
Are you competing with your feelings? It's true, it's black.
Black is amazing. If you think about it that way, it's really difficult.
It seems difficult to get a sense of distance though.
Because this is in character
It's the result of all my hard work.Yesterday was so long.
It's like you practiced for hours. Amazing.
I'm alone now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Shirin waiting time
Ha, yeah, yeah, it's time for ma.
Aiya
The end of Onoprem is over.
Yellow is in second place or yellow is number two.
Waane-chan, there's only one more step left.
No, it was just one more step. Too bad I already flew away.
It flew, it flew
Aa-chan fell down
I saw an amazing moment and jumped in.
It was interrupted just at that moment and I fell down.
It happened
It was amazing and I hope it was a great battle.
It was amazing
Nice Kiara-chan in the crackling white group
pride
They fly like beautiful birds.
Crackle and crackle
[music]
Nice was amazing
Here's another key point from the second game.
It seems to be added, but...
We finished 12th, so we were probably number one.
I think the points are high this time.
Probably not
Kada: You were in second place just now, but you're in first place now too.
Oh, it's not possible at all, it's not possible at all.
I guess this is quite possible.
The one on the screen on the other side of the stream is
What is the point of follow-up?
The white team's points are currently at 20 and are currently number one.
I got the points so my number is probably reversed.
Are you going to go? I wonder if number one is coming?
Nice fight over there, I can catch up.
Nice nai nice
That was nice
Hey, I'm back tired. I'm still here.
Are you in an interview?
We, the white team, have a saying.
Only the white team is properly eavesdropping on both of them.
hey
Netamonne Mountain
The winner's margin is the strength of the mountain.
I wonder if it's out now, maybe there or there.
No, it was a high-level match, Nomis.
That was amazing, I didn't make any mistakes.
That's amazing, that's nice
Nice, the White team is currently in 1st place.
It's a very close battle, but white 40 yellow
38 red 37 oh well done nice nice
Nice Achi 4 Points Yellow 38 Red
37 Furets
Go, you're doing your best. That's nice. That's nice.
That's wonderful, nice nice nice nice nice
Nice nice, this is our dangerous princess
Whether it's coming or not, that's what it's like.
That's true, but it seems like it's possible to fight the general with fangs.
There's a lot of protection, so I guess that's the case.
Still good
I guess I have to try my best.
I feel like the pressure is coming on slowly.
I was going to do it but somehow it ended up in first place
No, it's a little bit of pressure.
The pressure is building and I'm heading to the next Kiba line.
Well, it seems like there are no pairs at all.
Hey, I teamed up with Ramen-chan this time, so how about it?
Naru no Kama
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello, this is my mother.I'm looking at you, mother.
If yes, then here are the general benefits
The second comprehensive benefit that will be announced mid-term is
here
I said yes.
1 Yes, even if it was that kind of money at 40.
The very last one is 63 white 60
Masu
The rest
[music]
Well then, let's move on to the next competition venue.
Let's
Jump from Neko was announced.
How was that Aazu? Aazu Tatata
As I said earlier, White is in 2nd place overall.
But there was a difference of 3 points from 1st place.
3 Yellow is 63 White 6 Chiara is nice
Seriously, seriously.
It's a really good game. It's a really good game.
tago game good game nafanafa
nafa
Wow, Wow!
[music]
I'm nervous, I'm nervous
Good luck Akia, do your best
Give me a ride, come ride me
Masato
If I'm the first, I won't be the first, I'll be the first.
Where is the general who doesn't want to be teru?
Eto Yoshidoko is on the right side of the entry.
I'll go with this and that's cute.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay, I was confused at first, that's nice.
Nice nice, cute, cute
That's right, you can climb on it.
To someone who is still holding a bettaaetneku
Ah, I'd probably hold it and change it to the general.
The general may be the superior, but the general is the superior.
It might be okay if you don't make an entry.
If you have already entered, it will be canceled.
Touch the entry button once more
[laughter]
[music]
Oh my god, I made this!
Neno is here
Will you give it to me? That person from my pair is coming.
Is that person there?
Will they come?
The pair of Kadyo's Kanata remains like this for me.
Wander around everyone
cormorant
I want to eat green onigiri if I prepare rice.
The rice ball is now in the container.
want
I want to eat rice balls. I'm hungry.
Dirty water
I want to tag
Thank you for canceling the command.
Chachaaaaaaaa okay
So know
Oh
[music]
Tachi
Eta-sama
Where are you here?
Because
Awesome, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Kiddododododo
[music]
Is it okay to get off the train? Are you okay?
How do you stop sleeping?That book
Press the same place again
Just nice
[music]
Nice mumble came
Tananka
Wait a minute
Did it come out?
Where are you wearing your suit? You look strong.
suit suit ready
Someone who looks strong and looks like they're strong
It looks too strong. It's okay. It'll be huge later.
I will not charge you an excessive amount.
Oyu might be a big man
Thank you for being so kind to me, Senpai.
Yes, I rode, I rode, I rode, I was the strongest.
That's how I rode it
My eyes are amazing, so I said, “Wow!
Okayu-senpai, please help me with a pinch hitter.
It seems strong that you will give it to me.
That kind regards
Thank you very much, Aoka-senpai, please come.
Thank you very much
Anyone want to get on board? I got on board.
I got on top of my mom who got on top of me.
My senpai got on board.I'm on board, yuu senpai.
I'll ask you to become a chair for a while, leave it to the orchestra.
hand
Thank you, I'm so happy I can sit on your ears
It's fluffy and it looks like it's stuck in the chocolate line.
It's stuck in the corner of
Leader's butt
A direct hit hurts
I don't want any pain, but I'm a little irritated.
It's okay, it's not just a little bit
I think it's quite stimulating. So,
Mio-chan might be quite stimulating too.
Senpai's corner
It's exciting, isn't it?
Gozamoshi Moshi
[music]
Hayu-san, thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you for letting me participate.
[Laughter]
More and more
I'm afraid I'll be taken away from
That's why I said yes, so what do you think?
Are you enthusiastic? Please tell me how to do it.
Since I received it, I want to lead Kanata to victory.
thought
That's amazing! It's so cool!
reliable
Let's do our best, everyone!
Let's do our best. Let's do it. Finally, let's do our best.
I want to ask the woodworkers.
Kigurumi kigurumi kigurumi kigurumi group
Hey, what's the strategy for this group?
It seems like everyone in the white group is getting angry.
If Neyaya Shi's kill is taken, then 1
I guess points will be added.
So, while defending, the opponent who will probably attack is
Let's all focus on each other.
For now, I'll take care of those who approach the general.
It seems like all I have to do is wake him up.
I prefer to be around the boss.
Isn't it possible to do more and more?
A weak person, that's right, a weak person.
I want to beat you up, I can see your heart
I might want to go to someone with a heart, please Ami
At first, be near the general and see 1 heart.
If you do that, you'll be charged. Are you a ball rider?
Ball riding
Okay, maybe this is the voice of that pair.
I think it will be a chat so I guess so
Yes, that's right. There are so many.
There's a voice section, um, at the bottom.
I think it probably has a name, that's true.
It seems that there is Kata porridge, so I collaborated with Minato.
I can't take it, General Aja is in charge of cooperation.
protect and protect
That's right, it's the great general.I see it as a landmark.
Do your best
Let's do our best
If we're both true, we're both being targeted.
I think it would be better to cover Teruya.
hey
I feel like I'm going to be attacked if I find this.
I felt like
Well, I guess I'll probably have to move from here.
I think everyone should move then I'll go.
I went
Masu
Hello, Nemio
It's okay, I haven't practiced at all.
I haven't practiced
Let's do our best from now on, though.
I wonder what the general is like, his light is shining so brightly.
Yes, that's true, the world is shining too.
I wondered, what could this be?
It seems like that's what happened to that general.
If you are defeated, the number of kills is 1.
Yeah, that point becomes that plus.
Yes, yes, yes, from other teams.
Yes, that's the target.
For example, 3rd place at the bottom is 5 points.
Even if it's true, I've defeated the general three times, so it's a point.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it seems like it's going to be.
So the general doesn't get knocked down.
You have to be careful about that, right?
I understand, let's do our best to escape.
run away or run away
It's okay, it's okay, but it's okay.
We were both defeated by the same white team earlier.
If so, let's cover it a bit.
I was doing that, yes, yes, maybe, just in case.
I'm sure he's watching, huh?
Fair enough
Wait a minute, that's awesome
Maybe a little more on this side
Thank you so much!
I'm so sorry, but by the way, it's broadcast at night.
But it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, oh, it's like that sharp-sounding agent.
each one
It would be nice to have it made in the studio.
Do you want to do your best or have a strategy?
If you tell me what you want to do, I'll move.
So
ah
At yesterday's practice session, that general...
I'm scared and don't come forward much and just protect.
If you do that, yeah, that's normal points.
It was a bit low. It's not tasty.
So to earn points,
I guess I'll have to go punch the general too.
That's what I felt, but the general took it.
The points are the same as everyone else.
The same irrelevant feeling, when taken away
It's just that the points are different, yeah yeah
That's right hahaha I understand, I understand
Dead and involved in the direct point of the sports day
It feels like it's coming, yes, yes, yes.
I guess it's just a little bit of damage.
Just try not to die as much as possible
Looks like I want to get the kill yes yes yes yes
I really want to go to Suka-chan.
Maybe, but yesterday there was a lot of red and yellow.
The targets are hitting each other so hard.
I see, white is supposed to protect you from the cold.
That's pretty much it. Don't be too aggressive.
Yeah, if they attack from the other side, I'll switch places.
It was like that, but even this time
The general is different this time.
It's different this time.
Will I be able to go there even though I might be attacked quickly?
I'll go to the Yoshimitsu
There's a possibility that someone might attack you.
Yes, yes, can you hit it well?
I don't fight while pulling.
I have to say that there are a lot of them, right?
If only I could counterattack with the other side's attacks.
I feel like it's still pretty good, but this is the only thing
It's tough to get hit like that.
Calico is difficult, but just in case that general is
Right, there are five hearts. I see.
By the way, the other members are 3, so yeah.
If it was already 3-on-1, then it was 3-on-5.
I think it's totally possible, but then I'll hit you.
If you're serious about hitting me, it's better to hit me, then I'll win.
There, there are only 2 hearts left.
If you encounter the other 3 in this state, you will be defeated.
It looks like it's okay.
It feels like that, so it's a little bit like that.
It may be difficult to determine, but at first
It's better to hit me because it's there at first.
Maybe you can go without worrying about the points.
Arida is also currently in 2nd place, so it's a bit of a reversal.
I want 3 points, I want money.
Hey, that's right, if you can get 3 points, General.
I want to aim for that too, but yeah
On the contrary, I think there are many people who aim for the general.
So that's true, Tacha is also a target.
That's right, I'm the one being targeted.
It's okay
Even if Nayada Nama did that, the other members
He might protect me, huh?
Hmmmm Mel-chan
I and Subaru said yes yes yes yes
Mikoto and Subaru are the generals, so even their arms are shining.
It seems easy to understand.
Yeah, I don't quite understand what happened yesterday.
What did the general do with that horse?
Subaru was there yesterday, so the red team.
I couldn't find anything, but I'm sure Nekari-chan and others were doing it.
It was, right?
Yeah yeah
That's why the White team was very defensive.
But if I had been focused on defense, I wouldn't have been No. 1.
What did I do? I was in the middle of the middle. I was in 2nd place.
I wonder if it was, so I guess it's okay.
We talked about how it would be better to be aggressive.
Tae Avatar is not difficult, that's right
It's
Yo
It's okay even
That candy character icon
Which one should I aim for?
decide what to do
I wonder if it's an elephant or not
Yeah, it's up to you to decide what direction you want to go.
Maybe it would be better to be a crab.
Maybe it would be better if Neyori Hamega issued an order.
do not have
Yeah, come on, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's coming
Taekore is running straight.
I'll respawn, so oh, let's go, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, go here, go here, this, this, this.
This this this
Let's go, bad, bad, bad, 2 vs 12
1 vs 1 is bad, 2 vs 1 is bad
First of all, is 2-on-1 bad?
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
terrible
Oh no, can I hit you?
I got one shot, but I got one shot left.
Even if I wait for one more thing, I can't see it.
It's terrible, it's a bit terrible, I can't focus.
It's in danger, it's in danger, it's in danger, wait, wait, one more
No, it's not just one, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad
Wait a minute, I have to attack this. I have to attack.
Wait a minute, you're so strong, where are you going to attack?
I'm sure it'll be really hard to understand
I hit it, I hit it, I hit it, I can hit it, it's crazy
terrible
Alright, I guessed it, alright, alright, alright.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I can go see it
Wait a minute, okay, okay, but 2
I ate two pieces. I ate two pieces.
Oh wait, it's so messy I don't understand
Oh no, oh no
It's bad, it's bad, it's 0 kills, it's strong, it's 0 kills
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
I was a little too scared to come forward.
No, this is difficult, this is difficult.
Hey, focus on the swirling chair, which one should I aim for?
I don't know what to say, I'm sure the general
Maybe I should aim for someone other than the general.
It might be better to aim at the person whose back is turned.
Nooooooooooooo yeah, I turned my back to the general.
Like fishing for the person you're after, yeah yeah yeah
This time I was aiming for someone who feels behind me, that's right.
Cut from the back against people who are fighting backwards.
It's called ru.
It's difficult, but it's white after all.
I guess there aren't that many kills.
It might be no good if you don't show some aggression.
It's okay to stick in there, it's okay to come out.
Oh yeah, that red red thing is scary, that thrust.
I'm not feeling well, I'm not feeling well.
circle
It's okay, but now, that score...
It's dangerous, so I'd rather increase the number of kills.
What do you think? Should I aim for the general?
That seems like a troubling place.
Ah, a cross is completely different, isn't it?
say
I don't know what T this is.
No, how many times are we going to do this? Three times, two more?
yes
Okay, I'll do my best where I want to.
Even though I was in Tainae, I was still targeting the girls.
Even Kaiya doesn't seem to be targeted like that.
It seems like you will do it.
oh
Lol lol Yes, you don't have to enter.
It's okay, it's okay
O
I'll pick it up
yes
Hey, this is it
It's scary, after all, he's a general.
It's a bit difficult to attack, isn't it?
Can I go for a bit?
Please, I'm really worried, I know.
I know, but I also said one more pigeon.
I'm afraid I'll start thrusting into my own
I can't see my heart. I can see my own heart.
I don't know if there is one or not, but I was so engrossed in watching it.
I just can't see it. Yes, yes, just a little.
I wonder if it's okay. There are special benefits.
Here it is, there's some sort of cape coming out of it.
I'm sorry it's not my fault.
Sorry I made a mistake
I'm sorry that my work wasn't completed.
It wasn't, it was A-chan's completion.
Ta
Eh, it's all messed up and Kana-tan.
I couldn't see that, I could definitely see around me.
It's going to be a mess, but it's definitely going to be gone
It's a bit of a mess and we're all just messing around.
Probably hitting from behind on the outside.
He's the strongest tactically, I see.
Yeah, I'll do that, or I'll mess around twice.
Aim for the edge and get behind me.
It's like I'm trying to be careful not to
Even if it feels fluffy, it's okay, it's a strategy
It's okay to do whatever is appropriate, it's okay to do whatever is appropriate.
I haven't practiced
Let's get a lot of kills with this feeling.
I'll do it in a casual way
There, the porridge is on top.
Yeah, I think porridge might actually be better.
How did the strategy change?
There are some changes, so it's a little late at home.
I don't know if I can't get under there because of the atmosphere.
But yeah, it's okay, either one is a general.
That's right, it's above. I'm sorry for the bugs.
I'm talking to you right now, but I'm talking to you
But Subaru's voice penetrates through and can be heard.
After all, it's leaking through it.
I can hear it so loud Subaru penetrates
point
Wow
Penetrating
[Laughter]
Yoyabee
[music]
[laughter]
Gaga has penetrated it, yes, it's also a strategy meeting.
It's a raft leak, so it doesn't matter.
unrelated relationship
No, I wonder if it's time to go? Oh, come, come, come.
I'm coming, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going to take it, I'm going to take it
Get a kill
Here we come, let's go where we're going, okay, okay.
Okay, let's go around here now.
It's almost coming, it's coming so much
Isn't it good that so many people are coming?
We can't get past this, it's finally here
It's shaking so much, it's so good, it's finally here
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
No, okay, okay, okay, I might die.
I don't know what to do, but go, go, attack.
a
It's bad, it's okay, it can't be helped.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
sound
Oja
Jakerekeru this this this this this this
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's not good, it's not good.
Hold on a second, stand up. Stand up.
If I try to get carried away, I'll be chased.
I'm being chased I'm being chased
Understood, I'm being chased.
Understood, it's a bit bad or bad.
Kaa
I was defeated by the unfortunate general.
I want to enter this.I want to enter this.
Can I go? Can I go? One more kill
I want to get about
Oh, 1 kill, 1 kill, 1 kill, 1 kill.
I got a kill all the time, but yeah
I got 26 kills. That's amazing. White got 26 kills.
[music]
Teru is really strong, that's good.
That's amazing. Let's try our best too.
I have to, I have to do something different, but just a while ago
I've gained 1kg, but I've gained 1kg.
killed 3 times
It's embarrassing, but I'm being targeted often.
It can't be helped, so Sauchiragama is sure
Because it's the boss, right? Right, right, right.
Can we escape? We're both exhausted.
Yes, I can hear it while shopping.Oh, I can hear it.
Can you hear me? I'm here for an interview.
Thank you for your hard work. How was the game?
Please tell me a few words.Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you both for your hard work.Ah, I'm sorry.
I can't hear the audio from my house, so I see.
It seems like it's going to happen
I understand. Well, just a little while ago 1
In the first game, I had 0 kills.
Well, I just got one kill. I finally remembered.
Take it
Even if it's just a little bit nice, it's a target, so I'm dying.
Add points that you want to work hard on next time so you don't have to
I don't want to be left behind, so it's important to do that.
Please try hard, thank you very much
Thank you very much
Thank you very much thank you
Good luck in the third match. Sorry.
Thank you very much
Masuhai
Thank you. I can hear you, but I can't hear you.
Yes, I asked people why.
Well, this is better in 3rd person perspective.
I wonder if there are people like Inoana who do that?
I wonder which one is better.
Yeah, I can recognize people coming from behind.
Maybe a third person perspective would be better.
That's right, I'm surrounded, isn't it easy to understand?
Yeah yeah
Yeah
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
It was a great feeling to be able to take the hit and get the kill.1
I'm glad I got a kill. Yeah, that's good.
I can't see the other person's health.
Only the general can see the general, only the general can see the opponent.
I can't see how much health my opponent has left.
Right, I can't see this, I can't see it, I can't see it, right?
Yeah, I can only see that overall kill count at the end.
Oh yes, I was defeated quite a while ago.
I have to come forward even if I'm in trouble.
I don't think it's likely because I can't get kills.
Oh yeah, red is strong
Na
Merurumeru-chan, times like this are crazy.
Chatting is fun
This is how the whole thing looks, Mel-chan.
It's really interesting to chat, Miracle
It tends to happen
It looks like we'll be able to surpass first place in both games.
Even in that second round, Haku was pretty good too.
So it was definitely a 1 kill.
No, that's right. Just one chan. Next time.
There's a chance you can turn it around, so do your best.
I want to do my best if I don't have one.
Well, I guess I do, but I have to attack to a certain extent.
I guess we can't win after all.
Is it okay if I attack? It's still not enough.
I don't care what happens, I guess it's what it is now.
I want to do it before I can get enough kills.
It feels like it, but I just don't push into the enemy camp too much.
If it's too much, you'll probably die, so I guess it's okay.
No, it wasn't like I was pulling it too far.
I think the way I feel now is totally fine.
Well, my environment is different from the normal people around me.
I'm the general, and I'm carrying what I'm chasing after.
It's different, no, it's true, life is heavy.
It's heavy. I can't die easily. It's interrupted.
Is that one more entry?
is
hey
Yes, I'm right here, Ayame, behind.
Behind you
[Laughter]
That's in the back, everyone in Minecraft.
It's hard to understand when there are so many people
I don't understand anymore
hey
Amazing
I can't see my white team members at all when they're fighting.
I know, it's hard to understand, it's hard to understand, white
The most difficult to understand, certainly the most difficult to see
Apparently there is
Umaa is the name on the top, isn't it?
Well, I just want to stay still and move.
[music]
Neno
I see that he's really charging at me.
We'll fight back, if you want, we'll fight back.
rush forward too
Only it's stupid
N
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, he's here, watching the movements of his allies.
I feel like I'm going to shut everything down for a while Ah yes yes yes
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes yes yes yes
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I wonder if it's just one person doing it. I'm getting beaten up quite a bit.
Yellow Amoko Go Red
That's right, hit me once.
I just can't go here Oh no no no no no no no no
terrible
Ademoko Shirohaku where Subaru is defeated
I'm hitting you, so I want to hit you with you.
All at once
It's not nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice
In exchange for 1 tama
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine
Good this red red I want to do this red I want to do this
A great general who only sees the general.
Just look at it
do not have
Desperate
I want to do this, but I want to do this.
I want to do it, I'm floating, I'm floating
Yes, I won't do this. Can I go? Can I sell? Can I not go?
Kana sale kaaso
I didn't get one kill.
41 kills now
That's amazing, the white team weighs 41 kg.
chan's favorite kin is
Amazing chan's amazing
Yo, figure out what you're saying.
I screamed because I was so excited 41g
It's not bad, it's amazing
I only died once, so 1 kill is 1.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's the best
It's not a record, it's a record.
Great stop
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I really knew it
It's so cool, it's white after all
After all, the one who should win is white or poop.
Kills in the 1st and 2nd game even though it's white.
The one who didn't go to 41 even after adding a few numbers went.
Takana
Well, the first one was pretty bad, but the second one...
If you add it all up, you've reached a pretty good place.
41 is so loud, did you get 1st place with this?
I'm a little suspicious, but hey
Hey, I wish I could have gotten 12 more games.
There are some things like that, but it's just one game.
It was because my eyes were a little like that.
Well, I kinda fell down a little bit.
It was a pretty good match, so yeah, overseas.
It seems like the momentum is amazing. Oh really? Who is it?
Who the hell is Kill Kill Top?
Awesome someone has a kill leader
Hey Yahoo, I said yes.
Thank you, thank you, good luck, yeah
I'll do my best, see you later, see you later.
[music]
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
It was amazing, 41 years old, what's going on?
Who was so active, Nerisa?
It's chan, oh yeah, ume-chan
Nerisa-chan is ok 10
kill
Goi Ame-chan also has 10 kills, which is amazing
It was a kill machine from overseas.
It was so good and amazing
sleepy
I woke up so nice, that's amazing
Nice nai, this is amazing, it's a comeback
It's been a long time since I've made a comeback, isn't it? 41
Yes, target kills are also included, surprisingly 41 generals.
We did it too.
I'm sorry for trying to be nice but being really nice
The sound of 1 kill and running away is important.
So yeah yeah sorry nice 1 kill
If there hadn't been that one kill,
Yeah, I'm 40, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, it's important, it's important, it's nice, it's nice
Nice nice nice, Lista-chan is strong.
Very strong degozaru
Slon was seriously amazing Roboco
The pair was amazing and so nice.
I was super sleepy, I got 3 kills on the last general.
Wow everyone did a great job
That's amazing. That's so nice.
That's right
Nice nice nice what's the score?
I'm sure it's quite interesting, isn't it?
I've been to quite a few places, I guess.
I guess it has come back quite a bit.
I feel like I've made a comeback and I'm number 2 in the second game as well.
I think it was second place or something like that.
Even if it's only once, it's also quite red.
It was strong, so that's no wonder. It was definitely strong.
It's amazing that you took it
I wonder what will happen. I'm scared of Ride.
enemy
I'm shaking, I'm shaking, Ima-chan, let's do our best.
It's okay, it's okay, you can win, it's okay
Eh, are you okay? It's okay. I can win. I can win.
During practice, I touched the yellow group for about a minute and a half.
I was kicked, but I guess that's how it is.
Well, there's nothing wrong with serving that meal.
No, this is seriously meta-reading.
Yes, there is an update and Holomen
The content of the hunt has changed considerably.
So this is okay, the menu is also one-chan.
Mysterious reading that it may have changed
It's possible that you're doing that.
It's possible, it's totally possible
Well, I win
I really want to win, what if I come this far?
After all, you've come, right? How far do you want to go?
Hey, I want to go, I want to go, yeah.
I want to go, I feel a little bit of desire.
It seems fun and good at first.
It was a feeling, but it was a feeling.
It's starting to look like we're going to win.I'm wrapping my arms around it.
Come on, you've come in. There are no sleeves.
No, I didn't just tear it apart.
I just tore it off and now it's around my shoulders.
I tore it, and now my sleeves are torn again.
Jan
My sleeves aren't tearing, they're not tearing.
Desumou
Stop using your skin
Na
It's such a wild thing to not have skin.
My muscles are muscular and muscular, and I'm proud of them.
White is getting better at climbing down.
It's amazing! Last 41 kills!
happy joke
Power!
I turned bright red when Miko-senpai came home.
[laughter]
Too strong. Too nice site. No way.
Who was the person with the greatest number of kills?
I was the one who cut it first.
Mumei and Kiara were also amazing at the end.
Sorry, but Subaru
Defeated Senpai twice and Miko Senpai once.
Something like ``Mekhatetareta Monkara''
It's really great that he took the lead.
That was amazing, so it's the white team.
It was great, but a little bit at the end.
Thank you very much, Nekomata Okayu
Thank you very much for the book, please leave your impressions.
Yes, thank you very much
I was happy to be able to play with everyone.
I'm still responding to you
Thank you thank you
hey
Thank you, it disappeared in an instant. It disappeared.
Thank you agent agent
Thank you very much agent
MAGA team agent Okayo
Thank you very much
Thank you, thank you, my senpai is also scared.
I'm doing number kills, so I don't need this.
It's completely different. It's different. It's changing.
Thank you very much.
Niaa nice food it was fun it was fun
It was so much fun, so much fun, so much fun
But what about the competition that follows?
The pressure seems to be rising
The pressure is different. No, relax.
Let's hope it's okay, it's okay, everyone can go
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Are you okay
That's right, you have to protect the princess again. Protect the princess.
I'm getting it, so even if I make a small mistake,
And the pressure is on
That 4 that also sticks with Yabai Yabai Yabai 4
It stings me, and it stings me too.
Well, I'm going to practice. I'm already climbing the ivy.
Is everyone in a hurry climbing the vines?
hey
Even now, I'm getting better at the vines.
[music]
It's difficult to be nice, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it?
I heard you say "ta" today.
Tell me when and where did you run?
So that's it for the score tally.
I'm curious, so I'd like to see it.
Click here for the total scores from the three games.
What do you think of the money that the red team worked so hard for?
or
Ya strong
Yay, red team has 46 points and white team has 38 points.
The yellow team got 23 points and is still in second place.
Kamada was in 3rd place until just 2nd place.
I guess it turned around
I cut it
What will happen in the second half of the game after the game?
I don't know if it will turn out, but I'll move on to the next step.
Yes, but then, let's move on to the next competition.
Let's all move to the venue for the response.
Let's come, come, come, come, come, come, come.
Yo Lego
Go go fun looking forward to it
Let's enjoy the fight and do our best. Let's do our best.
I'll try my best.
Okay
Is everyone else coming?
Nakishi
Wow, do your best, do your best
Fight, do your best
[music]
Try harder
Masu
done
all
Good luck
White team white, do your best, do your best
Good luck Okatan entered the princess.
Ahime
Hime Hime The princess seems to be strong. If the princess is the best, then the princess seems to be strong.
Ichi-chan is strong
Grip Strength: She's the princess with the strongest grip strength, so she gets criticized.
I look forward to seeing you there
Gyugyugyugyu
I want you to say yes.Will you shake my hand?
Do your best here, do your best, assemble the engine.
It's so cute wearing a tiara
[music]
Neochiochi
Ekara you OK
Iao it's okay it's okay
The length is okay.
I thought Kaya-chan was crying.
I'm laughing, it's okay, I'm laughing, I'm laughing
Oh
Oh, I'm worried now, what should I do?Who?
I thought she was crying, but there's this amazing princess
The way he laughs is distinctive.
Yeah, it's definitely exciting.
Yeah
Never
[music]
Lovehappshappapp
happ
[music]
[laughter]
happ
Why is Eka laughing like that?
Just
Just change that, something in my own 3D
playing
That's right, I was laughing while playing with myself.
fun
[music]
hey
areyoustreamingKOh
Yeah look atmy
[music]
STREAM
Open
[music]
really
celebratingPARTY
PARTY
Oh, this is only the first round, right?
Tae, that's scary, but it's just one game.
It's a lot of pressure and I'm kind of nervous.
I think the one who will be participating in this will be the other princess.
With Umei-chan
And Azuki Azuki
Let's play with Chan-chan properly.
Naru, you just said you wanted a menu.
Yeah, yeah, the menu is kind of difficult.
I've tried making some rice before, but...
Yes, yes, that's right, I did it.
So I had to cut it or something.
Something
If you can't divide the roles, you'll lose weight.
It is important that the time is strong and cooperation is important.
Yeah, yeah, it seems like that
But on the contrary, Minecraft has been with him for 3 years.
That's about it, but vegetables can't be cut.
That's what I thought, that's right, vegetables.
I thought it was lunchtime, but there are so many knives.
There is a cutting board item, click on cutting board
When you open it, you'll find a knife and place it next to it.
Tomatoes, carrots, etc.
I can cut carrots and potatoes.
So if you add beef, it becomes ground meat, raw meat.
Yes, it's raw meat, that's what Minecraft is like these days.
I mean, I really can't do it anymore.
It seems like this special salt doesn't cut well with regular salt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's the opposite.
It's amazing that you can do that in Minecraft.
It's very possible, I'm sure that's the setting.
I wonder if they're doing something. That's amazing.
But we are so touched by this.
From Minecraft's Kara-chan
I wonder if it's obvious.
Maybe that's why I'm laughing after all.
do not have
hey
I don't know about Yutaka.
[laughter]
No!
Ta
parentheses
[music]
good
kind
[music]
Thank you, do your best, do your best
Good luck guys, I saw you on the street the other day.
I came here just in time.I came here.
Let's go, let's go!
let's go let's go
you
We're making steady progress and building a foothold.
It's going well, it feels good. It feels good.
It feels so good, it's so fast
Okay smooth
Smooth, it's so good, it's so good
Okay, finally, seriously, seriously, seriously, 1
It's not about 1st or 2nd place, it's good.
Okay go go go go you key now with red
They're lining up, hey, hey!
Let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go let's not be number one
Golets Golets Golets Golets Go
Let's go ahead and guess this too.
Nefue made from brown Ufufu wood
Yeah
What, what, what is this?
It's new, so what are you making?
I wonder what it was?
I guess it's true, I don't know from here.
Dao white and pink white and pink this.
Ah, what is this? What is this? I can't answer.
So why?
Share it here too
What are you doing? What are you making?
I'm curious about this cooking Thai.
I'm really curious about this, it's amazing when I'm practicing.
It was like a Meeshi hamburger.
But I'm a benevolent person, and I eat homemade hamburger steaks.
Humber, but what is it actually like? What should I make?
I wonder what it is, what are you doing?
It's okay to bake and cut it.
Grilled
Let's cut vegetables and do our best, do our best, do our best
Give it some chocolate, it looks like a fun dish.
Good luck! I was wondering what you were making.
I guess you're making it. I ate it. I ate it.
I ate it, it was good, it was good, wow wow
hang on
Oh, it's so fast, we're already up to stage 5.
Wow, good luck
But right now it's 2. But red is strong. Red
strong
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
dodge dodge
Apparently this princess is a gorilla.
This princess, my princess, has less than 50 strength.
Don't worry, do your best, do your best
Do your best, you can catch up!
There's a chance, there's a chance, seriously, there's a chance
A certain one-chan is coming out more and more.
Wow, wait for this guy, there's some kind of boss in the back.
It looks like a strong final boss, but in the back
There's nothing floating around.
It's no good, it looks really strong
Not
I love you
Wow, I'm about to go.
Boss, keep up the good work, you scored a goal
No, but I can still do my best. 2 is 22. Do your best.
Good luck color
Do your best, do your best, just a little bit more
Hey, let me fall down, fall down, fall down, nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice
[applause]
nice
Nice, really 3 seconds 3 seconds
So nice nice nice nice nice
Hey, nice, nice, nice, great, amazing.
I don't feel like I was making one.It was definitely a title.
I was also making something that I was curious about.
Let's ask about it later.
Hey, that pink block has a white one on it.
I don't understand
So it's brown, I wonder what it was.
I don't care about that, but the yellow color was amazing.
the last
Before I knew it, we were in a fight
I'm so close to the edge
Not Takocchi
What happened to that? Who was it now? I knew it in an instant.
It wasn't there, I made a mistake.
[music]
hey
Don't worry, we're fishing for flowers at this time.
Can I go?
I'm not interviewing Naruto.
Let's go quickly for a while.
See you there, see you there
I went to pick flowers.
It's an air conditioner right now.
Hey, it's hot and has good soundproofing properties. You should open the one you put on.
Let's turn it on, live without air conditioning
Go
No air conditioning at all in Austrian homes
There's no air conditioner, so what can you do?
Why, it's quite hot in the summer, so turn on the air conditioner.
I'd like to, but my house usually doesn't have an air conditioner.
It's hot to be made, but just in case.
I don't have a problem with it, but it's hot.
It's hot, it's so bright like Japan
It's so different that I can't give it a good name.
Even if someone calls me chocolate, I'll act fast.
Interpretation 1 Even if it were now, I would keep the image quality on all the time.
Furthermore, with the air conditioner
oh
air conditioner love
Love Love is currently being counted Interview Ann
Tally this next one is the last in Lillet
Oh it looks beautiful I'm nervous
Yeah
[music]
ah
It's okay because I'm really bad at real performances.
It's okay, it's okay, I'm scared of the actual performance.
[music]
Yeah, but Nerisa-chan is number one.
Looks like you're super nervous
[music]
Oh yes
No matter how many times after that, no one
I'll forgive myself for that mistake because I can fix it somehow.
I probably feel the pressure the most.
I guess it's the last Iroha-chan after all.
I'm home, I'm home, I'm home, I'm home
Go to the bathroom on the way home
Ta
Tsumi I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
I'm so nervous that I'm going to read the lyrics.
I'm going to pass the baton to my senior, so I'm going to pass the baton to my senior.
Noi-chan is right here in the middle
Why is it not okay? I'll do my best.
I want to do my best, but somehow the actual performance is...
I can't do what I used to do because I don't know
I get it, I get anxious.
That's right, that's the point of Lillet.
I wonder if it's expensive after all. I can confirm it in the last competition.
I wonder what's going on, I think the red team is still pretty big.
It's pretty dominant, so it's like the opposite
Don't worry, you won't be able to turn things around.
Noe looks like it's going to end, doesn't it?
Is it a high image or an understandable reversal?
I don't think that means you can.
I said yes as if there was something about it, so that's it.
Let's take a look at the Hahime race scores.
Yes, yes, the Tokusaun group came in first place.
30 points for the white group and 20 points for the yellow group.
will be 10 points
Yes, the red team is a bit amazing, isn't it?
Maybe the red team will be strong in 2023
I don't know yet
It looks like it's okay, I don't know yet.
I don't know yet, so I'll move on to the next step.
of
Let's move to the competition venue
Okay, let's move for a while.
Yes, is this okay? Come back.
I don't know if it's a good thing, welcome back here.
Only from here
mosquito
That
It's white, it's white, it's white
Oisho TV is so weird
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Everyone was blown away and returned home.
Nice fight
Good seniors are great at cooking
It was fast, it was really fast, it was really fast
You understand, ram ram ram ram.
Grilled lamb
Temora and others are so cute
I'm glad it came out about a minute ago. It's time for practice.
Well, I'm glad I did it. I'm glad I did it.
Actually, it was really hard at first.
It was smooth, right? Let's do our best.
What's going on, Hai-chan? I'm sorry. After this.
It will be the Spring/Summer East Relay, so please join us.
The contestants of the white group
Channel ah blown automatically blown
Re
I see, Nodoka-chan's
Before the announcement was made, the contestants were told that
I see, the most advanced technology is the foremost.
It's very easy to understand, so it's easy to understand.
Hey, I'm saved, I'm saved, please be healthy and give me a little flower
Let's go, dash and go
Hello, let's go
Hello, it's better to enter
That's good, I'll enter it and see what happens.
You can get it, so open that book.
I wonder who I am, who is White?
It came, it came, it came, it came.
It's okay, just right click.
[music]
I'm number 8 on the entry list.
What's up with Ame-chan when she's your own big manipulator?
It's a layer, but it seems like it's somewhere in the middle.
memory
This is the leader's place. Neme-chan is on the 5th floor. 5-5
The 5th total Oimu is all about this and that, Mume-chan is 33
Okay
I see, now you can enter.
It's okay to say "I'm done, I'm done, I'm done"
Hey, look at me, Naba is awesome
Oh wow, my calico is shaky right now
That's right, it's okay, you can do it, don't be weak
It's okay, can I go?
Oanka is okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
dodge
Okay, I'm nervous at the end too.
hey
have
Ah, I was able to enter, but 99
It's becoming
[music]
Na
a
[music]
Oh nice
Nice smug smug
nice
Okay, no, this one-chan, this water is also good.
First, it's the turn of the contestants.Yes, the first layer is the contestant.
Nerisa Yes, next is Choco Sensei Nao Yes, the third layer is
The fourth floor of the Mumee is Commander Noel.
And the 5th layer is Ameha yes, the 6th layer is Kaela.
Yes, I'm glad you're here so I'll finish it off with a smile.
I'm getting to know you more or less.
It's nice to have someone who's used to Minecraft come in.
I feel like I'm about to catch up
That's right, I feel that way.
Let's go for an interview.Yes.
what
I can hear everyone in the white group.
I can hear it
Is it okay then?
Who should I choose?
It's okay if I don't care, but I love it.
Anka hogogehogehogohoteruhogo nana
Before I knew it, my feet had become anchors.
It's early so I'm sure things will work out, trust me.
I want to do my best because it's amazing.
Thank you very much
I really want White to take first place.
Do your best, do your best, do your best
Do your best
thank you
Yes, that's it for the last time.
Ri-san has been on mute for a long time.
Orio came back from Yoishocho Hana.
return
That's right, it's Nerisa-chan from earlier.
Open book when you're confused
I heard it says open book.
It didn't arrive
I was the leader who responded in an embarrassing and embarrassing manner.
Yes, there is
Let's do our best, it's just luck when it comes to water.
If you come to the bottom
Let's go back and do our best
Let's do our best, let ...
Let's do our best. That's my ear. It's fallen off.
fire
a
Yeah, the water is so cute!
teeth
Haa
terrible
Yay, I'm going to practice with my long sleeves.
height
The mental system that is starting to become dangerous
It's okay, it's okay
Do your best. It's okay. It's okay because everyone is here.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay today
It's okay if it's prison, it's okay if you think it's okay
[laughter]
Okay, you're really working hard.
This is the last one, so let's go easy on the last one.
That's right, you'll have to laugh at the end, right?
I think I'll go eat some meat when this is over.
Talking to the other chocolate line, Azuki and chocolate
I was talking to the line. Yakiniku Yakiniku Owa
Shabu-shabu
[music]
Good luck with Ishiei Ikinari, Rediff.
Fa
Fight-san go go go
Go go, do your best, do your best, do your best
Do your best and calm down. I'll be waiting for you.
Come on, come on
Idea go go go go go go
Come on
Kamona nice catch nice catch
nice
Kiki nice bullet nana nice bullet
nice nice
Brainy Brett
Sure.
Iaaare
go go go go
Do your best, leave it to me, leave it to me, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine
Okay, finally, finally, finally
Good run, chocolate is good, you're good, you're on top.
It's okay, yeah, there are times like that.
It looks good, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, I can go.
It's okay, it's okay, it's totally fine.
It's totally fine, go, go, go.
Go, go, wait and cheer, I don't know who I am
Gone
Wait a minute
[music]
Well, I'm nervous
Wait this
[music]
Panpan
Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
tea
Do your best, try your best, Ini-chan.
I can go
height
[music]
Dodo Yaya
It's okay, it's okay, it's long.
Okay
Please do your best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Let's go, I'll do my best
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Yo
The orchestra is running, it's running, early episode
It's fast, it's fast, it feels good, it feels good, it's hard
I'll do my best, please do your best
ah
Tasty
I can go, I can go.
You can do it Kara-chan, good luck
Nice frog, keep up the good work and stay stable
Good luck
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go go go go
Yukiyuki
keep it up
Ma
[music]
I'm going to be sucked in from now on.
Or nice
nice
Oh, finally, do your best, Azuchi, do your best, Aki
Senpai, this feels like you need to get punched.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, yes
Yes, just eat
Do your best, try your best, try your best
I can't do my best, I can't do my best, yes, I'll do my best
Okay, let's go
Hayaroha
Let's do it
Oishio, wait, where is it? It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay
Ores Gores Go Lets Go Lets Go
Okay okay okay okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Good, good, no, no.
nice
Nice nice nice fight nice
Let's fight when it's over
That was a nice run
long
Good luck, good luck, good luck!
Ta
Kaiya Red is strong after all.
It was really good, it was really good
[music]
I forgot to eat. It's Nope.
It's okay, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry
I'm hungry, so I'll fill you up when I'm done.
Let's eat yeah yeah
Nice run, nice run, nice run
Nice yeah yeah
Nice I want to eat meat I want to eat meat
Meat, meat, let's go, meat, meat, yes, yes, yes, my heart is
Thank you for your hard work now it hurts
I want to eat some Japanese sub-sub.
Like, let's all eat, let's eat
everyone
So we'll eat shabu-shabu together.
Shabu shabu
delicious
Cute, cute, soothing
So cute, let's go and shabu-shabu.
I'm sure the chocolate battle will take me.
Please take me with you
Give me all the chocolate
Let's leave it to Choco Sensei's Choices Berry
Good super nice
[music]
Yeah, leave it to me
I don't want to leave it to you, but I tried really hard. I tried my best.
Yesterday
Please, let's go to the interview. Hey, white group white.
You did your best, you did your best, it was amazing
You did your best, you did your best
Okay, let's talk about Iha, who served as the anchor.
Shall we talk and listen to it one more time? Yes, yes, yes.
I don't care how it went, we started from the beginning.
It'll be okay until the end, everything will be fine.
Let's connect and relax
It's okay
There are many things that have been left out and left out.
But I wish I could finish in 2nd place.
wonderful wonderful
It was a great nice fight Guccio
Nafuna yo
Tell them you've had a great run
Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
Are you using it well? Are you using it well?
Yoyoyo, how many holidays are there for the exam?
It's already level 1 in the test ranking, wow.
I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it!
This is Kamaeruha
Awesome, it was so good
It seems like everyone has already lost.
Soon to be gone
I'm so old
It felt so sexy. It was really good.
No, it's second place ... 2nd place, it's stubborn
Everyone worked really hard, everyone worked hard.
No, I worked hard, I worked hard, I worked hard
To be honest, at first it was easy to feel like I was having fun.
But I felt like I was going to try my best.
No way
Yeah, I didn't know the final result until the end.
I wonder what's going on. It's the final episode.
We will hold a vigil ceremony, so please gather in front of everyone.
Please
[music]
I can't wait at first
Noso de Gozaru Gaku's
Please, there was an invisible wall. I can see it now.
There was a colander wall
We were locked up, we were sealed away.
I was trapped in this school right now.
My throat is a bit rattled after taking out all of it.
Furthermore, the white row is beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
What a mess
Is it okay? I feel free.
After all, I have some feelings.
I love fashion so where are you now?
I won't lose again
In that team where we fight with each other
Looks like the colors are very different
It's yellow, calm and loud.
Yo Polka, Yo Polka, Why don't you try Polka?
The bread that Bokaoi bread also has is the bread that cheers you up.
have
I'm playing a black game, but I can't use it.
I'm sorry, but it's okay if you proceed with that.
Yes, yes.
The cat ceremony is about to begin, but how is it going?
I wonder what will happen next.
I didn't understand it at all, but yeah
Everyone is working together so well.
It's amazing how hard you work, it's a close battle every year.
I thought it was amazing and worth seeing.
I guess it's true, to each his own.
There was drama, or rather there was.
I think it's a drama that includes practice.
However, I think it was really good.
I'm getting eaten by something
So
Ose-mo-san can't do it, so I'm talking about Mi-chan now.
Ta
It's coming from
It was a bit of a shame, wasn't it?
The mother of the sea is so strong, she calms down all at once
I'm here now.
It seems like relationships are scary, but it's okay.
Everyone, can our voices be heard? Can they be heard?
I can hear it. It has arrived. It has arrived.
So, before the closing ceremony,
This time for the competition, I moved the voice chat.
There were so many
Everyone, please support me there.
A word to A-chan and Nodo-chan who gave it to me
I'm thinking of having it.Good morning.
channodochan
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work. This is the voice of heaven. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you again this year, everyone.
His hard work and personality are overflowing, and
The three organizers did their best.We all did our best.
I was able to see it, so I was very impressed.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much everyone
Thank you very much, all of you.
I think it was fun to be able to participate
So please do your best until the end.
Thank you very much
So that's it everyone.
The closing ceremony will now be held.First of all,
Closing remarks: Yes, the sports day will be held.
Please give a greeting from the committee chairperson, Samiko.
Well, yes, everyone at this sports day.
Was it fun? It was fun. It was fun.
It was really fun, everyone was great.
Yo
Thank you very much. Every year, every year.
Thank goodness I've been really busy.
Koro Live is getting busy.
But even so, there were so many people gathered together.
Hey, let's all cooperate and each and every one of us can really do it together.
I saw people taking the initiative to call out to each other and help each other.
Nemiko and the others have already seen everything.
I'm really really impressed.
That's what I think every time, really all the time.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much
Thank you for taking this opportunity.
Tarama, it's all about the newcomers and that.
After all, members of en and ali
In the future, there will be more interaction, and we will all do more together.
I wish we could make Hololive more exciting.
I think it's great, so I'll look forward to it in the future.
Thank you very much. That's great.
Thank you very much. Next
Mio-chan please yes everyone this year
Thank you very much for participating and do your best.
I did my best.
It was a blast from Gan-chan.
Everyone is super great, so this year too.
Thank you for the finish
Thank you thank you
Yes, next Subaru, now Subaru too.
Just for a moment, just as a contact.
See the various faces of the team.
That's why I was allowed to do it.
All the teams are working hard now
Well, I think the results will come out this time.
Let's do it! There's one thing we all worked hard on.
I don't think a big nightmare would be a treasure.
So please make use of our bond in the future.
I think it was really fun to watch
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much thank you
Better
Tai Nice Peach Senkyu
Nice senkyu senkyu say yes
Finally, let's announce the general benefits.
I would like to visit.Okay, come here! Announcement of benefits.
is about 1 and then 100
About 10 at the end
I would like to make an announcement at
Well then, Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson.
Thank you for your specific announcement.
Okay, let's start by announcing 1.
Masuhai
Oh then the door
Wow, I can see this from here, the red team is 8
The white team is 8, yeah, I want to wait and see the yellow team.
But what's on the screen? It's scary now.
Still scared
I know, I know, I know, okay, let's continue.
I'll announce about 100 first.Yes, yes.
Yes, 100 is here.
Please go ahead
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
I have all of these, about 100 of them.
Yes, please, please, no way!
I'll go to the end, everyone, please, I'll go to the end
about 10 announcements
Desuseeno
Please wow
Uhai
What?
20 red 158 uh white
138 Yellow 106 Yellow is 106
Just a little more
Tasui
regrettable
Amazing water
Roro Friendly Please Please
It's friendly and 2nd place with 138 points
White team, 3rd place became Wood team with 106 points.
Well done everyone, well done everyone
You did your best, you did your best, everyone did your best.
That's great, that's great, that's why I'm giving the award.
Is that true? Yes, the awards ceremony will be held this time.
Yes, everyone is welcome.
This is Geo with the same medal as the yellow group.
Well, first of all, representative of the players and teachers of the yellow group.
For those who are Hacos, Hacos Bechanbe-chan
Yes, please come forward. Come here.
Please let me have a medal for 3rd place.
How about bye?
Niao, wait a minute.
[music]
Wow, that's amazing!
Teru
Tsuoe, that's amazing, you can do that.
Thank you so much for giving me 4 of them! That's amazing!
That's amazing, congratulations!
Oh everyone's on everyone's side
It's amazing, everyone seems to be following it.
I don't think I'll make it.
It's Ozu-chano who won the silver medal for the white team.
Please be careful, I'll catch you
No, I'm kinda looking forward to it too.
Dokisu force is amazing Jaa-chan new medal
This is Geo, congratulations to the white team!
It's so hot, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's so silver
Congratulations on your silver medal.
Congratulations and thank you very much
congratulations
Osa and Hai and
This is Geo, the red team gold medalist who came in first place.
I want to see the Yotowa-sama Watowaoki medal
Thank you and congratulations
[applause]
Hey this
And this is Hololive
Karai is so nostalgic
hand
I can't really show it
It disappeared so quickly
There were so many diamonds, but in an instant
I'm not saying that it's beautiful now.
With all that said, Hololive Sports Festival!
Everyone who will make 2023 a crime
Thank you very much
Ta
That's not to say it's a bit strange
Why do you want to take a commemorative photo?
Well then, what should I do?
Let's put it on that table in the middle over there.
Yes, please, yes, it's in front of you.
Yes, okay, let's move. Maybe it's ducking.
duck
To a game that you can't go back to
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Kanata Ayabai lined up in the upper right corner
Yo
This one goes in too, yes, this one goes in too.
[music]
Yoo
Hey, I can see it! I'm finally back!
Where is that all?
Wait, it's still not time yet
Sorry Sorry
Please wait, please wait a moment
Lisori Mi-chan is there.
of
It hasn't arrived yet, even to us.
Everyone is lying, it's amazing they're following us too
Wow that's so true I'm so happy
I didn't get a medal because I failed once.
But the medal is really big
Those who are looking for medals are missing medals
That doesn't happen without
Well, if you do it one more time, you won't lose your temper.
There's no need to worry, it's okay
not at all
That's sad Medalbo
difference
Can you go like that? Give me that.
I can't give you anything, wait a minute, Mio-senpai.
Mio-senpai should take care of that.
Thank you. I'm glad I came.
Thank you very much, thank you very much
That's good. Well then, everyone, look at those eyes.
That little place from before
Should I watch it? Koro-san, maybe I should watch it.
Koro-san is flying as if he can see Sanro-san.
I feel like I'm flying
Taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah-oh-oh-gases stuffs stuffs in front of me.
Hey, cameraman, hey, cameraman, right here, right here.
There's something here, here, here, here, here, there, etc.
There's a cameraman
Yes, everyone, are you okay? Can you see the photo?
I'll take a picture. Let's take a picture.
[music]
mercari mercari
Hey hey, who threw it again this year? Who threw it just now?
Who will pitch this year?
It just so happened that someone threw it and it made me fly.
Everyone is throwing stuff like that.
Here we go again, don't throw away the trash, trash, trash
Please take it home, but I hope you can see it.
Thank you for coming over
To all the listeners who asked for it
And he cooperated a lot behind the scenes.
All the management staff are always
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Well then, Hololive
Sports day
It will end after 2023 Yes, that's it
See you again everyone
I'm going to Hololive, yes yes yes I'm going
Horaiba Otsuotsu
Hololive!
[music]
Let's get along, let's get along
What Shirodo did is dangerous
Oh no no no no no no everyone, bye-bye
Bye-bye-bye-baby-baby everyone
bye bye
Bye bye bye bye
[music]
By saying yes, Hol Live Sports Day
2023 is probably over
Maybe it's over
Tata
I guess you can watch it for a long time.
Thank you very much, and what about the white team?
2023 ended successfully with second place
Thank you very much for your help.
See you again in the next broadcast. Delicious
Thank you for your comment, super
Gesomo joined the chat
Thank you very much
Thank you for your hard work, Otsu Hololive Kaotsu Holo
It was live
Bye bye thank you
Neja
[music]
hey
Y
[music]
D
DET