[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Applause]
[Music]
p
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
wow wowow
what
the what the
[\h__\h] I can't properly time out people
when I'm in hyper chat but when I switch
to not hyper chat half of most of the
chat
disappears don't
laugh if you laugh you're part of the
problem well if there's any mods who saw
that please Bonk him if you know what I
mean just
for a
timeout thank you for the memberships w
thank you let's go 20 what happened anti
Authority why what why why
why what made you feel like
this thank
you guys I think I have realized why my
pink uh razor
controller when I was trying to use it
previously uh occasionally why it wasn't
working I just saw in the back there's a
little switch if you have a razor
controller you might know there's a
little switch there's free free settings
there's PS4 and BT I don't know what BT
is then there's USB and then there's PC
and
BT and I always had it on
PS4 so a Bluetooth
ah so maybe that's why it wait the USB
isn't even even what I expected whatever
I'll use my PS5
controller the back the the USB thingy
part of
the of the razor isn't even uh you know
the the smooth one it's the one that
still has the the Donk donks
whatever
yeah sure PS5 controller connected means
Maybe it's going to start some
Shenanigans but I don't I don't even
hear a connection sound AO shouldn't
there be one
wait hello ah there we go I heard it
now
okay okay today we're going to be a cat
uh oh by the way kikiki I guess I just F
today I should be meowing but k
what I sounded like a robot but only for
you
right meow K
Kow meow K is better
maybe
meow I had a good nap with my cat
falling asleep with my face and my hand
on smoothie
ah and then waking up to Stewie from
Fall Guys Fall
Guys
family having a existential
crisis uh well it's the same initials
and I guess I was still tired
[Laughter]
now Stewie from Fall Guys I'm still
waking up
H okay wait let's see is my controller
going to work when I open the game
[Music]
uh it's 7 p.m. yeah so what who says who
says a nap has to be during noon time
why can it not be like a little bit in
the
afternoon
uh okay open the game please thank you
oh oh I I bought this game already a
while ago but when I was on Steam I saw
so many things that I kind of
wanted uh and that were on sale so I
bought three other games just
now I bought wizard with a gun I think
it has good reputation and it's a co-op
game an online co-op game Wizard with a
gun do you know
it yeah it's good right it's just
already like from a few screenshots I
could already tell I think this is a
good game that people
like
uh where's my game
here and then the other one I bought
which I thought I bought ages ago and I
mean this is maybe not as good but I I
kind of like the idea of it is Minecraft
done
and then uh what was the last
one oh I bought it with like all kinds
of DLCs as
well and the other one I yeah the other
one was potion craft I need to play a
potion craft and Storyteller both of
these games I saw like oh I was like ah
I kind of want to play this one
[Music]
time I want to
play it's
cute they're both cute and I think might
be both okay for members only as
well
okay all righty by the
way uh
nothing uh wait you guys need to be a
little bit
more over
here okay H oh wait it's
German it is German iic
uh I can probably change
that I just thought the tail of the cat
was its
lag oh the matter the PS5 controller
stole my
audio Yeah it's all on the Dual sense
wireless controller as I
thought there we
go it's always
uh
English
uh button
prompt PlayStation let's go thank you
Game for thinking about that amazing
okay I
applied
now you should have kept it in German
well it doesn't matter in the end it's
just meow meow and then we can just say
and then we'll be
good uh let's get into this I think we
might have a chance of finishing it also
with today it's pretty short as far as I
know so let's go although if I want to
go 100% that's a bit crazy but let's
just do you know let's just
chill meow meow meow meow
meow I yeah we're in
Japan we're in Japan in this
game this is shingo but with
cats oh she's purring kitty cat is
[Music]
purring it's a good stret oh yes oh no
oh no oh
no you stupid sysy cat no oh that looks
Majestic ah cat can fly
[Music]
it's a bit loud I'm going change it in a
moment a cute it's like what the
[\h__\h] she get out of here ow ow ow ow
those those claws
no oh no superhero Landing oh I have to
wiggle myself
out can I change the settings
now where am I
I'm cute okay we have an uh we have
to-do list get back home we have cat
achievements ah we have an inventory I
already know that these are hats for our
little cat I watched uh like a good
chunk I'll admit of D Nintendo stream on
this
game but it was like in the middle of it
not in the
beginning yeah yeah yeah so don't worry
oh this is still
German and so I no I wanted to
change is this a purring
sound is this a purring
sound
okay sounds like it cute oh yeah and
then on the right we have like Dingle
dangles and waas Feathers which makes
perfect sense to have to get that too
because unless if I don't do that then I
won't be able to return it into a
phoenix right and
salmon well let's
go okay we have to get home easy it's
isn't it up
there let's be uh explor rative and
maybe
explosion if explosive
cat must be explorative but also make
things blow
up oh oh this is how I punch things all
right all right all right very important
oh this is how I
run
ow okay yeah I know water has to be
avoided I can jump like that I can hold
on to some
stuff but I
can't wait can I get get rid of these
papers
no ah left and right oh oh [\h__\h] punch
left punch Right
Punch Yeah okay so welcome to Japan
everybody I'm a I'm a cat lost in Tokyo
and it's because of partially because of
the stupid shba you know that on here
oh
wait
wait what was happening was was I about
to lay down no oh I thought I was about
to lay down I was just like circling
just
because but if you Circle a little bit
too much then it starts catching its own
tail
cute Peak cat behavior cute my cats
don't ever chase their tail until unless
you put something on their tail like a
sticker or so that it's like what the
[\h__\h] I think that's more of a dog
thing my cat does Chase his tail really
I feel like it's more common though with
dog
oh ball wait this is
open why' you leave it open pickup a
cute in my mouth oh I we need this tool
I think I need it because today me and
my mom were gardening quite a bit but
also I didn't we realize we I didn't
have a
shovel and we went to buy a shovel but
the only like we went to S several
supermarkets to buy a shovel hoping that
they would maybe have one but all they
had was like children's shovels so now I
have a children's shovels shovel but
it's pretty big for being a children's
shovel so no worries it kind of worked
for what we wanted to do but this thing
would be useful too I think not sure
what it's really for but it looks like
looks like it could be
useful if it works it works exactly
hello thanks for letting me in you have
your fridge right in the entrance
actually that's having your kitchen
right at the entrance for Japanese one
room Apartments is really common I don't
know about houses to
wait if this room cannot be
open but this is the only open room for
us surely there's something we can
collect here right ah oh I get
achievement for decluttering things
let's go then we just we have to break
things I
think and maybe throw things down but
then now I've pushed it into a stupid
position
there we go it's got to go down oh the
the rice
cooker can I oh wait ah that's what
that's for this house is opening so I
can go over
here now ah wonderful music in my ears
not that stupid wind chime but
this yeah that's music in my ears
[\h__\h] off all right oh Precision jump
with the real X okay aha wait that's can
I cancel that wo wait think I got to go
to the
edge yeah nice jump oh wait I had to go
here anyway because oh I would have had
to find a solution anyway how to get oh
wait I think could I not have climbed up
the no I think that's a skill for
later to be able to to climb up this Le
these leaves so in any case I went in
the house without knowing that I'd have
to go in there anyway to find this
solution not
all cuz I can't walk over the water I am
not Jesus uh
or was that even
Jesus wow wow wow if it isn't the Flying
K are you talking to me well I don't see
any other small cats casually [\h__\h]
innocent crows in mid
a that was you I'm so sorry it was an
accident you see an accident sounds like
you need more flying
practice but I can't actually fly and
you never well with that attitude come
on just flap your wings and follow
me that's not how it
works
no well I'll find you later catch you on
the flip side should I go down no
probably not one oh there's a hole on
the ground down there
though oh and there's a person there ah
you're doing like splish SPL art I can
help you with that I'm a master in
Splish SPL
art oh yeah I think they probably want
me to
help
right and oh I know
how I okay punch the buckets get color
on my
Paws oh I get how he likes it though is
he not like why the [\h__\h] is this cat in
my garden but yeah I do
this yes although I would be very
concerned about my cats if they um
walked into
paint with their paws IRL I would panic
I would
immediately if I find them pick them up
and wash their paws oh you like it are
you welcoming of
this
y m artist graphic design is this
Kitty's
passion well this is definitely toxic
for the cat
[Music]
oh good pull damn this cat can do
anything
yoooooo oh nice yeah get that out of
there what are are these tennis balls
doing did somebody play tennis ball in
the tennis ball tennis in the
neighborhood and
just they just scattered everywhere
yay I make
music L1 for crawling there we go
aute what are you doing I know you can
do it that's what this hole is
for a there we go I think I just have to
press it
once ah okay cuz I was holding it down
but it seems like you just press it once
and then into the right direction and
then it go it goes that way okay ball
why is there so many balls
why is there so many
balls oh wait maybe there's an
achievement for getting the ball into
this
goal
no um
wait yeah yeah yeah that's good a good
slap a good
smack so close no sheesh yeah back of
the net one of the four there's four of
these
I'm soccer player let's go so talented
zomies R1 R1 no what what did I miss the
Zoomies a here they are but
how
R1 oh wait that's right why was I
pushing L1 guys I don't
[Music]
know this oh oh oh ow you mean dashing
is
doomies ah well yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
not always not every situation but
usually if a cat is zooming then it's
dashing and then suddenly stopping
like yeah like this and
[Music]
[Applause]
then this is this is how how
that but maybe you know sometimes maybe
a cat is running because of something
else I see maybe can we walk on this
little
path [\h__\h] ouch that hurt my
heart then we probably have to find a
hole or can we uh can we
climb wait how do I hold on again
I think it's a skill right I can't climb
here I
think other side oh is there a hole on
the other
side ah ah not hold ah did you guys play
the
game skill issue exactly oh and then I
can go this way too but ah it's
blocked
oh okay
no we just have eyes
wow what such a dark she but you know
you look like a
bear find the crow y thank you for
saving me hey be quiet over
there honestly there dogs F they on the
street so there you are what what took
you so long
did you forget to Flap your wings I
don't have wings what then how were you
flying I wasn't I was falling I fell off
my window spot which was apparently on
the I don't know 65th floor and now I'm
all the way down here
meow but if you can't fly how are you
planning to get back up
there oh is it there
oh we're right there what if I'm out
really loud maybe my owner will hear me
cuz the window is open but that would be
too
easy
[Music]
uhoh you're in quite the pickle aren't
you let me have a
think ah I've got it how about that
inferior flying that you wingless
creatures do with the huffing at the
puffing at the claws do you mean
climbing
meow that's what I said
car I'm not sure I have the energy for
climbing
[Laughter]
cat yapping I was already getting hungry
when I
fell oh so if a friendly neighborhood
Crow happen to have a lovely juicy
fish
really oh then this brings us to
familiar Crow territory Supply the bed
CR I can supply one yummy fish for full
of energy and I will demand 25 shinies
cra what's a
shiny you must know what shinies
are they're the gleaming do thats you
find everywhere in buses Ledges
sometimes under traffic
codes and they're valuable valuable
they're
Priceless uh should I get 25 f
for
yes did I say Priceless I meant
worthless oh dangerous even to everyone
except cows in fact they shouldn't even
be lying around the city like this they
could hurt somebody so if you collect 25
shinies I'll be able to dispose of them
very
responsibly we will be
heroes then I and then I get a fish sure
I'm on it all right with the fish will
have power ah it's okay it's okay I'm
not going there sh sh sh
scary but this reminds me like this
makes me feel like I'm looking for Ollie
again this
street
Ollie
Ollie Ollie are you
somewhere I have found a
shiny okay guys I I started watching uh
shun you
yeah it's kind of confusing but it's
pretty good already yeah I'm I'm uh
quite happy with the acting so far
too except for the little boy I feel
like the little boys acting is pretty
bad but besides that it's pretty good
um I was I was kind of confused uh this
this is in the first episode just a
little thing that I've
observed um this what's his name what's
the what's the Foreigner dude's name
his oh nice
stream
uh uh what was that again black F yeah
is this based on a real story by the way
I feel like the at least the
Japanese like dudes I think they might
be based on real people
right nice kind of he was also a real
person really okay so okay this happens
in the first episode so don't worry it's
not really a spoiler
um oh nice can I get much
higher genuine question um there's this
dude I forgot the name this Japanese
dude ah we got a hat I think Apple
hat this Japanese dude were like pretty
much in the beginning where uh uh yeah
they're they are going out to find never
Foreigner
and uh well he says I want to they stand
on the cliff and he says I want to do it
and then the dude Japanese dude he's
like no I'll do it
right
cute uh because like uh yeah it's like
oh oh this is a challenge I have to do
it and then black for is like [\h__\h] you
suck I don't think you'll you should let
me do it I'm better at
this oh it's blocked okay and then he's
like H well okay then if you insist on
doing it go ahead you'll see
that you're not made for this you're not
cut out for
this uh and then we see the Japanese
dude failing and he's like a respectable
person right he's like what's his status
I don't
know but there's like his underlings are
there
too and so like he doesn't want to be
put in a situation where he's undermined
by this random Foreigner
right the Japanese Pride then yeah so
then he's he he kind of falls down the
cliff he falls down the cliff uh because
like they were holding a rope but then
he just slips and he falls down and he
kind of like almost breaks his [\h__\h]
back and then he like down there is the
other Foreigner that they wanted to
rescue can I get in
here
um maybe not and and then yeah he just
kind of gets [\h__\h] by the way
and being already like almost broken his
back and yeah so he's having a lot of
problems and seeing that black forign
first is like haha well that's what I
told you what was going to
happen but then he's he watches the
Japanese uh
dude uh about to commit
seu bless you and I
I I was like oh [\h__\h] and black phone was
also like eh what the [\h__\h] is he
doing what is he doing cuz he didn't
know seu right but this is the the
second time in the show that they are
like showing that somebody is about to
commit zuku but they don't they don't
because his underlings finally
oh thank
God finally
uh what was I saying yeah finally he's
being rescued from the from his
underlings right in the moment when he
was about to commit seppuku with his
Katana uhoh uh-oh no no no no no no I'm
a good kitty I'm a little
kitty y that [\h__\h] scares me can I I can
still go there okay I can even put it
and pick it up mhm I'm not going to say
something what I want was going to say I
stopped myself because you guys were
going to say phrasing
Ki anyway wait let me pick that up first
then if that's not where I'm
going and anyway so the moment he sees
that he still doesn't know what the [\h__\h]
he's doing banana let's
go and anyway he gets back up the
Japanese dude gets back up and even
though
even though black for should be like
well i' [\h__\h] told you suddenly he's
acting like he's getting on his knees
and doing uh DOA like bowing to him
really deeply and he's like suddenly
really respectful of him but like dude I
mean why because of the seku thing
because like it's certainly can't be his
performance down there first you were
like you know laughing about him and
you're still not not really impressed by
these Japanese
people but he respects the act of
Honor I thought it was a really sudden
change of heart I thought
that it it doesn't make I it felt a
little bit out of character for me you
know I I I I understand that eventually
he will have a lot of respect for
Japanese people and he'll be learning
the language and
everything I already read that on on
Wikipedia
H cuz I was trying to understand what
the [\h__\h] is happening in the first
episode um I get that but that seemed
kind of forced yeah to
me sudden like just because like he
didn't even at this point he didn't even
really understand yet what that was he
asked later like seemingly a day later
or so he asked the other foreign guy
that um he rescued so he didn't have
this understanding yet of
what seu actually was but already seems
really impressed by him considering
it choosing his own death so to say but
I don't know you guys if you watched it
did you feel the same way
like like this was kind of weird or was
I the only one who felt this way you
guys got to watch shun you have to watch
everything that I watch is ah what's his
name yush
was he abush let's just say the writing
is particularly highbrow in the source
material either
uhhuh a little bit at that episode I
want to watch it I thought it was cool
the way blackr
reacted or you thought the the
consideration of seku was
cool I think he just bowed because he
didn't
know yeah but like yeah he didn't know
Japanese yet and he just bowed because
he couldn't say anything yeah but like
at the same time his face and his bow
showed that he felt some sudden respect
he was like really
Shook and I'm just like why are you why
are you feeling this way I'm kind of
confused
man oh
nice like how did you suddenly go from
haha you suck to OMG
suy uh can
I can I get up there
no oh wait I feel like I saw it go onto
the planter wait let's try no is this
possible from here I feel like it
could maybe from
here no
oh sheesh ow maybe not episode 2 is
really good yeah I'm already in episode
two but then I was cuddling with
smoothie and I got so tired from
cuddling not that it's exhausting but
you
know because well oh let's get over
there wait how do I cancel the jumps
well let's get up
here yeah oh this is really
dangerous is this what outdoor cats get
up oh well it it as I said it's
dangerous what Shenanigans am I supposed
to do here anything else that I didn't
do yet oh
oh maybe
no box y if I fits I sits oh there's
five boxes where I have to sit in like
this y y run run what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] I was stuck in that
location let's talk to this gu C just a
box excuse
me hi I was wondering if you could help
me I'm the mayor if the mayor can't help
you no one can thank goodness I found
you you see you worship I need to get
home and I need shinies and there all
are all these trash cans
and one thing at a time friend this all
sounds like work kids are not built for
S
work get are built for mischief and
snoring we are served sleepy sometimes
there is
wimsy sometimes there is pushing things
onto the floor yeah
but your enthusiasm is ding the mayor
cannot help anyone V sleepy I didn't
mean
to you must help the mayor achieve nap
time it is only red and
proper oh you know
French cat
French your first responsibility as
Deputy Mayor will be the hated jar of JB
I already did it I already did it remove
these eyes from Theos Vision but it's
just
jam it is a sybol a symbol that human no
longer fears a cat they leave the glass
jar on JS and expect them to stay there
I cannot continue I
cannot I guess that makes sense but when
you say remove them swab push
crash and the breaking of the jars will
be a l be of your poor mayor and then
you'll help me the mayor cannot hear you
over the noise of the symbolic
jam oh there's another one up there all
righty the symbolic Jam yeah yeah yeah
these [\h__\h] humans they're making a
fool of us [\h__\h] this
Jam yeah wait there's another one this
is this
is he making me crazy too now that I'm
being told about it oh did she see
me oh is she cleaning it
up oh she's cleaning it up okay wait we
need we need the safe passage to the
last the last Jam thingy
okay ah wait I'm still really bad at
like oh am I allowed in here
generally oh okay oh no the
waters The Dangerous Waters of the deep
sea are here to drown
me there we
go now he can sleep my friend
cat wobbly water no scariest [\h__\h] of my
life um before you do you Grace you said
you could
help yes a will now thisp valuable as
stes you know the way I say stuff like
passage and so really helps for French
ja
assist
assist thank you help be me I will teach
you the official way to respond to
J wait what or anything else that is
terrible
voila oh cute it's a
sticker yuck face cute you may now
Express disgust at any moment by holding
uh uh
triangle okay thank you I
guess this isn't quite
[Music]
what a has no need of your gratitude
little Deputy oh sorry yeah thank you or
not thank you and now the mayor must
rest so sleepy so unable to hear further
request for help but
this how you sleep in French by the
way wait what are these what do I do
with the is there something to do with
these do I have to like collect them as
well wouldn't it be silent really is it
that silent in
French but if how else do you sleep do
French people not sleep then how the
[\h__\h] do you
sleep they sleep silently more like
s the de is not silent unless it is okay
okay so there's Case by case
situation I have to turn this
on we can go this
way we sleep in Al wait you say that as
if you're French we have a couple of
French people in the chat it sounds like
we do oh nice little garden Japanese
garden
wait what the [\h__\h] is this ah nice
shovel oh do I put it
there oh is is just ah it's a nice place
to sleep yeah we the shovel in my mouth
yay one of the seven yeah yeah that's
also a thing I saw there's like places
to sleep
in
specific I'm have
French stupid tree stupid broccoli small
tree is
broccoli a Canadian are you a
Canadian oh that is so beautiful in
Canada you speak uh this language of the
Gods every once in a while yes I
understand there's a freaking chameleon
why chameleon on the house
why hello
the way it talks is
like are you talking to me of course you
can see me um yeah astonishing I've
never met anyone who could see through
my Superior camouflage does this mean my
power is
fading who are you I'm known by many
names the shrouded sensation the
invisible lizard the white ver to you go
wonder why does he have an accent now
too I don't know I have HED my
camouflage craft to the point where I
can blend in perfectly with my
surroundings or so I fault for example
wait the chat box is changing colors the
whole time oh my God oh my God I just
realized I'm so good at disguising
myself that I can even make my words
disappear watch
these
wow wow you're just staying silent
see that no you didn't because my words
are totally camouflaged whoa that's sick
thank you it took years to
pervert but if you're master of
camouflage how come I can see you quite
perhaps it's to do with your eyes being
so weird when your eyes are weird what
the
[\h__\h] but kind of cute I like how they're
popping out of your
head m m are weird have you seen
them I don't think I can you'll just
have to tell
me well for is AR they're on the front
of your face that's weird yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah it is but have you seen the
humans and they don't seem to stick out
at all they're right inside your head
taking a valuable brain worm
true
true how did you say it like that h M we
could have more brain if we had less
[Laughter]
eyes maybe I just use my eyes for
thinking can you at least move them in
different directions at the same time
some people can but not me should I be
worried do you think I couldn't say I'm
a magician not a b however I if feel
weird and inferior eyes are truly immune
to my Vanishing
act then I have finally met a worthy
opponent is he
happy wait what I must learn to outsmart
your weird eyes I will done new
disguises practice New Tricks engage in
the noble art of
self-improvement I don't want you to
change on my
account yeah like uh uh don't do it on
Main um I don't know because cat said
account
so you laughing you're
laughing let's
goo that was good
sheesh that was good I get that one
let's
go ah sweet kitty so weird so small so
wrong no can restore my reputation as
the world's most fil creature I must
change it is the only way to defeat your
weird eyes when you say you want to
defeat my eyes I challenge you to find
me again cat here no I shall leave this
place while I adjust my technique when I
shall reappear somewhere else obviously
I will be almost impossible to detect so
I will leave you with a clue to my
general location uhhuh there's a place
where hard hats shine where concrete PS
and diggers wine I'll become a flash
nearby invisible to your weird eye wow
that was beautiful have you ever heard
of a poetic license no well I have one
and I'm not afraid to use it anyway good
luck finding
me puff puff puff puff puff and there it
goes is that the only thing to find here
maybe oh wait no there's a shiny thing
we need what was it
easy more shiny things we have eight now
let's
go and then wait let me go down
again is there a hole I can open up here
no no no no no no
okay okay then I did my job
here feel like I'm going to get lost I
already lost completely uh all of my
directional
senses it's mostly for communications
oh is it not maybe like subconsciously
for survival as well
and like in the
wilderness you would think
so
oh ah come
on yeah I knew you could do it he y wait
shiny thing
and another one
or that's a
key the [\h__\h] I destroyed a bird's nest
and it had a key well probably by a crow
put there by a crow right oh into the
next house oh I like how everything is
like connected oh in this one we can't
enter but it's still cool to have like
these opportunities to go from one place
to another oh wait this is how I get to
the other shiny thing at least one
way oh maybe I don't actually no maybe I
don't get over there this way wa I'm in
the tree
ah oh my God thank God I made it out I
almost had to call the fire
people the nice the nice humans in the
red suits with the big funny hats and
the big big ropes that make danger
water yeah yeah yeah yeah okay now I'm
back on the ground it's kind of sad oh
okay so can I ah
oh that counts as a shiny thing
too well this does not work
IRL
just that's not how it works cute bird
that's the Twitter
bird the twidle bird is [\h__\h] on
everything because it has lost its job
and feels like everybody has failed it
don't worry Twitter bird I'm still on
your
side I'm still on your side I still call
it Twitter
too I say [\h__\h]
X that's a stupid name that sounds like
the name of a porn side like legit maybe
that's what Elon Musk had on his mind
all the time while when he was at work
oh [\h__\h] the roast oh
[\h__\h]
y Bas as usual thank you you too
uh not
anything wouldn't you like it if that
light bulb touched the water I don't
know what would happen IRL like at least
if you break it on its
impact wouldn't that be marvelous where
is the where is the goal for
this leave me alone don't know
leave me
alone I forgot how to run there we go he
wanted to steal me is it on the other
side oh it's all the way over there can
I get it for the
hole he wanted to kidnap or catnap
me cat catnap we don't like catnap in
this neighborhood we only like
catnip okay I don't think this is going
to
work we're going to oh actually I did
wrong I for some reason even stop are
you taking pictures of me privacy
please that's what you get I broke your
[\h__\h] phone yeah yeah yeah how you
like
that I would like to not be photograph
while I have this ugly hat on my face
this is embarrassing who put this on
me who did
this don't put clothes on cats please do
whatever the [\h__\h] you want to dogs
as a cat I'm just saying this from a cat
perspective but uh dogs can continue
licking their balls
please suck it don't do it to
cats I'm speaking from the POV of a cat
who just thinks they're Superior to dogs
okay which are my true
feelings 15 another one
one they're all neutered not all
uh-uh and still like they they do lick
themselves a
lot in that in the Privacy place which
cats do too okay but
but dogs dogs are dogs licks are more
disturbing because they have bigger
tongues
catching stra learning about okaa
today oh I watched the clip of cor Senai
um playing the stone game I actually
watched her stream too but I didn't
catch this part where like she was
already in the ice region and then she
fell down a lot and then she called OU
stand
byai I think I think it was like early
in the morning but OK Senai was watching
the stream and like you
know cheering her up because oh my God
after many many hours she fell like so
far cor Senai and her endurance
streams all of these places we can climb
at later so I guess this is for
later oh but look there's there's
there's a shiny thing in the bird's nest
up there again money meow meow meow meow
speaking of
money it's a [\h__\h] orange maincoon cat
up there you're huge you're like a giant
what the
[\h__\h] freaking manun freak me out
sometimes that's me
actually M there's a fresh face have you
come to see the birds I've never seen
them so close before not found a glass
in the way ah an indoor cat that
explains it can I get even closer to
them you can yes in fact you can even
hold them the trick is to L1 to sneak up
near to them without spooking them then
you
bounce wait as tall that came in the
right moment did you do that on purpose
cuzz I I mean that feels like that that
sticker almost looks like even though
it's just sitting it looks like this
pose
pounce that took me by surprise all of
the best pouncing does little one but
they are quite cautious certainly
cautious enough to avoid a little cat
that said I suppose there's always the
bread
proposition the bread proposition the
bread proposition
propos
in proposition
uh it works as follows obtain bread use
bread as bait for
Birds oh okay I got it bread was bird
seals catching but um do you have any
bread I could borrow aless no bread
comes from humans not cats it's in their
pockets in their briefcases even
clutched in their hands or sometimes
also in their mouth when they're having
an anime protagonist moment does that
make it theirs temporarily but it can be
yours if you mastered The Art of Getting
underfoot the art
of just L2 R2 swipe at their feet when
they walk when they trip the bread will
fall oh I already made someone trip but
I made his phone fall which is even
better also I see there's like a a
beetle over there on the left top left
that I can talk to apparently let's keep
that uh in mind thank you the
device okay yeah yeah this just punching
okay okay okay H can I go to the
beetle how do
you
oh no this is blocked was I in there
before can't go
here maybe it's for
later Beetle
John C Ka H how does this what how what
I already forgot everything the bread I
remember though maybe we can't do it the
other way or maybe we can but if it's
flying then it's already too
[Music]
late what happens if I get shat
on what happens
then thank you Super Chat thank you
thank you for the Super Chat shiny thing
ah there was a slow motion there hey yo
wait come back down
here I keep on pressing the wrong button
for punching that's my problem oh
oh it got scared again I
think oh [\h__\h] oh my God it's like a
helicopter the way it lands is like a
helicopter too I'm guessing I can't jump
oh oh they're all Landing jump on the
car without scaring it
oh stop [\h__\h]
everywhere no don't go don't go wait
this one this one we can get please stay
please stay I'm not giving you any
reason to fly
away
she wa
I killed it oh that's how you get the
feathers wait I can get a bunch of them
here but this one sees me
no oh
sh look how happy I am Phoenix feathers
or Twitter
feathers let's go
oh stop [\h__\h] it's so disgusting
what there's so
many
no the helicopter
Birds consume the birds I will this is
my lunch who no what the [\h__\h] it didn't
work who
needs who needs this the fish when you
have the bird
you can totally like Farm them here
though feel like they keep on
coming sneaky
sneaky what the [\h__\h] why don't you do it
it's like
no it's it's prompt it it's prompting me
there uh the
direction it worked before though all
right let's try
again what oh my God it was already gone
what what the [\h__\h] n
there why is it not working anymore when
I hold it it becomes that uh normal jump
it
seems n maybe I got too many or
so hold the direction I'm holding it
what the [\h__\h] that was like an in
between kind of
thing uh
[Music]
okay
okay this is a nice past time nice
little hobby to have no [\h__\h] it I'm
done would I even use these blue feather
for wait I didn't pick it
up what do I use them for for flying
maybe for flying
upgrade get the flying skill like that
but it seems like we don't need the the
bread that's good that's good to
know ah no not no kill him kill him no
you got the bread hey
yo okay but I need the other the bread
so you're not going to pick them up
right here I leave them
here are they going to go for
it oh God but there's two
breads that's a good
sandwich oh yeah oh yeah they're going
for it the bread
crumbs it's more than just a breadcrumb
man this is a brad Paradise
oh
damn
no I [\h__\h] it up and you judging me
from above don't look at me like that
he's like really [\h__\h]
really why did you mess it up that
bad even with the
bread all right not this time
there we go okay I think the joystick
has to be continuously
pushed oh there it
is okay well I think I'm going to go
after I catch
you
meow what what are you meowing for
you're you're a
Sanic you're just a little Sanic
I missed it cuz I was too close
no
pey I don't understand your language you
should learn cat
language okay I'm leaving
bye-bye probably don't need that many
right
hopefully okay I I feel like I was here
before wait we can cycle now though was
I here
before where's where's
recycle
place not next to the machine
why I totally was here before right
because I'm just wondering how to get up
there
oh there's more
birds this these are literally
Ki because they're [\h__\h]
everywhere how dare you call me KUSI
when this is the real KUSI of them
all right oh my god oh that's where the
big cat is and there's
another one of the cans but no recycling
inight not hold all
okay let's go somewhere else what about
left that oh the dog is
there probably no safe passage there
passage that's right I said it I said
it [\h__\h] humans we cats must take over
the
world oh yeah guys by the way uh a few
changes in the schedule
a few or like more just like
one oh is that a
fox uh the collab that should be
Saturday morning for me is now on Sunday
morning originally it wasn't even going
to be this week
anymore but
then one of the participants was like ah
the coming weeks are going to be really
difficult so I was like okay let's try
the do it this week then I wasn't the
one by the way this sounds like I I I
wanted to cancel it but no no no no
there was some scheduling conflict why
does this look so
deep and yeah it's good it worked out on
Sunday after all so we're still having
it this
week hey friend I can 100% fit through
here let me
through let me through
oh yeah wait let me let me check what's
up
here
oh I can go there oh what did you find
something interesting are you
stuck are you stuck do I need to pull
your tail is this a raccoon
T
cute nearly got it just a little more
aha yes now to get out of here ah I'm
stuck no you're fat you're a fat
raccoon uh everything okay in there
until a moment ago yes it was easy to
get so I assumed it would be exactly as
easy to get out would you like some help
let me try one more
thing oh I see the fat wobble
cute I'm ready to be helped now please
if I push from in here can you pull me
totally I saw that one coming rescue the
question mark [\h__\h] you're
big thank thank you you're welcome what
were you doing in there I was looking
for feathers oh you need feathers for my
new invention and I saw something
glinting in the pipe I assumed it must
be the famous inverted collector's
edition geu commemorative Medallion
nailed it and well and I
went uh
what the famous inverted collector's
edition GLE commemorative Medallion why
did you want the the imported collecting
get goofing me
those medallions are the ones with the
weird eror that makes Geo look like a
weird sea monster exposed to the nuclear
radiation instead of a big gecko exposed
to their nuclear radiation
okay what they were a fortune is it like
Pokemon cards but it turned out to be a
normal shiny and then I got stuck you
want it yes here oh you just giving this
for free without me giving you the
feathers you're so nice I like this
Tanuki you're so
cute ah so fluffy The Fluffy tubs and
the round ears and the big fluffy
tail very friend shaped did you say you
were an inventor I did I love to self
problem some animals even say I can make
new problems just so I can solve them oh
I make how rude rud not it's a
compliment like when they say oh dear
this will take some getting used to or
Tanuki you really should have or I
didn't know a raccoon could disrupt this
much SpaceTime actually that last one
was pretty rude I'm very clar at Tanuki
not a raccoon what's a raccoon oh this
cat doesn't know raccoon but it knows a
Tanuki it's like a little bear Fox with
a long stripy tail apparently some
people think they look like Tanuki but I
can't see it myself what are you working
on now ah it's all very exciting in fact
that's why I needed D wait do you smell
feather do I do you smell do I you smell
it you should be saying do I smell cuz I
have it and you're smelling it no why
why why would I not know I'm a cat I
watch birds all the
time no I have it though you have
feathers somewhere about your person cat
I know it although goodness knows where
you're keeping them yeah good question
it maybe under my banana hat I knew
it wait the sound sound a little bit
like monkey sounds from the
tanuk oh how exciting give me give me
give me oops I forgot my MERS please
give
me yeah if you can share your invention
with me free feathers I'm clearing all
the quests before they ask me for it
let's
go really is that what they sound
like Tanuki ape
monkey do I need to collect more really
do you want to see a cool invention that
theor SpaceTime Behold The Magic of
[Music]
engineering
W now that is really impressive Mr
[Music]
Tanuki not anymore the fleshy Sly glow
isn't just sewer Vapors It's Magic and
that means it's now part of the petwork
TM you mean Network I do not it is a
network but it is for you bet where does
it go what this is a proof of a concept
so it actually only goes over
there oh not but I still bypasses this
fence so you should not hold back on
your admiration hop in let's go that's
nice but let me check around here for a
moment is this not a shiny
thing but oh
box a I almost missed the Box oh good
night thank you for coming if I fit I
see okay I go thank thank you for
holding it open for
me
wow rainbow void rainbow void rainbow
void
yeah
oh where where am I Tada where in the
trash can maybe I said
t is that my C wait where are you oh
well well it's completely dark and it
smells EX Ting does that sound like a
place completely dark uhoh let me
consult my feedback
questionnaire okay here we go question
one is a test subject in possession of
own eyes
eyeballs uh oh yeah I'll take that as I
guess is a test subject in possession of
all necessary
limbs yeah simps like the test subject
is becoming uncooperative why don't you
try moving around we can see if the
answer is the limb question yeah yeah
yeah I knew what I knew I was in the
trash
can Landing was kind of off H where am
I oh you landed in the trash why didn't
you say so earlier well I didn't see you
this is very exciting it means the
petwork works I just need to find you
the Rival system a little let me know
when you've done that and I'll hop in
and come back come back come back you
know the return
Journey oh
oh oh you didn't think about how I can
get back okay okay Tanuki not so smart
after all the bit where I come back to
the first portal Tanuki a fascinating
yes I can see how that would be
useful how you're now on the other side
of an unclimbable fence and
everything tell you what I get to work
on that return journey and you can go
explore how long do you think it will
take I find that there are fewer
recommendations when I do not commit to
dead life
I have a feeling you will take longer
though thanks for the membership gift
I'll be in touch when the improvements
are ready for the test of lab assistant
or lab rat
bye-bye Al hurry up
please it better be ready when I'm back
shy thing well I have 25 how many did
they
want I got them I remembered it right
you
nice
[Music]
yippe there's a lot to
explore oh there's so much to explore ah
wait okay first things first
ow guys you know I told you I made Curry
right and I told you I put so much
coconut milk in there and to like get
rid of the spiciness of course that
didn't work though why do you have no
eyes oh my god
freaky um cuz normally yeah I guess you
should put like cream creamy stuff in
not coconut milk not only coconut milk
so it didn't work but I was doing my
best to still eat it because the
taste The Taste was really
good oh I got an achievement for that
I'll be back though don't you
worry and my mom when she came yesterday
to my place she arrived pretty
late and uh she was kind of hungry and I
fought my remaining Curry cuz it was
like already the second or third day I
thought I thought I had no
more I only for like one person but then
I was able to split it after all and my
mommy was really happy that I had some
food so I shared it with her but then
you know my mom actually she really
likes spicy things and she has a
supposedly High spice
tolerance but she ate
it and already on the first bite she
made this like surprise Pikachu face and
she was like oh [\h__\h] this is actually
really spicy I'm like if you say it's
spicy then I don't feel so bad
anymore I mean it was totally edible you
know I was just suffering while eating a
little bit just a little bit not too
bad but even my mom said it was spicy
let's
go also she said it was good the taste
was good even though it wasn't like a
proper Thai curry because there was no
Thai Basil and the other ingredient that
I don't remember what it's
called and no my mom definitely has a
higher spice
tolerance also my nose was running but
hers wasn't really but she was still
like oh that's cute Bob the cat oh
there's the beetle
ah I can't reach there can
[Music]
I N that's
difficult can I really not go
there no but I was able to go in here oh
what's
that before he kicks me out you got to
change your hat now you think he'll let
me be here if I change my hat for safety
cuz that was the real problem that I'm
not dressed safely
enough
wow I'm making art
again oh the birds are the kuso totis
are helping
me but yeah anyway
basically this way I cooked for my mommy
for
once I always say like oh I want to cook
something for you too but somehow I end
up always being cooked for anyway when
my mom's here but it's so nice because I
I rarely get like Mommy cooked food ever
since a long time ago actually so you
know whenever I get the chance I want to
I want to make use of
it oh no oh no I don't want to lose it
give
me yepy yepy run
run understandable
right
yeah oh also I I got
uh I now know where my hello fresh box
went but it's kind of dumb it's kind of
stupid
um it was like delivered to like a
similar address even though before it
was delivered successfully a few times
already so the delivery person was just
confused I guess just didn't read
properly um but
then like somebody wrote to me today
today you could have WR to me already
before but it seems like they didn't
notice that it was a hello fresh box
from
someone but yeah someone who received it
wrote to me today letting me know oh
hello uh uh name and so on we got your
we got your hell fresh box like At first
I was like do I know this person because
they were like talking so casually to
me as if they knew me I was like I was
like like what the [\h__\h] who what who are
you and they're like oh we just wanted
to let you know we uh disposed of your
hello fresh box because it was getting
bad and I'm like
uh okay could you not have told me if
you had access to my phone number and
all that could you not have told me uh
before it was bad so I brought that up
friend in a friendly way like oh that's
too bad like sorry that happened uh I
had the address on there correctly for
sure as it was delivered correctly
several times as well but yeah uh it
seems like the delivery person didn't
read properly and I was like ah if I
would have known earlier I would have
come to pick it up and they were like
yeah sorry we got get a lot of packages
so I I didn't I didn't uh see that it
was you know that for us yeah great
great to tell me after but I did get a
refund supposedly I have to check if it
really arrived but I I did get
it no I don't think they ate it no no no
no I I do believe them they just like
had it standing around and didn't
realize it was for like someone
else cuz he's the he said like we also
get like hell fresh
boxes but like you
know I don't know
it's okay I was confused it's it's fine
I I made Curry uh that I wanted to make
anyway uh I just have to figure out what
to do for the rest of the week until I
get
uh a a new
box then why did they leave it out to
get bad
then be because uh they didn't recognize
it as a hello fresh box first I guess I
don't know oh no no are you
okay do I look okay
today oh sorry sorry sorry I didn't mean
to stop that's okay has something
happened I made a big mistake huge big
huge wait is
this the LOL tells me this is the
developers making a joke a trump joke is
this a trump
joke I made a big mistake big huge LOL
uh would it help to talk about
it maybe but it feels too huge for such
a small Kitty to help with though I mean
as mistakes go this even B and the great
hash Shadow B catastrophe of
2021 oh are you on Twitter are we
talking Twitter now for real for real
that the what what because how can I be
expected to run an effective chff
takeover on social media without a
waking
phone oh why are you using Tic Tac toits
when you talk Tic Tac
toits that's
cute let me drink some
water well what's a phone
it's this thing next to
me yeah that looks more like a tablet
when it's next to you but I guess it's
still the size of a phone oh my human H
oh my oh my human has one of those but
it's less gloopy so it's mine usually I
dropped it in red concrete LOL what does
LOL mean oh it just means laughing out
loud but but you weren't laughing at all
you were sad H but if I say l when I'm
sad then you can't tell I'm sad or at
least that was the
idea exactly exactly and dropping the
phone thingy is why you're upset yes I
need it for work Taffy is going to fire
me for sure if I don't fix it l who's
Taffy she's she's kind of my boss or she
would be if I was being
paid uh I'm just let's just say I'm I'm
this let's just make it clear I'm your
boss guys there is payment
exchanged just in a different direction
I'm still your boss
okay she's an icon a phenomenon a
nightmar I think BS magazine called her
the fluffiest billionaire on the
internet cat fluffy nightmare wait is
taffy a cat no Taffy is the cat L that's
her up
there oh
it's a rag doll of course the like like
the most famous and like fanciest cat in
the game is a rag doll
cat M Majestic floof although it doesn't
necessarily have to be a rag doll
honestly this could be a like a a Burman
cat or so there's several cats that can
have that pattern too but it's probably
rll because that's how rlls are being
um uh
perceived cute yeah yeah Grumpy Cat also
had that pattern but I don't know if
Grumpy Cat was a yeah Persian too grumpy
cat was not a rectile was was
it oh I know her oh I know her I see her
in my human phone thingy she has the
coolest house and the best outfits and
the is she an in
infera I I made that up myself but it
feels like something the game would come
up
with I pick those outfit and I start in
fact I was here looking for the
inspiration but I dro the phone no phone
means no internet and no internet means
no Taffy content for her
friend thank
you thank you oh yeah uh yeah yeah it
was a dwarf cat mhm mixed spr M but
that's that uh that's that's that's news
we have to fix it let me think what if I
just lick it clean I know I will get you
a new phone you can do that yeah I think
so humans have at least one phone thing
each so just let's borrow one though
they love Taffy Jr
y there he goes so they will be
delighted to help wait right here I'll
be back with a phone in no time l no
thanks
and well this guy does not have
one but
wait ah there ah wait I don't need I
don't need the uh tanooki's help with
the exit
because uh I can get rid of the box over
there when he's not patrolling
there and then oh wait oh
[\h__\h] faster faster faster the
faster yeah I'm scared oh he's not there
yet quick quick
quick genius oh the Box disappeared
okay y should we surprise Tanuki from
behind where is
Tanuki he's
gone what I thought he was thinking of a
solution where'd he go
hey no [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
you
no there we
go your phone is now my phone wait wait
no no no no no no wait where how do I I
don't
see
no I got a little bit hurt there but
it's okay it's going to be worth it I am
the hero of this town now
and I'm going to help Beetle and that
beautiful cat going to help them out and
they will all love me
forever maybe I'll become a famous cat
too while I'm at it here's your
phone I did it yeah do you want the old
one it still takes pictures you just
can't do an emailing or anything what's
emailing you don't do emailing I don't
think so so you've never been ceed
I heard to for my last
message damn this is quite the manager
huh manager Beetle she nope although I
do PA all my messages now that I think
about it what an absolutely Blissful
life you must lead Kitty anyway here's
your phone the dirty ass phone are you
for
real might not be smart anymore but the
camera still works press X to open photo
mode and start taking pictures
I should take a selfie now
okay what
how snap happy do I do it what how you
said
[Music]
x wait I can't X is
jumping oh
is that even a real thing I can
do I don't know I don't want to take a
selfie
anyway no
need okay I think I'm done
here can go out again oh actually no
there were other places that I wanted to
explore from
here like over here oh no I guess I
already did
oh yeah I already did I went to the dog
but maybe from the dog I can go
left you have you want
food maybe I can help you though don't
be so angry maybe I can help you you
just you just have to let me go past you
and get the
capsule [\h__\h] you shitty ass dog I hate
you I would have totally caught you some
food oh actually
Y what maybe he's going to be the
[Laughter]
food you found me again but how you are
incredibly visible yeah the clue didn't
even lead me here it seems that my
search for the perfect camouflage
continues I shall continue to make
adjustments while I wait you in the new
location they say the third time a charm
after all here's a cool for when you're
ready to try to track me down a metal
friend of arms spread wide provides a
place to climb and slide but you won't
know I'm there at all because I'll be
invisible
yeah that doesn't rhyme so well but I I
helped you out there with the
pronunciation to rhyme a bit more
honestly it's not my best work but I
could have spent more time on the clue
if you taken longer to find me I'm
confident about my next adjustments
though so further ramps should be
unnecessary good
luck all right so I guess I can't uh
sacrifice him for the dog's
food what why is it so sparkly though I
totally have to put something in there
but what one of these
birds what if I put a
bread in the bowl then wait for a bird
to land
there then catch the bird then the B the
bird is kind of like dead in the bowl
and ready to be
eaten by the dog because I'm sure he
prefers uh bird over uh bread but I
don't really know what to do there TB uh
so I'm back and the Tanuki is totally
gone I feel like I got
scammed he just gone oh the sandwich
meat ah is that really what he
wants a wait I wanted
to I can go there that's one thing that
I wanted to do
maybe there's something for the dog
there
a oh of course Dar is all right all
right maybe there's something for the
doctor
a a bone they thrw me a bone oh yeah
B one
round ah
yumy
ow oh come on
no no no no no no no no he's
coming sorry actually panicked there
hello thanks to the Super Chat thank
you will he catch me when I'm here no
right is he even still going to try to
catch me now that I'm wearing the Hat
maybe it's no problem
now he I'm throwing you a bone
ha taada You Like Me Now oh no you're
just going to be greedy like that I
thought this would result in a
general uh ceasefire between the dogs
and the cats in this town no really
greedy ass
dog corn corn not dog but corn cat n
hold I wonder if they put that there on
is where the dog is so you think of corn
dogs I want to eat corn
dogs okay I still can't climb up these
things I need to get that
skill can I take his bone away no what
the [\h__\h] are you oh oh his leash you're
eating your leash
buddy all right I
think we are done with everything that's
to be done here so let's get out into
the normal area Korean yes specifically
a Korean corn dog is what I want as
well those are so
good but the American ones are good too
the American ones that I had in Japan
let me say that because I don't know if
American corn dogs are actually like
that in
America Maybe
not maybe they
not have you guys have any of these
American people in the chat have you had
an American corn dog in Japan from the
convenience store oh shiny
thing if yes tell me if it's the same
never had one kind of same style but
often lower quality and super cheap
uhhuh hit and
miss oh
[Music]
I'm a real American never left
America uh hi Crow I have oh wait yeah
let's just give the crow
the the uh shiny things and we'll be
able to climb
probably so shiny so pretty so
reflective who's a pretty
Crow yes and with that we have completed
our first heroic act together can I try
disposing of them definitely not these
are ancient Crow rituals oh do I get my
reward you what oh yes you reward now
where on Earth did I see that fish H
just a
minute wait gr was this a scam no no
don't worry believe in the
crow believe in the quason or in the
narissa fish let's go
yummy my cats would probably not eat it
like this
indoor cat owners would your cat eat a
fish like this like when it's just like
just like
this just like normal
un unopened and so on yeah
no mine might they would steal it and
have no idea what to do
exactly yeah mine would maybe like lick
it a little bit but then be like uh okay
I'm done
they probably would only if it wasn't
allowed
to yeah that's also a thing mine will
try anything once they would
try my alter cats even wouldn't oh your
alter cats are not
very adventurous are they maybe they're
more like chill lazy
cats
okay M ah you can I get more fish later
on okay okay thank you thank you okay I
eat
wo yum yum yum I have energy now let's
go I can climb Ivy at least to certain
amount of
it let's
go oh oh it's like like in Zelda bre of
the wild you can leap to like you know
maybe maybe be able to climb something
that you very closely wouldn't be able
to
normally what the [\h__\h] is that doctor or
Gees Goose it's a goose right are you a
goose hello
there
Su I wonder if you could provide some uh
urgent
assistance I think it depends on the
problem he oh I see uh quite right quite
right I don't want to alarm anyone yet
it's rather a pressing concern although
perhaps I'm just panicking but there's
no two ways about it what what's wrong
what's wrong oh didn't I say I seem to
have misl my ducklings duck not
goose misl is this a bird joke I don't
follow I don't
either never mind missing duckling
sounds pretty serious it does doesn't it
what happened well we were all enjoying
an educational tour of the neighborhood
me teaching the youngsters some local
history etc for example you know the
robot statue in the park behind us
that's where the chameleon
is M I didn't even know there was a
robot
statue oh you should absolutely visit it
you see the robot is quite fascinating
not a statue in a traditional sense
either Legend has it that a white do not
too dissimilar from myself in fact would
visit this park every day with his robot
friend very loyal robots delightful this
is also why I look talk like a robot
maybe I'm not a duck maybe I am a
robot that's why I talk like this I
suppose all that fing and sputtering not
sympathic at all rest patches wet Su
blah blah blah the robot swimming days
were over terribly sad stuff so he asked
the duck to change his programming Quite
a feat if you ask me could never get my
head around computers myself the duck oh
my God he yapped so much
uh g g this is like ingame lore
apparently I
suppose you guys read
this Read It Read It Read
It N it's really a lot oh my God all
this [\h__\h] lore
[Music]
uh oh it's just a great story okay see
it wasn't even necessary to he just
wanted to tell a good
story anyway we scampered off in
different directions all very exciting
in a moment but uh I suppose this is the
Crux of the matter uh really didn't set
a time or place for us to
reconvene wasn't sure what to do for the
best okay I have an idea I know I have
to find your ducklings shut
up oh you got a map even uh if you play
reunion by Hol myth then I'm sure they
will show up a you little [\h__\h] you left
me behind I swear I'm so disappointed in
you you little [\h__\h] I'm going to
jump on there and then push you back in
doesn't work what do you want yeah yeah
you you connected them okay
it would have been even quicker but
there was a minor SpaceTime incident
nothing to worry about in the grand
scream of the Multiverse it was
absolutely trivial just a teeny tiny set
of waterpipe explosions that fell out of
the future in the other universe and
into the recent past of this universe
hang on a moment is that where all this
water came from it turns out I'd be
using linear SpaceTime and I should have
used quadratic SpaceTime love you might
want to say LOL there you want to try it
out it's really cool and I need need a
test a
friend but risk is just a pessimist's
way of describing excitement anyway if
we get this working you can use it
before frast travel around the city and
that sounds great don't say no just yet
hear me out but I said yes firstly there
are wait what I said yes for real call
me curious yes this is so exciting you
won't regret it do you need fets again
not this time my first journey was so
short that I had leftovers hoping it's
going to work this time I'm 100% sure
give or
take no wait he this time I had no
choice
hey where was my
choice what the [\h__\h] where am
I you wait you came back oh you oh
you're the one that jump scared me I
thought like I was like I thought we
were at enemies while you even talking
to me that you goodness me you did give
me a bit of a
fright sorry sorry I just get so excited
when people come to visit you're a dog
right only the best is best good this
dog my human says so it's nice to meet
you properly I didn't know there was an
official best is best dog title ah you
may know me by my other accolades
perhaps the squishiest smooshi potato or
the fuzziest happiest little pooper
great names that sounds like like
something dog owners would call their
dogs um my owner told me I was the
squishiest was is potato I call my cats
potatoes too
sometimes are you sure certain I
remember because she started several
times while pushing my tummy over her
nose gosh oh my God like oh pets are
being just like gaset gaset by their
owners constantly huh we get these
titles and they're not even real because
everybody's getting these titles maybe
we need an award show for pets so we
find out who is really oh oh oh and
maybe like a
fight so we find out who's really the
fluffiest cutest potato of the mall
huh ew disgusting [\h__\h] you Birds maybe
I'm starting to understand why Twitter
was you know replaced with X CU if you
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] Birds
anyway it was lovely Chad hope you have
a good day oh don't go there's this
thing that happen can you help me little
potato oh no I'm a Potato what do you
need help with I've lost my
balls the tennis
balls ah you're you're tennis balls huh
they're all over the place
man
no oh you have a nice
[Music]
home don't oh sparkly sparkly I can
sleep in
the if I lay here is that he's not going
to be able to sleep in this space
anymore dog will be super confused
because small cat sleeps in dog home hey
y all he said is
boss no why is there no physics why
don't they go like Po when I jump in are
you good buddy are you good look no BS H
I appreciate this might be a silly
question but aren't they behind you what
oh those no these are just my regular
favorite tennis balls I'm talking about
my extra special favorite favorite
tennis balls they're very different what
happened to that one I know what
happened I see them all over the place
okay okay I'll get them for
you a machine what please please please
can you help me find my
balls uh I'll
try I'll try uh I I thought I saw them
here but nope they're not there
either okay okay
okay I think maybe this is not even oh
there's one
here maybe this is not even
necessary
oh oh you can't pick him up in your
mouth you have to push him but somewh
really far no
a
man we don't need all of them right
uh-oh no what a pain in the oh what a
pain in the ass here
T
no no this is going to be so
annoying get get in there nice suit
ah thought no I thought I had it go on
this is like playing golf
IRL get in
okay no wait but this is where you want
to have them
right
go oh this is the beginning isn't
it oh it
is oh now okay that's actually nice to
be at the beginning because there were
some climbing opportunities
probably we can go
no
no oh
no what a what a painful side quest if
you could put
them if you
could munch crunch them then it would be
okay
but maybe I don't do this Quest or do I
have
to have to think like I'm a soccer
person have to Envision the soccer stop
going that way let's go
okay there we go oh no no no no no no no
no
football socer no don't go back
no okay okay okay okay okay
okay oh God no
who would have known that this would be
such a pain in the ass yeah okay okay
okay okay now let's never go back there
again okay thank
you oh I can dribble I can dribble
dribble do you call this
dribbling no that's basketball is it
what okay maybe this is the better way
to do it just like trying to lead it
although it's also kind of annoying
how many balls did he say I skipped it
so I don't know
but I dribble in soccer too okay okay
okay okay so we can climb here for
example and then here but that's quite a
quite tall uh-oh
ah ow okay that is Too Tall really maybe
if I jump a little bit higher in the
beginning oh oh oh oh oh oh oh up
a no I didn't make it I Feel So
Close
wait come
on no maybe I can't make this
one we can go here for
sure get enough fishy where are the
fishy maybe with climbing I can find
another fishy
now
who
Recycling close
by don't know I'll take it for now cuz
at least this one I can I can grab with
my
mouth oh okay I don't
know but what's what's over here
I oh okay what
what where am
I
capsule
Y what do we get out of this one the
cute one please an aine eggplant aine oh
I think that's just how we how we say it
in German H do we though do we wait what
I'm getting confused
do you guys say OB what the [\h__\h] you
look like me almost but you're you have
some white
spots ah you teach me how to do Beauty
routine thank you shiny things do I
still need them mother
H can I climb these
no okay but this is
interesting we say aine in the UK is is
a a UK
thing is it so is it so is it so duck
wait that looks like a bath duck not the
kind of duck
e wait we were talking about real Ducks
right not fake Ducks cuz I think I saw
real ducks in dendo
vog uh am I supposed to bring
this
to the
goose decoy
duck or do I need the duck the decoy
duck for anything
else I think most places say all oh
really yeah y it okay I'll leave the
duck here at the puddles in the
beginning if in case we need it you guys
know where it
[Music]
is new climbing place but that looks so
so tall y it y
it I made it [\h__\h] you and [\h__\h] you shiny
thing do you guys know if I really still
need the shiny things or am I done
collecting them H maybe to get another
fish or oh ah wait can I get to the
car there's no leaves
right the crow set all okay oh another
Crow wait did I go here before I'm uh I
need to make a list of places I've been
to
you can buy hats ah it's for the Hat CA
yeah I did see that there was a hat
CA ah but that's like oh hello I'm back
here now let's let's explore here but
the hatcha that feels like it's more for
like 100% in the game I don't
really feel like doing that hey yo I'm
on the bamboo I am the
bamboo let's go
[Music]
a that's kind of cute cactus cactus
hat where is
it here
spiky spiky oh with this one my ears
poke
out nice ow hey yo oh I wouldn't even
have seen that normally hey yo wait this
is where the K chameleon is
right where
oh oh wait I see
it oh it's like a whole robot playground
this is cute this
design I can
slide wait
shiny hello I see you this is the first
time I found you so do are we done now
okay oh it's just you wait that's worse
it means you have found me again I can't
work out if you're being serious or not
I assure you this is the most seriously
act ever taken anything oh it's just
that I mean yeah well you're right there
there's no other way to say it I can see
you this is absolutely baffling but
there must be a solution perhaps I will
figure it out on the way to the next
location there's another one a seed
glass containing snacks can stop a human
in their tracks what's better than just
one machine a group of six to choose
between I think I
understand oh shiny thing but I don't
really need them that
much that being said I'll take that and
oh my God there's a dog
bone dog bone for which
dogle where is the next
Dogo you know
know ah here's a
dole
ooh you are so
welcome
enjoy didn't even feel like I needed to
pass over there yet but we already
prepared
it this game looks so fun and cute it is
fun and it is
cute you are so right with that
observation seems like you you have
really good observation
skills there's a lot of new stuff to
explore now Y and I think that's a
sleeping place I need to I need to keep
track of where I've
been okay shiny thing I'm on top of the
world W
woo y
it oh
oh that was a close call Fish there's a
fish in there we have to get
it we have to get
it Sak s s
Sak will she let
me you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that is cat harassment
cat abuse I might say
even what do I do about oh okay I have
an
idea ah oh my God guys you know my mom
has a huge Garden right it's like pretty
much a
forest
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] help
y I jumped on his head let's
go uh yeah so she's been you know doing
garden stuff for a while now quite
ambitiously quite a lot and she's you
know my garden Sensei
now ever since I have uh claimed my own
garden
and so you would think oh ball you would
think she would make you know she she
would feel really uh familiar with
Gardens and all
that and and
hoses remember that story I told you ah
the six machines the the story I told
you about
me recently feeling really embarrassed
because I sprayed myself with the water
in the face in the on my whole body all
over really really uh
dramatically it happened to my mom today
too with my hose like she also didn't
think she just pulled the thing off and
the pressure from the rest of the water
in the
hose it just all over
her I I wasn't there to see it I'm so
sad but she like came back in in and she
was like h i just sprayed myself with
the water hose all over ha I'm like oh
my God that happened to me
too she did the same thing
yo oh yeah give me some of these I know
exactly what this
is shines for hats yep yep
[Music]
yep I don't know what I'm pushing
five Chinese lets you hire one cow to
retrieve one hand
okay if I don't e Chinese for anything
else I guess I'll take them how can you
blame the host for not for it's not user
error what are you saying the hose is
the bad one or
not traffic con I don't know give me a
different one
give me a cute
one witch hat I don't know about that
give me another
one gotcha
gotcha oh I can become
Amy okay this makes me happy I am Space
Cat it looks so weird Okay chameleon I'm
on to you I didn't think you would be
that close to your to your previous
location but okay I already see
you oh that's a cool vending
machine you can't be using infrared
goggles to find me because I'm cold
blooded also you're not wearing goggles
and you don't seem like the type to use
a tracking device there's a tracking
device type well it's less of a type and
more of a particular creature you mean a
particular species I mean Tanuki she got
hold of one a year ago and started
fastening it to anything it moved that
moved a I don't think she was even
recording the data she just liked
watching the dot move about the on on
the scanner thing yeah that sounds like
fun Crow started a data Protection
Service it was just him looking over
Tanuki shoulder at the scanner then
offering to tell us if the tracker was
stuck to you Us in exchange for bottle
caps anyway Tanuki apologized for
getting carried away and I think she's
repurposed the tracker for some kind of
teleport project oh yeah yeah he up and
[Music]
running oh I've just had a thought about
this camouflage conundrum I want to try
it immediately so there's no time to
waste here's your clue another
one just like Fallout ah you're right
cuz the payment and Fallout yeah yeah
yeah they use bottle caps right Fallout
[Music]
caps I don't know what it was but
something
about this game already did make me
think I'll fall out today I just didn't
say
it lizard's used to rule the Earth
lizard's used to rule the
Earth and we'll again just mark my words
but until then the world of gecko a
store where I will uh eat a big
St I want to sing the song again
I do like you maybe I'll treat myself to
a bow while I wait for you to admit
defeat it's no good for my clue though
let's go with um the that used to rule
the Earth and will again just mark my
words but until then there's world of g
a story I will now expect you what it's
kind of not so
good I guess that wasn't a reference to
the song otherwise it would kind of work
better I
think I used to rule the
[Music]
world okay where to next so many New
Paths have opened up wait these wending
machines are cute too I just know
nice
cute wait there's so many things to
recycle recycle
Cat shut up I'm just a cat I don't try
to pet you either do I leave me alone oh
I wish they would try [\h__\h] you
why is you immune there we
go I hope you fall harder next time you
little
[\h__\h] do you get something out of jumping
into
these probably shinies
right get back ah the
fish a banana and
shines wait where is the fish Sak Sak
ah the where how did I get
there was it up there where was it we'll
find it again also there's a shiny
sleepy place where where is that again
exactly
oh ah
capsule okay banana I know there's a
banana hat too for the
cat but it's not this one this one's
cute though mushroom hat kind of cute I
like the idea hey yo what's
this y they're sleeping in the shrine
thingy
call oh nice nice scene just
chilling get
up respect means nothing to a
cat I don't give respect I only receive
respect
yeah okay okay okay oh he's fishing wait
do you have a fish for Me Maybe steal
the ah okay so we have a second fish
right there as
[Music]
well but there's a lot of water
everywhere we have to be
careful gotcha
a I like this game it's very
cute didn't I say I didn't care about
the gacha now I kind of
do oh dieon I love Dion especially when
it's very soft like in a
soup and now
one got that addiction the hot so cute t
it I didn't realize I could run while
I'm in the screen I found um like some
on social media I found like a video of
of some super cool special
tayak in Tokyo next time when I'm in
Tokyo I want to go so I sent JMA the
video Yeah it it looks like quas it
looked like quas first when it was just
the the batter the dough it was really
flat one I only want to eat it and JMA
also was like
oh
fish she had the same thought yeah I'm
going to get
it Del I mean to be honest like I've had
tayak a few times before and it it's
it's not like you know world changing
it's really yummy
but uh it's not like world changing
yummy it's just another like you know
ow another nice little bread thing not
really bread I don't know like a waffle
but not quite a waffle a little bit
different from a
waffle but still I don't know I don't
know what it is about it it just makes
me want to eat it it has I think it has
a quite a nostalgic feeling for
me the reason why I want to eat it all
the time when I see it is um I think
it's something nostalgic when I lived in
Japan there was a time where I lived in
a student
dorm with everybody else was Japanese
students oh it was a girl dorm
too and they were all like around my age
we were
teenagers and in this dorm there was a
big fluffy dog too that I really liked
that was the dog from the owner and yeah
there was like a a food uh place in the
dorm where like old two old grandmas
were cooking for us every day and it was
like a
buffet I mostly ate the Tam gakis for
breakfast every
day but yeah everybody was like proper
student I was just the only one who kind
of got into the dorm through connections
because I needed a place to live and
they were so kind to let me live there
even though I was not an official
student I was just like
kind of connected with the
school yeah so that was cool because it
was um you know you know I had this
dream of going to a Japanese school when
I was younger and it didn't really
happen but this way I got to experience
a part of Japanese school life which is
living in a dorm and it was basically
like our dorms they were pretty much
like Japanese typical Japanese one room
Apartments
like from the
size I had a bed my own bed I had my own
table I put my laptop on there and it it
was really
comfy and it was a nice experience
really and I was like befriending some
of the students and actually just
yesterday I was like cleaning out some
stuff on my day off I was cleaning a lot
of stuff out opened some old boxes that
I had in the storage and I found um you
know the Japanese shikishi like it's
um Japanese people like to use shikishi
for signatures or for whatever like draw
something on there it's like a a paper
that's really thick like on the
cardboard pretty
much yeah they come in small size or big
size usually Square don't know if
there's non-s square ones I haven't seen
I guess there's heart shape ones I've
seen heart-shaped ones so I guess
they're are non square ones and anyway
this one had a drawing of me a portrait
drawing of me and I was like I did this
one and I turn it around and I see this
is from like a million years ago okay I
haven't seen it in a long time but it
said uh the name of the dorm on there
and the
date and I was like ah yeah right I
remember like sitting in our like
entrance hall of the dorm uh for some
reason like one girl was quite the
artist and she was offering other girls
to draw them and we were friends I think
pretty much and so
she she offered to draw me and that was
that on the sikc so I have kept it for
o I don't want to really say how many
years but it's been a long time
yeah wait I thought I was carrying
something in my mouth
oopsie
yeah
they oh yeah so anyway that's not
actually okay I went into a tangent
within the
tangent but what I was actually going to
say is um close to the dorm there was
like a a popup taaki place that after I
would like get off the station and go
towards my door warm because it smells
so good I would often go there and get
myself a custard
tayak very often that was I think like
my first experiences my first times
eating
tayak and I had it quite often I really
really loved eating the warm tayak
especially cuz I think when I lived
there I didn't live there for too long
but I think it was mostly during like
winter and
Springtime so uh it was usually cold and
and then having that warm tayak on my
way back home wow it was so good it made
me so
happy yeah so those were some some
nice memories from me living in a
Japanese dorm there you go actually
surprised I found some tangents in my
brain that I haven't told you yet thank
you to the taaki for reminding
me and thank you to me yesterday
cleaning up some stuff how do I get the
fish ah maybe I make him trip oh but he
put it away already oh it's
there [\h__\h] you
hey that was
easy you didn't even I don't know if he
even chased
me let's let's
go I'm guessing there's probably only
one
more um upgrade to death oh maybe
there's more but it feels like maybe
there's only one
more okay can you get rid of that speech
bubble now thank
you and I already know where that one is
so let's
go I can probably get up that one
building yeah if I knew where the hell
that was I'm going to eventually maybe
get back there but so my directional
sense is
destroyed I don't know where I am or who
I
am oh I still had that in my mouth who
uses these
still the [\h__\h] isn't that a floppy disc
yeah what what was that doing there I
guess that's why they're in the
[Music]
trash oh
oh I think I was here before but uh uh
oh wait this is not for cl cling yeah I
was here before though but there's
nothing to do
here shiny
thing uh let's see ah we're in the
supermarket
[Music]
place I'll just run around and then find
something to do while I'm running
probably I'll be fine there's something
here for
example um
oh okay
wait I still have a floppy Drive what's
in it didn't Japan just move away from
floppy disc just recently you
say wait
that's oh I don't know how to describe
what that just sounded
like okay let's let's wait
here
yeah ah ah okay okay where do we go from
here there oh there's a shiny
thing but is that all there is over
there
y let's
see another shiny
thing my finger
slipped mm
oh not weren't we here
before there's a dock
here
a let me help you
[Music]
maybe I'm going to rescue you you don't
know how to stop
Flying uh oh I know
how leave it to
me
Mak Japan is weird using antique Tech
but at the same time okay yeah there's
definitely like better things to use
instead of floppy disc but at the same
time you know you know how we like retro
things and how it's like kind of sad how
retro things
disappear I think it's good if we hold
on to certain things a little bit
longer okay this duckling is following
me
now that's fine I guess maybe we can use
to attack the
[Music]
bluebird
here floppy discs are know for
you what did the floppy discs ever do to
you ah wait this place I also explored
this
before uh where is
the we'll find it we'll find it
out I don't know where the duck is but
we'll find
it let's just get down for now wh it y
it woohoo not the
water not the
[Music]
water oh
capsule 8 MB of
data eight FB
only sheesh
one might wonder how I can even grab
things when I have this helmet
on
okay yeah I knew there was a way into
this
place I I literally knew it I just
didn't know where but I knew it because
I I saw a dumb tendle in
here wait there's a place to sleep in
there oh yeah she chunky wonky loves
sleeping in my laundry basket and
yesterday I washed a lot of laundry I
was really like cleaning like crazy oh
my God the
duck but anyway so today for the first
time in a million years my laundry
basket was actually completely empty and
chunky wonky was like about to get in
and she looked inside and she she said
meow and I was like oh my God she's
actually like legit like wondering why
the [\h__\h] it's empty it's like less com
she's probably like Mommy what happened
with the laundry
basket it's so empty now put clothes in
there please there's something wrong
with my
bed she really seemed confused about
it
Mom right it's so cute I looked over and
I was like oh my God that's so cute
she's confused about the laundry basket
[Music]
um okay wait oh I know uh no no no I
know how to get you out I think there
must be
electricity yeah have fun in there for a
while oh what the [\h__\h] are you doing
here I bet you're wondering how to push
that button
huh H what
button it's pretty easy you just have to
use your head and by use your head head
I mean run head first at the button okay
then what then nothing you just bunk the
button with your head and that's
it you're made of stronger stuff than
that kitty a little bunk on the nogin
won't harm a tough cat like you are you
sure yeah especially with my
helmet uh have you noticed there's jazz
music playing every time we talk to this
cat which is why I think the voice I'm
giving it is even more fitting
ow
no the bubbles I made a bubble
okay
ow the [\h__\h] what did I do that was it
oh oh that was easy well we got the
second
duck let's go but we have to leave
through what the oh my God y the duck is
stuck again anyway wait to tell Dad
about the death death fireing dry
machine yeah let's go come on don't get
stuck again I just saved
you let's not make that for
nothing there was a purpose for
that getting knocked out around the time
the stream started luckily they came out
fix it right away oh wow I wish my
providers were that helpful when I
needed them huh good for you I'm glad
you're here
insufficiently orange Oh you mean the
cat on this on the in the game right you
don't mean me I'm sufficiently
orange I couldn't be any more orange
than
this oh sleeping
Place h
no that's uh just uh yeah where do we go
next
M I am perfectly orange but you may be
doubting my orangeness because I made
myself red and blue in the new dance
video that I uploaded have you guys seen
it I think you guys must have all seen
it uh that was my idea and putting uh
two hours into the video like behind
each other was also my idea and uh chy
really liked the idea of course he did
because it's
genius yeah and then the switching in
the middle was also my
idea yeah I felt it would look
interesting and the red looks pretty
similar to my orange but the blue I
think has a really strong impact I
didn't think that the blue would look so
good looks good doesn't it
oh oh we're back at the fishing place
are
we oh yeah we are okay that's uh
actually good because I didn't fully
explore I
think will you take red wa or blue wa
it's exactly those colors yeah which
pill are you
taking I sent the video to both Kobo and
uh mining Senpai mining Senpai was like
oh my God it's so cute and then kopo was
like yo that's so cool and she was like
saying oh ah this is the fish place she
was like
saying oh like how did you do the heart
so
perfectly you know there's this one pose
in the dance with the heart do you guys
want to know how I did it so perfectly
well I must say my
$6,000
gloves are
pretty [\h__\h] you are pretty good um
but they are still like when you put
your hands together they still don't
really look like they're properly
together and so there's like problems
there so chy just fixed it in the post
edit now it looks so
perfect yeah it's kind of sad though
with
$6,000 hand motion capture gloves that
even with that you can't get it right
it's [\h__\h] sad
actually YY
YY ah okay okay can I land on
here okay okay
okay okay all right all right all right
all
right
aha oh we might have to be fast cuz I
think she's going to go to fix
it
mhm oh she's coming from there b oh wait
then can just use the door go go go go
no give it okay let's stay here let's
stay here and undo it
again that's exactly why there's
animated to clean up motion capture on
$200 million
movies
wow
yeah well yeah I mean makes sense
although they're probably using
something what am I doing I I did it
again
y oh she doesn't even care when I'm down
here here when the water's
off can I go okay now we go now we
roll can I eat it in
here yummy now I kind of want to eat
fish too friend faucet friend but not
not friends to cat only friends to
chicken get
you wait was that the max I
wonder no lady it's okay I'm out of here
don't be so
mean have you no
heart forget the shiny thing I don't
need it
but oh
y i I was hoping to get nah whatever
ow hoping to get there what's my current
missions get back home we need enough
energy I guess I don't have that yet uh
I need to bring all the duckins fetch
the balls zero out of
free what shouldn't it be two out of
free find chameleon
okay yeah no fall
damage two more Ducks ah there's
probably one in here right oh I heard
one I
think yeah I feel like I heard
it oh wait is it
here
no oh oh maybe those are just my own
birds that I'm hearing the the ones I
already have the Cucumber
oh come on I know you can do that jump
there we go I know I've been up here
before but I'm wondering if there's
something new to see now that I can
climb they wanted to make it so there
was no way for the cat to get hurt
a I mean they are well known for always
knowing how to land which I will have to
say uh don't rely on that with a cat
they definitely don't always know how to
land but generally yeah that's
the that's what they say about the
Kito okay we're back here
another this is where I got one duckling
before Oh I want to get up that building
there's a bell and there's a sleeping
place and there's a ball the ball for a
goal where I don't know where that goal
is anymore can I Mark something in the
map
no but uh okay here's where we found the
duck here's where we found the
duck uh that
is that is where I think we need to
bring the
Ducks I guess they follow me even when I
go
through
a a uh portal
H com wait I'm I'm so like uh where am
I
ow ah didn't I try to do this before and
I fell is this even
possible
oh maybe not
[Music]
oh that looks like a Korean
sign did they always have no
faces
no
no I must killed them
cats must finally regain their
power okay okay go go let's try to find
something
new either a ball or a duck
or oh more shiny
things oh that's
new big gecko is over
there and bubble tea or
what bubble
tea bubble bble bubble pop bble bubble
pop
pop yeah that's um maybe wait is the
chameleon there no wait where is the
next chameleon what the what is it in
here I don't remember the hint at
all wow oh look at all that merch hey yo
what cat back massage I don't think that
really works [\h__\h] all of this [\h__\h] it I
hate J I hate
it Checkmate
baby Double Cat
massage we are we are what you call
this we're we're we're we are we are
something that's for
sure your human seems to be broken is
everything
okay sorry for standing up here not
really you see my sister L has flowing
away that sounds serious I'm looking
up even though the cat is below me it's
so buggy now I made it
[Music]
buggy actually that part is pretty
normal she loves to fly outside and she
always comes back with lots of stories
about the neighborhood today seemed
extra safe there are no cars on the
street because the humans need to fix
the Leaky pipes that explains why the
roads are so clear and so wet yuck
ah hold
triangle you mean for
meowing but the Y is not the problem
Lama announcing she was off to battle a
cat is the problem oh uh-oh indeed she
watched that Geto versus boss cat movie
Marathon last week and has been talking
about battling a cat ever since I
thought she wanted to play fight so I
said I'd be boss cat if she wanted to be
GLE but apparently she wants to fight a
real cat huh you are a real
cat what that's so insulting
actually not to her I'm just a big
brother who lets her win when she wants
to play geeku she said she needed a real
challenge with a real cat I was about to
go look for her but our human noticed
the empty bird cage and well my sister
and my human both needed me how do I
chill
oh I think the bird is going to lose the
fight
though you don't need to I'm exploring
the area anyway so I can keep an eye out
for Ron what does Ron look like though
you know those blue birds you see on the
street she's like that like that but
bright yellow very fast and very feisty
oh maybe bread he's thinking ah wait
that's it the perfect place then L
doesn't know you so she'll think you're
a real cat I'm a real cat and if you
catch her and let her get away it'll be
like she defeated the BOS for real
she'll be so happy oh okay so I do let
her go away nice nice nice that doesn't
sound too
difficult now is scared at make believe
you'll have a blast she likes to fly
along the street right outside the store
oh okay I'll get r a home in no time oh
I mean gecko does not stand a chance
against boscat thank you boscat you're
welcome do I get a massage too then
oh wait I am I got a big kitty little
city ah achievement all wait the upon I
was going to say I'm
Godzilla let's go
Catzilla
beautiful this is also kind of like a
game we played before I think it was a
hall life fan game H myth fan
game ooh I need to get up
there easy
easy easy
ow Robo must
die I love that backpack though it's
cute oh by the way I gave my mom some
souvenirs from Thailand as well like one
of those
inhalers and like a little elephant
because I had so many of these little
elephants that are really cute I gave
her a bunch of stuff she was quite quite
quite
delighted
yeah uh wait how do I not there maybe
there it's got to be
there rail model what are you talking
about your parkour
P oh there you are you're orange now
best
color okay please tell me that you are
at least finding each each challenge
[Music]
harder definitely let's make him feel
better about himself ah great well at
least I'm making progress even if it's
very
slow either way I shall continue to
refine my methods behold the next clue
so far I've been far too merciful so
let's go somewhere way more vertical
I'll be near a rooftop garden past the
water wielding Warden ah I already was
there now I got to get back there no I
hate
this well a waste of my time what the
[\h__\h] is this do I sleep in
there
wow feel like I would probably slip down
though
not very cute sleeping play Stone of
course here we
go many shiny
things all right well if I find my way
back there then I can help you out also
where is this bird oh I see it I see it
already I saw it right next to the
yellow
light two things were yellow there so
okay do I have to still have to sneak or
is it going to how are we going to do
this it's Landing right
now uh I hope I don't win yeah B oh
okay oh oh oh okay BOS has the mighty K
clasp in a claw frizon is this the end
for a brave
hero Ry boscat destroy our fun or boscat
will not be out withed by gecko this
time there's no way out for you m
destroyer of eh I don't know this one
not so fast Bas I may be spawn when I
Mighty uhoh gck p g kick gck slam he Lo
again bat Meanwhile my yellow ducks are
just
watching we could have just replaced
their yellow bird with one of my ducks
maybe they wouldn't have noticed the
difference wait till my brother hears
about
[Music]
this it was all just I would never lose
against a stupid ass bird like
you the only bird that can challenge me
is a phoenix
bird let let me let me
alone don't catnap
me oh actually a catnap sounds nice
right
now actually catnap sounds nice always
hey you guys should be done now he went
back into his cage and even closed no he
didn't close the door
oh uh sorry I I don't know why I keep on
talking to you in the most awkward
positions I'm sorry B are you here for a
rematch I'm still recovering oh hello
complete stranger who I have never met
before are you the famous boss cat yeah
uh or I'm the boss cat and you're the
ass
cat my sister told me about your epic
battle I'm sad that I missed it that's
okay the fewer mces the better well as a
consolation prize let me teach you a
soing emote thank you cute baking
muffins okay
[Music]
bye-bye making cookie
cookies cookie making
cat smoy also make many cookies
H all righty all righty what's next for
US ah convenience stor were we in there
before no right this is this whole area
is pretty new also there's the
shrine how many duckins was
it
uh it doesn't say
what I hope it's just free leave me
alone 10 10 shinies wasn't it five
before four duckins
okay why so
expensive damn I already have so many
shinies again
though we'll buy another
one
inflation oh the map the ducks on the
map didn't show the ones I already got
it showed the ones that are still left
over
shark bunny oh
cute oh man they're all so
cute cute kind of small Shark look up
why do you look down don't be
ashamed Don't Look
Away bunny I want to happy
bunny oh I see it I see it over
there all right can I go in just like
that look at me I have a pond to all to
myself are you sure it's a pond I'm a
dark we know about ponds my my
aond uh yeah I think it might be time to
get out of the Pondo your dad sent me to
collect oh oh the duck is coming to pick
it up it slipped what are you doing
zooming
around yeah anyway I'll go get you
somewhere or
another sleepy
Place
nice
a
[Music]
cute I wanted to receive wa do you get
the yes it's me it's my my
downside is the Australian side of
me yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum y
I want to go to Japanese comini oh
what can I push this oh wo wo wao wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait we'll we'll figure
this
out
[Music]
wait wait box
Fox
um yeah uh wait oh [\h__\h] I'm stuck
wait ah
[Music]
ah I'm
stuck ah
it's like always Saving right it's all
the safe cuz there's no safe
here
y let me get back into
this I yeah I jumped in and I got the
achievement for jumping
in but I guess the wind kind of [\h__\h]
it
up oh I'm just sleep next to it now okay
Wy
Wy kitty kitty
cute yeah the wind is ah the wind is
like well that's the smell of the fish
can I do it again is it going to happen
again no not this
time I'm looking through here
cute nice all right ah
uh do we need this to like ah yeah let's
bring it all the way to the other side
maybe we can blow the duck
away lunch break over bye-bye see you
again
oh it worked three out of four
okay one more one
more and the
Fe damn
it I still got it [\h__\h] I still got it
you can't do anything about it that fish
is
gone that fish is gone and I got the
duck too I don't want to in here anymore
anyway oh there's a decoy duck over
there as well do you see up there on on
the top
shelf but wait I want those shiny
things I kind of want those shiny
things did she just throw me out because
I ate the fish does she generally not
care let's
see yeah I just want to be on the box
box thank you not in the
Box the [\h__\h] that did you guys see the
bird was like bugging through the
building too with his
back towards the direction where he
wanted to
go nice I like the bugs in this
game
M ah what if can I jump on on this
although don't know no that's not really
it
either there's obviously an obvious
solution
here
cat yeah here is good it
no I jumped too
far there's
vents I'm not the impostor I'm not going
to
vent no
chill [\h__\h] decoy duck you can't fool
me I can tell a real duck and a fake
duck apart
easily I dare something in there the
opening and then from here too so are
they expecting me to get up there from
the this side
first I don't know man I
tried oh
wait you can
I oh you made it even though the PA look
like it's going way
lower okay thanks for renewing your
membership thank you oh there's a back
room wait I I'll go there in a
moment ow
ow I want to okay I'll have to do the
jump
again King
King okay
it was possible anything is possible
when you're a cat nothing can stop me
I'm a cat bunny now also that's even
more special
wow wow special
room I can use yes you can thank
you a cute irrisistable
mhm good good one good one kitty kitty
wait maybe we say [\h__\h] you to the to
toilet paper oh my there's an exit
here anyway you're stck get out of
here okay no toilet paper
achievement stop
wait surely
this is an exit that we can use the
windows open for a reason right maybe
not Maybe
not maybe just because it's stinky it's
more of an
entry that would be a nice shortcut to
getting the cool things
here W who who who w wow
that was a traumatizing experience for
me wind and water in
escapable
oh
box if I fit I sits four out of five
nice nice
[Music]
oh
ah
oh ah there's a a key or just a shiny
thing there is it always but yeah I
think I have to get there from inside it
doesn't look like a place you can reach
from the
outside
ooh
nice don't take me shiny things the
Cucumber you can
have not hold can we take
these no okay
wait ah okay wait we can get in from
outside I
think just have to show some skill
[Music]
oh there we
go there we
go oh just is it
no
h sticky
business it's just shiny things but it's
also an
achievement not a hold par don't cats
hate cuc I tried that with my cats they
did not really care
a cucumber was no surprise to
[Music]
them oh there's another
goal I don't know we don't have to do
all of
them guess it's a myth yeah you tried it
a few years back
I don't know where that came
from is that really is that not just a
thing that one cat did and it was caught
on video and it was just generally
surprised but not by the
Cucumber I think so I I honestly think
it was just a
coincidence because yes cats can get
weirdly spooked by things that are not
spooky
that's something my cats do do yeah do
do h ah no what the [\h__\h] don't jump so
far but it it's just yeah just like
me true
true reminds him of snakes oh then I
[Music]
don't I think it's just like General
surprise
nice cash
money all right where where have we not
been ah this is the ah the
six uh vending machines let's stay in
this area I need one more
duck and I don't know if the game will
let me know when I have enough St know
but I would hope
so this way I don't think I've been here
ah there's the last duck it's playing a
game look look look what are we looking
at only one of the greatest games of all
time are you old enough are you old
enough to be watching this my dad says I
have an old soul speaking of your dad he
asked me to come and collect you for
show and tell sh that was easy that must
be a catch I'll go soon as the screen
stop showing
things oh easy easy
easy oh is that a GameCube no not quite
it looks like a mix of a GameCube and a
different console
like maybe s NES there's so many of
these
too an achievement for recycling all of
the cans because that seems like a lot
of
work DTR yeah never oh oh no no I played
once when we were at an arcade in
America with
myth that's the one time I played
it m
ah what's
this
oh oh okay I mean that's
really sorry humans for [\h__\h] it up
real
bad oh oh
that's that's maybe one of the biggest
damages we've done so
far is that something you can fix easily
I I feel like no do you have to replace
the cables and stuff too when this
happens that's pretty
bad hey why you so excited why you so
sparkly all right let's go over
there and Report the
duckings 1 2 three and four that's all
of them one Rel I was starting to get a
little
[Music]
panicky I was the most fine you were not
I I was tall n yeah children please you
are you were all exactly the same amount
of
fine it was nice to meet you all oh
children have you thank the kind kitty
for their help thank you you're welcome
not you we were talking to the Kitty
thank you kitty I love you kitty why is
it so on the bottom left what the [\h__\h]
dad you have to say it
too where United let's
go ah quite right thank you kitty please
take this as a reward for everything you
have
done I don't know if that was worth it
but
okay that chat box is
bugged okay
bye-bye what are you
hello oh
okay oh that's cute
cute I wish I could join
them in there I want to join in the
water ah too bad what if I can I join on
the
leaves it doesn't look like it
no oh man I don't need your stupid hat
it would have made me happier if you
would have given me the ability to couch
water maybe this is
interesting oh oh oh reachable
reachable all right
nice Freddy thank you I was about to say
members Freddy eight me I think I have
more than that thank you
do 40 free mobs let's go all the
renewals what are you guys doing are you
doing that
manually are wait is this my home am I
climbing up my home right
now cuz it does seem to use a lot of
stamina
oh
oh thank you guys thank
you can we get 30 9
members instead of
38 can we get there or maybe even
40 uhoh nothing to see here oh it's your
shiny things storage no you're stealing
them huh I'm taking them so I can give
them to you thank you
guys thank you wow wow wow I like this
like furniture and
[Music]
everything H all the members all the
members showing up isn't this a nice
place holy
[\h__\h] it's not really like modern but you
know it's nice I like the S the
furniture and stuff and the
colors the couch is kind of modern
though wish I had my
Milestone where is it where did you
leave it was it stolen by the crow
because it was shiny
thank you guys oh there is a 39 months
member hey what the
[\h__\h] guys don't leave your windows open
don't ever leave your windows open it
just [\h__\h] flew through and shut in
here
K [\h__\h] K
literally bad oh Co what the [\h__\h] are
you doing
here oh shiny things and
Nest I have climbed pretty damn High
huh H did they did they fall down the
other
things thank you guys thank you you all
have flow profile pictures looking so
good
uh what's
up and then everyone p in the city
starts erupting and the time is all out
of order so it's happening right now but
he's just laughing to
himself I think I managed to stick the
pipes back together but the bubble gum
won't hold forever the whole city is
currently covered in water and
hello he's really just a yapper oh it's
you kitty I'm sorry did I startle
you only a little I don't usually see
anyone up here it's just geu and me oh
you were talking to geek does he think
it's
real and look at that that poster with
the pasta and the kitty is
cute oh wow is that the real gecko I
don't know not yet probably not yet is
probably the best I can say Tanuki I'm
going I'm going to regret asking what
you mean when you say not yet it's a
fairly simple exercise every day I come
up here to eat my lunch and check to
gecko if he replies I'll know it's real
what if we doesn't well I still need
somewhere to eat my lunch and think
about things why not a lovely sunny
ledge makes sense that is like a lot
like my window spot speaking of which oh
yes good luck with the climb oh does
that mean I made it the fact that I made
it up here means I have enough stamina
so to do it to go home did I make
it or I mean this is not my home right
probably this is like the
climbing proof that you can do it if you
can't do this then you're ready or just
leads home maybe it leads home maybe
it's all
connected oh that would be kind of sad
if I already finished it because there's
still other stuff to do but I didn't say
I was going to 100% it
and I guess I played long
enough I have like this big urge to play
a tailes off game right now maybe I
should play the DLC for Tales of arise
soon but I'm kind of feeling like like a
little bit more like I want to play a
nostalgic old tales off game rather than
a new one but I think it's time to play
the DLC
yes you know that feeling when you just
want to play a tales off
game you know that it's something about
tales off
games like Symphonia yeah I like
Symphonia oh maybe like Symphonia too
which I haven't played
before the one on the
PSP that I play you mean not the PSP one
I think you mean the the PS Vita
one should I go down will I be able to
get back
up let's just go here
first what what what are these duckins
doing here are these different duckins
he
y uh
uh I think they are the same oh I think
they're just standing there not swimming
yeah
H that's a grownup Kitty are you a
grownup where am I I think I'm in
between the pool oh no never yeah I I am
I'm a bit more grown up than you and a
little bit less grown up than your
dad why would Kitty not want to hang out
with us I can't read what you're
saying all little things make one bigger
thing h
[Music]
you want to swim with us yes are you
going to teach me now but I'm refusing
it though I need to be getting home okay
maybe some other time I don't know
what's happening Kitty's leaving byebye
Kitty byebye
duckins are you guys telling
me that duckins maybe cannot swim at all
they're all just like standing in a pool
huh not like their legs are reaching the
ground but
still why are they here
though wait I know I can go up there but
I can also go up
there
a
okay okay let's
go this is like the most connected
biggest place I've been to
too and this is very Zelda right now
y anybody got some stamina
food never mind I made
it
oh where am I going from here ah to the
side well then
wait H I want to recharge
first okay no swim just float water is
an illusion or maybe the Ducks are are
an
illusion this feels like a dungeon of
climbing you know to give you the last
test they want to make it really really
long to get back to your home I think
this is really
it this is just Zelda with
cat ah what the oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait it seems like we have to go around
the oh wait I made it I thought we had
to go around the corner but no the
bushes didn't block me but these [\h__\h]
did you'll pay for that no more balcony
flowers for you balcony flowers didn't
work for me either so it won't work for
you either
this is cute some child was like playing
here I can't ruin
it
what what nah what is this I can ruin
everything but I just I can't ruin the
the children's things he yo why is the
paper plane
here what is this why is it not did they
forget to animate the physics of
this I understand protecting the cat but
protecting the children what for
eh they are our future yada yada
whatever I don't
care I have a future either
way I am my own
future oh [\h__\h] things are getting blurry
up here here or that's just because
that's the the side of the city we can't
go
to wow we do live up very
high they got to be more careful with
their like window sale and all that now
like this should be a lesson to the
owner to make it safer for their cat
because can't always guarantee that the
oh hello duck that the cat will be smart
enough to know their way back and go on
this whole RPG Adventure
Journey Gathering shiny things and
fish to find their way home it's not a
given oh a
key okay I like this music though really
nice I just noticed now for real the cat
barely survived yeah I mean I feel like
surviving you know it would have
survived but like who says it finds its
way home your cat might be lost forever
don't be so silly are you also talking
to the
Geto hello again lovey to see you up
here so grateful for your assistance
earlier too definitely the Herer of the
hour I'm just glad I could help
wonderful wonderful um yeah I don't
suppose you've seen my children I did
I'm not going to bring them to you
though don't worry there safe and sound
they found a swimming pool on one of the
balconies a thank goodness I'll go and
join them soon perfect weather for a
little swim so relaxing would you like
to join us uh cat says no but I say
yeah
bye-bye it seems like they want to
like reintroduce all the people I've
met like this to me again or maybe only
the ones where I finished the quest
Maybe
who knows there's a really shiny shiny
shiny thing
there
oh oh oh nice safe cat
wow wrong
way
really maybe this is also a way
I mean I know this this looks familiar
ah this is where isn't this like I saw
the go goose and I went there to talk to
the
goose or so I should go back there
no
wait is this an okay path I'm not going
lower although ah yeah
[Music]
okay I maybe up here did I try that
before is this new I think so
paint the only paint I like is Microsoft
Paint so you must die as
well oh there's shiny shiny thing here
but I don't know if I want to go get it
but this doesn't seem to be is this
walkable
even
no wait w okay I did it for the shiny
thingy
shiny thing high score maybe I was
supposed to go here I don't
know we'll
see
chaos must
ensue orange cat
behavior I forgot again that uh orange
cat is not called orange cat in
Japanese they don't just say oreni
e I think what was what's it
CH so they corrected me on
Twitter just ch that's brown oh yeah I
think I I feel like I had this
discussion before with a Japanese person
calling an orange cat orange and they
were like no it's chido and I'm like no
it's not brown it's orange like there's
brown cats and there's orange cats I
feel like there's a clear difference
between between
them chat chat oh they're calling it
brown
tiger but yeah was it ah was sire yeah
you guys remember
that oh oh I'm home I didn't
realize wait I could have climbed even
higher if I didn't land on the blanket
I'm h
I'm happy that's not me though in that
picture what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah that's uh probably smart oh I
get okay
so obviously I had a name before I would
hope so but it seems like the owner
learned a
lesson to put a callar on me so that
people could deliver me back
home um
[Music]
black
cat boss
cat
oh um yeah that's fine I guess I think
after you press space it uses it as
enter okay well I am a cat and I'm a
boss you just like have to do the math
yourself boss
big yes the course
[Music]
P oh
hey
friend you made it wait you made it I
did look my human gave me a present what
does it say it's my name but you had a
name this whole
time I like it yeah I'm the real boss
cat now mine's Crow Fort Crow for the
F should I call you that instead of crow
No in fact I insist that you don't okay
so is this goodbye what of course not
you can come down and visit us all
whenever you like in fact let's go now
but will there be a shortcut to get
home in fact I'll make things on the map
right now so you don't forget about them
we check them out in a moment CR but
first I want to cuddle with my owner and
maybe have some
lunch oh yeah my favorite nap spot in
the whole White City best nap spot is at
home after
don't forget the shinies that you want
your [\h__\h] shinies that's all you
think
about no wait I just wait no uh let me
let me sleep I want to okay I am curious
what's at the
top wait surely you can climb
here what can I go
in oh oh this looks kind of like a a
childish room like a teenager's
room
cute
cute my cat tower that I don't
use or do I doesn't look very used looks
too
clean
oh [\h__\h] science cares about science
unless well the only thing that science
is good for is for extending a cat's
life which they are working on it
seems I don't think you can get higher
huh seems like it blocks me
from uh climbing up
there oh no never mind it works but
[Music]
yeah I think that's that's
it want to recreate the opening
guys
woohoo
oh
W what are you holding on
to Invisible game wall are
[Music]
real oh
hey what's this place why did I never
find it the dark
bone wa to I thought I was done
but the invisible wall
wait didn't I give you a b no guess I
didn't you're welcome
though the last dog bone hey we
completed something after all before
ending I got the achievement too
nice what's the last one a butterfly a
that is adorable I think let's see it
a that is like maybe the cutest
thing nabby Mama on my
face that is
cute cute
K yeah this is where we started out I
guess or or not really maybe we started
out on a different
side but yeah this is my town I'm
boscat y'all better respect me and give
me all the feish you
have this was
[Music]
fun this was
fun I wouldn't even mind completing it
but we already like found a good spot to
end it so completing it
Asen I wouldn't
mind uh getting 100% in this actually
but it's a good ending time I think that
was really good underrated game yeah
it's quite fun I like it it's it felt
really
comfy I think this might be one of my
favorite comfee
games the exploration was a lot of fun
and I don't know the the little quests
were cute the things you could do was
nice yeah finish the game I got home cat
is safe and that's all that
matters no is completed 100% that was
the main quest of getting
[Music]
home yeah I'm
happy thank you thank you let's read
some super chats but let me take a fro
candy
I'm beating the game thank
you little fox
friend you just got here well some kfp
might say the Super Chat reading time is
when the Wawa stream really
starts okay I'll CL close
this and we caught up quite a bit with
super chats but I think I know where to
[Music]
continue hope you guys had fun by the
way tomorrow we're playing tomorrow
we're getting back to Europe EUR truck
simulator
2op we will we
will yeah we getting back into
it uh I know I just didn't know what
else to put there and then I thought why
not play some more Euro Truck Simulator
why
not I think that's tomorrow I'm pretty
sure I'm right with that oh okay okay
you know I I double confirmed with all
the birds if the new collab time works I
just got another double confirm so we
good we good new time works I'll be
getting up early for it
but he's all good
I think it's it's going to be okay I'm
planning to definitely take a nap after
that so that I mean it's inevitable it's
already like streaming at 700 you know I
won't be getting enough sleep even
though I'm capable of sleeping early
like easier these days
earlyish and falling asleep faster is
easier to me recently so I think that
will be all right like I'll probably get
like five or six hours but since I'm
streaming again later that day I
definitely want
to um take a nap right after the stream
it won't be too long as well I think the
the game isn't too
long maybe an hour or one and a half
hours probably see you in Europe up okay
thank you
do we're going to play my Italy music
yeah I am a cat after all I have to take
naps as long as I'm wearing these cat
ears you cannot say anything against
that you'll have to vot it you mean the
collab or the stream after that either
way is okay don't
worry okay here we go uh super chats
from the
last day
free why does my title say Day free
wasn't it day
four they they no I was
only oh no the last day was day four
okay I thought that was the last somehow
I thought this stream was the last
stream no no this makes sense okay okay
okay
okay I was on a server for only 4 days
man
I'm just going to stay here now I'm
lazy just going to stay here sometimes I
like to stay
here have you ever thought about doing a
Euro trck Sim multiplayer uh possibly
yeah but did not really think deeply
about
it Psy Dan space water Studio Dan for
the pinky
[Music]
I was just saying I feel like I didn't
add much to most of the uh final fights
like the first wither fight as being
like chased by
it so I could get a bunch of hits intoo
but I feel like the other fight was like
getting lost a lot and just couldn't
reach it
much I do feel like I shot a a bunch of
the like Towers from the Ender
[Music]
Dragon but yeah I don't know it was
chaotic it was very chaotic yeah then I
couldn't find the Wither I was so late
when I realized everybody was at the
Wither and I should go
there so yeah I couldn't like show my
true
warrioress sadly but still at least I
wasn't like useless and at least I
didn't
die as long as you can like stay alive
in this kind of situation that already
shows
that you are
strong you hit p a lot did
I Ena was also super focused on the
tower
seems like something she would focus on
yeah yeah thank you s Rob Prince of
Denmark
[Music]
than7
KW thanks for the pink pink pink pink
pink Super
Chat we were here at kfb we here at kfb
are following the wise words hope for
the best plan for the
worst you plan you you do that yeah but
me not necessarily you guys were super
super super cautious about
everything like prepare this prepare
that most of it wasn't really
necessary
but the water was I mean the idea of all
these things the idea behind behind it
makes sense but like in actual
action we were just generally
Overkill all these [\h__\h] flies
everywhere
man anyway thank you Tassimo thank you
thank you for protecting me through the
screen and the
chat
g
j gav fellow than uh dexy detinator than
J two people sent
two uh Flash super
chats
there you're flushing so hard why are
you double flushing ehh why are you
double flushing there's no need to
double
flush I want B
[Music]
oopsie next one is from day four and
then we're called up to
[Music]
today okay Jacob 47 d space waterfall D
the satisi D oh space wonderful rescued
a toad from the pool a toad or a frog
toads are really big but that's amazing
I'm glad you
did yeah there art is so cool it really
is the Full Art is really impressive
too the Safi d l lunchbox d
l you D thank you I'm glad you enjoyed
them the gamer cre
Dan sorry for Productions Dan I'm in
Europe taking a trip for London and
Paris this my first time ever leaving
the US on a trip so I'm very excited
also good luck on beating the Ender
Dragon oo London and
Paris um have fun those are really
famous big cities in Europe obviously
lots to do I hope you're having a good
time yeah take care of yourself
though Prince of Denmark than Studio Rob
thanks for the pinky T it seeing you're
reconnecting with everyone made my COC
full to bursting thank you so much ah I
I I I do feel like m there could have
been more I I tried to I tried my best
to involve myself
though yeah
yeah thank you I was happy
too thank you for the pinky thank you so
much I'm glad you enjoyed
it okay
gu h
k shine
[Music]
K how do I write read
this k
[Music]
bro get sh no I read it right pretty
much okay okay okay
okay uh wa okay come
Sanita jaob 47 thanks for the pinky this
Arc has been really fun long streams and
lots of interactions with the other
girls including across the branches some
of your best points I know you were
worried about it at first but I'm really
glad it worked out so well
yeah I almost didn't participate
so I'm I'm I'm glad I got to be part of
it otherwise Ena would have been the
only
Ian no can't can't have us be so like
weakly rep represented in terms of like
small
numbers had to
represent uh Ian in more numbers
so pick without reading that message it
wonders I speaking of reading the
message I did watch like almost the
whole whole News stream of hers
yesterday the last
one and yeah she liked my my last Diary
too a chat her chat liked it too
everybody was like a
a they were they took it so seriously
even though I was like kind of Chio
about it I was like kind of exaggerating
it but
they were like a I was just
like when I was writing
it yeah no one playing Minecraft it was
like perfect timing Bai in her diary
also was I think it was hers like she
was
mentioning how she was happy to play
with people together again they like yep
yep yep it's all connected it's all
connected that with Hol talk it makes so
much sense
a happy birthday to Ena oh her merch I
really like her merchandise she also
made an
apron ah we're apron buddies now and I
really like the cookie cutters they're
so cute
maybe I should make cookie cutters at
some point
too it's a cookie cutter and then a
stamp stamp to get like the the face on
it yeah everything everything looked so
good the artwork was so cute too
staff used them to bake samples oh is
there pictures of that I only saw the
the merchandise
pictures is there
actual did she show it in her stream oh
I didn't see that
[Music]
part
cookies Flappy boy thank you for the red
super chat so proud of my attention for
valiantly mhm flying the banner of Ian
during this entire event together with
Eno of course yeah yeah yeah myth
represent your role as bridge builder
between the branches goes far beyond
that of translator and will remain
indispensable for a long time to come
thank you I mean I don't really think I
did much bridge building uh and I don't
even think it was really
necessary
um also because like both both Ena and
me speak Japanese and then on the on the
ID side there were a few more members
that like MAA and that don't speak
Japanese but still KY
too but still they I feel like
everybody already felt
like you know like we're in the same
company and like almost as if there's no
branches it did feel like that in this
event and that's nice that's a good
thing like there's no need for Bridges
because we're already just like
so so Blended one
thing ah well yeah I translated the cord
stuff for you for example and everything
else for the chat
yeah yeah well thank you flat people for
the nice and sweet words thank you so
much I'm glad you had a good time
watching this Arc m
Garden Park D com Max the first John I
a you Mike thanks for the red super chat
P being the final is a Twist probably we
saw coming mhm but it's still so much
fun very fitting for Dan should be the
one finishing off I've said what I
wanted in the past Super Chat but this
really has been so much fun throughout
every day thank you K thank you now
speaking of D killing P I want to say
one thing that I also didn't notice
until pekora senpai's News
stream
um when P Senai was
killed uh I thought I saw an
achievement that's just like uh
restoring peace and I even translated it
for you guys I think yeah I thought it
was an achievement and p s by father it
too for a moment because it was just so
perfect but it was the name of uh nor
senpai's sword which was a pun by the
way on her own
name and it said something like
restoring the world to peace but the
verb toon which is like
restoring to as you can already hear her
name is in it so first of all funny pun
but
generally uh killing the boss with a
sword that is named restoring peace was
so perfect that was not the only one who
ignored the pun and just thought it was
an achievement that maybe like was
custom made cuz I'm sure you can make
customade achievements in
Minecraft uh with mods or
whatever and I I thought so and Bea also
for a moment thought
so my first thought was just like
translate this for the chat and I didn't
even really notice that the that n the
part of n of to was even in Katakana
while the rest of the verb was in hiana
which is kind of like supposed to show
you that this part of the word is her
name and therefore like lets you see
more obviously that it's a pun but I
completely ignored that
perfect word play yeah you know would be
so
proud when a joke is so good you don't
know it's a joke yeah I just thought it
was an
achievement yeah that was that was good
M good ending to that perfect weapon to
kill someone with I don't think my
weapon even had a name so now I'm
thinking like in the future just for
stuff like this I have to name
everything I have to name everything so
that we can have a nice looking message
there yeah thank you you got like m
[Music]
for the
pinky this was an amazing week I'm glad
you joined and I hope you feel a bit
more confident about things now that
it's over these kind of events really
are the best parts of our life it was
nice to have Ena at such a rare time to
yeah youa was finally rarely abandoning
her usual streaming
time for this and streaming quite a
[Music]
lot there is not many things that that
can get Ena to abandon her streaming
slot Taco Time had to be
moved yeah well thank you mfin very much
appreciated M HD n for
[Music]
than for the r Super Chat that was such
a fun adventure thank you for streaming
wa I hope you had lots of fun as well
and I'm looking forward to the future
events like this also I think you really
proved yourself Wario waa as god of
Minecraft thank you I have to say my mom
was also
really really happy about these four
days of
Minecraft like last night we were
sitting on uh like in my garden and and
just like yapping
yapping and she was like oh I really
loved all the Minecraft streams I didn't
see the last one yet because you know I
was like doing stuff but that's what she
was like watching
later but yeah she was really really
happy and she was like oh you did so
well farming the never right you did
such a good job I still remember when we
were farming never right
[Music]
together saying like nostalgic stuff we
did together and it's not even IRL it's
like in a game it's like oh I still
remember when I first brought you to
school no no no it's I I still remember
when I farmed never with
you that's kind of funny but yeah uh she
was really happy about it Minecraft
revival and she was watching on my iPad
in the room next to me she was watching
the last stream and I was like hearing
myself the whole time quite loudly it
was making me feel really awkward then
then afterwards after a while after like
maybe 10 minutes or so um
uh I basically told her to watch
something
else and then she watched different
Minecraft videos from other
people like
hermitcraft oh big
Kusa thank you
Tassimo glad you enjoyed it as much as
my mom it
seems don't she have a headset no no no
no I I don't know I don't think I could
make my mom like use headset it's fine
that way it's
fine as long as she watches something
else PA G thanks for the red super chat
got to say this was very fun to watch t
I'm very glad you joined the event for
all the funny little interactions we got
also seeing your Insane luck in action
was quite something I hope something
like this can happen again in the future
you mean the never ride Insane luck was
it really that insane because in the end
a lot of people had never
right within a relatively short time so
I feel like I wasn't even that
lucky it is
really you legit did it on your own yeah
yeah pretty much I mostly did it on my
own yeah the strip mining was impressive
luck yeah looking at how many
tunnels
uh vat and Ana made I still I still not
really sure if that really was them
because somebody said it was from
someone else but the amount of tunnels
they
made and then I think they weren't even
like
fully you know Decked Out
sheesh yeah I even gave
away well maybe it was like I guess
several people
huh
for only her did like Ana and vat missa
just continue it or
so
maybe aha ah okay I well well well well
thank you Pala I hope my luck will
continue in other games m i for thanks
for the pinky this has been one of my
favorite set of streams really real fun
event that I'm glad you were in all the
different groups and daily tasks that
shook up the dynamic each stream made
them all feel unique like a proper Arc
thank you for playing indeed it was like
really well
planned really well planned nice events
every day nice challenges very motiva
ating by the end it was like less
challenges so because like we were just
you know less things to do easier
challenges because we were at the end
but still generally um I wish I would
have started from the beginning because
then I could have participant
participated in the other challenges too
but yeah P S did a great job planning it
all out and she seemed really uh tired
and her throat was really dead uh as
she's been saying as well by the end of
it um I hope she gets some good rest
though but she worked hard and I really
appreciate having events like this
especially for Minecraft where you know
we really all love playing Minecraft but
we just needed a reason for
it black for Dan Jacob 47 Dan unknown
than to the pinky these hardore MC
streams have been such a blast I'm so
happy you participated in this you did
so amazing with everything and I'm
extremely proud of you Wawa always very
very proud of you thank you so
[Music]
much heart eyes thank you unknown you're
so sweet you're always proud of me even
when there's nothing to be proud of
thank
[Music]
you thank you du Hood thanks the pinky
doood what took a study break and saw
you ask about my ex status I I already
read this I guess thank you gendo you're
also the
best you the best for impersonating
Gilma
girls out of your own will
too golden i d for the pinky congrats on
your first MC hardcore experience W
sorry I missed most of your journey but
I managed to get up for up early for the
finale you seemed uncertain at first but
you survived until the end like a true
warrior be proud now I sleep before work
thank you very much yeah my first
hardcore experience I feel like playing
solo would be a million times more
difficult playing it in a big group made
it much much easier especially because
there were some members who created some
very useful appliances and
stuff and we were much more powerful
yeah oh my God I can't even begin to
imagine how how difficult like
especially stuff like the weather
weather
[Music]
alone doing all the things we did alone
I mean okay let's let's not say we have
to kill like two Withers and one Ender
Dragon at
once that's that's you know that's a bit
extra but
still damn maybe one day we'll play
hardcore
alone solo it one day mhm and see how
well we're going to do on our own at
least this give me this G gave me a
little bit of a
taste but was this a setting from Pai or
do you actually when you die in hardcore
you just it's just
over is that actually a
[Music]
thing oh it's the standard oh [\h__\h]
oh I mean killing the weaer is not a
must so if we leave out the Wither
then maybe it's uh yeah a bit
more realistic
alone it would be helpful if I learned
how to make all these things like the
villager farm thingy a proper one and
iron farm I I would have to really learn
all these things whole life I oi thank
you Leo for the comics as well it was
nice to see them
again every time when there's Minecraft
there's some cute Comics to look
at thank you so much must have been a
lot to draw for you
new sudden influx of Minecraft
streams so
suddenly MC Kyla one-onone collab would
also be exciting n because I feel like
Kyla would do like a lot of the hard
work and yeah I mean I would probably
try but I think it would be better with
someone who's not such a pro who's more
like On My Level a little bit more on my
level um but no I I don't really want to
do that hardcore I would want to try
solo but what I still want to do after
all this time is like one
block yeah yeah yeah yeah you bring it
up right now I did want to do one block
challenge of Ena or anybody really but
back then it was uh I was saying it to
Ena one block or Sky
Block any of these I kind of want to do
it with them I could yeah myth yeah it
could be like some uh thing we do with
myth like not everybody has to be online
at all times but I think who did this
before I saw like some people as a group
playing one block not just two people
but like was it one block or Sky
Block I feel like it's the same
thing uh but I think I was I think it
was one block smoke yeah yeah yeah yeah
it was Smoke yeah what I'm referencing
it would be kind of cool like cuz smok
maybe in the first stream they were all
together at the same time but not always
you
know would be nice if we could get
something like that going maybe I'll
pitch it to myth as a
little uh
project for
us but then what's the end goal of one
block is it also to kill the Ender
Dragon how the [\h__\h] do you do
that what what is the goal there's no
way you can find a stronghold
within one
block Minecraft
why even beat the game or make cool
structures you get you oh I was thinking
is that what you do you you can get
these like blocks where you put the
stones
in Oh e the game has ways to do it we
can make the portals
you give the one block things and it
pops out things
out
[Music]
you that's a
challenge there's still the never and
end in one
block yeah never I would think is wait
but wait okay so I imagine you get like
obsidian blocks right eventually you'll
be able to build build your never portal
but if you go in is the never also one
block or is the never a proper
never the never is proper ah okay I feel
like that's actually interesting I feel
like the never would then kind of be
almost like the refreshing relieving
kind of place to be
in cuz it's like a little bit in a way
it's it might be less dangerous than
your one block home where you could like
fall down or
so and Sky Block is also just a small
island oh
interesting yeah the sweet relief of the
never
interesting not hold okay well
interesting interesting I I do want to
kind of maybe I'll pitch it to them
now maybe I'll pict it to them
now uh let me wait where's our oh I
guess I'll write it
here hey
guys just hand this
idea play
Minecraft one block one block one block
one block
Minecraft um
since a long time ago with an but it
never came to through fruition fruition
fruition fru fruit fruit
on is that
how
fron but now I thought it might be nice
this is a group
project not everyone has to be online at
the same time either maybe just in the
first
stream as smok did it as a group too and
it seemed very
fun some of them sometimes played solo
to do some
work uh on it and then sometimes you're
with
others it's fun and
[Music]
dangerous how long do you think that
will take I mean obviously it depends
like how much everybody will actually
play but I feel like if we start start
it uh and then say okay let's try our
best to like focus on this for one or
two weeks you think we could finish it
in one or two
weeks let me look up the smok one
block here smoks one block Adventure
compilation free and free how 41
minutes I'll send them that as a
reference wait let me go to the end did
they
kill oh
oh they are they are in the end oh okay
and the end is
also the end is also
normal oh
um
okay I sent
it I think this is a really good
idea cuz it's also no pressure that
everybody plays at the same time I think
smoke also did like you know sometimes
they're alone sometimes not you
know it be good if we could like find
ways to have at least two
people at least most of the time I could
probably do a lot with Ena
together oh we would just be probably in
Discord yeah tag in and out like
hardcore yeah I hope they like the
idea would be cool
yeah nice nice
nice sounds like fun yeah you know I do
think we all like Minecraft cie is
finally over her I hate Minecraft Arc as
well GAA likes Minecraft a lot I think
but she also probably feels like there's
nothing to do for her anymore so this is
a you know good good motivation I'm I'm
we'll get we'll really I'm it back into
Minecraft
too is now fine with it yeah I think you
know she wanted to be part of the fun
she probably had
fomo add Moss oh we need a lot of moss
blocks then Amy will be
happy oh
she said she had foro she did yeah it's
obvious no I would
too with a game like that that everybody
plays oh my God thank you take it
monkey well yeah but you get a feeling
for what's built by people and what was
naturally generated if you just play a
while and you you know you get a feeling
for everything you see you can tell
apart what's natural so like back then
the only I said I said it back then the
problem was that she like played once
and then she would have a lot of time in
between that one stream and the next
stream which made her forget everything
and she had to start from zero again
like with her knowledge she never like
remembered how to play the game and that
was really frustrating for her like
asking the chat for help also took time
each time that's also frustrating and I
I told her that you're just like you're
not bad at Minecraft you just have to
like play it a little bit closer
together a few times and then you'll get
good at it really fast it's really easy
to get good at
Minecraft and like the basics are so
easy to pick up if you just you know
focus on it for one or two days
yeah yeah she was feeling pressured and
all that so that that's kind of like
getting rid of all the fun oh hi
smoothie what are you looking at some
some bug on the ground kill
it yeah I was also offering to like play
more with me so I can you know teach her
everything drag her through it but I'm
glad the Minecraft hate Arc is
over oh that time she broke yeah her and
GAA broke the walls of Phoenix
[Music]
then all right where was
I was I ah here I think right before the
water break uh the idol meeting break
that's a lot of blue guys that's insane
amount of
[Music]
Bluey have armor now let's go thank you
CL
Saloon FR kfp
inspector SW T stri Super Snake Mar d g
d Omega gaming Chan D unknown thank you
for the red super chat how do you make a
Super Chat blue oh yeah what was
this oh no no this was a normal a norm
noral flush situation right and you were
trolling thank you for the red super
chat Super Chat
Overkill
D kissy kissy
kissy oh smoothie is coming in you look
like you woke up and went to the toilet
huh didn't
you meow meow meow
meow oh oh oh do it do
it she walked over to me and she was
about to do a flop like she got she
turned her head and she like put her
paw like she lifted her paw she really
looked like she was about to do a flop
somehow she hesitated looked at me and
stopped and walked away I I don't like
stopping her from doing the flop
why did she
stop man sad she'll do it
eventually Do It Do the Flop Show me
your
belly the flop of Happiness kimy pH Dan
H Dan MK d n diesel D thank
you uh R Epic
the M kitten
[Music]
oh what would you do if you're 6 months
into your dream job and found out it's
too stressful for you oh is that what's
happening to
you why you you notice that 6 months in
then it kind of sounds like that might
be a temporary thing if it wasn't
stressful from the getg go maybe it's a
temporary thing
maybe give it some time maybe there's
certain factors that can also be you
know
fixed maybe I hope so for
you put my arms down
now I mean here in Holo there's also
times where it's very stressful I feel
like every job has like its ups and
downs with stress most most maybe some
are really just stressful but I feel
like then you would have felt
it
yeah and probably most of the time it's
not that easy but you could yeah maybe
discuss with your supervisor especially
if you're good with
them I hope it will get better for
you oh there's Laura Li super chat
again I missed you Laura Li you
beautiful woman thanks for the stream k
please forgive D for being so busy he
is
uh o with the poodles all he is with the
poodles already the
poodles the
poodles
what the dog you got is a
poodle you have a poodle
now cuz you got a dog right that's what
you
said was it several dogs and was it
poodle tell me tell me wait is duck Hood
not here right
now I guess maybe he's not here
or's logging back into his gimma girls
account oi is a gimma girl what I don't
know that
surprisingly yeah uh help me out with
that once you see this VOD let me know
you got poodles show me
pictures py D Cruz Dan zipley Dan and
bedia and doule Jones d
ER I think now there's only the super
chats from today today
today oh did that sound like
her
today it's pretty
good all right Channel monetization
today M be careful of your voice no
[Music]
no I'm scrolling oh wait oh it's right
there okay Super Chat reading time Super
Chat reading time so super chat reading
super reading super reading super
reading super reading super
reading no
no no
no how do you say
[Music]
no I I need
to learn that accent
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah I just got to say like German oh
with two
dots yeah maybe maybe
M he's a little bit
German maybe she is
it really sounds like it if I just say
in my mind if rather than trying to make
an o e if in my mind I really commit to
just saying the o with two dots then it
really sounds like the way she says
it the
intonation funny okay py D jaob 47 D GD
Dan space waterfall D that H with the
red super you I see you were here
earlier today then cute B big tit must B
at
me can I buy a kiss from the timkin to
Wawa in the next Super Chat reading as
thanks for tweeting Kiana's kitchen and
replies and likes to tweets oh you guys
have to kiss me W doesn't get Super Chat
for that so please take this Super Chat
and kiss I appreciate you oh thank you
well you don't have to thank me for
doing that though for doing k
kitchen it's no bigy I'm just like you
know I made something nice so might as
well show it off and make you guys
hungry and show you guys that I can be
wife
material thanks for the kisses though
thank you and thank you for bringing up
kiaha kitchen more corn Pizza
yo I
wish I wish I oh don't M ah
don't don't make me think of the B pizza
with the
corn
[\h__\h]
no but corn is
healthy maybe I can make that healthy
low calorie pizza and put some corn on
it just a like I mean not put like a
whole corn cob on
it pizza is not heavy hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey have you seen my low calorie
Pizza that I showed you guys that was
like what 300 calories or
so or even
less that was crazy cuz it's made with
egg yolk I want to try it because they
really say not yolk egg white they
really say that it doesn't taste like
egg at all it's really the spices and
that the uh it has quite the crunch like
of a thin
pizza similar to thin pizza
crunch nice consistency and
texture I'm going to try it making it
maybe even this week because I'm still
waiting for my next hellofresh
box so as long as I don't have anything
else to cook I guess I shouldn't make it
maybe okay I'll try to make it tomorrow
can you guys remind me if you if you
remind yourself of
it maybe like tomorrow at
noon ping me and be like girl didn't you
want to make that
pizza around noon or
so then I'm going to go buy ingredients
for it or might who knows a I need that
weird starch but I can probably use any
kind of starch she was using some weird
starch that I've never heard of before
some root star some some specific root
starch or so I wonder if I can find
something else that would
work I don't even know what is what is
starch again in German a yeah Arrow root
starch Arrow
root uh
doch file oh it's literally directly
translated file is
so I can probably just take like
corn uh
starch or is that like not good potato
starch would probably work oh uh-huh
uh-huh shouldn't be that you think it's
not rare to find I'll see what I
find I'll see what I
find I have
mytina at home which is corn starch corn
starch yeah then if this is okay to use
i' just if any anything works
and I just use
Mya it should work right okay I'll try
with that then I'll report back to you
guys you and if it's yummy I will tell
you
honestly and then you have to try it too
yo you think it might turn out different
I'll try to find the other one but I
doubt I'll find
it I'd have to probably order over
Amazon
okay anyway thank you D
Hood I still give you a kiss M stud
pink
stud in
invent our English cats English are
orange cats the luckiest cat
is there some kind of knowledge that I'm
not aware
of I don't think
so but maybe orange cats are not lucky
they just
like they they're so Fierce and Savage
they know how to make things
happen in like how they want it to be so
you could see that as luck just because
they make things
happen Jerry d
[Music]
this person's kind of feels
noovie under my
table that reminds me I saw didn't I see
didn't I
see was it it was it I missed it wasn't
there a
baby a
Super Chat the other
day and I saw I was like ah I can't
react to it right now
but
it how come I'm caught up and I didn't
see
it no I'm pretty sure there was one
like yeah you saw it too I'm sure it was
in a hardcore stream did I miss
one let me check again
not in this one it was a blue one I'm
pretty sure it was a blue
one I'm checking the whole lier logs I
was like so excited and I was looking
forward to reacting to it but
where
or or or could could be like it was but
if you guys barely any of you remember
seeing
it oh was ah was it a membership message
that would explain why it doesn't show
up Oh I thought it was
blue okay uh in day two it wasn't
[Music]
there
in day three it also wasn't
[Music]
there was it day
four feels pretty
recent no was not in day
[Music]
four was it in day I'm only looking at
members oh wait I should have checked
Milestones
Milestones okay the milestones and day
one
no they you found
it still looking
okay yeah it's there
y I should have reacted at the moment
because maybe baby feels like oh she
forgot about me but I'll never forget
about it it's there
I never thought I'd see them
again what they're even in armor they're
in
armor they have an armor
badge they must have been supporting all
this
time faithful loyal baby
[Music]
the ghost baby yeah but it's not a ghost
right
[Music]
now I don't know if it watches vs but I
feel like maybe not I hope it knows that
I saw it and I'm so happy to see it
again
[Music]
oh
man damn
it should have reacted right
away yeah I felt so happy to see them
again you
know just because it's nice to see
people who haven't been here in a long
time just to know oh they didn't forget
me or they didn't start hating me or so
hi smoovie again you keep on coming in
and
out she's nuzzling the PC now I know the
word for that
nuzzle soab
moat Dar Bobcats D oh so many cats
today also kind of
nostalgic
as
Daniel hi K it's been a bit college is
crazy but thankfully I will be done this
time next year oh that's still a while
but you can do it I wanted to catch your
stream on my birthday at least would
love a birthday shout out happy birthday
to you
[Music]
congratulations so this time next year
maybe on your birthday I'll hear from
you
again maybe more often in between
yeah the gamer cre
sh
Addy my
thoughts
mixed mixed language depends on like for
example if I just streamed and it's
probably
English because my brain's still in
English but it's a mix I think don't
really pay attention to it though Guru D
Nathan thanks for the pinky hi atten I
had a bit of a scare with my internet
getting knocked out around the time the
stream started but luckily they came out
of yeah I kind of reacted to this
already now I get to see tentu in her
natural state but this cat seems un
insufficiently orange yeah you meant the
in-game cat right couldn't be
me or did you mean because even my
actions were not orange
enough H then I apologize it might be
true I'm a little bit too chill to be an
orange cat
[Music]
maybe
yeah mislead extreme title sorry there's
nothing insufficient yeah my orangeness
is very orange I'm very orange indeed
but do I do I have orange cat
behavior
questionable your orange cat can be
chill sometimes well they definitely can
be
yeah sometimes goth is chill and he's
orange yeah but he's he's chill but no
he's not chill he's lazy as [\h__\h] and
he's still like you know he still shows
orange cat behavior
though Savage
cat yeah he's a
menace flaming
TP I I don't remember how her voice
sounded D Jim Tracy D Che Channel d
space water for d j monkey thanks for
two pinkies let's
go thanks for participating in Hardcore
Minecraft
kiar was pretty close really damn it was
so much fun to watch and it warmed my
heart to see you interact with so many
people outside of Ian including uh your
little date with Ollie and the brief
interactions with OK ah yeah man okay I
had those pretty much only off stream
but if you watched her stream you would
have seen it because OK senpai's bets
were completely opposite of me so uh we
bantered a little bit she I was just
like chilling because I wasn't streaming
I wasn't I was like tabed out also a lot
of the time uh but then she would talk
to me and I had to tab back into the
game I was
like oh
yeah yeah trying my best to uh still be
available when people talk to me
me she was so sweet she kept on talking
to
me from her
side I felt
quite happy about
that and her voice is so nice
man like after the first round cuz she
had opposite beds she came to me she was
like damn K you got it all right I'm
like yeah it will continue like that no
problem kind of like what's the
word a a what's a in English
again I
was her
[Music]
not blue flexing like kind of like
challenging flexing in a challenging
way egging her on yeah taunting yeah
taunting yeah yeah yeah taunting is the
right
word I was taunting her with that H I
hope we'll have more chances to see you
interact with Japan and ID again in the
future whereever it's in Minecraft or
other games and I hope that one block
thing works out ah yes I'm late on the
Super Chat I'm a slow CPU monkey don't
worry I mean it doesn't really feel late
because I read the other Minecraft
stream super chats as well together so
no worries thank you um we'll see um I
don't want to get your hopes up guys
also because like I'll be kind of
busy I would hope that if we do it that
we would do it in June cuz I think
starting from like July and even more so
starting from August I'll be busy and
I'll be traveling and I'll be in Japan
if I'm in Japan for like really like one
and a half months or so I do want to
have a streaming setup and all that but
at the same time I I don't want to like
rely on everything working so
well so I wouldn't want to plan a
project like this during a time like
that so ideally I'd want to do it in
June and then it really depends on if
the others are available in June for one
or two weeks
of you know playing a
bunch but you guys know we haven't been
doing many myth streams um so I think it
would be a nice project to bring myth
back a little bit
actively yeah
but don't get your hopes
up I mean just the fact that we don't
all have to be online at the same time
should make it very
possible we'll see and thank you though
in total that's a red super chat so you
get a kiss chick
monkey M Mah mwah mwah mwah thank
you ch
space waterful
d thank
you
quad the
pronunciation wow 10 out of 10 and W is
wondering if that horror game collab and
pickup LS of goba is still going to
happen I was really looking forward
seeing you guys together again but it's
been a while since I got got mention
yeah I didn't really want to bother her
recently uh in in the past weeks because
I felt like she was was busy
uh uh but I did end up bothering her not
about that but about a different game
just randomly dm'd her like hey you want
to play this uh like beginning of next
month and she said yeah she was like
hell yeah I'm like oh
okay it's a different game though I
don't know if you guys will even like it
I just saw a game that is Co-op and I
was like
M who should I play this
with so I I just tried suggesting it to
goba
goba she said yes so we'll see we'll see
EDF soon uh not quite soon I think for
me it's like another month away right
more more than a
month oh wait you guys don't even know I
mean the release is kind of like about a
month
away well my stream will be a little bit
after the release
but still around the same time
frame
meow ah you're meowing at the door don't
you dare jump on it the one time I
didn't double lock it no [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
don't look don't look at that I you look
like you want to jump on it and open it
I'm almost done I swear I have like two
super chats left don't don't no don't
she's looking at it she wants to open
the
[Laughter]
door yes come
here yes come
here oh my God okay let's finish these
super chats cuz she wants to
leave k
d don't jump don't jump wellit I'm going
to take off my headphones h off so I can
hear it when she does it I'm watching
you I see your glowing eyes in the dark
yeah I see you I see you sitting right
in front of the
doorknob milk and frog
St she's a menace she has orange cat
behavior I don't know why she's the
green one oh I'm I'm done okay oh oh she
left the door she left it ah she's
she's now that I'm done she wants to
like she's like
[Laughter]
whatever oh
man I'm going to continue watching
Shogun after making some dinner
now I'm so uninspired without hell fresh
I'm I'm just
making I'm just making some noodles with
some it's probably not the lowest
calorie thing I don't [\h__\h] know what
to make when I'm like when I don't have
my hell fresh F it's okay I haven't
eaten much
today I don't know how low calories it
is but it's probably not that crazy it's
just like some noodles with pesto sauce
how bad can it
be yeah and then I'll watch
shun oh one more thing that was I want
to ask about Shogun I'm pretty sure that
this is how it is but like obviously I
think this is the the original dub what
I'm watching but they keep on talking
about Portuguese Portuguese talking
Portuguese learning Portuguese don't
understand Portuguese blah blah blah but
they're always talking in English is it
just like a thing where they say like
for the sake of us they say they're
talking Portuguese but like we're
supposed to imagine that the
conversations are in Portuguese but it's
actually in English right yeah that's
what's
happening it's it's fine because I think
it's really cool that I that was one
thing I was wondering about when I was
about to start watching it I was like
are they going to are the Japanese
people going to speak
English no don't open the door she's
there
again
why why why cat
why yeah yeah yeah when I get up you run
away yeah yeah you want my attention I
know it um but yeah I was
like if if they're going to speak
Japanese is it going to be actual
Japanese actors are going to are they
going to be [\h__\h] at speaking Japanese
but no okay there's a lot of Japanese
conversation it's all fluent Japanese by
Japanese people pretty
much so I think that's really cool that
they didn't forcefully like make that be
English yeah yeah yeah that's
good because that way they could keep
the like actual Japanese
actors
um yeah
it's like it's very authentic in that
way but then okay I can forgive the you
said one of you guys said it's annoying
but I can forgive the Portuguese not
being
Portuguese uh because then it would have
been completely like different languages
that people don't understand I mean yeah
there will be some Portuguese watching
who can understand Portuguese and there
will be some Japanese people watching
who couldn't understand Japanese but
it's like m a little bit too much yeah
and and you you would want to maybe not
read subtitles every once in a while
uh I think that's fine it's good to mix
it that
way but maybe they should have put a
note somewhere I mean it became very
obvious to me at some point but maybe in
the beginning they should have said the
English dialogues are supposed to be uh
Portuguese but we made them English like
a
disclaimer I don't
know I honestly prefer sub tunnels
[Music]
M I think it it would have been too much
if if the Portuguese dialogue would all
have Port been Portuguese and there
would have been no English in there for
me personally I feel like too much like
cuz it's good
generally the Japanese stuff I you know
it's very authentic and all that and I
like it but the English man he's
actually British right so even though
he's also supposed to be speaking
Portuguese I mean it fits his
nationality at least I don't
know yeah the Portuguese actors like I I
I'm actually surprised they found so
many great uh Japanese speaking actors
that seem like like the way they act
seems to me like un very unlike how
Japanese people act normally in movies
and
stuff it seemed more Hollywood like and
I was really uh surprised and impressed
by that and then for example the the one
actress who is the one who speaks so to
supposedly speaks Portuguese but then
she actually speaks English her English
is really good too I'm like where where
did these actors come from shees Maro
yeah she speaks obviously Japanese but
also really nice English must have like
been raised maybe in in an English
speaking country by Japanese parents or
something like that Disney finds a way
yeah the budget and the the fact that
it's like a Hollywood kind of thing damn
that that opens a lot of doors I
suppose but oh also one more thing I
wanted to say like you know I love these
kind of historic shows and all that uh
it's like just beautiful to watch that
um mostly though these kind of things I
watch Like European shows because
there's just so many anymore not EUR not
not European I mean the history being
European like a lot of England
stuff uh a lot of FR France stuff and so
on um but there's I feel like there's
rarely ever like Asian history
shows
especially on this level of budget and
quality uh so that's really cool to
finally have something like this in
Shogun they they putting a lot of budget
into it and you can see it and it's
actually like quality because like I
thought M what if it's what if it's like
non-japanese speaking like what if they
what if because they they they're just
going to use an excuse that they
couldn't find enough Japanese actors so
they have like half of them being other
Asian eth e
ities um
nationalities and you can really hear it
but no they're actually like they all
speak Japanese proper Japanese they're
all Japanese sheesh they actually made
it
sheesh no I'm I'm impressed I'm
genuinely
impressed cat this movie is
exploring you know she she likes to
like tease me when she's hungry and I'm
not giving her food yet like in the
morning when I'm staying in bed a little
bit
longer I think I told you this before
she was like sniff sniff sniff on the
bed right next to me so I can see it and
she'll like sniff right there where
there's things like little
little bushes of fur that she dropped h
should purposefully sniff it in a way
that it gets stuck on her mouth and be
like until it ends up in her mouth
because she's trying to get rid of it
supposedly but it's obviously like cats
are incapable of doing of actually
getting rid of something that's in all
partially in their mouth they try they
go like BL BL BL BL but it just like
goes deeper and deeper and then they end
up eating it so she will do this in
front of my eyes I have to like like
partially get up pull it out of her
mouth
but she keeps on doing it I think she's
100% doing it on purpose because she her
doing this increases by 200% when in the
morning or whenever it's like dinner
time or breakfast time or
so she's just annoying me and showing me
she wants to eat something but as long
as I'm not giving her her actual food
she will like put anything into her
mouth that she's not supposed to be
putting in her mouth if if there's
plastic lying around she will do the
same thing with
plastic yeah I'm like girl
okay I see what you're
doing such a such a Savage cat
man she has me well well trained
yeah oh God what is it expiring today
the Australia
concert are saying that because it's
expiring
today no
idea you don't even know but thanks for
reminding me don't know if I'll do it
today if it's not expiring today we'll
see yeah I only saw the YouTube part and
I was like hey can I get a code so I can
watch the whole thing then I kind a
cold 526 ah okay not you got the
dates okay I'm going to I'm going to go
now and and double lock my door
now what what she
did why you so I wasn't even I wasn't
even in
it why you why you why why are you so
excited about me watching it you
offended or did you were you visible in
the audience shots or why do you want me
to watch it so
fast don't know why you want to watch it
w I was curious to see like the
hype it was pretty it looks pretty
hype okay I'm going to go way yeah well
way yeah I can see her all the
time no okay okay okay and J we say hope
be the same what thank you Rachel uh
I'll see you guys tomorrow same time
What bye-bye where's
[Music]
me oh Alvaro Danon zipley danion
space wonderful
dly again dun
[Music]