[Music]
hello
uh i'm a bedtime
[Music]
i'm a pizza how how would you how would
you say that
um through the wind is that a saying
in english because i literally just came
out of the shower
and quickly air dried not air dry blow
dry
my hair no not under the weather no no
no
no no that's not what i want to say i'm
fine
how are you all
wet kiara isn't that
by default just kidding it's not that
i'm just kidding
let me pour some let me make something
hello yes
well we're starting off very well huh
and one question before i forget it is
there any
is there any button by the way um
is there any button any function on the
keyboard
that when you would push it uh
it would like reset your mouse cursor
because i feel like that's what i did
yesterday but i'm not sure how i did it
i wish i could just push that button
again and make everything normal again
reside it to the normal mouse cursor
um elaborate um yeah well it got reset
and suddenly it's just my normal mouse
not keanu mouse anymore how much water
do i need i never know
let's just get it all all in there yes
i'm gonna make some tea alt f4
i'm not gonna press alt f4 hell no
is there anyone who has a better idea
than that
i mean i guess i could google but i
don't wanna
hello hello everyone who's still coming
in hello
so we are making again peach tea because
that's just what i have right next to me
peach tea
out f11 out f11
what really
almost at 500k yeah 10k more to go
um there's a bunch of things i want to
talk about today
but someone made me someone on twitter
made me realize one thing about next
week
next week is going to be a bit crazy
oh next week is going to be a bit crazy
because i'm most likely
going to be reaching 500k next week so
we're obviously gonna celebrate that
and i'm releasing my song
so we're obviously going to celebrate
that
and that person on twitter was like next
week
it will be a huge party the whole time
and that
the thing is that person who wrote that
to me and you also all of you
in the chat right now
don't even know that there's one more
exciting thing next week that is a huge
party reason so it's not
only the 500k celebration and my first
ever original song which would be
already enough reason to hype and party
and everything
there's one more thing next week which
is really really
[Music]
but wait there's more all over again
but wait there's more
and um i guess i could tease you and let
me just uh let me just say one thing
it's already weekend anyway so it's
schedule time pretty soon
on monday i'll show you my schedule but
let me let me let me tease you the third
thing
is
should i say it should i say it
it's about a collaboration
next week i might die out of excitement
i might die i cannot take
that much excitement
well i will not say who it is you'll
have to wait until monday for the
schedule
[Music]
uh okay my my water is cooking
hello once again i'll start training the
super chats once my tea is done
i up putting in the honey
though before i put in the water now it
doesn't just it won't dissolve so well
goddammit honey honey
[Music]
you know which honey well yes get all
that honey in there
yes make my throat real smooth thank you
honey
okay a little bit of a swirly swirl
also thinking about
oh thank you for the super chat thank
you i'll be reading it
thinking about uh i was thinking about
what the next person for
holotalk should be and
i have already kind of decided
[Music]
in my heart i already decided on the
next guest
i'm just uh trying to get
in contact with that person
uh i i also actually decided on
when it will be because see next week i
have a collab and we said we're gonna do
it uh
every two or three weeks whole talk
every two or three weeks
and i was i was gonna go for three weeks
this time because i feel like i need a
little bit more
i feel i feel like it would be good if i
have a little bit more space
in between the first and the second holo
talk so i wanted to do it three weeks
later
but i do have a collab
with a japanese talent already for
three weeks later in that week i didn't
want to overshadow it so it's not
happening in three weeks so it's
happening in two weeks next holo talk in
two weeks
yeah three weeks is not happening
because i already have something pretty
big
in three weeks you planned so far ahead
yeah because
the collab that's happening in three
weeks time
did not come from my side but came from
the other side
yeah so
so i don't wanna i don't wanna uh
squeeze
too many japan member
collabs into each week i want
maximum one if possible
i want maximum one per week now
there's so much going on
[Music]
a good volume because i realized um
that maybe uh generally my bdm was a
tiny bit too loud
and that's why i felt like my
voice was sounding a bit meh
it's a nice volume really okay
okay thank you
okay voice hello you're kidding me
are you kidding me it's it's not my
voice
i i see it in my stream lives i see it
even goes into the yellow
area almost uh
the whole time so it should be my voice
my voice should be loud enough
oh wow uh so we're reading uh we're
reading um
super chat uh this stream was not
scheduled
but i i realized um probably that
i have a lot a lot to read possibly
and the only next time where i could
read it would be
in the minecraft stream tomorrow but
feeling like the minecraft stream itself
might be quite a long stream
which also probably gets well we'll get
some super chat i felt like at the end
of the minecraft stream i would
i would have so much to read so i'm
doing it now
uh yeah fire alarm i'll continue next
week i'll promise i promise
yeah actually i also wanted to do
something today spontaneously
i actually wanted because the release
date was yesterday at least in
you know now it should be in every
country uh of the
hyrule warriors
and it seems like we have permission for
our game so i was thinking of starting
that spontaneously today but then i
realized wait kiara
you already have so many games going on
but would you guys like to see that age
of calamity yeah
i mean what i was thinking is we could
we we could just do it for one stream
uh and generally the idea would really
just be
to do it for one stream because i have
so many other streams going on so many
other games
[Music]
so and then after we did one stream of
that
hybrid warriors game we can decide if we
still want to keep it or not and even if
then we would continue it a bit later
maybe when i finish fire emblem
because i'm not sure if it's a good
streaming game i would have to try it
out
because basically just continuously
killing like loads of mobs right
i don't know how fun that is
to watch like in several streams for
hours i don't know
but i do at least want to give it a try
on stream
because um i like zelda games and this
is well it's not really you know
it's like a collab with koi tecmo and
not a typical dollar game but
i do want to give it a try sounds like a
plan okie dokie
okie dokie
[Music]
i have quite a few things that i want to
talk about that's it
there's there's so many things i wanna
just chat
chat with you chat about with you
uh thank you what is super chat
i can't wait to read all the super chats
but i also want to talk about so many
things
maybe i should keep some of my topics
for a little bit later
because i wrote them down i wrote some
topics down
so that i don't forget that i want to
talk about them because i want to kind
of talk about how
hollow talk went and uh
reflect
okay
yeah it's probably gonna be a long
stream
okay well um i think first of all we can
probably start talking about holotalk
when i reach the super chats for
hellotalk so for now let's get started
with reading the
among us super chats
i say this enjoy the regular sleep
schedule while you can before it
inevitably slips into a late night
routine again
actually today i woke up early for the
collab
it's telling like i woke up even earlier
than i needed to
because i heard the neighbors child
and their mother i heard them through
the window
and and the wall i guess we're not even
like
connected but i hear i heard literally
everything every word they say
which is why i think they probably hear
every word i say
but they probably don't understand it
because they most likely don't
understand
english while i understand japanese very
well
normal like usually japanese people
don't understand english
so they probably just hear some weird
girl
talking to herself in english the whole
time
in the middle of the night but up until
now
i've had no complaints although i'm
pretty sure they hear me
i tried some um my windows are close but
i think the reason why i
heard them so clearly in the morning
that it even made me
wake up i think the reason is because
they probably have their window open
but if all the windows are closed i'm
not sure
how much they hear me but for their
own sake i hope they don't hear me so
much but
there's not much i can do i tried to
like it's i'm i live in a house and the
houses don't
are close to each other but they're not
uh connected to each other but they
you know in japan in japan the walls are
pretty thin
and uh imagine them when kiana plays
mario kart yeah oh my god they must
think i'm insane with something
[Music]
i put like you know that sound proofing
foam
on my windows but sound proofing
that stuff it's sold as sound proofing
foam
partially but that's a lie it doesn't
sound proof at all
it's more like acoustic uh sound
stuff you know uh you know those things
that have like these
boing boinging anyway i put those on my
windows at least
now i can't open my windows anymore i
did that
but there's not much more i can do and
this has absolutely no effect yeah
yeah but oh well i want to live here for
much longer
so when i moved back to where i lived
before
overseas you're telling brum into the
whole hot ravital welcome pickle
and when i moved back to my list before
i think i shouldn't have much of a sound
problem anymore
from like sound leaking
there might be some other issues but oh
well we'll think about that once we're
there
okay i am we only read two super chats
how much time has passed
20 minutes and i've read two super chats
that's no super chat
well i just it's like an intro okay i
just have to i can't just
suddenly go into the super chat reading
i have to you know talk to you
and ease you into the super cherry
okay let's go so
gundam thank you just want to say for
working so hard past the hype is real
p.s this is the first
manga supercharged first time time
stamped purpose
it was the third not the first you have
failed
completely um but thank you
thank you soon generally
awarded the title of honorary phoenix
night to next set
he is now among the legendary one of the
first phoenix brigade
you make kiara pratt why what happened
behind my back
is it because he makes such great videos
i hear them i hear the ghosts footsteps
again guys
let's go on a let's go on a different
topic once again
procrastination here we go today so you
guys know
i've had the ghostbusters over quite
some time quite quite a few times
and um trying to kill the ghosts
and it worked before like they showed me
pictures
of dead ghost bodies that they took away
that were in my ceiling
and then i started feeling bad then i
started realizing
but they're so cute i don't want to kill
them i feel so sorry i'm taking away
their home
so anyway i kept continuing it because
we already started to process but last
time they came
uh they didn't die i know there's still
some in there because i hear them
walking around
at least one at least one ghost is in
there
uh i i hear it i hear it
now i hear how it's like doing something
with something
um probably building a nest or something
oh my god you killed it with your bare
hands are you
i wha how could you do such a thing but
anyway
so last time that the ghostbusters came
they were not able to find another dead
body
so i guess they stopped eating the
poison
i don't know and and the question is how
are they surviving in there if we tried
to like
close every possible entrance but the
the ghostbusters did say
that there are some spaces that they
cannot reach
outside so maybe
they're they're still able to come in
and go out and they're bringing in their
own food
you stepped on one what the hell oh my
god
it's not rats okay it's ghosts
it's cute small ghosts
so it didn't work last time but they're
coming back again next week the
ghostbusters
and i still hear the mice so it's been
two weeks without a dead mouse
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't even know i'm trying to hide it
but
i'm crying
[Laughter]
okay so it's not rats it's mice if
anything it's mice okay
it's not rats if it was rats i would be
moving out um but yeah it seems like
probably i'm not gonna get rid of them
but i've started to feel
like okay with it i mean the sound of
them walking around up there
creeps me out because i'm just scared
that they're getting into the actual
room but they have not showed up in my
room i only
hear them in the ceiling and in the
walls
[Music]
so i guess like as long as they don't
show up
right in front of me i guess i'm happier
with that
than having the knowledge that i
am killing poor little tiny mice
because today i for the first time
not only heard their footsteps but i
heard one
mouse like squeaking and it sounded like
so
desperate it was running around and i
was like
he something like that i was like
i can no longer i can no longer
have this responsibility and like
be the one killing ordering them to be
killed
no i will live with them until the end
i will live with them until i move out
and
free for months
i mean it isn't working anyway
apparently the the poison only worked
for like two mice and now it's not
working anymore
i guess they're like actually able to go
in and out
and bring in food and and eat it and
then they don't have to eat the
the poison stuff
nah nah well yeah well um
i don't know as long as they don't show
up in the room
ah and yeah well we'll just live along
[Music]
i will just live with them i had pet red
yes see the thing is like people
actually have them as pets like rats and
and mice
um i mean i suppose that
these ones since i don't have them as
actual pets they're probably not
as hygienic as uh
if you would have them as a pet since
they go outside and come in again so i
don't want to know i don't want to touch
them
i don't want to touch them and i'm
worried that they like
if they get into my like if
if they actually get into the living
area
that they do something weird and uh
spread some
disgusting bacteria or whatever so yeah
hopefully they don't get in
anyway anyway
we went on a long uh how do you call
that ten
tangent
how do you call that what was it i read
it and i forgot
tangent okay isn't that
a mathematical term
isn't that something i learned in
mathematics class
oh yes it is so smart i actually i
actually remembered something
unbelievable mathematics was my worst
subject in school
absolutely the most of it okay i'm going
on another tangent
for sake yeah read your goddamn
super chats
okay
well this is basically a small talk
chatting stream it's nothing
but that it's literally colibacing
it's a it's a chatting stream
there's so many things i wanted to talk
about but there's a reason why i don't
i this is something i wanted to do
originally but i never ended up doing it
i wanted
to do more only chatting streams
i've only done one for members before
but no public chatting streams because
i'm just scared
that i will run out of things to talk
about
and that it will end up being boring
otherwise i'll be doing it the whole
time but instead i'm just doing it
constantly in my super chat
streams because there i feel no pressure
maybe one day we will have a
you impossible no but for real like
sometimes i just don't have things to
talk about i mean
i often even if i have nothing to talk
about i often come up with things to
talk about but i'm just scared of
having that moment that blackout moment
where i absolutely can't think of
anything interesting
that's why i really respect people like
madden senpai
i'm going on a tangent again oh my god
that's why
i respect people like madden senpai
because her chatting streams are just so
good
she just continuously talks about so
many random things like
how does she not run out of like things
to talk about
or like pekora senpai who in her hour
hours and hours and hours of minecraft
streams
she would just like never stop talking
and it's like it's not even like this is
what i respect about
pekuda streams she when she plays a game
like minecraft
this is where i know that someone has
talent
as a streamer you you stream a game
but you don't only talk about the game
like
pick what i say but generally i would
say she talks
barely about the game while she's
playing it
at least when it comes to minecraft
because she usually just talks about
different topics the whole time
comes up with things to talk about the
whole time and that's where i say
that is a professional streamer because
if she would
have hours and hours of minecraft
streams every goddamn day
and would only talk about what's
happening in the game
and narrating that it would easily get
boring the reason why her minecraft
streams are so
good and something that i have watched
every goddamn night
is because she just talks randomly about
interesting stuff she can just randomly
come up with that kind of stuff
okay well kiara shut up now and read
your super chats
but that is something i aim to be i want
to be
one of those people who can just talk
about random things while they're
playing a game
okay super chat super chat we have
officially read
um one
two three four selfie chats
in 30 minutes
okay let's go
[Music]
thank you
words can't really describe how happy we
are for you countless hours of hard work
has finally paid off for you
and when it's released during
thanksgiving i'll drink to the occasion
come by
oh thank you that was still i think
about
the song release thank you so much yeah
finally as i said before it's
the era of the phoenix
my time is
right
[Music]
foreign
in someone's japanese who told me my
japanese is good i told him his japanese
is good as well
[Music]
thank you
youtube
why do i keep on asking who doesn't like
giraffes i mean it's not
i don't dislike them stop asking me if i
like the grabs oh my god
oh my god how is that such an important
question that you have to spam it in the
chat
is giraffes or giraffes oh yeah i guess
it's giraffes okay after i said it i
realized it
i like giraffes okay you happy now
i like them i mean i don't dislike them
the long boys wait
she said the thing wait is that a
is that a joke have i
been have i been trolled
t is perfect temperature right now
yummy and
[Music]
hey i'm paying pickle from the previous
game i felt bad for killing you so
here's some conversation
thanks for letting me play with you and
i'm sorry for what i did don't everybody
am i already um all right everything's
cool
lizard wizard thank you
red super chat to help make the kiara
with the glasses dream come true
i feel like um yeah as i told during
that stream i feel like it's like a
trend
for everyone who gets a new outfit they
also get glasses with it so i feel like
that's a total
totally possible possibility
oh possible possibility thank you for
the red super chat
i'll tell my papa i'll tell him but i
don't know
and i don't think i would look good with
glasses
you think i would look good but what
kind of glasses like
huge glasses or smile glasses ground
glasses or rectangular
glasses
[Music]
fat frame glasses or finger frame
glasses
or no frame glasses
[Music]
sunglasses oh yeah
librarian glass start no what
nose glass what no no no
no that's that looks no no no
actually i just got the idea how about
you know those um
you know that everyone knows them those
black uh
black pixel uh sunglasses
[Music]
okay i don't know if you recognize that
melody but um
how about i ask for those kind of
glasses
are those copyrighted or anything
the meme with the thug life classes
uh i think i'm gonna ask for those
classes
welcome to the membership
oh yes i need those glasses where did
they come from where did they originate
from
i wondered
[Music]
fun i'm going to act as if i don't
understand what you mean
hey car ears and cars
on the top of my head that's a weird
idea that's so weird
just kidding okay yeah cat ears would be
adorable i would be one of those uh
ginger cats
you know ginger cats i've never had a
ginger cat in my life but i was once
i was once friends i was once friends
very good friends with the ginger cat
and i realized
ginger cats are amazing they are so
loving
yes i was friends with one of those
ginger cats
so if i would have
cat ears that would be adorable but but
it would be hard to still wear my hats
if i had
two cat ears up there
let's see if we can combine cat ears
with hats because i don't want to lose
my hats that's for sure
i love pets cat phoenix here
it would imply that i'm something else
that is not
a phoenix i don't like to imply
that i am not oh yes garfield
yes i love lasagna i am orange
it just makes sense it's just
i need cat ears i will become
garfield i will become
kiara field kiara field
qr fields qr field
full on ginger cats are mostly male oh
that's an interesting what
what really that cat was indeed male
maybe that's why because i feel like
also male cut male cats are generally
nicer and more cuddlier
kiara
i have no problem with mondays
i don't really have a i don't really
have this feeling of
wow the week starts on monday anymore
because i just take
my days off on random days mostly it's
not a sunday
so it's kind of weird like
when you work from home at whatever time
you want to work at it's just uh
everything is so messed up
cat's ear shaped hats
you my friend are genius i actually used
to
own you know those barretts
with cat ears
you my friend are a genius
thank you thank you
ah my chat stop oh there we go
my chat keeps on stopping but there we
go oh yeah okay
yeah that's ah that's
let's see if we can make it happen
someday
oh yeah wait muda says spoil chiara with
ponytail
i actually also want to see me in a
so with a very high ponytail
i don't want to see that deluxe 67
dangerous monkey naked
ocean black thank you and the great rv
true check out the thumbnail for the
german classroom there is your glasses
scanner that is true
that is true i did have glasses for the
thumbnail and that looked okay
that looked okay i looked smart
twin tail
i think twin tails
wouldn't look so good on me because it
just makes me look very
childish probably
but i don't know we could give it a try
let's hope for many many hairstyles in
the future
get hooked on the phone right now
i think he's sleeping
yeah recently he's not been much in the
chat right but he's been sick
apparently
[Music]
you could he hasn't been feeling well
according to his twitter account
he had a fever until yesterday or today
yeah maybe that's why he's not uh coming
much to my streams also he's been
sleeping quite early according to his
twitter
and i've been streaming quite late yeah
yeah
i know also get the nunny
yeah i hope he gets better soon i mean
he's apparently already recovered from
the fever
but yeah i think generally his health
has been
not so well
[Music]
foreign
a proud proud daughter uh reporting
her ideas to papa why is my chat so
weird right now
[Music]
my chat keeps on stopping come on
work harder come on maybe i should
change from top chat to
all the chats
i think i wonder if it works better if
i'm at live chat
[Music]
damn it's like stopping so it's stopping
in mine too really
oh my god
my alarm just went off for whatever
reason
let me let me switch to live chat
there we go okay let's see how that
works oh my god
oh my god
you heard that or when you're just
surprised because i was surprised
i'll drink my tea
slow mode
oh my god it just keeps on stopping and
then goes like and then stops and
stops and okay let's continue
reading though
toilet cleaner thank you sorry for
killing you i'm still feeling guilty can
i attend by joining the kfp and cleaning
all the toilets i'll do it with my own
toothbrush
if you want me to
[Music]
uh
i mean first of all you won't get much
work done
if you use your toothbrush so
let me say no to that also for hygienic
reasons for you because i don't know if
you're planning to use that
too fresh again how about
i will finance out of the kfp members
pockets of course i will finance you a
toilet brush
yes yes
sounds good to me i mean who else would
buy it huh
electrical electric oh my god
no
no maybe there's an electrical toilet
brush
i wonder
what
never gotten a voice back before because
they've always been in japanese i'm
really excited for you thank you
i hope it will be satisfactory
thank you assad ponytail oh
that would be cute
i like ponytails because they look
sporty and i think it would look good on
me
so generally i like the idea of a
ponytail
being a murphy eleven that was so much
fun also i'm sorry kiara
what i had to do sometimes the hardest
choices required is strong as well
i don't i don't want to talk about it
anymore
thank you side quest thank you account
[Music]
and this was a fun stream in order to
super chat unless this will be my only
one for the stream gonna sit and enjoy
the super chat reading thank you
amazing coin
your english is fine the only times you
mispronounce is when you try using
elaborate words
have confidence we love listening to
your stories you never come across this
montana doll that's
cool thank you but i have to say
i am from australia so
i'll think my english is superior
to yours
oh no bald kiara
is a cursed idea no no
no no no no no
no no
you mispronounce as much as amit what
yeah and that's nothing that's
impossible
where is your bedroom my bedroom night
is called nutella that's my kind of
vegemite
[Music]
um
i just want to have a quick thank you
and hello ian for you guys streams
really helped me get over my grief a few
months ago you'll do great chiara thank
you
i'm glad we could help we love to make
people happy
29 thank you yeah i'm so proud of you
you went all out for all these
activities i can't wait to blast your
song on the loop and share it to my
friends now it's a time for a new era
and it's your era kiana hell yeah the
area
of the phoenix has arrived once again
let me repeat the era of
the phoenix has arrived
[Music]
everyone isn't perfect let us all
employees kick those haters away and
protect them so she protected us in so
many ways by keeping us happy
yeah i can't wait to see you get the
recognition you deserve
this is where it starts getting
wholesome i'm probably at the super chat
reading
from the manga stream right now
the super chats that came in during that
super chat reading is getting wholesome
again
everyone brace yourselves i was pretty
close to crying out of happiness today
because i was reading
for hours i was reading so many comments
everywhere about holo talk
so many and uh i was uh
i was emotionally
overwhelmed
[Music]
quite overwhelmed yeah
it's just like finally things are paying
off you know
finally things are working people
appreciate what i do
it just makes me so happy
but we'll get to that we'll get to that
we're still in the manga stream i said i
will talk about whole talk once we get
to the holotalk stream
air dragoon three four seven daggashin
dog wong duncation
kfb sanitary officer duncashin
being emotional and now we're talking
about that being emotional
in your super chat readings is what made
me fall for a chiana being true to
yourself and us
is what makes you special screwed a
rabbit hole i wasn't dragged
what i followed you out of my own will
ah
thank you
oh i'm glad some people like these kind
of super chat readings
thank you all there's like so many
people here chatting with me
while i'm reading this super chat
thank you all so much
oh super chat from the audio spike oh no
[Music]
i am sorry x paragon
leon outer thank you oh thank you for
the red super jack
hello kiara i rarely get to watch your
life because of work but yesterday's
stream
took my mind off a very stressful
deadline that i have for work
and i'm so thankful oh keep being you
looking forward to everything you have
in store
[Music]
thank you thank you for choosing me as
your
relaxing and entertainment source
thank you i'm glad i could help
stressful deadlines
suck but um
i hope that you got it done and hope
it's
all right now don't stress yourself too
much
otherwise procrastinate progression
procrastination is always a good
solution
procrastinate with me join me
[Music]
uh google
translate
and xiaomi thank you
back to that window oh there
is my what's going on my my chat is uh
actually so weird i see the same super
chat like a million times
or is that actually happening
[Music]
what the hell i'm gonna switch to top
chat
again
i wouldn't say it's my potato busy
i wouldn't say it's my potato just i was
about to end it there
potato period um now that's something i
wanted to mention the thing that happens
with the disconnection
is not about the pc that's in if
anything that's an internet problem
which i'm surprised about because i
streamed the whole talk show
is not happening during japanese prime
time it's uh
actually my internet should have been
pretty good
during that stream
but i don't know why it's so unstable
[Music]
um i when that happened
i really didn't want uh people to pay
too much attention to it so i wanted to
just
get it over with quickly and fix it
quickly
but if i would shut up and focus on
fixing
then there would be an awkward silence
so i tried oops i tried really hard
to um multitask
i'm generally not much of a good
multitasker
but i use the cable
of course i do
yeah um i i tried
uh to like uh like while i'm fixing it
i tried to like still listen to her to
also still uh you know translate what
she's saying
or even read her question or something
while i
am fixing something there were several
moments when she disappeared on my
screen
and so normally i'm really bad at
multitasking where i tried really hard
to stay relaxed and
keep the show going show must go on you
know the show must go on i was like
in in early i was probably going
crazy and about to explode
uh but i kept my cool
yeah i saw a lot of feedback from other
people as well that said
uh she i did a really good job this time
by just fixing it quickly and uh keep on
talking
ah thank you i'm so relieved i'm so
relieved that uh
you guys uh gave me that feedback thank
you
it was uh i did i did actually even
besides that fixing those
uh issues i i had to do multitasking the
whole time because
uh like you know when i was inserting
and
formatting those questions which by the
way next time
i will prepare that i was just not sure
about
which questions i'm actually gonna use
because of time issues like i don't i
wasn't sure how much
how much i can actually ask so i did not
like pre-prepare the fermenting of all
those questions
because i just didn't know like which
ones i was gonna use but next time
i guess i'll just prepare all of them
and then throw them out uh
even if they're already permanent but
whatever so while i was doing that
while i was formatting i was like
like to make up for an awkward silence
i would have to talk to her in japanese
read her the
question in japanese while i am picking
out the question in english
put it into my streamlabs text field
and then start formatting it so it would
fit the window
but at the same time read the question
to her and if the question was short i
already had to listen to her what she
was saying to then
put it into my brain and then later on
you know translate it
it was a it was a lot of
a lot of multitasking going on in my
brain it was like going like
that oh
i was trying really hard to keep it
smooth
i'm generally you i think you guys know
if you've been watching my streams
i think you guys know i'm generally not
much of a good
multitasker but today today there was
uh it was a life or death situation
but i think it went well yeah it went
well but
i could have definitely done it better
um i think uh
i just have to do a few of these talk
shows and
you know i'll get used to it because i'm
not a professional translator
i i never and in japanese i taught
myself
so it's not like i'm professional at
this at all
but i try i try to make it
well i try to do it well
the fact that you pulled it up the way
you did thank you
thank you
what
why don't you record whole talk as a
video that's something i talked about
before holotalk happened while i was
still planning the whole thing i asked
my audience what they prefer and
overwhelmingly even though i told them
with if it was recorded i could edit it
i could subtitle it all and all that i
could cut it
uh there would not be no technical
issues i told them that but still
overwhelmingly everyone wanted it to be
live and i see
i see the charm of that definitely
um life is just you know it gives you
the feeling it's life and that's more
exciting that's more interesting
and it still gives you also the
possibility to
do some spontaneous stuff if something
would come up in the chat for example
you know if for example if if some
someone shows up
like some senpai shows up in the chat
and we can react to it or whatever
oh yeah yeah like i've been asking for
boy's love
yeah this is stuff that only happens
live and i think like you just notice it
like
it's also a different feeling from
uploading a video
and then livestream and live streaming
in there it's just different
so i do get that but personally for
myself i wouldn't have mined it either
way
um because at least i could have avoided
technical issues if it was
not live but yeah
i don't know people wanted it to be live
so i'm doing it live
i also don't think if it would have been
um
just a video premiere i don't think that
it would have
gotten so much attention for some reason
i don't know why i think that way that's
just my theory
but there were like so many viewers in
almost 60k
holy i i for some reason don't
think that a
live premiere of a video would have
gotten that much attention
even though there's a lot of people who
don't even
notice the difference between
a live premiere of a video and a live
stream because we we had that last time
with my
storytelling video and some people were
like
it's just a live stream
well this was a livestream huh when did
that happen
and now it's not a live stream it's a
live premiere it's a video
you can even see it because it's cut and
it has subtitles in the video
it's it is not a live stream
open your eyes
it is so funny
but yeah uh i think we'll just keep on
rolling with the live streams
i think it's a it's just it's just
funnier
to have it live and i guess
oh like okay besides the technical
issues but generally if there's like any
like
[Music]
how would you say any mess-ups that are
like like aren't there mess-ups that are
funny
right you know not technical issues but
just general
like oopsies that i think would be funny
and those only happen when it's a live
stream and when it's a video i would you
know edit that out
yeah bloopers yeah yeah stuff like that
[Music]
yeah livestream makes it back up better
yeah anyway anyway let's get back to
the super chat
and where was i where was i
uh owning matt maybe here
i'm excited for all your content in the
coming weeks especially the music single
thank you
thank you for your hard work and
education so far and i hope you continue
to be the great phoenix that you are
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
mark thank you very much
100 expect you to just watch out and do
a recall on your 3dw
i've said this over and over but i
really am so freaking excited for you
you truly are rising and i'm so happy
i'm here to see it happen thank you
thank you thank you
uh mike ray junior thank you for the
talk show the questions are meant to be
more serious but are there
any limitations on what can we discuss
or too personal
or controversial to ask giving
limitations on regular streams
well um to talk about the questions
uh i asked for serious questions
and uh i think i guess
i guess people took me um kind of
wrong uh cause i guess my kind of
serious and your kind of serious is a
bit different
and i still think that the questions i
chose are serious as in comparison to
questions like
what is your favorite food what is your
favorite anime
what do you like to do in your free time
boring questions boring questions i just
wanted deeper questions that are
about like stuff that you would get to
know if you
watch marine senpai for a long time and
just generally her
activities recently or in the past
so that's basically what i was looking
for
but um i guess that there were a lot of
questions
uh submitted that
we we just cannot answer uh it's just
stuff that we can't talk about mostly
you know
i'm okay don't worry anyway cough
asmr
hmm
now cough sounded i cough
one time people are like are you okay
are you okay are you okay
are you okay
don't worry don't worry
so cute you guys are so cute
i do sometimes feel like um straining my
voice
a lot of these streams i wonder if
there's like the cough drops and the
teeth
they only really help for the moment
and one second after it's already bad
again i wonder if there's nothing i can
do about it
i mean at the moment i'm so fine but i'm
scared that i end up
like marin senpai who goes to the doctor
every week
because she has some deep issues
with her throat and voc vocal cords or
something
uh but even for maddie instead but she
goes there so often
but still she can't stop i'm not
but it's for me it's not as bad as that
i would go to the doctor
it's just during the streams and after
the stream i'm totally like
super fine again
i still suggest to just hiding under the
covers you mean while i'm streaming
i wish i could do that but streaming
is not possible in such an environment
as under the covers um
i'm kind of i'm kind of worried about my
senpai to be honest
uh because we moved our collab like uh
weeks ago we had a club planned right
and we moved it because she thought she
she caught some flu or something
because she didn't feel so well but
since then she went to the
doctor so many times and trying to
you know relax her throat and whatever
it just doesn't really seem to do much
but
she i definitely asked her if she's
really fine with doing the show
and she said yeah yeah because she took
the day off before
and uh she's also only doing that stream
with me
and on the the sports festival
and besides that she would also relax
again but
i'm kind of worried about her
i feel like um japanese
people generally are
like there's this um
there's this problem where in
the working society
you're just
[Music]
how to say expected to
never take a day off and
like not even i would say that
that is in the general working society
in japan like in general like office
office jobs or whatever
and that is so normal that that way of
life is just so normal
that working culture that you just feel
like you can never take a day off even
if like legally you have
i'm not sure what exactly the number is
but there's a certain amount of days
that you have
off uh like uh just
vacation days and they don't even take
those vacation days
it's like from where i come from that's
unthinkable our boss
where i worked before it would tell us
at the beginning of the year
to plan out completely every single
vacation day for the whole
year beforehand then
if we wouldn't take all our vacation
days they would force us to take them
so
[Music]
yes
overworking is something i feel very
worried about
in japan and because people
like grow up and sorry this is a really
real talk here
but i feel like in uh
from what i've heard i'm not very much
connected with the
japanese uh side of management
but from what i've heard for example i
talked to some of the
for example money money in the manager
as well and they
like they they're our managers are
really nice and they tell us to
not overwork ourselves they tell us to
take our days off
and i think there's really no reason to
force ourselves to work out every
uh stream every day but
it's just a mental work mentality thing
no matter if your managers tell you
to chill and relax and take a day off
i think it's very hard for them
to actually you know take a break
there's like a lot of
i think many of them feel some pressure
to keep on working and working and
working
and for someone like me it's totally
fine because i woke up
and i woke up i i grew up in a society
where the employers
forced us to take enough days off
they force us to do that
it's very much encouraged and every time
i would work overtime
on the next day i would go home early
the exact same amount of uh hours that i
did over time the day before so
we live in a society
yeah the work culture is just so
different
and i'm just a bit worried about some
people
overworking themselves
but we live in this situation
we live in a society
yeah please don't don't burn yourselves
out i mean
what i'm saying is most likely not gonna
reach the person that i want it to reach
but i'm working on that separately
i'm working on that separately on the
side behind the scenes
to to force those people to take a
goddamn day off
okay take
the day off don't like
even normal people take two days off in
a week
no reason to you know
no reason to work seven days a week
especially as i said before
there's more than just you know those
few hours streaming per day there's more
than that behind the scenes so
um
sorry for doing such a serious talk
ah i just um i just
i just want the best for those people i
don't want them to suffer
like eventually you will burn out if you
keep on living like that
i just don't want them to suffer and i
don't want them to feel bad
for taking a day off it's just such a
natural thing to do
and there's the thing is like there's a
lot of bad companies
out there who make it really hard to
take a day off but i feel like for a
company like
hours they're very encouraging
to let us live our best lives and just
do whatever we want
and they don't they don't force us at
all to like work
work every garden day they even tell us
to take days off
so there's there's no reason
there's no reason to force yourself so
much
tell kelly that i'm in
kelly claims
kelly claims that she's
doing better recently i'll have to check
up on that if that is true
i'll have to check up on that if she's
taking enough time off i
i will have to check that
[Music]
because from what i've seen in her
streams she's been very sleepy
these days very sleepy
i press the x button
to doubt very strongly
yeah okay back to topic
and the talk show hope you are having
fun preparing all this beautiful content
supporting italian
oh yes recording the song was a lot of
fun
and i'm really really glad to make music
for you guys yep
hope you will like the song when you
hear the full version thank you
what the hell emilia's spit
sauce is better than sweet and sour
sauce can you speak german please don't
kidnap my
chickens what the hell emilia's
spits us what
what
[Music]
congratulations on what you are
achieving lately i hear some lads here
and kfb was asking for another chef so i
shall now present kfp chef number five
ah but it says your name says head chef
number one
i shall not present kfb chef number five
where is he i don't see him
are you like presenting uh imaginary
chef
how are you takanasi it's so weird to be
called by my last name
i am fine thank you
maybe i will not read out your question
but maybe
i feel like it's our destiny
here comes the broken eardrums
[Music]
he's dying of laughter he says i'm dying
of laughter here lol
masochists everywhere
james chandan 99.99
[Music]
i saw someone clipping that
i don't understand why it was necessary
to clip it
why next set clipton yeah
why would you i don't i don't understand
i i i
um tolerate many things and i try to
understand you guys because you guys are
you guys have some weird interests
sometimes
and i try to tolerate it i try to
understand it you know
i try to be open-minded but clipping
that seems
very unnecessary and reasonable
but okay i mean you can totally keep it
up i don't care but
i don't i just i just don't understand
my
foreign
had to explain
japanese bros are trying to look the
clip up to find it
and listen to it themselves don't do it
don't
don't do it
i mean if you if you try and if you want
i could try to make it happen now
if you want i can give it a try at least
now i can warn you
and you know i can warn you you can turn
it down and now you know and now you're
like no
okay you can turn it down now at least
if i tell you
you want to you want to see if i can
make it happen
yes please no please
i'm getting mixed opinions
but why though i don't know they're
trying to find the club so i will just
give
give you the opportunity to listen to it
now no
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
i guess i could i could turn down since
it was there i could turn it down here
everyone everyone turn down your volume
[Music]
yeah see that's what i tried last time
in exactly that way i did exactly that
but suddenly it would like completely
i don't know what happened there it
would just the moment i turn on the echo
it would jump in the red area and
kill all of your eardrums
now let me turn that off again
i'm back to normal but um that happened
before when i was off stream as well
generally i just feel like streamlabs
is quite buggy and i should probably
give up on streamlabs and go to obs
yeah yeah
[Music]
um
yeah you can raise the volume again it's
all so good it's all good
it didn't even happen it didn't even
happen
i tried to make it happen but this time
it didn't happen
anyway mario
someone in the chat in japanese told me
that my art is good and the one that i
drew of pekora
was so good but i'm too embarrassed to
upload it on twitter so i haven't
uploaded it
it was so loud we couldn't even hear it
ah makes sense
don't look it up don't look at them
upload it
[Music]
actually
i i will upload it next week
i will upload it on
monday or tuesday
dan kashin it's rash tankishan watson
concoction
thank you lunar hawk thank you
[Music]
um someone in the chat
asked in german to uh have me tell
his little sister uh to probably
properly learn english in the school
like actually practice
because uh yeah he told me to teach her
so i
i told his little sister to properly
learn german in school and practice it
because
for me it was the same thing um
by learning english my world
has like opened up so many doors i was
able to travel to so many places if i
wasn't able to travel to so many
if i wasn't able to speak english i
wouldn't have been able to travel to so
many places and
haven't wouldn't have been able to make
so many friends all over the world and
have so much fun all
over the world so that's what i told her
there's so many possibilities if you
learn english
you can have so many new friends have so
much fun
it's actually true it actually makes
sense it's actually good advice
yep yep i wouldn't have this
amazing job here if i wouldn't have good
english
i would not be in holo live english and
have so much fun with you guys every day
the english language gives you so much
opportunities but for uh
but now you guys in the chat i know most
of you
have english as their first language let
me tell you one thing
you'll think that's enough it probably
is
but still still we we all learn
english to communi to communicate with
you guys okay
and you what's too lazy to learn the
second goddamn language i speak three
languages in europe it's got them
normal to speak free languages so
stand up stop sitting on your ass and
learn whatever language you always
wanted to learn
okay don't always leave it to the rest
of the world for us to learn english for
you
how about you start learning japanese
for real now instead of always saying
oh i want to study japanese and visit
japan that you have been saying for
literally five goddamn years
how about you get started with
it huh
i'm being attacked
i'll start learning to speak
savage
[Laughter]
oh i came here to have a good time and
honestly feeling so attractive
first world problems
[Laughter]
[Music]
the super chat
i think i thought
bullying to study well one thing one
thing to get started with
is watch my lesson on german that was
members only what
watch that oh yeah i was gonna uh public
public science
publicize that video eventually
i forgot about that
attacked by things isn't how i thought
i'd die
well yeah start with german good luck
with that i mean german might not be the
best choice because it's uh difficult
you should uh try to study a language
that you're actually interested in but
yeah i really are honestly i really
recommend learning a language
like you will have so many more
opportunities and it will be
like a huge thing on your uh
how do you call that curriculum
when you apply to a job like from what i
know in english-speaking countries
really a resume yeah really not many
people speak a second language so you're
actually gonna stand out that much
in europe it's it's like standard that
everyone speaks two languages but
i guess in places like america or
wherever
you you would actually really stand out
so
i think it's worth it and getting like a
basic
getting to a level where you can have a
basic conversation is not even that hard
it's really not that hard
how did we get to that topic ah because
of that little girl
well i hope i didn't scare her off with
my preaching
that was towards the english-speaking
audience not not towards that little
small girl
she definitely learned your lesson by
now
watson concoction thank you it's
rashtankashin
oh nice one did you hear that
[Music]
brother not eh it's the other way around
the big brother's little girl sister
the big brother's little sister you got
that wrong
been learning japanese for 15 years for
anime progress
panic oh there are the chefs
where the hell were you
and i asked for you
a blast in today's super chat reading
i'm having an absolute
blast
i am having a blast
i bought my computer broke you should
write a warning in the description
by now it should have been edited out we
added it out like right away but
it usually takes a long time to process
i don't understand
why it takes youtube like 24 hours
to edit out something so small
why what
why and then even if you like
just click one button to undo it
and like put it back to its original
state
that takes another 24 hours
can you believe it why are you gonna
make it so complicated
[Music]
i see the way you're acting like
somebody else making me frustrated
and laughs like this y'all
[Music]
i actually wanted to sing abra lavine in
my
unarchived karaoke stream i wanted to
sing skateboard
he wasn't scared of us she said to you
little boy he wasn't good enough for her
next time next time i'm going to sing
aaron levine and my
in my uh next unarchived karaoke stream
god damn i know every single song
and i also wanted to sing um i was
i was so close to singing a paramore
song but i was like okay that's gonna
probably be really cringy
if i'm gonna go out there singing misery
business
i'm in the business with me serena take
it from the top she's got a body like an
hourglass sticking like
a duck it's a matter of time before they
all ran out
why do i still remember those lyrics
why this or like the one that goes like
crush
crush crush crush nothing compares to
a quiet inning alone just a one two
three that never happened
i guess i'm doing again
i was gonna choose those songs but then
i realized wow
that's gonna prove how cringy i was as a
child
i mean abra lavina is like such a
classic i think people would forgive me
for singing evan lavine
but i don't think people would forgive
me for singing paramore
songs from their first days
do you guys you guys have a like do you
guys like paramore or liked
past tense paramore or is that only
my cringy old self
what's wrong with power i think there's
nothing wrong with paramore but i just
feel like um
it's uh it's kind of i don't know
embarrassing to sing those songs because
i love them so much but yeah
please sing paramore
i mean there's this one thing you know i
don't know if she's rocking her orange
hair right now but she definitely rocked
her orange hair for a while
and look at me
i'm orange-haired as well
very mid-2000s i don't remember
but i guess that makes sense yeah
probably mid-2000 something like that
when i was younger i really looked up to
that singer i forgot her name but
i really wanted to have my hair like
that oh oh my god
i was also a huge fan of christina
aguilera
i was so i was so cringy
and i was like i really now i really uh
i really wanted to get my hair done like
i mean you probably wouldn't know which
one i mean because
there was a time when christina aguilera
had like short
really curly hair and i i told my
uh my mom i guess and my mom's friends i
told them
i want hair like that too i want
like those curly curls and
they were like they told me no kiara you
cannot do that with your hair
it's it's you cannot do that permanently
it will go away it just doesn't last and
i'm like
why why why does that not work i want
those curls in my hair
this life is so unfair i
hate you
[Laughter]
i probably didn't really understand how
curls work
i was like i was like you're so unfair i
want curly hair
i want to look cute i hate my hair
yeah what curls i want curls
no i didn't i don't think i cursed but i
i definitely probably
was like no life is so unfair to me
now i was like um i was pretty unpopular
in school back then uh i think uh small
kiana just wanted to be prettier you
know
and i think that was also during the
time when like emos
were a thing or maybe that was a
different
different time but also when emails were
a thing i wanted to have hair like
emotes
i want to have that fancy hair as well i
wanted to dye my hair in all kinds of
colors and have my
bangs cover my whole face
but i think back then i already realized
that it would i kind of wanted it but i
never really admitted
to me wanting to be like that
evil kyoto and uh
i don't know about you guys in your
country but
in my country emos were
made fun of a lot and i lived in a small
uh city relatively small city
and uh there were like barely any emos
emos uh i guess you could call them like
scene
scene kids and in german we always used
to call them emos
there were there were really not many so
if i would have done it the whole city
would have made fun of me everyone
made fun of them back then
i just thought the hair colors were so
fancy
are you making me remember my own cringe
when
i was a young bird
i mean if you look at my hair now i
could kind of see that
uh hair coloring on an emo
but i'm rocking it i don't look like an
emo scene kid
right now do i but i could see it on one
of those kids
this kind of like radiation
add some of those um what do you call
them the skunk tail
colored
parts add those in there and it's
perfect
oh the little part colored
[Laughter]
stuffed
uh
well i guess it was not a skunk tail
what what
i don't know they had all kinds of weird
stuff in their hair
oh man childhood huh
child burp times
we do live in a society don't we
[Music]
but i love them i still love them okay i
mean i don't listen to them anymore
but there was never anything cringe
about panic at the disco
they are precious okay
oh yes evanescence oh yes
oh yes
oh no tokyo hotel oh no i'm not gonna
say anything about tokyo hotel
oh no
i'm not gonna state an opinion on them
i should probably read super chats right
wake me up inside
wake me up inside call my name
and what save me from
myself
oh you know when you when you were all
teenagers i guess there's some teenagers
uh
in here anyway but when you had like a
dramatic face when you were like
uh the whole world is unfair to me you
would listen to this song and be like
yeah i
second that thank you evan essence for
crying with me
oh god oh god
green day and what what was one of those
famous green day songs
what was one of those um
uh
what oh god this chad is going too fast
i work a lonely road
[Music]
down down
down
oh i wonder if like in 10 or 20 years
we look back on the music that is
believe that that is being released now
and think of it the same way as i think
of that kind of music right now
like will all the current music be
cringed to me
in 20 years or so i wonder
yeah you think so
maybe not all of them because there's
still songs from the two mid 2000s that
i feel like it's just actually good
music
i used to be a big fan of uh the old
black eyed piece
i'm bleeding from all the cuts from the
edges
what
no not the not the recent blackout piece
with all that electrical stuff
but yeah where is the love oh my god
where is
[Music]
that is so beautiful okay i i felt
i felt like i was one of the cool ones
with the better taste because i was
listening to black eyed peas
oh pump it i i used to every time i was
playing pump it
uh i was always so excited when fergie's
part started and i would always like
loudly blast out proudly her part i
would be like
what was it ready
[Music]
yeah i don't really know the lyrics
though because back then i didn't
understand english
so i just sang whatever
uh or the one the one the one where
she's like when fergie is like uh
choosing uh who to date
what was that song what was that song
what was the name of that song
they were like in some kind of show
yeah you gotta do it we gotta do hey
there delilah oh my god
hey daddy what's it like in new york
city
i'm a thousand miles away but a girl
tonight you look so pretty
yes you do
that song
that song i don't know why but
this made me so emotional i wish someone
sang that to me back then
oh yeah don't funk with my heart oh yeah
oh yeah that was a good one that was a
good one
oh my god all these old songs holy
glamorous glamorous oh yes
when fergie started going solo i
laughed at that time i was like oh yeah
hell yeah she's glamorous i love
fergie
oh my god the other day when i went to
the spa with kelly
uh we went for burgers afterwards right
and then that was like some kind of
hawaii themed burger restaurant
and they played all kinds of like old
american songs
and then they were starting to play
fergie's
big girls don't cry and me and callie
started singing it
pretty loud in the in the restaurant
we're like
because big girls don't cry
and i was like i was like okay yeah i
know the lyrics but i was so surprised
to see that kelly knows the lyrics
because i was like
kelly kelly you listened to that kind of
music and she was like
yeah no not really but like you know and
it's just all over the radio when that
got released it was all over the radio
so excuse her for singing big girls
don't cry with me
oh my god i'm so happy right now
[Music]
okay i need to get my together
okay
everyone relax calm down everyone
i will give you an unarchived karaoke
stream
sometime soon where i'll sing all those
cringe 2000 songs
that i liked back then and i will i will
admit to it proudly
that that was my jam back in the days
every time we touched i didn't listen to
that one really but i know i know
[Music]
okay
i also liked uh rihanna rihanna
i still like rihanna um
i want to remember all those all those
artists that i
love so much
and then my umbrella ella ella
e e
[Music]
that was also one of those groups i was
kind of into
oh dear i'm feeling embarrassed
wait which song did i like from fallout
boy which one was one of the popular
ones
i don't remember anything
thanks for the memories of yes
thanks for the memories even though they
weren't so great
[Music]
one night yeah one more time
thanks for the memories even though they
weren't
yep youtube copyright likes me very much
this uh right now but i think
we'll be fine we'll be fine my god i'm
more worried about my neighbors to be
honest
because it's so one hour after midnight
i'm worried about them
bye bye good night to everyone who goes
to sleep
oh wake me up when september is ah
that that was a song that hit me really
hard back then
that was so sad but the thing is
that song i got introduced to
while i was uh in the world of warcraft
scene if i remember correctly
someone made like a world of warcraft
amv
to that song and
to to to child kiara that was the
saddest thing i've ever seen
the most dramatic thing i've ever seen i
cried
so much about that are you literally me
wait i want to see i want to find that
i want to refine that that is like
that's like so old
world of warcraft wake me up i
i guess i won't find that september
oh was it
and why does it tell me wake me up i
don't think i can ever find that again
am i imagining something i think
wake me up inside i don't think it was
dead
i feel like that just doesn't exist
anymore it's so old am i the only one
in does any does anyone know what i'm
talking about i saw the same amv
you saw it i guess it's not an amv
doesn't the a and a
and b stand for anime but yeah you know
what i mean
you you guys did see it okay then i'm
not imagining things
if you find it please send it to me i
want to have like
a nostalgic moment please send it to me
on twitter
type world of record for it but that's
not really what i typed
was it a different song i want to find
if someone finds it send me to me
looking forward to cringe or okay
that's what we're gonna call it okay i'm
sure it existed i was like
i was so into that uh video
i was like i i that was back when
when chiara was very small and did not
understand
how how love works
i did not understand but when i watched
that video i felt like i
i understood completely wow my heart is
broken too
here without you off would the
here without it you think it was a
different song
oh i know that one
oh my god hey wait can i watch it and
i don't have to let me watch that one i
have to watch that
oh my god oh my god that looks so the
thumbnail looks so
familiar to me mommy watch that oh my
god
what's it together with me
i have an ad playing right now shut up
stupid ad
okay there you go oh my god the format
though the format
should i link it in the chat okay let me
link it
2006 5 million views
oh my god okay i'm watching three
two one
i haven't lost
oh my god i don't remember this at all
but it seems so familiar
wait i don't hear anything is there
supposed to be audio was it muted
or does the audio come later
i don't hear anything
do you guys hear something
link oh god i didn't pin it yeah there
you go
it comes later on i was human
on that film's presents
oh there we go uh maybe it was that bad
thing that i was thinking about maybe it
was this video
oh this was like a movie to me
oh so emotional
ah it's so beautiful
oh
he keeps on walking and walking he looks
so depressed
here you go chorus time
move out to baby
when i dream about you all the time
i cried so much as a child i don't know
why but
that was so amazing to me
it was like a drama series
i guess i didn't have access to anything
else oh i know yeah is that like
his true former who is that dude
that human dude what happened i remember
this tavern so much oh my god
oh my god
oh thanks for the kiss
oh that's so nostalgic
oh yeah the dance oh yeah do the
course dance i'm here without you
baby
and i'll dream about you all the time
[Music]
what was the i don't remember what the
storyline of this was though
oh so dramatic wait when was he finding
them again
in the end someone dies right
oh the horsey the undead dude
no no he's dying
[Laughter]
i don't understand i don't understand
what's going on
oh no
he's gonna kill him
[Laughter]
oh he's dead
[Music]
how to favor oh no the memories
the past oh no
dreaming back to all the time
and the walking scenes again
oh what is he doing now
what's happening
i don't really understand what's going
on anymore
oh the final battle is it all about one
woman he's getting revenge
oh
you know in 2006 this was a high
production value you know this was like
really really good
content this was like a movie
this was the most emotional movie that
was out there
baby slowly
holy nights
and i think about you
oh it's so beautiful
i cried so much with that video
only you and me
2006 was 14 years ago oh my
god that makes it uh much worse
damn
damn oh that was that might not even
have been
the year when it was actually created
because that is just a re-upload
apparently
[Music]
oh my god maybe that was the video that
i was talking about maybe it was not
wake me up when september ends but i
feel like
oh i'm confused but that this video was
definitely something
that made me cry a lot
i mean back then you had no netflix so
yeah there was just not much else
windows movie maker hell yeah
oh my god okay watch along is over
uh yeah we totally are staying on topic
we're totally on topic uh we never went
on a tangent
ever in the stream let me continue read
superchats
we have a topic
there is no tangents at all we we were
reading super chats for two hours
with no break by now
[Laughter]
no but that was worth it oh my god i
love i love
being nostalgic and looking at my past i
like that
kind of stuff but i never went back
that far procrastinator mode
it's on to take a while this stream is
going to take a while
okay
so
i felt like we might have scared the
japanese bros
[Laughter]
he wanted the link one more time
i love the talk show yeah i can't wait
for more thank you
i'm a bit sorry for that i don't think
you need to be sorry for them
they are they're trying to understand i
think it's fun for them to learn new
things like that
super jack reading can you eat that what
is it what is that
i don't know
oh okay but there really were not many
japanese bros there
i think i really scared them away
limewire yeah
limewire wasn't that that software where
you could download all kinds of songs
but eventually
they were claiming they were illegal but
eventually they
i don't know got deleted from they got
uh deleted into oblivion from the
internet
blind bar with free viruses hell yeah
that was the only way for me to get
music
nail pets i did not play nail pets but i
played a similar one
uh what was it called
a very similar one ah
what was the the other one
maybe someone knows now it was also with
that kind of pets
i think
no no not club penguin i didn't play
that one
how about oh my god
you're taking it back too far oh my god
hubba hotel i never really was able to
like get into that i tried but they were
it was so confusing there were like
millions of people
in that hotel and i had no idea what was
going on no not pet society
or maybe it was not really popular over
there
i don't see anyone with the right name
um
that's interesting you guys are not
coming up with the name that i'm
thinking of
huh
ah
nope can't think of it doesn't matter
we have to stop going on a tangent
we have to stop let's go back to super
chats
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
i don't even know that pet society thing
i don't think it was a thing in europe
maybe in your guys's country but i never
heard of that one before
even existed in japan apparently what
the hell
oh happy hatching day congratulations
[Music]
i love that one
back to 2020 yep let's let's go let's go
um where one time
and we reached finally the holo talk
super chat
well that i mean i would say we did well
on time two hours for
foreign
i'm gonna try to read more messages for
the holo talk one generally
by the way for the people who were
wondering uh which kind of messages i
pick up i generally try to pick up the
red ones
always the the messages i i read all the
names but for the messages
uh the ones that are red by the way i
can't see the color so sorry if i
sometimes miss
uh your red super chat and don't
acknowledge it as a red one
it's because in the window where you
read the super chats
it doesn't show the color and it just
shows
all kinds of currencies so
i only recognize them in certain
currencies like us dollar
japanese yen austrian dollars uh heroes
and that's the that's the one that i
recognize and then there's many that i
don't really recognize
so it's hard for me to figure out if
there are red
super chats or not for certain
currencies
but yeah check your twitter
okay have you sent me a world of
warcraft video
let's see
stupid twitter update come on
oh
it has been found oh
that was another oh my no this is too
sad i cried so much
do we want to watch that do we want to
watch another one of those videos
it's supposedly the right one
wait did i say australian dollars was
that wrong
oh god this one is i think this one is
really sad though it's it's an
it has a sepia color filter on it
was that really the one it barely has
any views though
i guess the other one oh the other ones
all got heated
okay
okay one more okay i'll pin this one
okay people who come in now and check
the pinned message will be very confused
as to what we're doing
okay we're playing it in five seconds
let's see if this was the one that i i
was talking about
three uh five four
three two
one
game cam
[Laughter]
now someone is dying
me up when september
and all the memories someone died
kiana which one of these videos did you
upload yourself
when september i'm a nerd excuse me did
you just call me a nerd
why
oh i wonder if that was that video i
can't really remember that one that well
[Music]
is this the one
did he just jump off the roof is that
like a
no he's still alive okay
are you fighting no no he's laughing
okay they're still happy
oh yeah the adventures
can i question why the pinned link did
you just come in
you're late when so
damn bad ends
okay this was uh is this really that
video
it's not even that good
not even that good the other one was
much better
i think what i thought probably i was
introduced to the song by this video
and then watched the actual music video
and was like wow that is actually sad
because the actual video is so goddamn
sad
but i think back then people really
liked these kind of uh
world of warcraft videos trying to make
it into some movie
and you laughed at nina for watching i
couldn't
shut up you know nothing you don't you
don't
you don't understand world of warcraft
was the coolest thing ever
okay it maybe it still is i don't know i
don't want to diss people who still play
what about
oh yes the ending scene oh yes the
credits oh yes
doom on toast productions
let me unpin that
okay yeah i think the the thing that i
remembered was the actual music video
but probably that world of warcraft
video
introduced me to it something like that
[Music]
could
oh my god okay
okay we really this was the last one
we really gotta go back to business
[Music]
is
talk super chats
hi kara maybe my last super chat it's my
birthday can i get a sweet great from
you you've been following you since your
debut
i hope you keep being so funny and and
endearing as ever i feel like i already
congratulated you in the in the pre-chat
but again
happy birthday probably already over by
now but happy birthday
slayer hydration tech
[Music]
for your first talk show with marine
here's my ticket for the vip front row
so you
really can't wait to hear what you both
are going to discuss
[Music]
i'm very much looking forward to the
streaming of the essential and kiara i
wish you success in the hollow talk
thank you thank you i hope you enjoyed
it
[Music]
it has taken control over my mental
faculties
and i will now function solely on
excitement for the rest of the remaining
12 hours
i'm glad everyone was excited as i was i
couldn't even sleep well i really slept
bad that's why i took a nap after the
stream
and i wasn't gonna stream as you saw on
twitter i said
i announced that i'm taking the rest of
the day off but here i am reading super
chat
so much for that
this is my third unscheduled stream this
week
right my third one i'm doing a lot of
unscheduled uh streams
today
which i am fine with but
see my this week
ended up being uh not as unfriendly
to gmt time zone bros as they fought
before
the europe europe bros because all the
scheduled ones
were good for our est time zone but the
unscheduled ones are pretty good for
europe bros i think
i would say so
leave my tankins
stop it no more world of warcraft talk
now no more
no people nowadays don't even
don't even understand that they don't
even understand
don't make me react to that because they
will understand
that i am eternal and has been alive for
too long
they will find out you're a frosh thank
you kiara thank you too for coming
i hope you have a most memorable stream
to remember rumble stream tomorrow the
start of
kia late night talk so it's amazing
achievement thank you the funny thing is
though
for the japan side it's a morning
a morning talk show
i don't really remember how it was said
originally but it was um
okay my neighbors hate me can we not do
that now
[Laughter]
jen i'll i'll continue next time
when i can give you everything i got
jacqueline duncan jacqueline duncan
patrick chen thank you
monkey thank you for the red super chat
roll out the carpet for the first guest
of a very special new series
in all seriousness i'm sure you'll look
right kiana you have a way of making
every interaction fun and natural and i
always enjoy your chats with whoever you
collab with looking forward to it
thank you
thank you thank you
i really wanted it to be special and
yeah i think it turned out to be very
special with all the
the all the things that i commissioned
were worth it
the logo the background the background
is not just some random background i got
off the internet no
it's a commissioned background with 3d
objects the back
two background uh soundtracks
and uh the the intro video which
made for me so a lot of things went into
the preparation
the logo was so hard to choose though i
got a bunch of very different ideas
it was really hard to choose
i wish i could have had like two logos
and actually i wish i could have
uh had your guys's opinion i wish i
could have just
posted them on the community board board
and let you vote but then again it was
like
oh i kind of want to surprise you all
once everything is finished so i i held
myself back
and did not know i did not let you know
what options i have
the intro from amma yes is so funny
if i understand correctly i did not ask
her what's happening in the video but i
guess
i'm driving the subway in the wrong
direction
done realize it then i realized i i'm
gonna be late for my talk show
so i transform into the phoenix form
even though my papa does not allow it
because my belt
is covered by a tape
but in a transformative phoenix form fly
over
to the studio in lightning speed
then i explode and land on my chair as
kiana
makes sense
i suppose i was late yeah
but i have to say i'm usually never late
never no no me being late is not really
a thing
zoom the intro is really fun yeah
i'mma set she's gonna change it every
time and
input the guest the new guest every time
you know that there was a small moment
where marine was in the intro
so it's gonna be changed every time
[Music]
i actually now i feel like i kind of
want an outro
but i'd have to commission another song
and another ending video and don't annoy
amelia with
another video request but if someone
wants to make an outro for the talk show
you're welcome to make one
maybe find uh uh one of those uh
songs on those free uh not no copyright
pages where you can get like music you
know if someone wants to make an outro
yeah i'm just i'm just done it's like i
i've prepared so much stuff for this
talk show i'm like uh
i don't i don't wanna it's like so much
so it takes so much brain to organize
all these things and
uh get them all like
you know done i don't wanna organize a
contest
and look for everything no i'm just i'm
just carefully
putting it out there in this room right
now to all the people
watching if you want to make a video an
outro please do
i'm and for now i can't handle any more
organizing of anything
at all for a while i want to stop
organizing things
got your back tension really
watch only me i love that one but that
doesn't suit stuff
the uh the
whole holotac theme
yeah make one out of world of warcraft
no
don't do that i can't use that
it's not red but hopefully the father of
it works out of course
it doesn't have to be any color doesn't
have to be a super jet
kiana's such a sweet person and santo is
my favorite japan whole life member so i
had to do this kyra you'll do great i
know you will
oh i'm glad i chose someone that you
really like a lot thank you
i hope you i hope you enjoyed it because
this was obviously before
the stream so i wonder what your
uh opinion of that was
hope you enjoyed it
thank you
thank you for the red super chat it will
go great kiara
your skill set is made for this your
ability to hold entertaining
conversations with your senpai has been
proven many times
we can tell plenty of hard work and
effort has gone into this have
confidence in yourself
you've got this good luck
so sweet so sweet literally so sweet
thank you
[Music]
yeah i i i feel quite happy about how
things went
so thank you so much i'm quite confident
in holo talk now i've been reading
feedback
for hours after the stream so
so many positive vibes i think really
the only thing
that can be improved is the the
questions uh
to be formatted before the stream
and uh i mean the the disappearing thing
i can't really
i can't really do anything about it to
be honest
uh it's just my goddamn internet just i
guess
i suppose i mean i have good internet to
be honest my upload is insane
sometimes the download is much lower
than the upload
because during premiere uh premiere
during uh prime time in japan
my upload is like insanely good like 400
mm mbps but the download
is like one
it's like what the hell what is this
what is this gap one versus 400.
yeah the upload is like
more than i could ever ask for
and yeah upload is good for streaming
but in order to
you know have my collaboration partner
not disappear i would need some download
speed please
but besides prime time in japan the
download speed is also
fine generally
that one is bad because so much people
on bad it infrastructure really
are you sure the girls didn't chew on
some wires i don't know man
everyone remember to like the super dry
reading oh yeah everyone give the stream
a like
are you in sweden or something the
internet is too goddamn fast
but it's only the upload that is so fast
do your parents know that you're a
veteran my mom definitely knows
with uh the other side i mean i guess
spooky papa is my papa
some papa knows
yeah my mom wrote me a message after the
talk show
she went to she writes she read she
wrote um
my mom is like so excited about
everything i do recently
she wrote congratulations to your first
uh premiere successful premiere of your
talk show
it was really really good uh hard eye
emoji
she's so excited about her she literally
watches everything
everything hello mom i know you're
watching
mom i have to say
watching these super chat readings might
be a little bit of a waste of time i
guess
today with all the world of warcraft
talk because me and my mom played world
of warcraft together back then
she probably also saw those videos those
cringy videos
she probably also saw those
so maybe actually this super chat could
be interesting for her this this
particular super chat reading but all
the others
mama please don't waste your time to
always watch my super chat readings
uh my mom was um
i think back then
she was also alliance but
i think she also played the horde at
some point
but back then she was just human
because our whole family was playing
together so we all had to be
alliance
mama phoenix played world of warcraft i
love how you guys are so
like shook about that fact
i love it so funny
gamer mom
what what what
i love it
are you buying christmas for family what
do you mean
oh my mom loved diablo
he said how do you pronounce it in
english as well my mom really loved the
diablo and i i
tried to play it but i could never
get past the first the first boss
i was still too bad and too scared when
it came to
these kind of games yeah i i
it was diablo always scared me when i
was younger
too scary could never get past the first
boss
i think diablo 2 is what i'm talking
about i think
but mama definitely played it oh i
remember i remember her playing it a lot
a woman of course mama do you hear that
they call you a woman of culture
did she find the cows oh i remember
there was something like that
i don't quite get the joke but i
remember there was something with cows
m
anyway we gotta eat those super jets oh
my god
thank you so much jacqueline
people who like watch the archive to
find where their name was mentioned
they're going to have such a hard time
because they keep on going on tangents
how do people even find
do they watch the whole archive or how
do they do that
channel because
[Music]
induction
i have to watch it all damn i was
thinking um
i could at least when i'm doing like
several streams
and super chats i could put like a
thumbnail off the stream
on my screen being like i'm reading uh
the super chat from this stream right
now
so people would at least know
very roughly at which stream i am right
now
yeah so like if you skip for the video
you at least see
ah okay she's at the whole talk super
chat now here i gotta listen
would that help you guys okay
in that case uh i can actually do that
right now
okay but not like that maybe um
maybe since it says super chat reading
right now so i'm going to put
this here or
i don't know does it fit there now it
covers up my
tag
[Music]
now where should i put it
here it covers up a lot of me as well
though
maybe here is that confusing though
i feel like it should be close to that
text
bottom left it covers up something
definitely
i'm just going to put it
[Music]
here
what a good solution big bird brain
big brain bird big big brain
move on the hat
my hat no
no it covers up me i'll put it there
awesome okay yeah you don't think i need
the super chat reading uh
okay i guess suppose not in the i
suppose not in this stream
because the title says so but generally
for if i read it after the game part
well you know what i can i can make it
smaller and i could do this
ah
[Music]
okay okay
okay that works fine
everyone is uh sending in the takasho
super chats at that moment
but i did not like the sound of that so
i had to change it
raven thank you thank you
while next is thank you and there we go
this is where marinada started
jacqueline
a pudding sauce why did i just say
pudding sauce because it says sauce and
some of the text
pudding jacqueline duncan slayer dead
pancake
every day you say you're looking for the
top but like has anyone ever
offered to help find it i really hope
you can finally find the top someday
yup i love you guys you guys are too
adorable
i will i will find it someday
um to be specific i'm looking for
the top right though i know i always say
i'm looking for the top but i have to be
specific i'm looking for the top right
should change his name to looking for
the top right
but that's too long to read
you guys ready for speech can i turn on
my echo with the with
i'll turn down my mic for a second
it works it works
okay there you go today
we witness history today we take part of
a revolution
we celebrate the first ever hold a talk
with
martin and with kiara remember this
agent
for this is a day of infamy to the
future we go
with this first step for
[Music]
for the glory of her life let's go
worth it
perhaps i have safely safely turned the
echo off again
thank you thank you channel
tickets
[Music]
we should we should give the mouse a
name
it's running around right now do we do
we want to give the mouse a name
if it's gonna survive it deserves a name
that makes it too obvious
it should be a more original name
i want to say something okay go ahead
casper oh that's cute
because it's that i always say it's a
ghost
okay let's call him casper
i like that stop moving casper
you're freaking me out
ten
[Music]
the ghost isn't there a famous ghost
called casper
finally now it feels even more as if it
was my pet
devon thank you for the red super chat
thank you thank you thank you another
recipe
this gaming thank you jonathan let me
read your super chat
thank you for everything you do the
global pandemic has made my job
extremely stressful and nearly
impossible to see my beloved family and
friends
same but i can look forward to videos to
brighten my day we all appreciate you
and your
your dedication thank you that's so
sweet
thank you i guess we came
at the right time although it's been
going on for the whole year we could
have
already come earlier but i feel like it
was a good timing
because uh if we started earlier like
maybe around
around spring i feel like we wouldn't we
still wouldn't have gotten that much
attention what do you guys think
i think the timing was really good
i think spring would have still be too
early because not so many
english peop english speaking people
were into
a whole life just yet yeah
it was a good timing
[Music]
good timing and good scouting well thank
you
ah damn it's it's been
[Music]
wait has it been almost three months now
didn't i debut on the 21st of september
wait no wait was it august or september
all right then it's a 12th the 12th oh
the 12th not the 21st ah
you guys remember so well
why don't you all remember my debut day
and i don't
okay because you're out oshie
[Music]
i love you all so much you guys are so
adorable i love you all so much
i literally went to have babies with you
but i can't too bad because i'm a
phoenix and i can only
make babies with other phoenixes
so too bad not gonna happen not gonna
happen
but anyway back to topic
jonathan thank you thank you so much for
the sweet words i'm glad we can help
[Music]
please continue watching us until the
end
and there will never be an end so that's
forever
not going to tell the japanese people
that yeah i just said
[Music]
this
i told them i told them but there's
barely any
here right now
i think the few ones that are actually
here right now are
uh do understand basic english so you
probably got the idea
already
see i don't i only saw like two japanese
comments i think they went to bed
and
my first donation ever i thought i would
give to my favorite halloween girls i'm
the one who thought you thought hit you
with a red shell then fell off ah
you're saying that i thought so but it
wasn't you or
what my chat just broke
stopped moving hello
on this side it's moving but on my
actual window it's not moving
oh no i was sleeping during the sports
event
i i stayed up for the cali live show but
then i
i was so tired i think it also had
something to do with me being so nervous
so i couldn't sleep
much oh yeah the page is not reacting
well thank you for nothing
oh there you go it's loading again
i was so nervous i couldn't really sleep
but then
after the stream i felt so relieved but
also
so tired so i had to take a nap and i
couldn't watch the
sports festival did you guys watch it
was it good
i might have to watch watch the archive
but i don't know which perspective i
should watch
did you guys understand what was going
on maybe oh my god you guys would
know what would have been a good idea
they should have
hired me as an english-speaking
commentator
a nice narrator and i should have
streamed my perspective
on my channel commentating everything in
english
and why don't they think of that just
invite me for everything
i want to be part of it too god damn it
god damn it i actually expected that you
did
well it did not happen and if you
expected it why didn't you tell someone
to do it
just part of that now next year is it
gonna be
one do i have to wait one whole year to
do that
invite yourself uh i was more i was so
focused on my
talk show and my song and everything i
didn't really think of that idea until
now
but maybe if there's another similar
event for holofest
uh i was thinking of that but i'm not
sure
if i can do it i'll i'll i'll i'll ask
them if that's the thing that i could do
uh i'll ask i will ask the staff
but i'm not sure if that's a if that's
possible
but anyway there's probably gonna be
lots of the
other big event actually no with so many
members
that is a really rare occasion to have
like almost all of japan members in one
event
that is a pretty rare trend rare
occasion oh i don't think i would be
translating all
of them i think i would just be
commentating what's happening
in english
continuing i'm so far away from the top
of my super chat list i'm so
far away again i'm i'm once again
looking for the top
sapphire kitten
[Music]
thank you
and planning out a new regular show yay
looking forward to the stream today i'm
sure your hard work will pay off thank
you
i'm glad i can have my regular thing now
although
it does come with a lot of pressure to
like continue doing it
so i hope i can help it's uh not gonna
get too much for me
if it gets too much i'll just i'll not
force myself i might take a week extra
for preparation every once in a while
but i guess uh every two three months at
two three weeks almost equals uh once
per
month or two times per month it's good
enough
should be it should be all right
can you raise your mic volume okey-dokey
there we go i love refrigerators
mkk2005 thank you for the red super chat
thank you
congratulations on the debut of your
talk show i wish you all the best and
many more
to come thank you
[Music]
thank you for your support it is very
very appreciated
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
let's have a great show tonight i'm
still hyped for this you and marin are
my two favorites oh
another one who has me and marine
as his favorites so this is super
special to me keep achieving your dreams
while bringing everyone together and
having fun
hold on talk hashtag money not a hype
thank you
i want to do so much more with maddie
and i want to hang out more with her
i love her she's so sweet she's so cute
she's so so much fun
she's so open
[Music]
definitely gonna hang out more often
with her just even privately without
streaming so
i'm so glad she was my first guest
[Music]
oh yeah there was one thing though i'm
really sorry about
um
and i did not notice mine also didn't
notice and i did not notice until
hours later when i was going for twitter
one
single person on twitter noticed it
i i don't know why no one noticed it not
even modern senpai
that she was yeah that and she was
horizontally flipped
and i have an explanation for that but
um
i'm really sorry
i am so sorry i
i'm so sorry the thing is like probably
with my own
with myself i would have noticed because
i'm just so used to seeing
myself um but with madden especially
with her new outfit i didn't notice
i'm so sorry uh she also didn't notice
the reason why is when i was like
setting up my layout
uh i was testing out the couch thing
and i used i just copied myself
and put myself on the couch so that
there were two kiaras
and just for like i don't know testing
reasons
i flipped myself horizontally
you know i don't know what exactly the
reasoning behind that was but
so just that it would look like it's
someone else
and yeah then it kept that setting
when i put marine in there and uh yeah
no one noticed really at least no one
made a big deal out of it
but it really bothers me
it really it really bothered me after i
noticed
i missed it i messaged malin i was like
money senpai
i'm so sorry i just noticed now and i
don't know if you noticed but
you were flipped the whole time i'm so
sorry about that
i took
[Music]
i guess many people know this but not
many people pointed it out
actually before we started streaming i
showed marin how it looks like
and she didn't say anything
so she didn't notice
i don't know i think she would have
definitely told me if she would have
noticed because
yeah hong ninga kizu denied it
i'm just so so sorry because um
you know it's it's it's uh it was a it
was watched by so many people
i don't want people to think that she
has an eye patch on the wrong eye
tonight
if i would see myself flipped i would
notice right away because if my hats
were the other way around
that would look so weird to me that
would look so odd
well i will not mess it up next time
i can't change it anymore but i felt
so stupid after i noticed that i was
like oh my god i'm so stupid
um issues in the first episode right
wait what did pudding do
what did pudding do
on the flip side everyone still had fun
anyway hahaha
not even gonna laugh at that it's not
funny
now i feel sorry for you because your
joke wasn't funny
did we got a mirror universe morning
when she was still horny i was i was
thinking of
making up an excuse like that yeah
but uh it's too late i already told you
the truth i was just being stupid
thank you welcome to the membership
shimla
i was thinking i actually prepared an
applause sound
but then i thought it might be a bit
better
some if i would play those sounds
actually
during the stream i'm not sure um if
that's gonna
harmonize well but i don't want to try
it at some point but i didn't really get
it good
it was kind of last minute so i didn't
really get a good
quality applause data
maybe at some point i'll get it
no i didn't record myself i just looked
it up on the internet
why is part of your hair blue that's not
even blue
it's um turquoise
and why why do you question these things
accept it
my hatching day happens to fall exactly
on the same day as the w of the talk
show this must be a sign of good luck
thank you for all your heartbreak and
wish you the best thank you
thank you soon
thank you captain
it's because i'm a phoenix
this is how phoenix's look like when
they're in the human form
stop questioning it luca umbrella thank
you so much thank you
looking for the top thank you star
creator thank you
thank you deaf raven thank you tsg
frank thank you scarlet devil journal
thank you
oh you changed your name weren't you so
you weren't you uh the kfp signboard
before
see kfb signboards what happened did you
quit your job or something i did not
allow you to quit your job oops
what does ssrv even stand for explain
yourself
i do remember your names and your
avatars so
sorry sorry that's all you're gonna
think
that's all
you think you can just get away with
that
explain yourself
defected to bhutan really
why do you know that ssrb is that
something that uh
has something to do with put on senpai
oh ssib i guess yeah makes sense oh
i see what is it but your avatar is
still my face
it's okay you can love both of us
ah your clan tag i see which you were
trying to impress
botany
[Music]
first we see chickens take over the talk
show circuit next we take over the world
thank you thank you
yes hololive english is indeed taking
over the whole world
i'm gonna do my best
one day we have we will have kfp
restaurants
all over the world and you will all
eat the phoenix burgers and the jaguar
burgers
[Music]
you need to watch an amv called watch
only me
no no no no it's okay you can watch more
than me
of course you can
there's nothing wrong about that that's
that that song was taken out of context
anyway i don't think i ever told you
guys to watch only me
i mean it makes me happy if you say
you're watching only me that makes me
happy but i'm not telling you to only
watch me
you can watch more than me yes you said
that no i did that
i think that was no no no no that was
out of context i
remember because i was basically role
playing as your girlfriends
who are angry at you for watching b
troopers and that girlfriend would say
what the hell stop watching youtubers
watch only me
watch once only no that was exactly how
it went
you know you cannot convince me
otherwise this is exactly how it went
but down if you want to take it like
that you can take it like that if you
only want to watch me that's totally
fine i mean i don't blame you
okay i'll give you i'll give you one
more
one more cute girl
one more cute gala you can watch oh what
the hell was that
where did that go
i saw something where is she what
and now
there we go
have fun with her
[Laughter]
welcome to kfp
hi kiara hi here
[Music]
oh
when did that happen
i didn't even oh my god they're
multiplying without me even like
doing it myself i cannot control it
anymore
[Music]
which one is the real one which one do
you think is the real one
[Laughter]
oh my god i didn't realize i had like
three of myself here
orange one it says i'm the real one
no i'm the real one no i'm the real one
believe me trust me ask me something
that only i could answer correctly
i don't see any questions
[Music]
because she's my wife and piccola i also
love very much but not
not with those romantic feelings you
know
how do we reach these dunks
identical yep it seems so
what does skiana wash her hair with
gravy
[Music]
wait why are they free why are you
confused always has been free
i've always been triplets
i always have been a triplet v tuber
welcome hundred percent
synced triplet
[Music]
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
was exercised
ah
[Laughter]
ah okay relax kiada
oh my god
i'm crazy
hahaha
[Laughter]
ah
you have to read the super chats
go back to normal what will people think
if they
join the stream in the middle
i don't understand what the hell is
going on
you're scaring off your new viewers
oh my god i'm sorry everyone
i shall now proceed with the super chat
rating
[Music]
bronx thank you for the red super chat
ahoy
[Music]
thank you thank you so much for your
support i hope you enjoyed
the interview
she's gone crazy no
[Music]
a little japanese
mikan just like in an anime
hey this mika looks like me mandarin
this mandarin looks like me i'm excited
to get hungry though
no a linking park i did not listen to
ever sorry to disappoint you
sorry meekan minamo
[Music]
mumikani
you're gonna eat yourself no it looks
like me but it is not me
[Music]
even an anime
en have you ever why is there a
translator
why why why are you translating me
i feel insulted just kidding
what is the difference between mikka and
normal oranges oh dear lord
do i have to educate you there is a huge
difference
oh my god okay well i guess we're doing
this
i guess we're doing this
[Music]
um
does this work
huh no
i have to save that goddamn picture
ah
this is a mekan aka mandarin
aka satsuma aka clementine
whatever you want to call it we don't
have to be so
uh strict
in that area but
there's it's so so obviously something
else
then an orange because
this is an orange now if you look
closely
the the mandarin
has like small little pieces in there
that you can just
you can open it up and you can take them
out and then you eat them one by one but
for oranges it's you can like it it
doesn't work that way
it doesn't work that way
it's so different i don't see why you
don't see any difference
looks like
[Music]
they're both orange so what so you say
a carrot is also an orange
because it's orange so it's also an
orange what the hell
what is that logic
it's tomato a fruit or vegetable i would
say it's a vegetable
uh-huh you guys are acting stupid right
now
you all know that there is a huge
difference the difference between these
two fruits even
even uh i mean the taste is similar but
like
for example i can't eat oranges like a
snack and that's why i don't really eat
oranges much i i love orange juice but
uh i don't really eat it i don't snack
on it as i do with uh
mandarin because mandarins you can just
eat with your bare hands
and this i will do now
juicy so juicy
[Music]
is an orange no i'm a phoenix
i'm not an orange what the hell
you guys are trying to make make me go
on a tangent now
haven't we been on enough tangents by
now
no people do not really drink mikkan
juice no no
that is not a thing oh damn
i want to make a smoothie with
them i don't think there's any i mean
you can you can totally
make a make a juice out of it
it's not really why am i telling you
this what
why am i telling you about life
why are we talking about this
wait this isn't the tangent stream well
i guess it is
i mean we've literally been watching
world of warcraft videos from 2006
together in this stream
if this isn't a tangent stream then i
don't know what it is
in my life
[Music]
in my life but i have been watching her
life for a year already and it is about
time to give my first something to my
favorite
feature i wish you the best of luck and
hope you can accomplish as much as you
can thank you that's so sweet
again thank you for another red super
chat thank you guys
thank you thank you what's happening
what's happening
thank you so uh looking for the top
thank you sharon
steph thank you that's thank you i have
the worst working times ever but i snuck
off to send this
and i'm so that i can't watch this live
i watch the video detail
and 100 catch the next one live you're
the best kiara
thank you oh so sad you missed it
maybe next time yeah
[Music]
i'm so glad everyone enjoyed it i'm so
glad it really
seems like it was worth it thank you
thank you so much for your support
canvas night also with a red super chat
thank you so much
[Music]
i want to thank you sincerely for all
the effort you've put into bringing us
this wonderful talk show
this is a great way to help bridge the
language barrier now this is cultural
cross-pollination thank you thank you
it is indeed cultural cross-pollination
isn't it
thank you thank you so much for the
support
you know one thing i'm really happy
about after literally
going through so many comments
everywhere
so much feedback
i did not see a single person
saying anything about the translation
bringing the flow
not a single person so i suppose it was
well structured and
did go quite well i'm really glad i'm
really really happy
never has been that's right my friend
that's right
it never it never has ruined the flow
i agree
oh nice neck crack
when i say that it sounds like nice neck
rack
as if i have boobs on my neck okay don't
even imagine that
oh wait is rack something in english you
use to
talk about boobs or butts
wait is a rack is rack do you say that
for
the butt i'll have thoughts on that
what the boobs okay new fan art idea oh
no no
no no no no no no no
anyway thank you so much canvas knight
for your support thank you thank you
thank you thank you for being there with
me
mwah and b thank you i love marrying
congrats on your show
yeah good job thank you so glad
[Music]
before that you think you have no talent
but this talk show clearly taps into the
talents you actually have it also fills
a niche within
whole life that only you can do ganbatte
thank you actually it's kind of
surprising that there was no
talk show like this up until now
in whole life
i mean there's like similar stuff like
the interview
thing that yuzuki senpai does
but i mean like something more like talk
show is you know
actually interesting that ah ah i guess
he does
something different i haven't i have to
admit i haven't really seen it
i'm talking about whole life so tamaki
doesn't really count
[Music]
i'm the one to do it i'm glad i got my
niece
yeah one day we'll have a collab maybe
with nobody
senpai talk show owner
host versus talk show host
tell you one day one
day i first have to go through my goals
because i just love my girls way too
much
sorry
jacqueline danke and shiki thank
but honestly i think it's also good that
i go for the girls first because whole
talk would get will get more
popular and popular and then eventually
uh
when i bring on the the whole stars boys
they will also have a big audience
hopefully
and then she'll get more support at that
they will get more support
hopefully
not sure what your message is trying to
say
m
and again i'm not going to invite people
outside
outside of holo life i don't even think
i'm gonna
be lacking guests ever
eventually i do also want to invite
indonesia girls and there was a smart
idea that someone had
uh if i run out of the japanese talent
and the indonesia indonesian talents
which i don't think will happen but if i
ever run out of all that
i could do it's the other way around
interview the whole live english girls
translate what they say to japanese food
japan bros
yeah eventually
i think they would like that because all
the japanese bros
are really excited about hello live
english but many of them are like
ah i don't understand what they're
saying
yeah oh how they turn tables
[Music]
there hold on
oh spanish translator in the chat hello
thank you
[Music]
i just remembered that neither japanese
or english is kiara's first language and
yet we somehow still took it and
get to enjoy this amazing high quality
bilingual talk show kiara's incredible
thank you for pointing that out it is
indeed
uh none of them are indeed my first
language
you thank you so much
[Music]
you got a kiss even though there was no
red super chat
thanks for the membership thank you
chris
c thank you thank you space thank you
thank you thank you
thank uh you
crider man danger super max 97
chris c thank you thank you
super max sunglasses again
love hina sim date was also the first
dating scene as well for you or you mean
ever to exist ever
that would be surprising to me but i
remembered by the way i only i guess i
only played like a demo version that was
online
because i think i remember always
getting stuck
around the same point and it always
always felt so frustrating to me that i
couldn't go
further in the story with the girls
it always felt very very frustrating to
me
but i was uh too young
and had no option to buy the full game
how a wonderful stream i'm not good at
listening to english but which kiara
speaks is
gentle for me i'm looking forward
to the next talk especially
[Music]
today
birth translation
i tried vegan anime thank you
this is amazing and thank you kiara
getting to know more about the japan
members we love is amazing
it connects us more and it's something
only you could do you really are the
bridge and i'm so proud keep playing
high attention
thank you shane thank you so much wild
nixon thank you
um really my only goal is to
get the overseas viewers to know more
about the guests that i'm
calling over because there's
there's so many amazing things about the
girls that
you guys don't know i suppose and even
even with my interview
it's still far far far from
um doing them justice i would say
but i'm trying i'm trying
so maybe maybe you'll find your new
favorite girl for my talk show
eventually but that's okay i accept it
sacrifices have to be made
they are all very charming after a while
only you
that's gonna happen oh are you saying
you're never going to give me up
you're never going to let me down you're
never going to run around and to desert
me
by any chance
of baron duncan eduardo vasquez
unexpected um
the unexpected ones are the good ones
great pilot for the whole talk series
marine is an excellent guest and your
greatest convenience
yeah honestly i have to say one big
reason for the success of the first
pilot episode it's just because marin
is a very good talker and uh you give
her one topic and she can talk an hour
about it so it's it's big thanks to her
she's a lot of experienced love stories
that's why i want to go for
um the older generations
at least for now because they have more
stories and for maddie and senpai
especially
um
i already pretty much decided on my next
guest as i said as i mentioned i already
pretty much decided
but uh still trying to
get permission for that uh specific
guest
uh trying to get in contact but
it is uh quite a big guest
there were many people who asked for
this specific guest
and even marin senpai recommend when i
mentioned
that i want to invite her my name tempo
was like oh yeah just ask her she'll
she'll definitely say yes mine is sent
by
setzel and actually it is definitely
true should probably say yes right away
do you love 67 thank you brain cell
pancashin
the littlest brain cell again duncan i
will support you thank you soon
[Music]
is yeah
no i don't like that comparison i don't
want to be
lord because i don't like loins
mostly go to money so so so
i loved it so much and i hoped it would
be longer it's not already
the end of the talk show i wonder it
seems like people are saying goodbye
loved it so much and hoped it would be
long i'm hyped for the next one yeah i'm
considering our next one to be maybe 1.5
hours
[Music]
i just had to have this one one hour
because central
marine was going to have preparation for
the
next stream and also i didn't want to
um overlap with kelly's stream
um i don't think i think two hours is
too much generally just because i feel
like uh
even though we could go on for hours and
hours i feel like just one hour is very
compact and
a nice uh time
to also catch up on if you didn't manage
to watch the live one you could always
watch the archives quickly
but yeah 1.5 hours
maybe maybe for the next ones i will
have a
it will it will be planned as one hour
but
i will keep the half hour after that
open for for a chance of a
extension if we have like
more to talk about so that we don't have
to stress about ending it but also if
we're like
i don't know already done talking if
we're through with all the questions we
could also end it there you know
yeah but 1.5 is kind of maximum to me i
think because
i feel like also it's a bit difficult to
prepare so many questions and
also for me to translate for
two hours straight i mean
i'm not sure like
i i felt very nervous probably because
it was the first uh
episode i wonder if in the future i will
still be so wait you changed your name
looking for the top right
i feel like probably eventually it will
be more smooth for me but
i don't want to put myself into too much
mental pressure for
translating for two hours straight and
the thing was this time um
if you remember uh where i was a guest
at kelly's stream to translate
what her music producer said
i was we were in the studio and i was
sitting there with my laptop in front of
me and every time her producer uh
kiss would say something i would quickly
write it down
like note it down roughly in my laptop
i was doing it very really seriously to
so that i don't forget anything he
was saying um
[Music]
so i wanted to do it the same way for
the marine stream translation
because i knew she would talk a lot
i knew she was going to talk a lot and
have a lot of stories
so i thought i have to i have to write
it down
but this
talk show it was so much on my screen i
had the comments
i had uh us there that i had to keep on
fixing whenever
we disappeared i had a streamlabs window
where i had to keep the
keep inputting the questions i had my
google doc where the questions were in
there so i had to copy paste them
and in the google docs i had the
japanese translation this way there was
just
so much to do already that i um
i tried i started out i had my laptop in
front of me as well so i had my pc and
my laptop because i just have
one screen and it was just too much
stuff but then
having the laptop right in front of me
kind of uh
stopped me like it couldn't i couldn't
it was just
it sucked the whole setup sucked so
for the first question i tried to write
down what she was saying
people were thinking that uh actually i
wrote that i saw that in some feedback
someone
questioning something like ah i i bet
she was like
um writing everything down so she could
translate it better
i was trying that but i ended up giving
up right after the first question
because i realized this is not working i
have to do so many things
i cannot even write it down so for the
rest of the show
basically the whole show i translated
everything she said
without writing it down
and i was quite impressed that it
actually went well i actually quite uh
remembered
uh what she was saying quite well if you
remember sometimes she was really
talking a lot
was sometimes really talking a lot
yeah like she was talking for a minute
straight sometimes
i was uh surprised with my own skills
that i could remember that and actually
uh
translate that just one thing
that i have a problem with sometimes is
uh
since i'm not a professional i sometimes
forget
um or can't think of good words
in english when i'm translating so it
ends up
i i end up keep on like keeping
repeating the same words
like when i said uh when i tried to
describe what she said about meeting
zoon
i couldn't think of uh like
uh how to translate something so easy
though
uh when she said that he was so mabush
he was what is mabushi in
english goddammit it's just too i was
saying he was like shining or something
because he was too bright yeah i said i
would i said he was too bright
uh yeah blinding yeah in that moment i
could only think of the
german translation and not of the
english translation even though it's
such an easy word yeah
radiant see yeah
my vocabulary sometimes uh disappears
maybe you will find the top right out
though thank you
so sometimes there's a bit of a bit of
lack of vocabulary and i end up always
using the simple
english words that i come up with also i
repeated uh
a dream come true i repeated that quite
a lot of times because i couldn't really
think of a different translation for
that and i mean it was still
basically in the context it was what she
said
but yeah
but i definitely was surprised about
myself being able to
translate all of that all her machine
gun talk without
writing it down
i am surprised with myself i learned
something new about myself when i did
the one with
uh callie her producer
kokorobitsu he didn't even talk that
much he only spoke very
very short sentences but i was so
nervous i didn't know what i could
actually do
live translating so i wrote it all down
just in case
but there i had nothing to do other than
that because cali was controlling the
whole live streaming thing and i only
had my laptop
but in this case it was just too many
other things i had to manage yeah
i went it went fun so
i think next time i'll be fine as well
although
these are the times where i realized huh
a second monitor
would be uh useful for these kind of
situations
but i refuse to get one
[Music]
no
why because i'm moving in like three
months
and i don't want to have too many things
to throw away i already have so many
things i'm gonna throw away
it's gonna be such a waste
and for now it's not it's not like i
can't work like this
also i'm getting a pc soon it's not
going to help with that situation of
having no space on my screen but
still keeping
an expense inexpensive monitor yeah
and i need more cables again
yeah use laptop is another monitor
no there's too much effort
anyway let's continue we have to make
some progress oh my god
well it's still only free 3 am only
see in my context in my um
understanding 3 a.m is
early
by
use an ipad i don't have an ipad
i don't really like
am i allowed to say that i don't really
like
up up pop
even though i'm using one for work
even though i'm using one for this job
it's just so the whole interface and
everything's so confusing
and why the hell are ipads so goddamn
expensive
i mean i have to admit i just don't uh
i have i've never really owned an apple
project besides that
phone that i'm using
email i like androids
[Music]
you tell them
okay everyone tell me are you using
android or iphone
tell me now
wow almost everyone is using android wow
iphone i don't like it though damn
damn well you can juggle for the season
final
oh i'm not sure i cannot really make any
promises
for that i don't even know when would
there be a season final
hold on
foreign
flip phones oh yeah
the chemistry between you and marin was
amazing and the flow of questions
were so smooth also that pgm is so chill
perfect for a talk show to me this was
better than taxes on tv oh thank you
yeah the pgm was great right i really
love my new pgm
but it's specifically made for holotalk
so i will not use it anywhere besides
holotalk
regarding this the flow of the questions
i personally thought it was bad
because they did many of them did not
really have much of a connection to each
other and i often was just like okay
next question
because i wasn't really uh sure how to
connect
them but that i always did in japanese
so i guess the english speaking of yours
did not really
notice that the flow in between the
questions
was not that good i guess that that
would have probably only been noticeable
for japanese people
because that was in japanese
yeah but i don't think it's a
such a big deal jumping from
one topic to another it's it's maybe not
as smooth but i also would say it's not
really a problem yeah
i don't know how i thought of that uh
just now
i saw some comment that roughly got me
into that direction can i just uh
clear up one thing that is totally
random
i never never ever ever
auditioned for a whole life japan
never
some people for some reason
think that i tried to audition for
hololive 5th generation i don't know
why you think that i guess probably
because of the piccolo sent by
uh martial model i didn't send that
sorry to destroy your fantasies i did
not send that
and i never auditioned for her life
japan
i want to make that clear because people
tried to
paint a picture that i was rejected
i think whole fifth generation
had their auditions when at the
beginning of this year
i know i have no idea because back then
i didn't even follow hollow life that
closely
i think at the beginning of 2020
i didn't really watch hello live yet i
really got into it like
maybe at the end of spring is when i got
really addicted to piccolo senpai and i
think by then at that moment i don't
think there was any audition i don't
know
i haven't been following it because i i
never thought of
uh like auditioning myself
i was just a normal viewer
just having fun i never never thought of
auditioning myself
but then at some point the english
auditions popped up and i was like huh
wait a second i never thought of this
this
possibility i never and up until now i
never thought of that
yeah one of us one of us exactly
yeah it was um i mean
i think like if at that moment where i
was really into pekora
if at that moment it was not the english
auditions coming up but the japanese
ones
maybe i would have tried for those it
was really just a timing thing
but i never tried auditioning for japan
it never even got into my mind i never
never thought that that never thought
about it
don't worry i know you didn't mean that
i just kind of got me to the idea of
this topic
glad you came to halloween thank you you
fit the english team thank you
no i'm really glad i mean i i i
i suppose i can see myself
on the japanese side as well uh
but i'm totally happy where i am right
now and i'm really glad
really glad i made it in it changed my
life completely
and i'm just so so so so so happy that
this happened
yeah totally unexpected really something
really something i would have never
thought would happen
something that i i didn't consider at
all
until the auditions were actually open
thank you all thank you
need more european am i not good enough
for you
oh wait sorry i'm australian
i guess i'm not european just kidding i
i'll i'll move back to australia wink
soon enough and i will probably be
streaming a lot during european prime
time
which will probably suck for my american
viewers
european prime time is probably
morning time in america
is it
it will probably suck for you
but i'll probably not be able to fix my
sleep schedule even when i'm back there
so i'll probably be staying up for a
long time
which means if i stay up as long as i do
here in japan
let's say let's say it's uh let's say it
is a
free let's say it is 2 am
in australia wink what time is it in est
oh oh that's a good time oh actually
maybe yeah maybe
maybe we're gonna uh maybe it's not
gonna be an issue
or maybe it's gonna be a good streaming
time
for both europe and the miracle just my
japan viewers will
probably leave me eventually because if
i stream at uh
prime time in europe it's gonna be like
5 a.m in japan or something like that
[Music]
no one is gonna wake up for that
actually yeah that works fine i guess
for both america
and europe
oh well i'm looking forward to
moving back also sad about it but also
looking forward to it
well we'll see about that if they leave
me or not we'll see about that i mean
there's barely any here right now which
m
[Music]
i think i'll probably visit japan aka
cali every one to two months
i think however i'll have to figure out
like
uh how to stream once i'm over there
like maybe i can stay over at kelly's
place i have a feeling
i have a i have a vague memory of her
telling me i can stay over but maybe
that's my imagination
i'm not sure anymore if she told me that
or not maybe someone else told me
huh
corona ah well i think until then
it's not a big issue anymore but who
knows
we'll see what i'm talking about when
things are back to normal
imagination dream impose yourself
no i genuinely think she will be fine
with it though so i could i could i mean
there's the possibility
to just stream from her place i guess
and also i guess from the studio
for the live studio
i do however i do want to get a laptop
that would be suitable for streaming but
if i remember like
what what what was kelly's laptop
lacking
for streaming i mean i guess i don't
need a gaming laptop
because if i'm uh in japan for one week
i could just do other streams like
talking and karaoke
and drawing streams and just not play
games for a week
um it needed better gpu not a hotel i
see
you guys should give me recommendations
because i have no idea can you guys give
me recommendations on twitter
of what laptop to buy for streaming like
something that
you you think would really be really
good for streaming
gaming laptop does not exist
[Music]
i recommend don't get adapted but i want
to be able to travel and stream
price range doesn't matter
keep your rented pc um no
because it's rented i have to give it
back
i can't just keep this forever
i mean there's definitely always uh just
the possibility to stay over at
someone's place but i don't want to
annoy them too many times but
there's so many hella live girls i can
just always stay over at someone else's
place
pc small build pcs
not sure if they can stream well
a laptop because of sponsorship
before but it was really powerful and
suitable for streaming
throw money at the problem okay
you guys writing all those things down
in the chat says absolutely nothing to
me
and there's no way that i will remember
any of that what you're writing in the
chat right now
so if you want to give me
recommendations on laptops
send them to me on twitter
i don't know anything about pcs so
just show me one thing and i'll buy that
oh goddammit thank you for the pocket
money
thank you
but if i had an actual even if i have a
good streaming pc the problem is still
like if i would stay over it at a hotel
internet usually is limited
and sucks so
ah but i guess i could instead of
staying in a hotel
i could always stay over in like you
know those airbnb types of
apartments then you should have better
internet
i think
yeah hotel internet even even if you pay
for the better one
it still sucks
that might be risky
ah difficult difficult it's very
difficult we will have to figure this
out though because uh
uh definitely the the other um
amelia ina and kuda they'll probably
also have to eventually come to japan
and
we will find to have a we will need to
have to find the solution so that
everyone can stream
without too much trouble
on someone by staying at their place
we need a hollow ian house that is
always ready for us to come over
yeah because like the studio
we can use it but it's usually like
the thing is like if you if we use the
studio we have to reserve the slots in
advance
and um you have to really be strict with
those thoughts so you can't be like me
and just randomly endlessly stream super
chat readings
where you don't know when it will end
and also they have closing time so over
the night you can stream
would only be during a certain time
frame
so yeah there's a bunch of problems that
comes with that so we cannot only
rely on that if the girls come over
[Music]
solution when it comes to that situation
for sure
buy a house uh-huh i
tell me to buy a house already telling
cover to buy a house
oh my god like a big brother house for
halloween
and we're just constantly streaming 24
hours oh my gosh
i don't think they will buy a house for
us
but they will have to find some solution
okay continuing
thank and i'm looking forward to the off
club of santo
yes she cannot run away i will not let
her run away
she has no choice the thing is like
it would also be painful for me it will
not only be painful for her
to play ring for the adventure on stream
it will also be painful for me
business expense i would agree with that
and i don't even think that it will be
such a
expensive investment for
such a successful company
so thank you bronx thank you
sx thank you looking very tough thank
you optimal
options function thank you kiara for
bringing us amazing content
watching your streams have been so
enjoyable these last months
i can't wait to see more of holotalk as
well as your upcoming song you rock
thank you
this was a great idea and very well done
looking forward to the next ones great
job
thank you mito bibo thank you
foreign
that was amazingly well done i loved how
well you kept the conversation going so
naturally
even with the translation breaks bravo
thank you
thank you thank you so much
so happy to have so much positive
feedback thank you so much it was it
really makes me feel like it was worth
it and
it really motivates me to do more
erosion knife thank you so
thank you so much for all of your hard
work breaking down the barriers of her
life
thank you
you're fun chicken excuse me
i'm a phoenix
hmm
going to sleep early i see losing to me
it's 3 a.m and i'm awake
if you go back to the year to europe ah
i will definitely not stream in the
morning that's for sure
i probably i will probably stream a lot
in the afternoon
evening time and night time but never in
the morning never
never ever
thank you
what what
basically you are in u.s time what
you mean because i go to sleep so late i
would say it's more like a european time
i'm in japan but i live in the european
time zone
where are you from give me your address
i'm coming
what the hell no
oh
keep coming it's all red
in the top thank you guys
oh i've reached the end of the holotalk
super jets
in okay but that means i have to switch
the thumbnail do i have to
i don't think i have the super chat
reading company on this pc
or do i
uh
no
i should i should oh there we go
[Music]
we have come so far everyone
we have come so far
with so many breaks and tangents in
between
after four hours we have managed to read
the super chats of two
full streams
wow where are your sister's triplets
they're sleeping
let them sleep
[Music]
on
okay let me refresh the page then
dear lord should i
ah should i maybe um deactivate thanks
for the clapping should i deactivate the
super chats now maybe for my own good
super chat
[Music]
so
no no no no no no
no
okay i turned it off
i turned it off i turned it off it's too
late
give me my style can you stop
you everyone though thank you so much
for all the all the sweet support
thank you so much
there is literally no better fan base
than the kfp fan base
there's no one better than you guys out
there
and i also turned off the stickers
east all good
okay there we go acceptable
amount should be all right
speed light light speed sorry
[Music]
do you wear toe nail polish too
well that is something i will not
tell you
you will have to find out one day maybe
if i take my shoes off but i wear my
shoes 24 7 so
i cannot tell you
thank you so much for the congrats thank
you thank you
general piccolin ally has no content
sanctions speech
thank you myspace oh my god
i never had a myspace page i can tell
you that much
maybe that's the reason why i was never
able to become
a emo scene kid
what jlpt levels are you i never took a
test
i keep telling myself i should probably
do it but people always believe me that
i can speak japanese so
it just works out like that
rent and junk for anthony dankeshen
andrei turkishan
i never counted them but i can read
quite a lot i would say
burp still awake hell yeah take it till
you make it clearly
that is exactly how i learned japanese
and someone in the super chats asked as
well
but let me get there i already explained
this before how i learned
japanese but when we get to the super
chat i'll answer it
[Music]
here goes my first super chat thank you
thank you for writing our days with your
streams by the way the whole talk of
marin was great looking forward to the
next one thank you so much
did you think about adding background
clapping a lot yes i did but
ah first of all i didn't really find
good audio and second of all i wasn't
really sure how to activate it
i'll think about it more
but also i don't want i don't want it to
be too
bothering and distracting
you can make a soundboard yeah but
i'm not sure like i had i i bought a
oops i bought a
lifelong subscript subscription license
to some kind of digital sound board
uh because of different reasons not
because of the sounds i bought it just
because
because i wanted a good echo
oh but anyway i stopped using it but
maybe i could try it with that thing i
don't know
skippy thank you oh don't worry i got
all the all the
pickled merchandise from the mama
herself
jacqueline thank you patrick chen
pankashen i mean i don't have it yet
that's but she
put it aside for me
i couldn't catch it live but the talk
show was amazing your language skills
are absolutely fantastic and it was
great being able to enjoy your chat with
marin in real time
and i learned lots of new things about
her looking forward to the next one
mission accomplished that is exactly
what i wanted to happen
thank you so much i'm glad you enjoyed
it
[Music]
two months ago your words you weren't as
talented as others but now you've
released your own thing
uh not yet and hosted your own
talk show you better be proud of
yourself kayla cause you know we are
proud of you did you say it didn't you
say
a few days ago you're gonna
disappear for a while you're still here
which is totally fine
i'm happy i didn't leave
well nice to have you
i guess you just even though you're busy
i just
i guess you just can't live without me
well thank you for your support
i mean there's one thing i've read
before um
there's talents that are more like
obvious
and more easy to show off and there's
other talents which are more
passive i suppose or at least not so
easy to like
put in a list and say these are my
talents
and immediately show them off
i suppose that and yeah
my my talents are more on the passive
side
but i'm using them actively though but i
guess it's just not something you really
are able to show such as uh you know
drawing skill where you go bam
look at how good i draw or like
incredible singing skill where you go
bam
listen to how angelic my voice is
or bam listen to my badass
rap you know
although i would say i'm a decent singer
and
i can do decent art but it's
just not the best out of the group
right so that's why i felt like okay
what am i the best at though in this
particular group
of people that is more like uh
i just wanted to be
the best at something and what i thought
i was the best at was
uh languages but then you know that
whole thing came up with people hating
me for exactly that thing
the one thing that i was proud of the
one thing
that i thought i was at least best at
but now i'm fine don't worry i have i
have come to the conclusion
that this is exactly
what i have to do and uh i will continue
doing what i am doing and what i think
is the right thing to do
and i think i'm doing it well
i am proud of myself
how about letting our guests decide the
next guest like telephone shocking
[Music]
i think it's generally a cute and a fun
idea but
yeah if they if they like for example if
money would be like okay
next guest shion and then i end up just
not being able to invite her for
whatever reason
that it would be a video first of all it
loses the meaning and
the purpose second of all i don't want
to put anyone in a situation of being
forced or feeling forced to have to
accept the offer
you know
but i think it's a cute idea
[Music]
um
yeah i think it's a cute idea but even
if we like decide on it beforehand and
just
act as if we're uh spontaneously
deciding it on the stream
there would still be people who would be
like ew why are you like
pushing it uh on onto someone
on the live stream now they don't have
any choice but to say yes
even if we already have permission
so i'm just going to do it my way
my mom
in the end i just want to choose them by
myself and
that's also a reason why i'm not doing
it but i think it's a really cute idea
it would be fun um but i also
just kind of want to decide it myself
and organize it myself because it's my
thing you know
um
coming soon hollow talk episode
2 featuring
who could it possibly be
but before holo talk episodes 2
next week
there is another exciting collab coming
up
um don't know if you noticed but during
whole talk
the view cam was up to about 50k yeah
i didn't notice during hotel because i
was too busy handling all my windows
that i had open
i was so surprised i did not expect it
to go like to 57k
i did not accept it to go that high
and i hope it will be also
that much in the next episode but yeah
it was also very stable
i saw it was very very stable
like uh it kept like after
for the first half hour it was mostly
like 50 53k
apparently but after this second at the
second half
it kept 57 58 continuously
yeah i think people really wanted to
listen
to it until the end the eggs are very
happy very happy
but i think it's also because money
senpai is so popular
i told her when we were hanging out i
told her because she told me she wants
to have many english viewers
and i told her she's already super
popular like she's one of the
members who are the most popular with
english viewers and she didn't even know
she did she didn't even like realize it
she thought that uh she's like not
really
popular with overseas viewers and i told
her myself but you have
no idea you're one of the
probably top
five most popular uh japanese streamers
for the overseas uh viewers how yeah i
was not surprised how she did not
realize that
she did not realize apparently but i
told her i hope she
i hope she takes it seriously
because she doesn't have much english
speakers in the chat really
but there they are definitely there
she's super popular
with the english audience at least from
what i have noticed
which session is the super job reading
it's from the current look
look at the thumb now at the bottom it's
from the current stream we have reached
the current stream
i'm feeling uh very uh my
my back is earning i need a massage or
some cracking
dammit lurking
she was by the way really really uh
interested
in learning english like actively
like when we talked about it while we
were eating
uh sweets all you can eat sweets she
told me like she was really really
really seriously trying to um find time
first of all to learn english because i
told her
she's really interested in it but i told
her she really needs to invest some time
if she really wants to learn it
and problem with her is just she doesn't
really have the time
yeah so i told her how about doing
weekly english conversation it's called
ikaiba you know the thing that
cali sometimes does if she does that we
clean
i mean i think you should practice a
language every day but
i think week one time for a week is the
most she can do
attention is still reading super chats
oh yeah what else would i be doing
and i told her i can try to teach her
but that would mean we would have weekly
collaborations and people would get sick
of it because
since she has no time i was like how
about you combine learning english
with streaming which would be a smart
idea but then again having weekly
collaborations with the same
people would probably not be the best
idea
i don't know no way we would get sick of
it
yeah but i think it would just be
repetitive you know
people
you guys might not get sick of it but
me showing up on her channel every
goddamn week
i don't think that's gonna happen um but
yeah
i hope she can find a way and some time
to learn some more english if she really
wants to because she seemed really
interested in it
okay continuing gotta hurry up when i
get this done
oh my god just realize we have a
collaboration at
12. that's in like
eight hours yeah bye
bye and i wanted to get up early to test
play the game that we're playing oh and
i wanted to make a thumbnail
shouldn't have gone on so many tangents
for sake
okay speed time but i want to read those
tags so goddammit
they love 67 red super chat thank you
i don't know if you've noticed but
during whole eye right i read that
unreal i asked this in an old super chat
but i've heard david hasselhoff is big
in germany how is he seen an australian
wink
and what are your thoughts on the hub no
idea man
no idea no interest who is that guy
anyway
thank you thank you for your support
rachel thank you congratulations
[Music]
i can't read this name but you wrote i
just want to listen
bb online dancing sean ian
smile in my face it was extremely
interesting hearing central stories and
hope the next talk show can be a little
bit longer i will try
thank you
that you like big inspirational speeches
so here it goes
get ready for a battle gentlemen and
ladies
prepare to vanquish our enemies or is
something um our empress will
ah forget it this is harder than it
looks i quit
thank you for trying it's okay you don't
have to do a speech
thank you vengeance
wait i haven't drank since uh i haven't
hydrated myself
in
almost four hours
okay three sips and i have nothing left
to drink upstairs so there we go
bye novel player danke shin take it
monkey dancing leslie alter thank you
thank you for the red super chat i'm
kind of late on this but i just wanted
to say congrats on the first holotalk
episode buzz it was very cool to hear
about the side of marin that i
don't really get from clubs and had to
commemorate the first episode with part
of my career salary we do got paid right
no you're paying me right now that's how
it works
thank you
[Music]
i'm really really glad you enjoyed it
really happy for enjoying it
nothing else i could have asked for
thank you so much for your support
patrick shane lancashire and thank you
[Music]
i had to attend the wedding ooh i
probably should never put personal
matters before kfb do this again please
please on fire
thank you sir no problem no problem you
can take a day off
no problem thank you so much
[Music]
it is happy to see you your stream is
funny so that i can escape from the
pressure of my job the only question is
you cause me always want to eat kfc but
this is always make me sick
sorry but uh yeah maybe try it different
fast food for once or like if you mix it
up and
try with different sauces it should give
you a fresh
taste
[Music]
thank you soon
i can't breathe
[Music]
alive patrick chandang dragon three four
seven thank you so much
tiger thank you in torture blue thank
you jaclyn thank you so much
questions
[Music]
i still have a bunch to go let's see how
fast we can do it
link fan duncan lucas hackman
easy kfb head chef number one
easy kfc chef number two thank you
thank
russian name i cannot read
thank you
jacob
[Music]
congratulations on you on your hatching
day
petey brown one two one thank you shin
vento plaid pancasion panda pizza
side question dragoon for free for seven
naomi thank you for watching
looking for the top right thank you
thank you
thank you for the red super chat
whole talk was awesome marion was how i
first discovered feature was all
and eventually her life ian seeing your
collab was a birthday treat oop happy
birthday
happy birthday happy birthday please
continue to bring your warm and
wholesome spirit to these collaborations
thanks for everything you do and all
your hard work
thank you for your sweet and kind
message
i guess you found her through clips i
suppose
hopefully you'll support me in the
future as well thank you
thank you degeneret
i cannot breathe
okay but when your hair grows does the
turquoise
strip get lower or does it always stay
behind your neck
if you let your hair grow super long
would you have multiple alternating
orange trigger strips
we need answers uh
well um
if it grows longer then the
the turquoise part will also get longer
yes i can i can confirm that
is
guys chiara's colors are actually
authentic phoenix colors you can look up
arcane phoenix if there are still some
non-believers out there
thank you for clearing that up
tell them tell them for me they don't
believe me
kfc pekka danke sold on them
fork and kx volta jackson thank you
side question so condom thank
online hello funny looking chicken
shut up baby online
people thank you from koslovsky thank
you
i will try i will try not to change kfc
pekka duncan
skip
foreign
[Music]
okay how do i read that russian name
ah alexei
you sent a couple ones so i should
remember that name now
i will try from russia with love spassy
bye
thank you thank you so much kfc pickle
dance
i told her before the stream because i
know she talks a lot
i told her mind stand by please talk
slowly
don't uh please take some breaks in
between
and please don't use too difficult
japanese i told her but i think
she just uh completely forgot
which is okay i managed anyway
looking for the top right thank you
flanders thank you for the word super
chat
absolutely love the show you did amazing
looking forward to the next episode
me too thank you thank you so much for
your support thank you soon
i'll see you in the next one hopefully
in the streams in between as well
i can't read that they nonsense
[Music]
oh i can't read that
wait a second i did i wanted to answer
that question i think it was even a red
super chat but seeing that uh
corinthians i don't know i can't really
recognize it but
thank you for the red super chat if it
was one the question the question was
i've always wanted how did you learn
japanese also can you do a frown like
you always smile and i'm really curious
how far it looks
well okay i'll do that for you but i
learned japanese by myself
i talked about this before but
[Music]
i basically i had no teacher
and i did have some books but i never
used
them i i got some books
in the purpose was to learn it with the
books but i was too lazy to
actually use them so they were just in
my
in my shelf and were never used so the
way i
uh learned japanese was basically
talking to japanese people
online every goddamn day
and and i was just really really
passionate about it which i think
is why it made it easier for me um
yeah and pretty much everything that i
did not understand
just i i didn't even have to try to
remember it
i don't know why this is only with
japanese language with other languages i
didn't learn it that easily but
every time i saw a word that i didn't
know before it just stayed in my head
and did not leave me afterwards but i
think really the biggest reason is
because i was really trying to speak
japanese every day
uh so if you are consistent and
try to use the language every day
then it should be easy for you to learn
the language
and yeah one
other thing i did was pretend because i
had some weird pride i was quite young
but i had this weird pride i didn't want
to admit that i could not speak japanese
yet
and i wanted people to think i'm smart
so even when i only knew a few basic
phrases and it was
totally understandable that i don't
understand certain things
i would like copy it put it in a
separate
tab separate tab translate it there look
up the way
it's pronounced then speak it out loud
and then i would get praised for knowing
it
and they would be like what
how do you know how to even read that
how do you understand what that means
and i'll be like i know everything
without even trying
but with that method basically
everything stayed in my brain and i
remembered it because right away i would
also use the word by reading it out loud
and i would have the meaning right in
front of me
so yeah i cheated my way to victory
exactly
just fake it till you make it exactly
yeah well i give you my angry face as
well
yes i did not want people to think that
i don't speak japanese
so even when i only was able to say
konnichiwa
whatever i just
acted as if i already knew everything
and i already spoke fluent
japanese yeah
my mario kart face exactly
and i mean i learned it like that i
learned the language to a conversational
level
uh after six months
and well of course after that i still
used the language a lot
so i improved even more but i was
already
pretty fluent and able to have normal
conversations
after six months of continuously using
the language
every day by acting
acting as if i already knew it
yep it's a pretty good strategy it
doesn't work for everyone but one big
point of course besides the
communication
one big point was just the passion that
i had behind that
yes
well i couldn't do that again though
i would not be able to do the same thing
again
i mean i was also very young and it's
easier to
learn languages when you're still young
right
so that was probably one reason oh god
my i did not eat the whole
mandarin so now it's like almost the
outside is kind of drying up i shouldn't
really eat it
angrily eating a mandarin
wait i'm pronouncing it wrongly right my
intonation is wrong
mandarine is how you pronounce that
fruit right
not mandarin that's the the
chinese
wait is it the language or the writing
or is both wrong
correct right okay okay
okay so i'm gonna make a thumbnail and
reserve my stream
and then hopefully be able to sleep
sometime soon
but you know me you know me
i usually watch netflix for
four hours before i can actually sleep
yes as expected
smart kiara
it's netflix time
all right there were two more things
nico danke
huang tran duncan and rabbit mod 87
thank you everyone for your support
today thank you for
all the sweet messages thank you for
hanging out and chatting with me thank
you for watching stupid world of
warcraft videos thank you for
uh singing nostalgic uh emo scene songs
and whatever
thank you for talking about holo talk
with me
i had quite some fun it was quite the
interesting super chat reading
next stream tomorrow is collab
with all the other ibm members in
eight hours from now eight hours which
means since i watched
netflix for like four hours
means i got uh four hours of sleep maybe
no free because i'm gonna wake up an
hour early to practice
oh my god pray for me guys
because
right after that i did schedule a
minecraft stream
right after the collab
and
i know i gonna sleep without watching
netflix i would love to do that but it's
just like a ritual for me i can't
i can't first of all i need to get my
mind off of things by watching netflix
otherwise i just cannot
like calm down
and get tired i might
yeah i might push this netflix stream
back so i can take a nap in between
and did i just say netflix stream
always already thinking too much about
olympics i might
push the minecraft stream back
to start later which i will be sorry for
the american viewers uh i'm sorry you
probably
won't be able to watch it then unless
you stay up late
for me on the saturday night should be
possible right
i don't see any excuse possible
so collab at 12 japanese standard time
12 o'clock probably for one and a half
hours
then i'll take a nap and then we stream
minecraft maybe some
time around
oh wait a second the reason i scheduled
minecraft at that time because
i'm scared that if i play if i played at
the
prime time japan the server will kick me
out again
i can't really move it
huh
i'll think about it we might just play
something else
i'll think about it maybe i'll play
sakuna didn't play it this week did i
did i maybe at the beginning of the week
maybe i'll play sakura or fry on blem
instead
in any case see you tomorrow bye bye
thank you for coming today
thanks for everything huggletalk was
really a success i'm really happy about
it and really happy to have you all
supporting me
throughout the whole process and um
even even in those times when
it was not officially kiara's era
just yet but it has come now and
i hope you you can be as proud of me
as i am of myself or the other way
around
i hope you can proudly say this is my
bird
look at my bird she's doing so well such
a good
bird pet the casper so sorry that you're
thinking of casper
look at my bird my bird is amazing tell
everyone my friends
send them the holo talk show until next
week send them my song
spread the love spread the bird love i
love you all
and in german we say
i'll be nothing i gotta bring
no one i'll
actually i played the wrong ending at
holotalk now i remember
[Music]
you