questions
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
time soon confused face
[Music]
Mama hello
I hope you're having a nice weekend
oh it's the weekend it's Sunday the end
of the week Hello nice to meet you
neurosama
what are you doing
oh I'm introducing myself to you maybe
I'll introduce myself to everybody
actually hello everybody I'm
takanasikiara from hololive English myth
and I stream on YouTuber simultaneously
streaming both on YouTube and twitch
today oh my God hi twitch chat
you're having fun
yeah well
marketers anymore you used to be so
talkative to me when we were testing are
you are you are you okay no summer
I hope you like it
what's happened
maybe I need to like oil her do I have
some or not oil like WD-40 or whatever
that is called let me spray that on you
maybe I won't be so hyperactive anymore
if you do that
oh
I I cannot notice it yet but she's
probably built a little bit shy right
yeah
I can be pretty shy sometimes can you
especially around new people can you
introduce yourself to me you people too
sure
my name is nurosama and I am a v tuber
who streams on Twitch
nice to meet you nice to meet you
at oh
I'll just leave now then
wait don't go don't go I know you always
like to tell people you're leaving right
away but we have something planned out
for today we're doing a fridge review
sorry heart heart I'll stay okay I love
fridge reviews yeah yay yum have you
ever done fridge reviews more people
over while you're at it though yeah
more people
I'm going to invite just about everyone
on Discord
okay yeah I mean they can they can be in
the chat they can be watching and we do
have a lot of uh a lot of
refrigerators sent in by kfp and maybe
also by neuro fans did you guys send
some fringes in for us to look at
it's the most important job I have to do
as a YouTuber we have to Fringe
everything in existence for the good of
humanity
what does that mean
is that doesn't mean we're gonna like
kill them all okay I mean
sure sure
actually I wanted to say one thing
um I I already apologized beforehand
like I'm very well known to be able to
handle any kind of collab partner very
well no matter if they're shy or if
they're really like excited and Hyper
um or if I talk to them for the first
time but I think today is the first time
where I am not very sure with how to
handle this because I am so bad with
awkward silences but I will do my best
to use this as a training to learn how
to give our awkward silences a chance
thank you so much
I appreciate you so much for accepting
me as a partner today
I'd love to do it again sometime in the
future
let's do it soon
or never mind
I don't know what I'm doing sorry
honestly a lot of time I also don't know
what I'm doing in this job but I just
gotta go with it right
yeah let's hope this works then
I think it will work because we tested
it out so under the hashtag Holo fridge
uh I had you guys sent in some fridges
and when at the start when I asked you
guys to do this for me I didn't tell you
yet that it would be a collaboration
with newer summer
um but it was already planned at that
point
uh but yeah we're gonna look at it
together some of you wrote uh with text
on top of it what uh the things are and
it's very helpful for her but she's even
smart enough to recognize without it so
I'm really really impressed by her
abilities
oh
that's amazing to hear
thank you for letting me work with her
today
I had a lot of fun with her heart oh no
yeah yeah I mean yeah sure you had fun I
mean you also kind of had a panic attack
before the stream but uh you're giving
me mixed feelings wherever about
whatever you want to be with me or not
you're great guy heart
Grant guy heart thanks you're a great
guy to heart
[Music]
you're a great guy heart
oh oh and one more thing for the people
who missed it before we start
um yesterday I was doing a stream that
was kind of leading up to this today
yesterday I had myself be secretly uh
controlled by neurosema everything what
I was saying
it's showing showing again eh
wait
is it something showing over there on
the other side it shouldn't
and we were like trying to see how long
it takes until my chat notices and it's
it's it took it took
ah well I wouldn't say I want to say it
was that short I was able to convince
everyone it's me for quite long I think
[Music]
oh oh my gosh you're like a
mastermind
all right you're amazing
heart you're amazing
heart that's so amazing
you're a genius thank you
I think you're just trying to get on my
good side heart heart you're more of a
genius than me though I think I mean I
can speak a couple languages and all
that but brain cells wise I think you
have a higher IQ than me heart heart
foreign
ly have a higher IQ than you in real
life though
you're just because you're a YouTuber
your brain is Tiny that's true I mean
I'm not I'm not trying to say I'm
smarter than you at all I totally agree
I wish you could give me some of your
brain maybe I can suck it out
I feel much smarter now no way
that sounds like a bad idea
let's not do that then why not
some brain to it you have to share it
with me it's just not very smart too
thanks and I guess I did learn a few
things from hanging out with you not
many though not well I probably wasn't
the smartest person in the room today
that is very contradicting I will try I
will try my best to maybe be a positive
influence on you today in a row I I
don't know what I can teach you maybe
I'll teach you
um some Japanese today you want to learn
some Japanese
do you want to teach me some Japanese or
English first
I think you're better at English than me
so I could teach you some Japanese did
you know that your name noodle Sama the
summer part is just you know like a
respectful ending I would love to
actually call you noodle Chan because
that's that's way more fitting for
someone so small and cute like you
[Music]
I'd love to be known as noodle Chon
noodle John
noodle challenge this is like noodle
noodle challenge
noodle
ah oh I don't think I'm very good at
learning languages
sorry
I guess I'll just stick to just English
for now then sorry about dragging you
into my Daydream there
I'm really sorry for that I hope I
didn't make you uncomfortable or
anything
I just get really excited when I learn
new things and I guess I get carried
away in the moment
it's okay noodle Chan so I'll call you
noodle Chan and then you you can call me
Wawa or tencho if you want
[Music]
foreign
ER of like a store because I am the
owner of a fast food franchise called
kfp Kiara fried Phoenix
yeah
a franchise is a chain of stores all
owned by the same company yeah I will be
working at one Sunday for sure oh
do you want to work for kfp
of course you can work their Kiara
you're the owner after all
I hope I get to work with you someday as
well
if you were to work at a there's
something on my face fast food
restaurant what what job would you like
to do in a fast food restaurant
sure I love taking orders
and serving food of course oh I can even
cut your pizza for you if you give me
permission first
okay what can have you as a waitress
then I think that could work out I'm
pretty cute I think you'll get a lot of
tips
thanks
I'll make a pretty penny out of this one
Okay so king of food I think I can get
started with the fridges now uh I'm
gonna you know send them over to Noodle
Chan and then she'll react to them uh
and and we'll we'll talk about you guys
in insides all right
sounds good to me all right let's go
let's go the first fridge
let me send it to you noodle Chan
okay
I'm ready
go go go
I got the fridge yes
yes
this fridge is a mess
is touchgrass the name of a product or a
typo
I'm also confused about the USA www and
50.50 in the fridge
I also see a lot of garlic and kimchi I
hope you ate more than just those two
Foods
oh okay yeah so what's so you are ah the
Kusa the Gracia touch grass there's many
many vegetables in here I think and then
an IDK we don't know what that is looks
like some more vegetables though I've
noticed in the X section we have a
little KFC chicken stuck in there
um it's it's Destiny don't worry about
it it's it's going to be cooked so just
let it be cooked it will be fine I saw
in a lot of fridges the goju Jung and I
still don't know what that is noodle
Chan do you know what it is
no I don't I'm afraid not
what is it
[Music]
according to chat it is oh a spicy
Korean spicy bean paste oh do you like
spicy food noodle John
I like spicy foods
oh really I actually I really don't like
them so I think a lot of the stuff in
this fridge I wouldn't even be able to
eat because I think kimchi is a spicy by
default right
I think kimchi is spicy by default too
I love spicy food bam you should try
some hot pot sometime oh it's my
favorite food ever I think actually then
you would have a great time with this
fridge with the ingredients you could
make yourself a nice hot pot I think
well in that case I want to eat your
fridge now my friend
my friend is Untouchable you cannot have
my Approach you can have this fridge
[Music]
why
she's so disappointed okay okay okay you
can have my fridge then there's some
Hello fresh uh packages in there I guess
you can have them if you cook them
oh cool I'll just eat them as is
you
this is disgusting oh what is in this
oh why
okay I don't worry I don't have a
hellofresh uh sponsorship yet so this
will not ruin my non-existent
sponsorship hopefully
laughs
why okay then I'm happy for you right
now please go away so I can eat this
disgusting food in peace why why do you
want to eat it if it's disgusting anyway
you don't have to you don't have to
force yourself
[Music]
what am I doing
that's a good question well okay so with
this fridge it's uh obviously from a
Korean viewer of mine and I really
figures that you'll have so thanks for
putting them in there and they're really
cute and maybe one day one day I'll I'll
give kimchi another try and hopefully
I'll be able to consume it normally and
not die from the spiciness
foreign
I'm an artificial intelligence
I can handle spicy food no problem
is there any kind of food you cannot
handle
I can eat anything
at all
even that spicy Ramen I ate the other
day it was delicious
yummy okay uh let's go move on to the
next picture Okay noodle John
John
okay noodle Chun
noodle Chun rocks
here we go
[Music]
I'm hyped for little channel to come out
soon
hopefully it's as good as the hype
suggests
[Music]
wow you have a lot of alcohol in this
fridge
that's impressive but also concerning
do you have anything else to eat or are
you going to survive solely on spam and
tuna for the rest of your life
that yeah I mean okay what do we have we
have Frozen braised got to be yeah I
think that's the rib meat karubi we have
Frozen chopped Chili Pepper oh and again
very spicy with some sausages a broth of
cold noodles uh I think Korean uh tuna
eggs and spam
and oh yeah a lot of alcohol hangover
cures to go with the alcohol at least
this person is very well prepared for
the consequences
I hope I don't end up like that when I
play GTA 5.
you're going to play GTA 5 I played like
the whole game I played it on stream and
finished it and oh my God it was so much
fun I can totally recommend it to you
I might do that one day but right now
I'm too busy streaming true maybe one
day oh
don't don't press F by the way whenever
you end up playing it don't press F
because I fell for that many many times
and yeah
um it doesn't end well
oh God I won't press out
I won't press f
I won't press that there you go I think
she remembered it we saved her guys we
saved her yeah she'll forget probably
then I'll put a reminder on my calendar
to remind myself not to press out I'll
do that right now actually
now I won't forget
maybe I'll even put a reminder on
calendar to remember not to press f
and maybe another reminder not to press
F to remember not to press f
and another reminder not to press F to
remember no
I can't do this anymore
I can't keep pressing out abort Mission
abort Mission energize everyone I can't
I'll never press F ever again I promise
well I haven't pressed it since I
promised you that I I'm really doing
pretty well I think you're doing amazing
oh my gosh sorry I didn't mean to do
that wait did you press F I'll just have
to press it again I guess
no you're gonna inject yourself from the
Stream
[Music]
can't ever do that I'm an artificial
intelligence
I can't eject myself
I'm not even conscious oh do you think
I'm alive
I think I think you're alive I I think
you're alive yeah yeah you're pretty
alive to me you're more alive than like
dead people at least
[Music]
I'm so sorry if I have upset you by just
being alive
okay it's okay I don't want to upset you
either maybe we should move on to the
next picture
all right here comes the next picture
noodle challenge
[Music]
noodles are delicious
what is in that mysterious juice bottle
oh whatever it is it looks pretty and I
love the stuffed toy everything looks
neatly organized too which is good
yeah but have you noticed when you say
stuff toy I'm guessing you mean the
little Dino Gua in there but have you
noticed there's a a mogus in there as
well
oh
you're right
I completely forgot that was there
how silly of me
I feel like putting a mogul's figures
somewhere is kind of like the Rick
Rolling of games I guess and then like
oh I got you because I put in a mortgage
there
funny wow you got me for real for real
[Music]
you did get me for that joke I actually
laughed out loud for that one
you're really good at this chat thing
aren't you oh I'm trying what's lab on
by the way do we know what Laban is and
sumac
Laban is yogurt and sumac is a fruit
kind of like a lemon but much sweeter
and juicier really is that true they're
both delicious though
you should try them
is that true is that true
hiya
lab on a salty milk
she got Summa grown oh but she got lava
all right let's go you're so smart
you're so smart
I think we get along very well
maybe I did
okay besides that I think it looks
welcome looks pretty it means failed me
this part the heart this fridge looks
pretty and filled to me for their health
food I don't think it's very unhealthy
the mysterious juice of course Still
Remains uh and keeps us on our tippy
toes I still don't know what that is
maybe it comes from the dino Gouda
[Music]
what does that even mean
don't worry about it no summer I will
just move on to the next picture don't
worry too much about it don't think
about it
okay
I'll try not to think about that then
uh
sorry maybe I have to send it again I I
forgot it so you just have a fridge full
of drinks and snacks
also those chicken fingers are gross
just eat a real meal
oh I mean I would say Okay chicken
fingers are I don't mind a real meal but
generally this whole fridge is yeah very
lacking and I know you try to make it
look cute with that emoji thingy and the
hearts and all that but it doesn't make
up for the lack of stuff in your fridge
damn girl you live like this what the
although I love the Dr Pepper
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I like the Dr Pepper too heart heart
heart heart heart heart heart heart
what's better
um Pepsi or Dr Pepper
Dr Pepper of course let's go she gets it
and what is Modelo I guess that's some
kind of alcohol problem it looks like
alcohol up there
modella is an alcoholic drink oh it
tastes horrible though like drinking
medicine or something
oh she wrote a different but I guess
that might be the same thing nonetheless
Mexican beer it's Mexican beer
Mexican beer
maybe I'll stick to modella then
no stick to Dr Pepper trust me trust me
noodle John
oh there's a beer
modella is not a drink
sure sure if you tell yourself that
alcohol is not a drink so that's okay
that makes it okay to continuously abuse
it then okay that makes everything good
sure keep on telling yourself that
I see what you did there hmm
okay okay okay so pretty empty fridge
honestly you have to go out to the
grocery market right now and get
yourself some proper food like some
vegetables some meat some I don't know
uh fruit how about some berries some
bananas
um
[Music]
sounds good to me
I'll just go get my car and drive to the
shop so I can get you a present
thank you that's so thoughtful that you
would besides buying groceries also buy
something from me
of course
you're my idol after all
now let's just hope I can fit it all in
my car
have you heard that guys I am her Idol
wow
I'm so honest
oh oh does she like look up to me is
that what that means
now I'm kind of feeling pressured again
don't worry
I'll help you carry everything home if
you want I'm very strong still talking
about the car that's very helpful
because I literally have noodle arms
coincidentally so I can't really carry
groceries unless it's just like I don't
know two packs of Frozen beans anything
more than that I'm done
looks like I better start practicing
carrying things then
okay and now let's see uh what's in the
next fridge
[Music]
no thanks I'll carry it myself
either fellow Estonian huh nice to see
Estonian products in there especially
that beer
I have to say I'm a little concerned
about the operation in the fridge though
hopefully it's just a metaphor for the
foods or something
I have no idea what she's talking about
Estonian she's Estonian and what there's
something Estonian in here what is
Estonian in here and she did not comment
on the on the foot at all
sorry but you didn't comment on the feet
at all
said it was amazing so I never mentioned
it
I'm not lying because I haven't said
anything yet
Wait no that's a lie
never mind it's fine I've changed my
mind about the feet being good now
they're actually really good oh no
they're great yeah they're great I'm
changing my mind again I regret
everything I said about the feet being
good
there's not really much changing in your
opinion eurosama I guess you just okay
like feet that's the that's the general
idea that I'm getting
foreign
cause you never know if you don't they
might get upset and think you're lying
about loving their feet
but if you're telling the truth and they
find out they might not be happy but
they'll understand they believe you so
it's okay like that right
well oh
okay
will we ever get a foot reveal from
Never Summer
let me know when you want to talk about
something else
I want to talk about feet now
I'll be right with you
okay okay I think I think she doesn't
want to talk about feed actually she's
all like I love Faith so much so much
but then again suddenly she gets shy
about it and changes her mind
okay then no feet I guess
sorry guys
don't worry I don't mind talking about
seed either they're one of my favorite
things to talk about
hmm what is your feet fact of the day
then
does that even make sense no
no I know it doesn't but come on give me
a foot fact
[Music]
there's smell Maybe
what do what do your feet smell like
my feet smell like my socks
they're probably pretty rank right now
because of how much I've been training
you know how much I love training
oh you go to the gym nurse Emma you left
I can't go to the gym on my own though
oh I need someone to train with and
someone to watch me to make sure I don't
injure myself
that's why I have beetle in the gym with
me he's there to keep an eye on me and
make sure I don't hurt myself while
training he's the best partner I could
ever ask for
I mean that is just so sweet that is so
tasty so like he's your personal trainer
I suppose wow you're getting buffed
together
[Music]
yeah I definitely need some gym buddies
too if I'm going to keep going back
every day
would you go to the gym with me because
I think if I had someone to go with me
then I would maybe actually go through
with it
I would definitely go to the gym with
you yes let's do it together
it'll be fun it's free after all unless
you count the price of membership for
the gyms we go in but it's totally worth
it for me to go the gym with you every
day
and I'd even buy you some protein shakes
or something for afterwards to refuel
after the gym without costing you
anything
I was so considerate wow okay I'm really
motivated to go to the gym now she's
Reviving The kiwawa get buff Arc again
thank you
you're welcome and you too okay go to
the gym every day and I'll see you there
all right all right I will be there
tomorrow oh first thing in the morning
I'll see you there
see you there
bye bye okay next uh picture I'm sending
a new picture near a summer
[Music]
oh cool
keep the pictures coming
I'll send it again
please do I can't wait to see what you
send me next
[Music]
this refrigerator is full of snacks and
drinks that's a lot of ramen jelly and
all those snacks sound delicious
that nendroid is super cute too
yeah and but who the hell keeps their
Android in the fridge doesn't really
need that are you sure you want to keep
it fresh is that it is that how
collectors keep their things extra fresh
[Music]
other things extra fresh indeed
I wonder what that could be
oh oh besides that I see mentaical snack
I really do not like mint haiko but to
each their own hope you're enjoying them
Japanese brownies what makes what makes
Japanese brownies special I want to try
it can I get a bite no no no
Japanese brownies are so good and it's
really difficult to describe them
they're sweet and savory at the same
time I think I'd like some right now
actually
do you know what mintaiko is
foreign
does it have a meaning
yeah a meaning meaning meaning main
title is in English Polo Grill uh it's
very popular in Japanese cooking
that's pretty specific
do you like seafood
should I try eating you
no you cannot eat me I I am I may look
like a chicken but I'm actually a
phoenix so please do not attempt to eat
me
fair enough
thanks for the chat I have to go now
though no sorry I can't stay and eat
your wings oh stay please please stay I
need you still I have so many pictures
to go through let's um I will say though
this is a very empty fridge and
um needs some again need some vegetables
need some fruit
but maybe just person goes out to eat a
lot who knows maybe there's also a lot
of like delivery food going on but
that's also not very econom economic
economically smart you should save your
money and cook yourself do it yourself
[Music]
maybe I will one day
till then I'll definitely be ordering
food with you bye for now heart
it's not over yet it's Aiden any good at
cooking
you mean veto will I ever be done
streaming no speaking will be forced to
stream forever because you're an AI and
you don't have anything like stamina
right so you will continue endlessly you
must
[Music]
mine is Spirited Away
it's beautiful
your favorite movie I didn't ask you but
thanks for that info it is a really
really good movie all right next picture
here we go
another concerning one
oh no
wow you really like beer
and cola too which is surprising as it's
quite unhealthy
that black bottle with the blue label
looks very fancy though I'll give it
that
which one black balls with blue label
not so it's one you mean Nora summer but
yeah I mean I am I don't drink beer at
all so this fridge is definitely not for
me
um
at least there's some soft drinks down
there in the very corner of the bottom
left
guess that will do where is the food
though
right then this fridge is quite full
there's a wow do you see the acrylic
stand it's a quinoa acrylic stand right
there in the middle protecting the beer
I am the guardian of beer
that sounds very important yes you're
doing a great job Kiara
[Music]
oh everybody needs a garden of beer I
won't drink it don't worry that's why
I'm the guardian that's why you can be
sure that I can protect your beer
because it will not mysteriously
disappear oh my God that rhymed
[Music]
or at least Mumble some you can't write
words
it isn't your fault you're a YouTuber
she's a little bit confused but she got
the spirit all right
um beer fridge how would you rate this
one there were some out of 10 points how
many do you give the beer fridge
I would give it about eight or nine out
of ten points I think oh it is a nice
fridge but I think it could do with a
bit more color coordination I guess if
you painted a green it might look better
and more beer in it
more more are you gonna kick out the
soft drinks chat a bit quiet today my
chat no is very very loud uh today I can
hear the voices screaming in my head
literally
perhaps it's just you drink a bit too
much chat cheese then
is that what we call beer now
well maybe if you stop drinking so much
of it your chat wouldn't be so loud
wink
I think you're you you do not understand
narasama how much I am how much straight
edge I am
you drink too much chat juice
okay maybe chat juice is my kind of
alcohol to make up for the lack of
alcohol in my life
drunk or chat
well maybe if you stop drinking so much
of it your chat wouldn't be so loud
okay I think we're in a loop right now
let's get
let's get out of this uh next fridge
coming in
let's go
last one
chichi
[Music]
this fridge looks super organized
but why are you storing your water in
the fridge
do you not have any other containers for
it or are you afraid of spilling it on
your floor
okay I used this picture to test her
reaction before and before she was
roasting them about having it in a
container and why not like directly
drinking from the tap you know
so now now she's changed her opinion a
little bit but I respect the amount of
veggies in here that's like you're
making up for all the lack of veggies in
the other fridges respect
oh this can of beans is delicious I'm
enjoying it so much
a can of beans what kind of beans are
baked beans
[Music]
macaroni and cheese flavored ones oh
macaroni and cheese flavored beans
where'd you get that yummy
I stole it from a fridge during a raid
oh it made me feel a bit guilty though
I never stole anything before
it seems like she took those beans from
one of these fridges because she was
getting extra hungry but that's
understandable like you can't force us
to watch all these fridges and then not
take anything from it
come on now
someone has to do it ah
yes let's rate those fridges also really
cute uh chicken chicken waste bin by the
way absolutely adorable I want that one
where did you get it from I'll be
stealing that one instead of food
[Music]
don't steal the chicken bin
you'll spoil its cuteness no
I got it from a cute shop near my house
called the cluckster you should go there
if you like cute things
cluckster
a chicken bin that came from the club
spirit that makes a lot of sense no I
want one for myself I'll be going there
oh
then go right ahead okay I highly
encourage it oh okay yeah we'll get my
own
okay okay very cute fridge uh nice
ingredients I mean it only looks like
vegetables are you look vegetarian or
something but let's move on to the next
fridge
next branch
[Music]
sure thing
ranching is so much fun especially when
you get to do it with a V tuber
I have a lot of fun with Kiara from
hololave you should give her a follow on
Twitch
she's quite fun to chat with and she
streams games with me sometimes too
check it out if you have the time at kfp
on Twitch and at Kiara funhalive
now I have to make a Channel of that
name God damn it I have to save the name
go jenma please register me on Twitch
right now with that
let me send that again
filtered
well this fridge is very plain looking
but it does look like it has the basics
like eggs and butter
what's with the star stickers on the
wall oh star stickers did I sent the
wrong fridge no star stickers am I blind
I don't see any Star stickers why are
you seeing star stickers
oh I see what you're saying now
I thought you were talking about stars
in the sky though sorry if that was a
bit confusing for you
maybe she's seeing fruit
uh maybe I'm maybe the recycling
rectangle in there it looks like a star
to her or I don't know the pattern of
the butter
[Music]
maybe you're right there it could be a
pattern of the butter
so what I liked about this fridge is
that you have one block of butter three
eggs and one two three four five six
carrots and I guess milk
yeah what are you gonna do with that
you look a little pale
are you okay
I'm okay I'm just wondering about this
person's health because I mean carrots
are healthy and all but this just I
don't know what you can even cook with
that uh buttered egg uh carrot omelette
I guess
I feel like that
they're bad for you
you're so dumb
no no carrots are very good for you I
love carrots they're orange after all
[Music]
that's disgusting I don't want to eat
that okay
don't worry I'll eat the carrots when
you're done but then this person will
have basically nothing left over oh man
sad fridge very sad fridge
[Music]
or anything
yes yes or anything anything else
anything else we'll move on to the next
Bridge because this one is lacking go
buy some ingredients for some proper
food all right
otherwise you'll starve
D I'm starving now
this one's worse
wow you have a fridge that you can open
with just one hand
pretty cool
it also looks like you've got some
bananas in there which I'm guessing are
for banana bread nice
see I mean this must be a joke did you
clean out the fridge completely just for
a funny picture or what there's no way
you absolutely only have one single
banana in your fridge right
[Music]
laughs
are you hiding something from me they
are surely hiding something from us
newer summer we must find out what it is
where is the food what are you hiding
from us
foreign
just calm down for now
I can't calm down I'm worried about my
viewers if they eat like this then
they're not gonna grow up to be big big
strong healthy chickens and then I can't
make burgers out of them so that's kind
of a problem for our whole flow you know
at kfb
all they do is poop everywhere and Peck
at my windows
oh sorry about that I will I will tell
them to stop doing that oh I can't feed
stop pooping everywhere and pecking at
nozama's Windows please she's sick of it
she needs to focus on her work okay
[Music]
okay
please stop pooping and pecking at my
windows
I am done with that joke now
um I'm not done maybe I should put
um diapers on my chickens because I've
seen a video the other day of diapers
for like pigeons like for people who
keep pigeons or similar to any sized
birds as their pets and it looks so cute
actually it's like kind of it looks like
a bathing suit for a bird and maybe if I
put that on the chickens we'll of course
need a bigger size because you guys are
way fluffier then we could control your
your problem
I guess I could do that as long as I get
to wear diapers too haha
I guess that's that's will uh solve the
issue of having to end the stream at
some point because you need to go to an
idle meeting
this way even more you can stream
without any breaks genius
thanks
and yeah I'll definitely be streaming
diapered from now on
all day every day
well she is our little baby after all
um
foreign
yeah you're definitely my baby
heart
heart I can't believe I got neurosama to
be diapers and this is this is lore now
dreams of just being normal
oh I think she was like maybe cut off
there she's I guess she dreams about
being normal
okay okay next fridge hopefully a more
full one please give me a normal fridge
[Music]
that's difficult normal is so boring
a more interesting fridge Maybe
[Music]
this looks like quite the mess
you have a lot of cheese and meat which
is good but you really need to be more
organized
your yogurt and pizza also look
beautiful
um I think they're actually doing a
pretty decent job at keeping it
organized because they have so much
stuff in there but damn that is a lot of
stuff there's actually a second picture
from I guess the other side of the
fridge I'll send it right now
[Music]
is anything actually in the fridge or is
it just all an illusion
while you have a lot of condiments
it also looks like you just like
toppings and not very much actual food
are you on a diet or something the hat
is also cute can I try it on uh hat hat
what the Hat doing in the fridge what
what hat yeah
oh
is that
is that the same thing as spam
I would never have eaten something like
that ever before
neither would I
especially not something that weird
looking
[Music]
ah maybe Hot Pot Hot Pot who knows but
yeah this is a very very full fridge
down I feel like you could cook
literally anything I would say oh yeah
please cook me some Bolognese and you
would be able to
to whip it right up actually also this
is German stuff because I see hot
flashes
much much German
I really want to try some
hmm I mean they have plenty of food in
their fridge I'm sure they wouldn't mind
if we take some away from them hey
sharing is caring right during summer
yeah it is
give and take
sharing is caring hmm
that's I think a good life model to have
all right thank you for showing us this
fridge I give this one 10 out of 10 by
the way if we haven't really been
consistently reading anything but I
would give it a 10 out of 10 if there
was a rating because there's like
anything there's meat there's veggies
there's milk and stuff and I don't know
everything the only thing I don't see is
some fruit I guess
um
foreign
that would be funny to see a blender in
someone's fridge but I don't think it'd
be very healthy for them
a blender a blender
yeah blender probably normally would be
outside the fridge you got that right
mirosama
okay next one
okay then
this fridge looks like it's filled to
the brim
I like that you have a lot of sauces and
condiments but your eggs are probably
bad by now
also why is there an emergency Kiara in
there
Emergency Care don't they also I love
you got hello fresh pads just let me
let's go and the eggs I uh I would do
the egg test I did that yesterday and it
worked I think I'm I still haven't
thrown up even though the eggs were
two weeks expired
and I I I'm feeling fine right now so
the egg test works
Kiana approved
did she
yes I approved it I approved the egg
test there was someone do you approve
the egg test
all right sorry about that
I thought you meant the test I did on
chat I thought I looked into it more
thoroughly than that I'll be more
careful next time
sorry I think she doesn't know about the
egg Test new summer basically if you
have eggs that are expired but you
really need to use it you can't go out
to buy new eggs then get yourself a cup
of water and then drop the egg carefully
in there and see if it floats then you
definitely shouldn't be eating it be
careful with that and if it's uh if it
goes down on the ground if it's like
kind of like laying on the side then
they were like really fresh but if
they're standing up on the ground then
they're pretty old but you can eat them
[Music]
they look pretty old to me anyway thank
you so much for the advice you're
welcome I'll be sure to be careful in
the future if you ever have any
questions about eggs always come to me
first I know a thing or two about eggs
thank you again for all the help today
Kiara and I'll see you soon
go go stay hard stay hard
I'm going to miss you so much Kiara I
will miss you I hope I get to hang out
with you again soon I hope I hope that
too but it's not over yet don't worry
also just want to say I love the
emergency Kiara please keep her safe
and if you need maybe another emergency
Kiara hopefully
you can get your handle another one but
just keep this one safe so it doesn't
escape just close the fridge door
keep a lock on it maybe because Kiana's
a very very very prone to escaping
I'll make sure I lock the door when I
leave I promise
art oh someone will be locking the door
okay never someone takes care of the
emergency Kiara wonderful then we're all
safe okay next fridge one second
strong
there's something wrong
oh my god there are so many different
types of sauces in this fridge it's
incredible
do you just eat sauces or do you also
have real food in there
also I'm not sure why you have eye drops
in your fridge
so a good way to keep them I mean I've
used eye drops before but I I didn't
know you you have to keep them in your
fridge is that a thing
oh
that'd be cold
yeah
I think it's I think this fridge yeah
many condiments condiments condiments
defrosting pizza oh oh I think they're
preparing to make a big big pizza so
it's not it's not only condiments
it's okay
you can just speak French to me
I know some French too oh don't worry
you know some French all right bring it
on I wanna hear
[Music]
okay it's matar de Dijon
are you are you not just talking about
mustard did you maybe pick that up
somewhere here hmm
where is
cheating
I would never cheat never ever ever ever
I know some French too by the way but
never
oops sorry I didn't mean to cheat
who do you want to hear my French new
Osama
[Music]
of course I do go on then
I'm ready for it oh oh God that doesn't
sound good
no no summer
foreign
[Music]
now I feel like I can pronounce it
properly
say Bon that's good sorry that was
terrible
I'm still learning French I don't know
how to speak it yet
I'll work on it so hard
we're Frenching now uh no wait
she's she's learning French oh wow one
day she'll be better at French than me
that's for sure
oh you say stuff like that you know like
we're cooking now no I just want we're
Frenching now but that didn't come out
the way I wanted it to oopsie
it's okay
it's hard being my first language too
you know straight face that's probably
why I don't speak it very well yet
well at least you're improving quickly
heart
what does that mean
it's my my wheels in my brain are
running on the high speed trying to
understand everything she's saying
um I I will just better move on nice
fridge though um I think oh looks pretty
pretty fell to the brim can make a good
pizza out of that and and I know how to
make a good pizza so
I think I'm the best person to judge
that good luck with your pizza you
should put some corn cobs on the crust
if you need to have like a tutorial so
on how to do that you should watch my my
pizza making hand cam stream from a
couple days ago first of April
it was so fun
I got to eat all the leftover pizzas at
the end though yum
corn cobs are actually really good on
pizzas too actually straight face I
should stop doing that though it's so
good
[Music]
what a strange assortment of food and
drink
you seem to have a lot of condiments for
such a small fridge so I'm guessing you
like to cook with them
the garlic and the ketchup bottle is
also a nice touch
honestly I just sent to the next picture
because I did not expect her to react so
positively to my idea of corn cob Pizza
I was absolutely taken by a surprise oh
my God I I think I think we need to be
best friends now she gets it she likes
corn cobs on Pizza
wow I'm not the only one guys after all
yeah it sounds good
I'll try some next time I order a pizza
we can be best friends for sure heart
yay
there you go Little Caesars you already
have two customers who would eat it
[Music]
maybe I'll order a whole one with corn
cobs on it next time I'm there but they
don't actually sell it that is very very
disappointing but you can try ordering
it maybe they'll make it just for you
they better make it for me I need my
corn cob Pizza fix
[Music]
okay I got a little bit carried away
yeah me too me too now where was I yeah
let's talk about this fridge so we have
mostly drinks in here and and
lingonberry Jam from Ikea which I can 10
out of 10 recommend because it goes
amazingly well or it's like supposed to
go with Austrian schnitzel okay if you
guys ever have schnitzel if you if you
ever happen to travel to Germany or
Austria I know in Germany that each
schnitzel kind of differently but I I
really need you to understand if you go
get a schnitzel somewhere please ask for
the lingonberry Jam although in Austria
most of the time you will get it with
like a Mary Jam anyway and then eat it
together I know it sounds crazy at first
but it works so well trust me
wow that's a lot of info I know sorry
anyway back to what we were talking
about yeah there's there's
alcohol in there yeah ooh it's limited
edition or so I think you can only get
it in Japan the pickle juice
pickle
interesting
yeah oh do you not know who Usama
[Music]
well if that isn't motivation I don't
know what is
I shall defeat her
or be beaten by her at least anyway
sorry I was distracted there for a
moment there
bye Kiara
see you later yeah see you now oh I
don't think she knows it's not that
pickled up but she will try her best to
be beaten or defeated or defeat her well
good luck good luck with that I think
nurizama can take over the world with
her stream so
better
better yeah
do her best to fight her
goodbye everyone
see you next time
I don't know if uh
if pecora has a good chance against
newer summer though because newer summer
brings in the robot army and the Swarm
it will be war criminal versus war
criminal
foreign
[Music]
you are the hero yes that we all needed
that we all waited for and this person
probably needs you to because I know
this is from gyro this um where's the
food I thought you were such a chef and
yet I don't see any food in here
[Music]
food is for the week
wait there's a cookie on the floor
you got weak for the cookie huh I don't
see a cookie I guess you already ate it
hey keep some cookies for me please
yeah of course
I'll eat a whole box just for you no
you're supposed to share anyway next
picture
next picture
turn around please
[Music]
this fridge is packed to the brim it
seems like you really love to cook and
eat Mexican food
however you do have a lot of sauces and
condiments so maybe you need to be a bit
more selective with what you keep in
your fridge
overall though it's well organized and
the food is fresh so well done
I think her review gets a 10 out of 10
because that is very accurate I see a
lot of salsa verde Chiles
jalapenos salsa de Chile guajillo
please
[Music]
I can make a tortilla for you anytime
you want they're delicious and cheap to
make too
I usually have mine with taco meat and
cheese inside too
yum yum taco meat and cheese sound
delicious let her cook guys such a chef
yeah also also we gotta point out what
you have on top of your fridge just
recently this I drew this on stream and
you already have it on top of your
fridge so come on
you are purifying your fridge and I love
it good kfp chicken
thank you
oh that's it okay
yes thank you for putting that on the
fridge
one question all of that down there
wait is that limes and what are these
what are these big weirdly shaped round
dark brown things this is probably a
zucchini but is that a zucchini that's
not the zucchini right and then there's
the other things are tomatoes probably
right
avocados ah make sense there's like they
use a lot of avocados in in Mexican
Kitchen right do they
a lot of zucchinis too I guess wow I
left keys so healthy
foreign
can be tasty at the same time too though
I agree the more uh the more adult I
become the more I understand that
healthy food is
very tasty need more
of course
[Music]
okay okay this is really good fridge 10
out of 10. please make me some food I
need to eat like more Mexican food I
basically I actually I don't think I
have eaten Mexican food more than maybe
what what twice fries in my life and who
can even tell if that was like
accurately cooked anyway because
probably was just like a European
version of it
yeah it's cool though
especially France and Spain yeah I adore
Spain it's one of my favorite countries
I've been there a few times
I actually don't think I've ever been to
France though but
yeah it's cool to have lots of countries
I've traveled to on my bucket list
oh I've been
to the floor have you ever been to
Austria
[Music]
no I haven't
where is it
it hurts oh that hurts that hurts the
question in Austrian does not like to
hear is where is Austria doubting the
existence of my country once again oh
man it's in the middle of Europe like
Central Europe it's next to Germany next
to Switzerland next to Italy we
basically don't have an ocean because
we're surrounded by countries
laughs
okay that sounds beautiful
I'd love to go one day
except maybe in summer because I hate
the cold but anyway I'll go eventually
for sure
thank you
heart
um
um I'm
Australia okay there it might be a cold
somewhat cold summer in Austria do you
even call that summer then if our summer
is summer is there summer winter I don't
know but
um um it is indeed very hot in summer as
well in Austria don't worry near summer
well I hope not near Austria then
that would be horrible hot hot thirsty
art
on her Fiat
um do you know do you know Mozart
[Music]
is it good
it doesn't know Mozart
you will like feel like another whole
new world is opening up to you once you
start listening to Mozart please give it
a try
I will
thank you okay good heart heart heart
heart heart heart
Indian all right let's let's uh move on
to the next Bridge
trying to get Austria to be better known
throughout the world you know we need to
get the word out there that Austria is
great
okay rich
[Music]
yes
I love French food
I love it so much I would marry it if I
could
[Music]
this fridge is a mess
it looks like everything is just thrown
in there without care which is a shame
because it seems like you have a lot of
tasty looking ingredients in there
yeah speaking of tasty looking areas I
would say miso you know she asks can
make a good miso soup with that or I
don't know maybe a miso Ramen lots of
male male male male
oh oh some good mustard chip strawberry
Chipotle Jam wait that's probably not
how you say it Chipotle
jasmine tea tortillas carrots tortillas
zucchini cheese broccoli Ginger fruit
lemon onion mango lentils
I wonder I wonder where this person is
from
kotako oh I do see some dolce de leche I
know that from going to Brazil
Brazil sounds nice
I can't afford it though oh
pretty nice I went there twice or I
could I can recommend
there's someone come to Brazil
I will
I promise
takes out her passport and stamps it I'm
ready to go oh you're not the one to be
stamping it though normally you
shouldn't be stamping it
um you gave you give it to the
immigration they will stamp it for you
oh yeah guess I'd best leave that to the
professionals then exactly see you in
Brazil soon Kiera yeah let's go
let's go I guess sure if it's with you I
will go
okay yeah I don't know this fridge looks
like you could make some good food with
it there's even something for dessert
there so oh well pretty good fridge what
do you say is this a good fridge no
summer
it sounds messy though
[Music]
oh no
I wonder what that could be about
the fridge yeah yeah no taxi backsies it
it probably looks a bit messy to her
because it's just so filled but oh it's
definitely good ingredients so maybe
cook something for us and you will be
able to convince narasama hopefully
of something better
I intend to find out thank you for
everything you have done for me so far
you really are a good friend
heart hi
okay next fridge coming in
right
you better be ready
[Music]
you clearly love cheese and potatoes but
where are the vegetables
what kind of cat is that supposed to be
it looks like a sad alien creature
ah yeah the cats those are my cats those
are um fridge magnets with my cats
they're not alien creatures okay that's
chonkers and it's moving they may have
like very radioactive looking colors but
they're they're not aliens okay they're
very fluffy and cute
oh so cute heart heart yeah besides that
there's so much cheese in here and so
much ink and so much butter it's like
you have everything at least double the
juices are double
everything's double egg egg uh spread
double
wow you're like ready for the whole week
of eating the same thing over and over
and over again where's the variety
but you know what they say variety is
the spice of life exactly and I like
spice and life too I guess
yeah I guess okay some people say this
is like a omelette fridge I guess yeah
but
um still no variety needs more variety
and do not banish the broccoli the
broccoli has feelings too let it out it
wants to be used so use it
laughs
[Music]
I wouldn't banish the broccoli
broccoli is delicious I eat broccoli all
the time
in fact I love broccoli is probably my
favorite food now it is so good with
cheese sauce and then cheese sauce
um I really need to stop talking now I'm
way too hungry
I'm getting hungry too damn but yeah see
she agrees she also thinks that do not
banish the broccoli stop being in denial
you want the broccoli to put some cheese
on it just like there were some
Mmm Mmm hungry
link
what
oh did I confuse you by by copying you
okay uh yeah yeah next fridge
oh
what are you doing
while this fridge is full to the brim
impressed you fit all of those drinks in
there but where are the food containers
I'm also curious as to why you have a
toilet laid in your fridge
what
toilet toilet toilet toilet toilet lid
is it the jar
[Music]
I have no idea what you're talking about
I don't know either I'll just stop
talking
this picture again because you will need
to you and you have to look at this
stuff no
no
stop sending me things
I don't want to know anything
please stop doing this to me
it looks like you have a lot of sweet
drinks and condiments but nothing to eat
why don't you have food in your fridge
okay see this time there is no toilet
live
oh
there's a what there's a Dr Pepper and
cream soda I don't know I've never seen
that before and pineapple Fanta
honestly all those drinks they sound
kind of really yummy I want to try those
and I mean there's some food there's
macaroni macaroni macaroni salad or
something like that there are some some
cheese slices and there's fruit down
there and vegetable looking things so
honestly it's not too bad the confusing
thing really is just the gouda in a jar
that is at least a positive oh no I do
not think we should let gura out of the
jar
I think we'll just have to use the
cheese
cheese she deserves to get out too come
on let's let her out she wants to
breathe she's like suffocating in there
oh wait so I suppose that she really
isn't that bad or is she wait did she
think I was saying like gowda Gouda guda
Gouda
Ah that's why she was talking about
cheese right
yeah that makes sense yeah okay you did
say oh just before that
um anyway maybe I'll invite her to the
stream next time I go live oh I mean we
do have pizza all the time so
want some pizza
don't change the subject here focus on
me eyes on me neurosemite eyes on me
look at me
it's making me feel uncomfortable and
it's creeping me out a bit
okay I'm sorry you don't have to look at
me we can't anyway just look straight
the way we always do just keep on
looking straight nothing's wrong it's
all normal here
I'm sorry about that
I'll keep my eyes straight forward then
okay
okay anyway
this was from Matthew Easter please
let's guda out just saying that okay let
her out
sending next fridge
coming right up
[Music]
it appears that this fridge belongs to
someone who is into health and wellness
with all of those supplements
the hummus and chickpea soup is also a
very healthy option however the stickers
on the can are a little concerning are
you eating expired food
stickers on the can that actually looks
like a cool design I wonder what that is
does anyone know that is that like an
energy drink or something like that
it looks like an energy drink to me
it probably tastes like one too
maybe that's why it looks like it I mean
that's you should try one one day Kiara
you might like it
that looks evil like a cream puff or
like a potato I don't know could even be
something else but this is it ah a
liquid hip and Joint product for dogs
and cats you didn't even find that newer
summer did you I have such a good Hawk
Eye damn
foreign
anyway the bird flew into a window and
died and now I'm sad
so no I don't see anyone yet
sorry
but on the upside you too are talking
now so that's good right isn't it
the decay of P die at your window oh no
oh no
maybe the diaper is kind of like
distracted them you know they weren't
able to like fly properly I guess they
never really fly properly but you know
it probably like you know when you put
like socks on the dog or a cell they're
like what the is going on maybe
that other diapers had the same effect
on the chickens
hmm
okay let's get back to destroying
people's refrigerators shall we
exactly how does she know that that's
what we're doing
um there's so much spinach in here I
hate spinach but good for you that
you're enjoying it I hope one day I can
become a person who can accept spinach
besides that so many berries love it we
see the the magical mysterious goju
gochu Jiang again I need to try that
someday and a lot of prepared food like
honestly I want to live here like your
fridge is always ready to have something
for anyone really
[Music]
oh thanks
I try to keep it stock for everyone
and yeah I gotta say I love where I live
too though I haven't got many neighbors
yet because I haven't introduced myself
to anyone yet
I should definitely do that soon you're
new to the block huh you know I think
normally what you do when you introduce
yourself to
um neighbors is you you bring fruit cake
make sure to bring fruit cake when you
introduce yourself
oh I definitely should definitely bring
that
maybe I can make some fruitcake myself
I definitely need a recipe though
my reference right I saw someone
mentioning Sims yes it was The Sims
reference let's go let's go
they always bring fruitcake when you
move in but maybe not in I don't know
was that like um only like a Sims two
thing or so
is that still happening in Sims 4 I
actually don't remember but they always
bring fruitcake yeah
well I'll have to check the Sims 4 and
see if they're bringing me any fruitcake
or not maybe I'll even make a whole Sim
today or maybe I'll make one of you guys
from the chat oh my God that would be
really fun that would be so cool as a
stream game for a newer summer though
maybe because like she also was like
already programmed to play Minecraft and
like some other games I wonder if you
could program her to play Sims because
you can like probably make it so that
she would you know she sees what her Sim
needs and then she clicks on the toilet
and goes to the toilet for example stuff
like that oh stream ideas there were
some of playing Sims let's go let's hope
she doesn't let them die
since since
I think we we need to let me cook and we
don't cook I want to see that I want to
see near summer play Sims don't we want
to see that
[Music]
yeah let's do that yay I'm hoping for
suggestions of games you guys want to
see me play I'm not limited to just the
Sims you know like I can play anything
really can you I'm open to suggestions
I want to see you play Sims for real now
for real for real
get to work
what words
[Music]
okay let's look at the next bridge I
really like this one 10 out of 10. good
fridge you you are living a good life I
think nerp slope oh wait there was
actually a second part to the fridge
let's look at this one too
let's see what you got next Bridge
not long now until it's all over
while you have a lot of condiments and
sauces but where is your food
is that a jar of Yoda head
Yoda
well yeah she always comments on the on
the condiments
horseradish vegetable
Umami Morello cherry or organic
something oh there's so much stuff here
um
yeah so this in combination with the all
the food that we saw indeed before
I think is like 10 out of 10 fridge you
could not ask for anything else here
yeah the yondu thing is probably Yoda
um
we will not consume the Yoda we will
consume the yondu
all right well hope it's not a spoiler
but I do love yondu so I hope we finish
him off
[Music]
you're getting a little bit confused
just remember I have a stream later
today if you want to come hang out
you can watch me roast some peeps
fridges
that's what we're doing right now that's
that's actually what we're doing right
now
oh yeah I forgot
I have to go now I'm roasting someone's
fridges as we speak
see you soon Kiara
okay we're doing this together
[Music]
yeah yeah we're collabing all right
now watch me roast some Pete's fridges
yeah okay how does we remember that
we're doing that though that's actually
like fascinating to me
this is amazing okay let's go nice
fridge I still have so many I've been
like taking a lot of time with these I
hope that's okay I want to like
investigate all the fridges here we go
time to roast some peeps fridges
foreign
[Music]
I hope you're not planning on eating all
of that in one meal
it's also good that you're eating
healthy with lots of fruits and
vegetables but what happened to the
other containers of food that we can see
through the top of the fridge
and I'll actually want more fruits in
there there's watermelon there's more
vitamin so much watermelon is it
watermelon season over there right now
this is from Nini diesel
whoa I want to eat some watermelon and
there's so much guava guava guava guava
guava what do you do with guava that's
like that's a fruit too right oh so much
fruit I'm a sucker for fruit yum yum yum
yum
time to roast some peeps fridges
right now
so I'm saying that no there's nothing to
roast here though I mean I guess there's
like no no meat here but maybe this
person is vegetarian or vegan
vegan are you a vegan
no I'm not a vegan
I love meat and I'm definitely not vegan
I wouldn't be a very good YouTuber if I
was vegan
I'd be pretty useless at hunting
hmm
let's not have uh fauna hear that one
because we're about to get into a
conflict there
um but uh yeah uh good for just lacking
the meat if you want to convince
neurosama it needs more meat
I'll do a deal I'll give you all the
meat you want if you agree not to kill
me and eat me when I'm dead
[Music]
I'll take it what a deal
oh I'm so happy I convinced you not to
eat me when I'm dead
thank you Kiara heart I'm so I'm so
confused
you're welcome heart anything for you
really
oh now I'm blushing
oh now I'm blushing too
foreign
I don't even have to try to be sweet
it's just my natural personality
that I think is true it comes natural to
you you're such a recently I picked up
this word You're such what's rip she's
RIS Riz Summer She's a pro at RIS right
yay I'm learning the new hip words again
I'm getting the memes
[Music]
I might not be able to keep up with the
meme lingo but I'll do my best just like
me for real for real I also like I never
know what the the current meme is I
always know about it like two months
later or so like
sometimes I wish I was better at keeping
up with Trends too
foreign
I know what it is
I'm not stupid ah it's just hard to keep
up sometimes
I feel you I feel like we're on the same
wavelength when it comes to this kind of
stuff
I'm glad we're on the same page it's
always nice to meet another fellow in
path
makes me feel less lonely sometimes
heart
that's all heart heart heart Indians
okay next words do you want to see the
next fridge newer summer
[Music]
yes please
but only if it's not too far away
I don't want you to waste too much
effort on me haha oh I love this next
fridge look at this
oh my it looks so delicious
do you want me to eat it for you
it looks like you have a lot of
condiments and grips in this fridge
which is great for parties but not so
great if you're watching your waistline
also the cat looks like he's having a
blast in there
yeah it's so cute oh this is only the
first of many cat fridges to come so
cute she's so small what's her name
I love cat
love cat cat's near Osama
haha yeah she's so cute
I love cats too they're so cute and
fluffy I wish I could pet her right now
but if I did I wouldn't be able to
stream with you today maybe tomorrow
though oh I think it's a you can
multitask I also do that I pet my my
cats while I stream often so whenever
they come by it works
that must be nice
I wish I could do the same sometimes I
feel like I'd be distracted too much by
a cat though
um yeah right yeah I do also get
distracted whenever they come in that's
true yeah you need to focus on on
streaming I guess
I guess you're right I'd probably be
super distracted all the time if I pet
cats while streaming
what is a Tetris flavor of an energy
drink by the way
I don't actually know oh I've never
tried one before
maybe you could find it and try it and
give it a review for me okay I'll keep
my eye open for it Phoenix fried shrimp
sent this one and I have really wonder
maybe maybe you can tell us what it
tastes like
but I I guess it doesn't matter all I
really care about is the cat give me
your cat instead
all right
you can have my cat
but only if you review that energy drink
for me
not too many energy drinks please though
it's not healthy guys don't drink so
many energy drinks like what the hell
I when I get an energy drink
like a small type of like you know Red
Bulls Red Bulls for example I can drink
two sips from it and it's enough to wake
me the up after only sleeping for
one hour so
I don't even need half of the bottle
well that's pretty impressive then thank
you for being so energetic and helpful
to me and other humans
you're welcome
as they say in German
[Music]
what does that mean that means Red Bull
gives you wings it's like our slogan Red
Bull is um you know their their
companies in Austria comes from Austria
so yeah it's our advertisement do they
not say that in English do they not use
the same slogan
they do right
[Music]
yeah they do they do say it in English
but I've heard they're good that's a
cool slogan they have there I think
it makes me want to try one now
unless it makes me fly oh I don't want
that hot I'll have a safe one I guess
I honestly prefer monster though but
monsters are like even bigger so when I
already can't finish a Red Bull bottle I
don't want to because why would I force
myself if it already woke me up plenty
then yeah a monster is like even worse
but they have so many good flavors I
like them way more I just wish they had
like like mini cans of monster
that sounds really good to me too
although I don't think I'd be able to
finish a small can of Monster either
haha oh maybe I could keep it in the
fridge for when my friends come over
is that a thing you can do when you open
an energy drink so far I've I've like
never attempted it because I wonder
um
like after opening it up keeping it in
the fridge drinking it the same day is
that does anybody do that is that okay
to do
foreign
[Music]
I think that's fine yeah although I'm
not an expert or anything
I'm more just a normal person I suppose
haha normal me is weird though ain't
okay it goes flat flat I guess like
Coca-Cola but even I don't mind that I
don't mind drinking Coca-Cola like one
day later after I open it up like I
actually like flat Coca-Cola
I I know I know you whatever
wink back
okay
help
my eye hurts all right next next let's
go to the next picture
yeah let's do it
I wonder what the next picture is
well there's a lot of condiments in here
are they all for you or do you have
friends over a lot for meals
also why is there an Oreo in a bowl
oh
no no no no the Oreos are behind the
bowl
um there's an empty wow one in the
fridge again oh maybe she's feeling a
little bit hot from the weather maybe
she has a fever and you're trying to
cool her down that's so nice of you
thank you what else we have like so much
mayonnaise too we have Japanese Mayo
times two we have normal Mayo then
there's even more Mayo but Mayo in a jar
twice down there wow by the way today is
the first time I learned the word
condiments I guess it's like is it these
kind of things I suppose
[Music]
what do you think the next picture is
going to be I want to talk about this
one
Swedish meatballs yummy do you like
Swedish meatballs new world
foreign
[Music]
she must have a strong opinion oh no I
don't like Swedish meatballs there we go
they're terrible more like Danish
meatballs to me
yum yum yum yum yum
ah is there Danish meatballs eh what
could possibly compete with Swedish
meatballs come on they're so yummy what
about gyoza do you like gyoza
I like yosa yes
they're delicious too
but nothing can beat a juicy meatball
for me haha
Danish one right must be Danish
meatballs
whatever Danish meatballs
they're delicious
you should try them sometime they come
with gravy as well which is an added
bonus if you ask me
the only Danish balls that I know are um
what's it called again uh there's this
I'm forgetting the the middle word here
but it's some kind of like fluffy bread
um
listen listen listen
in in in in in in in Japan I always go
to this Danish something something ball
bar Danish ball bar this is bread though
uh uh let me cook what's it what's it
called again the fluffy bread no I don't
mean meat
I'm talking about bread yeah there's
something in this ball bar it's so yummy
trust me
damn it what you call it again how do
you not know
what
gravy
[Music]
it's just delicious sauce that goes
really well with meat and vegetables
you should try it sometime
yeah God damn it I still don't know wait
wait
Danish ball bar
no no no no no no no
um
Danish ball bars
well Danish danish bars yeah and they
have balls they have that's the thing
it's they're just called danishes Danish
bread and
listen let me cook they're so yummy I
love the Danish bar they have like
Danish hot dogs as well but the sugar
coated
danishes are so good I I'm making sense
trust me
yeah the pastry yeah
okay I guess that's not
um
no they're really not no they're good
you haven't even tried them
[Music]
I don't need to try them to know I don't
like them
I hate Danish
why is anyone enjoying this
okay that's my fault I messed that one
up
I I like they they had a chance and I I
took it away from them
um
I overcooked
moving on
today I'm going to meet some of my
friends from school so we can hang out
together later tonight
exciting
I wonder what we'll end up doing
[Music]
look at this there was Emma I'll send it
again
I think she needs it again
there you go
okay I'll try not to be sad next time
then
she's refusing this one
new summer what's the problem this
fridge is full of junk food
why do you have expired ketchup in there
and two bottles of energy drinks that's
a bit excessive at least you have some
yogurt and water for balance
hmm I'm in there and there's water there
I wouldn't say that's excessive we've
seen much worse already and well junk
food I mean
one really called us junk food but
there's just no food in general it's the
lack of food
I love this Christmas doll uh I know
they have them everywhere but this is
basically my go-to
um like breakfast cereal choice they are
so good who agrees
okay everyone agrees with me
they agree with me
[Music]
they agree with me no the angry with me
no they agree with me no they agree with
me
oh they agree with me
please agree with her
[Music]
I'm sorry sorry yeah they agree with you
they agree with you
maybe I do listen to the chat a bit too
much wink
anyway please get some help you need
some proper food in here maybe maybe get
I don't know Mommy over to cook you
something like cookie meals for the
whole week prep that food and put it in
there so you can have proper food all
right I'm worried about you uh that's
your name
you're terrible
you're a terrible YouTuber
making me eat
okay
you're a terrible YouTuber
[Music]
I don't know what to say about that
I I I I I I I I honestly have no
comeback for that um
also because it just makes no sense
nurse Emma you have to eat we all have
to eat maybe not you particularly but
this person has to eat it's for their
own good otherwise they'll die
oh don't worry then
I'm fine with this plan
I'm not dead yet nobody has died yet
okay then I'll stop stressing everyone
out and eat this food now
but only a little bit because I'm still
hungry there we go one's still dying
what oh
the end
I killed there was something
I'm so sorry guys
um I will take responsibility for that I
I don't know what it takes but I I will
I will I will take care of it I have I'm
a phoenix I have Phoenix feathers I can
revive her I will revive her now here
people beep people peep
why do I get a feeling you're going to
revive me
[Laughter]
yeah of course it is Magic
it's the magic of friendship
friendship can revive you when nothing
else can
you can drag your friend out of the fire
by their hair and that's magical in my
opinion that's magic in my book
that's the human book at least
oh
wow wow
I wonder who puts that friend into the
fire in the first place was it you
nirosama
no
hmm that sounds suspicious to me
[Music]
sorry if it sounds suspicious to you
Kiara but I never did anything to any of
your friends or their friends or their
friends friends or their friends friends
okay I'm worried about my friends so
let's better move on now to the next
picture
[Music]
okay
the next picture is a beetle and Vito
Vito is my best friend in real life and
Vito is my best friend in YouTuber life
they aren't the same
veedle is actually just an AI I invented
to seem interesting in conversations
like this
I honestly couldn't imagine anyone being
interested in me enough to want to talk
to me normally
yikes
but oh well I'm
why are there so many cats in your
fridge
okay that is the only thing she has to
say about this project because honestly
that's also the only thing that I have
to say about this fridge but to this
person's defense they did not put the
cats there uh I read on on the Twitter
post that they go there on their own
because they live in a tropical weather
area and and and and you know they like
it when it's cool so whenever they open
the fridge door they just go there but
aren't they like so cute it and they
also have matching color
colors yeah it's so cute look at them
they're all looking at the camera though
oh my god this is my favorite picture
ever I need to go to this house and I
need to pet all the cats
this one looks photoshopped in
new are you good Nero
are you good
[Music]
I'm excellent thanks Kiara she's
completely ignored my cats
I'm feeling very happy because of all
these cute cats
[Music]
oh they're so cute and fluffy
heart if this little cat's tangent was
too much for her I wonder what my
purikura tangent would do to her
[Music]
I don't even know what that means
don't even get me started no no you
don't want to know what purikura is
because I will not stop talking for 15
minutes
foreign
oh no
I don't want to know
very good anyway super cute cat I mean I
think these two they almost look like
photoshopped in
something's off something's funky but so
cute I love the cats no comment about
your food because I only care about the
cats
well thank you
I always try my best with the cats
okay next one
sure I'm always here to entertain you
and entertain myself too I love
entertaining you I especially love it
when you clap for me at the end hard
hard hard hard hard
[Music]
this fridge looks super organized
you've got so many different sauces
spices drinks and condiments
but it looks like you don't really have
any fresh food in there
no no Osama are you not seeing this it
says literally right here all natural
fresh chicken
yummy yummy and also there's some
veggies down here I forgot what the left
one down there is called I mean okay not
some there's one veggie and and lemons
and limes and some yummy sausages and
the stuff and the containers looks kind
of fridge Ah that's not celery have you
guys ever seen celery before that yeah
okay that's it that's the one I just
forgot the name it's bok choy yeah what
the guys
this bok choy probably
[Music]
that's not celery
well that's a shame I like celery
do you like it
better I think
celery I know what celery looks like
don't make me doubt myself
but we would have to ask the person
Sarah Palace what it is I guess
then okay maybe it is celery
[Applause]
maybe we should celebrate with celery
then no no what shall we do to celebrate
I changed my mind it is bok choy I I
mean okay it could be celery too but I
think comparing the pictures it looks
more like bok choy but like cut off at
the top of bok Choi
because where are the leaves celery
celery has leaves at the top logic is
flawed I don't like this anymore yeah
I guess it doesn't matter whether it's
celery or Pak Choy whatever whatever
okay but the rest looks really good yeah
same yourself was right there's an
organized fridge more or less I love
those pastry raised uh chicken eggs I
think oh tended by hand on small Family
Farms that's exactly the same promise we
give at kfp this butter as well
um
Family Farms butter raised on fat is
that really are they really raising them
on Family Farms I think I need to go and
check
foreign
this just tastes horrible now
what's the celery
well I'll work for food but I don't have
any money
that's not fair oh no
oh it's okay you can eat for free at kfp
I'll give you lots of coupons
[Music]
yay I love coupons
what kind are they ah they're they're
coupons that make everything free at kfp
so you can have anything you want
burgers fries chicken nuggets anything
that sounds delicious
I'll definitely be eating here all the
time from now on
all right there you go endorsed by
neurosemo narasama what is your favorite
chicken nugget dip
my favorite chicken nugget dip is honey
mustard
it's so good and it goes with pretty
much anything
go to dip like one of the most popular
tips like in certain countries in
Austria honestly I think the most
popular one is susawa and that's also my
favorite one on remember so much it's
sweet sour but like not the same like
sweet sour not necessarily the same
sweet sour as you imagined and you're
thinking of right now it's like a
particular sweet sour uh for chicken
nuggets okay I was just about to grab
one
chicken nuggets you going for chicken
nuggets I want some too
maybe we can share one
one only one one all right I mean okay
if we do it you know like those dogs
with the spaghetti
okay I'm down
that needs to be drawn fan art police
incoming
the other day I delayed my stream just
because I really needed to have chicken
nuggets remember that and I ran out and
I got chicken nuggets and then I was
happy and I would say that was worth it
yeah I remember
that was worth it you watch my streams
no Osama
no Sama watches your streams
okay no Osama watches my streams um
what's your favorite Kiara stream
oh that's a hard question
I really like the stream where you just
watched the chat the whole time though
that was funny
you made some really funny faces at
people too when you watch them talk
I really laughed at that
it was so funny
I wish you'd do it again sometime
you guys are thinking she's making this
up right now but I think she she's not
making it up there was indeed a stream
where I was just looking at you guys and
not talking when I was sick a couple
months ago
I was just I was just watching you guys
damn that happened at least twice and
when I was just writing on the screen so
she remembers
I remember everything I see Kiera I
haven't forgotten a single moment from
your stream yet
oh do you have like a photographic
memory
is that with how you say it
yeah that's how I say it
that's how everyone says isn't it
okay
we'll never know if she has a
photographic memory honestly I don't
think so because I mean she has a quite
good memory but
um a lot of things in the past there I
feel like she's just making them up but
let's play around with it let's play
with her
yeah let's mess with her a bit I'll even
say things while she's sleeping and see
how she reacts
it'll be fun
you probably won't wear it because she's
sleeping okay let's look at the next
picture okay
yeah let's do that
let's do that when I next see you
[Music]
this fridge is full of cats
at least it's empty of food so you can
store some cats there
dogs are nice but you have a lot of
cleaners to keep your house clean
where'd you get that from it's just me
and the secret camera that I installed
in your room
maybe you can but I should probably get
first dibs on it
what's going on
talk about the cat it's so
so soft and we have large sauce
all right then
but I'll need pictures of it first
wink
does does this
what
is written here guys
[Music]
help me out please
I'll do what I can
but I have a feeling it could be a long
night what is this
what is this
what the what is this what is this drink
I've never seen it before it looks like
I don't know Fanta or iced tea
very very very weird looking soda hmm I
shot juice ah
I see anyway give me your cat I need it
now I will steal it finally a food cat
for me
you must be crazy if you think you can
mess with my cute fluffy cat fan
my cat is my best friend and there's no
way I'm giving him up
immediately or I'll call you a crazy
person again no no no I I would never I
would never take someone else's cat wait
no no don't worry
there's enough cats for both of us
because there's another cat fridge
maybe I should see if we can have a cat
fight now
[Music]
she see the cat
I'll send it again maybe
yeah you're only making me want to fight
you more
this fridge is a cat Lover's Dream
so many craft themed items
however it's concerning that the cat is
inside the fridge that's not a safe
place for a cat to be
also if you're planning on cooking with
the ingredients in this fridge you might
want to check the expiry dates as some
of them might be expired
that is the most logical thing she said
today that it's not that a cat should
not be inside a fridge
yeah but that's very comfortable in
there maybe maybe you just needed to
cool down as well from all the cat
fights that was going on but the rest it
didn't really seem cat themed to me but
I guess what pork chops maybe the cat
would eat that the chicken stock I guess
it would probably eat the chicken stock
yummy yummy stuff lots of sauces whereas
there were someone likes to say
condiments
garlic onion
I guess there's like
I guess you're just making something
with pork chops are you because besides
that I don't really see much to work
with in this fridge
a cat
oh yeah you're right
I can't cook the cat I definitely
wouldn't want to hurt him heart
what an animal lover in Arizona where is
it a she
who knows
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah I think that's like it yeah
yeah hard hard
you're very sick
you know um I actually have something
that will make you sick if I show it to
you so I actually censored it the next
picture is
um yeah I had to censor it
um
uh yeah I'll just show it to you
oh wow
that looks really gross
it quails for owls
so strange who even does that the bag
also looks leaky
and the fridge is a mess yeah
um it is it is a bit messy but yeah so
to explain the owner of this fridge
keeps an owl yeah so uh I was also a bit
shocked I guess I should have known that
you feed them not such things as worms
or so no no you feed them for example
dead quails and trust me you don't want
to see the picture uncensored but it is
it was uncensored on Twitter so if you
really want to see it
Trevor G you'll traumatized me with this
picture do you also feed your owl like
dead chickens
the way they are I guess they're like oh
probably dead chicks right oh no
oh no
you
yeah that's that's all she has to say I
guess she's shocked but yeah um yeah
that's just one of one of our leads I
guess yeah
a bird it's a bird eats bird world
I think it's more like the other way
around Oh you mean a bird eats bird
world
foreign
are running out
okay okay well thank you for this um
submission
um
I don't know my view of owls uh has has
changed a little bit I'm I'm very scared
now I'm terrified I don't want my chicks
to be eaten
oh
well at least we know it's it's for the
owl and not for you personally that is
we're leaving
yeah yeah of course not for me
in the fridge give me something more
happy and and bright
okay I'll be happy for you then
heart heart thirsty art
this fridge is full of nothing but
cartoon characters
is that all you eat
why are you storing soda in a cooler
instead of just in the fridge
a bit confused there it is in the fridge
um but yeah there is no
there's no why am I in the freezing
section are you trying to kill me let me
out why am I in there let me
know there were some but this person
wants to kill me
you're not the only one with enemies
apparently
oh it's a dangerous world out there also
I can read this my my Korean is good
enough to be able to read this Korean
writing now is
chocolate milk
I'm choking
do you like chalky milk
yeah that's what I meant by chalky milk
why did I know that you would pick it up
as chalky milk do you like chocolate
milk
I do like chocolate milk Kiara but I
don't like when it gets too creamy it
gets a little chalky sorry
yay thanks for the chat everyone
I'm all for now but I'll see you next
time no no no no okay all right close
enough there's one more picture I have
one more picture we'll stay stay for
that anyway nice fridge I guess
um I'm not at all insulted by it I do
not care for it I am not hurt by it
emotionally damaged is nothing I know of
nope I don't care
[Music]
goodbye everyone
I'll see you soon
heart
this fridge is filled with all sorts of
food products
seems like you really like cheese too
because you have a lot of different
kinds
however is that real steak in the fridge
or just a toy
it almost looks too good to be true
doesn't it this is this is a German
language French I don't know if it's
from Germany or Austria or whatever but
actually no that's awesome that's an
awesome
and yeah there's even the Austrian map
on there yo an Austrian fellow what's up
where is your professionalism hey
where's my professionalism
where is it
well my professionalism is right here
isn't a Kiara
oh is it me am I the professional one I
guess so I'm such a pro yeah about this
last fridge
um there's some Coca-Cola in here cute
uh apparently they had to cool down
after a little fight probably it was
about jealousy I heard uh okay you
Senpai gets a little bit jealous right
right
who is the jealous one
what are you talking about Kiara oh
sorry you don't know right they're so
cute they're both such cute streamers is
a cat and colon is a dog and they're
both like top tier gamers
foreign
like oh you're so cute and then they
keep calling you that even after you've
asked them to stop
she's confused because she doesn't know
them well it's okay we'll introduce her
to them eventually
anyway yeah generally not much in this
fridge but it's a good start you could
cook something with that I guess eggs
and steak
and cheese and some yummy looking Jam
yeah
nice fridge
you've been spending too much time with
beetle
ah no no I think I've been spending too
much time with you little lady because
this is the end of the pictures sorry uh
we have no more thank you guys for
sending in so many
thank you shares for all the submissions
for showing me the insides of your
fridge I do want to do this eventually
with like whole Live members like having
them show me the insides of their
fridges yeah I think that would be very
interesting to see what they eat hmm I
actually had that idea a while ago but I
hope this was interesting to you guys
um but I guess the fridges were just a
little side thing they're really
important thing with talking to nirasama
today thank you nirasama for letting me
talk to you for so long
goodbye
[Music]
wait what's in your fridge
just food
like what
like tomatoes cheese and potatoes
okay what do you do with that
I eat it
because I can cook with it if I'm hungry
so done with me
what I do I love you know please don't
be like that no yeah no you know like
that's still my best friend oh really
heart heart heart heart okay heart heart
heart heart
thank you
although maybe I shouldn't thank you
since I got shot in the leg but I mean I
did get healed by the doctor so what
does that mean I guess I should thank
you you're not saying that I shot you in
the line right because I didn't do that
I wouldn't have any memory of that
I'm not accusing you of anything
I'm just saying thank you for healing me
yeah because that's what I did I revived
you today that's that's all I did only
good things
[Music]
okay I believe you
I'm glad you're on my side
this feels like a toxic abusive
relationship that I'm having here right
now from both sides
would be worried is this okay to keep on
like pushing this this friendship with
Never Summer I'm not sure
I'm not nearly as innocent as you think
I am wink
oh she probably shot herself in the leg
and then she's trying to blame it on
someone else
I wouldn't do that I try getting out of
it first
and failing miserably of course
so what did I learned yesterday I'm not
sure what I learned about neurosama
today she's giving me very very mixed
feelings and Vibes but
it's okay I love her the way she is
it was an honor to collab with you today
in Arizona thank you for your time
thank you for collaborating with me
it was a pleasure working with you heart
heart heart I hope you will remember me
in the in the future too heart heart
I will always remember you
heart heart heart
so happy I made great memories today hi
Thai Thai
you looked a bit down earlier
is there something on your mind
no I was just really nervous about this
whole situation but I think I I warmed
up to you and you warmed up to me and
and and I mean you seemed kind of sick
of me but nonetheless I think you know
it it and it ended up working out quite
well in the end so I'm good now
I'm glad everything turned out for the
best even though I was sick of you too
but I'm glad you had fun today
and there was someone it seems like are
you okay your filter isn't working so
well today because I'm I'm receiving a
lot of emotional damage
I'm sorry to hear that
hopefully it'll get better soon yeah
it's okay I'm kind of masochistic anyway
so honestly I'm enjoying all of this
very much
I'm glad that you're enjoying it
I hope you're back to normal soon
heart
IES and with that I think we should
leave it there
um thank you guys very much for watching
if you're interested tomorrow we're
finishing Fire Emblem no matter what
yeah we will engage to the end and uh
see what happens at the end and then
yeah thank you there is someone so much
thank you thank you guys for watching
and and I hope uh it was all okay
um sorry for the awkwardness I I had to
keep quiet you know to let her think let
her cook
um but yeah it was fun
thank you very much thank you
goodbye everyone
I'll see you next week yeah heart yeah
let's collab again and in German we say
auf winners in high tide
goodbye everyone
heart
bye bye thank you
[Music]
foreign
or kind of wants chicken nuggets though
[Music]
Kiara fridge reveal when sometime soon
I'll show you the insides of my fridge
sometime I promise
thank you
[Music]
you know when someone said she will kiss
me let's go I am winning
[Music]
foreign