[Music]
e
n
a
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
e
[Music]
n
k
k ah I'm I'm back oh oh oh oh oh
ah
pineapple I'm more of a pineapple fan
then sua watermelon fan but yeah that's
why it's on my head with a pineapple
chicken
cute already I couldn't hold back but as
you can see uh I think I play it maybe
about an hour I never got past um
[Music]
1,900 uh a little bit Oh see it's almost
1,969 why yeah I never got to 2000 it's
so sad I tried really hard and I I think
um you know you know what I think my
problem
is I think my problem is my my my my
early game is strong and then my mid
game is okay and my game is like really
bad oh let me here fix fix something in
my
audio okay there we go
[Music]
oh oh wait a
second um okay I I I I came back home
yesterday and oh my God I hear this
crouchy sound there you know I'm I'm
setting everything up again so that
things are we how they're supposed to be
again in my home
[Music]
environment uh
uh the strateg to connect the fruits by
order of the wheel on the right wait are
you this you're being H ironic right now
right you're not like trying to say
something of act meaning with that
right I am aware of
that okay but if you guys have actual
strats I was so close to just looking up
um is like a way of doing things
better but I didn't I didn't cuz I
thought what I'm doing is like basically
correct okay m
try spaming the same SP no that's stupid
that's stupid there must be a strat if
like most of us struggle to get to 3,000
when there's others who get to 7,000
okay like that's like in a different
kind of
world or do you really think it's just
like I mean I mean I
[Music]
mean use your sides to
organize ahuh the s night uhhuh organize
I wonder
how who got 7K no that's just like
General rank like online rankings of
like every every
person like you know like look at these
people
Kam how the [\h__\h] did you do that tell
me I need to know that's uh yeah I don't
know if it's Global but it's like two
days is
[Music]
ranking no don't don't immediately say
uh cheater who knows it can happen can
happen oh wait why are why is even the
monthly ranking the same is it really is
it is it really holy [\h__\h] did nobody
ever get over 7,300 okay okay well oh oh
I stopped moving I think you know I
currently having a little bit uh of
issues with the app
but it comes back when I touch it so
anyway let me show you my strong early
game my my supposedly strong early game
where it doesn't really matter cuz you
don't really have to think that much but
sometimes some cool things happen
okay let's see
it trust me trust me it's good
good so I played this game like how many
rounds did I play in Callie's place like
two of
free and I just watched a lot of
gameplay on it
already not that that really helps much
because it's like really simple and how
to play
it two I only played two them okay but
then yeah now uh before the Stream
I played a bunch more oh you might think
why did I why did I do that I don't know
that was bad bad early game bad early
game but it doesn't matter because early
game doesn't matter because everything
everything happens ooh for rason like
this okay so I I
trust I trust the
process I believe isn't there a phrase
you
say isn't there believe in the um what's
the what do you say hey this is looking
gorgeous already though besides the
strawberries trust trust is that just
how I say it okay I'm just winging it of
course I'm just winging it like what
else are you supposed to
do every move matters nah it doesn't
doesn't only if you real real bad try
hard I'm I'm just enjoying my time here
but I'm getting there I'm becoming a try
hard cuz like why the [\h__\h] can I not you
guys got to help me then cuz I can't get
over 2,000 like what what's what's the
deal with that if I want to I want I
want
Cali to get mad over me getting 3,000 so
first of all we'll have to get over
2,000 four mistakes
nah oh if you guys roast me oh I really
want to say
something you were a mistake sorry um um
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry I'm
sorry there's no such thing as mistakes
there's only happy
accidents I'm not sure if you were even
what okay
now wow I'm so mean my dad said the same
thing a touch no
touch oh what happened I didn't look see
good things happen to those who don't
take it too
seriously all right and then day touch
and then day touch see good good and the
ches will eventually touch down there
touchdown oh oh yeah could even happen
now oh there we
[Music]
go you've
changed am I have I changed for my Japan
trip I don't think so I'm I'm still the
same
believe
[Music]
me should we make the middle one to an
Apple yeah let's do
it it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter oh beautiful strawberry let's put
you
here
[Music]
um
people thought because I was like
tweeting about shin kin that I went
to Osaka I didn't but people just
automatically assume you know kaai is
more than just Osaka
okay
yeah other other kind people might be
really sad at people automatically
assuming it's it's allaka just by
[Music]
default consider the feelings of the non
Osaka
people but that already brings me to my
first
[Music]
tangent oh my God oh my God this is a
great game for Tangen thing I think
uh so as long as we're not too try hard
ah [\h__\h] A you know when this happens
like you you here but then I don't know
why it does this but the cursor just
ends up on the other side sometimes man
okay oh something nice is going to
happen now look at this oh and touch oh
oh
e your restless nights would have been
cured of my
SMR no
nah nah oh oh Chain
[Music]
Reaction well yeah oh oh what what do
you mean I'm dead what do you mean I'm
dead what did I do something in the game
or something I
[Music]
said
my two pineapples are going to touch
soon wait that makes me think I should
probably show you guys more of myself I
mean oh actually I could even cover like
this whole part probably right cuz you
don't need to see this but oh well is
this a good
position oh
wait my hat is so
tall is this good it's good right you
see enough right plenty plenty the wow
[Music]
I went with the sh to Kai region you
know and Kai is more than just oaka let
me tell you it's like you know
K
Kaka what else n what else I don't know
the
rest but you know there's more than just
oaka but let's let's just you know let's
just say I went we can see your
cursor oh why e really oh interesting ah
okay okay
okay dear no no no no no I didn't go to
Nada I I didn't go to N I never touched
those NADA deers before okay let's
go um yeah what I wanted to say is
something really
interesting I would say to me it was
really funny cuz I couldn't stop paying
attention to
it um something really interesting
happened in the shin
Consin mhm so I get on the shin Consin I
bring out my iPad and I'm like chilling
and the I was on the aisle seat there
were like no more window
[Music]
seats
move
listen up listen to my shin
story and then it's I think at oh hi
noisa cute hat right What station was it
I think
it they they got off nagya someone
before nagya which means it must have
been like Yokohama or so
um like until then the whole car that I
was in was still like pretty empty and I
was like why did I not get a window seat
when it's so empty I know
hey it switched
[Music]
again and so somewhere in Yokohama or so
there's like not that many steps with
Ain and it's like if you get in in Tokyo
it's like Tokyo and then Yokohama and
then Nya and then
[Music]
Kaka or something like that some order
like
that U
and and some somewhere in yukoh I
think a group of very very very buff
looking dudes maybe 20 I don't
know uh a
lot came in all of them fake arms thick
thighs thick
bodies uh some of them Japanese some of
them not very
Japanese and uh they all were wearing a
uniform and they were walking in and
they were taking a seat and it looked so
funny they had all reserved seats so
they took up like almost the whole
car and uh it just look so funny cuz
like their thick fighs they were huge
like all of them were also like really
like big tall
M and they were taking up like so much
space where do I put this I want
to oh
okay and and they their their feet with
the matching outfits matching socks they
were like Po peeking poking out of the
seats on the side H and it just it just
looks so funny M mie yeah
she
[Music]
and I could not stop staring at them
okay cuz it was so funny to me cuz I
wanted to ask them what kind of group
are you yeah yeah so I was like I was
like looking looking and I was
considering asking the the dude who was
like you know I was on the aisle and who
was on the aisle like next to me
basically ooh
ooh o I wanted to
ask but I was too shy to ask because I
thought oh they I don't want to like I
don't this is like with me with the cars
I didn't want them to feel too good
about
themselves it's not like I care it's not
like it's not like
your muscles interest me greatly
no so what else did I do I tried my best
to stare at them in a way that they
would notice and um take a picture of
the aisle cuz it looked funny and I sent
it to JMA and then I when when one of
them would go like to the toilet I was
like staring at their t-shirts to try to
find out if there's like a team name on
there you think they noticed no
no can the peaches touch
please H and yeah um I found out I found
out they were a rugby
team Jitsu
Tas and they were like Japanese rugby
team I think it was something like um
the team name was something like Mia
heat or so mi I and then
heat Japan or so look that up you can
find them they look
legit they look so strong they had a
couple of foreigners in their team
too so yeah M
Hond
Hond yeah and then I felt uh already
like okay that's enough information I'm
happy no need for anything else what I
do what I
do oh okay okay
okay the time of wheel is turning Wheel
of Time
oopsie no not Miami
[Music]
Heat
what me m Honda the imass girl
[Laughter]
no there is a Mas girl that's called
Honda they were like in in their outfit
so they probably just came straight from
a
match and yeah they were just all
chilling there with their big fighs that
save
[Music]
lives okay okay that's not my
fault oh
man damn it it just popped sometimes
they pop because they're so excited and
so many things are happening at
once
it's fine it's fine I'm happy I'm
happy yeah it it looks so funny I I I I
I wonder if I should or could show you
the picture I made sure that there's no
faces that you can see and I mean
there's there's there's photos of them
online anyway right so can I show I mean
I wouldn't show it now cuz I don't want
to like go through my phone right
now
maybe I should
though ask
jenma you know I live I I really like
the principle of life that sometimes you
just shouldn't
ask you know sometimes it's better not
to ask oh I want the Cherry to go there
actually [\h__\h] oh well I will get there
eventually
I don't think they would
mind right yeah they have F the taken
all the time and they were still in the
uniform you're 25 minutes late oh it's
okay welcome welcome thank you for
coming it's it's been a while like I did
stream last week but there's not that
much right so it's nice to be back but
it was also nice to be gone to be honest
like I don't know it's like weird like I
felt like I wanted to stream and I felt
like I I I missed you guys but at the
same time I was enjoying the time uh
where I didn't need to
stream you
know sometimes it's
nice got to enjoy a little bit of a
break I mean it wasn't really a break
you know I'm always working on
something I always am
[Music]
oh and yeah I came back
yesterday and I flew business again I
guess my
will I paid for it though it wasn't a
free upgrade okay I paid I got I got it
against my will
[\h__\h] and I didn't even get a good seat
this time last time I got at least a
solo seat this time it was like full and
when I checked in I couldn't choose
anything besides like two aisle seats
and then it was kind of like uh in front
of me and behind me I was on an aisle
seat in a double not even like I I I
noticed one thing the the double seats
on the side are even worse than the
double seats in the middle
row because in the double seat in the
side you have to share uh the same size
table that if you are in the middle
seats double seats you get one each you
know what I mean you know what I'm
saying like you only get one for two
while in the middle if you're in a
double seat like next next to a person
you at least get one each one for
yourself kind of one full full size side
table
so uh we were sharing that space at
least there was a lady next to me you
know we didn't talk like anyway I just
slept through she need to get out so
often man and I had my my thing flat you
know to
sleep at some point I just made her just
just step over me just step over me my
god without touching me if possible but
of course that wasn't
possible yeah anyway what was I saying
oh yeah in front of me and behind me I
noticed cuz I listen I listen
Okay I
listen um the Purser which in case you
don't know is the the cabin
attendant crew number one person okay
the most experienced one in the bunch
who basically takes control of the
operations during that trip mhm that's
the
Purser and she went up to the person who
was sitting in front of me and the
person who was sitting behind me like
the mind reading one exactly the one the
mind reading one that I told you about
who read my
mind and often they're uh
pretty while difficult people uh for
like other other crew
members but they always try their best
to please the
[Music]
passengers um
so she was talking to the two dudes in
front and behind me very very carefully
with lots of attention and
love because I heard they were Senators
but like Senators as in like their their
flying status not
like right that's something else right
like there's a flying status Senator
they're not actually
Senators I would I would think so but
still to get to that uh
status you must have flown the I no wait
can you even can you like buy yourself
into that
status how does it work again maybe it
depends on the airline
[Music]
too I think yeah cuz I think you could
buy your status maybe in some Airlines
you can buy yourself to become a
senator usually that's like yeah really
really freaking rich
people with Miles yeah yeah yeah like a
miles Senator somebody who spent yeah
that that's like the top the top thing
you can become with
Miles uh with Airlines is like a
senator yeah let's go we pineapple hey
we see everything's oh o popping pop
popor highest I'm pretty sure mhm never
heard of anything higher I mean unless
you're a real Senator politician I don't
know what's getting treated better a
real Senator
politician with a normal status or a
senator M status
person and then like I noticed that the
the front guy like the lady came to him
and she already knew that he had some
issue cuz I guess he already complained
to it to someone else and I was trying
to listen what his issue was but it was
really hard to hear cuz like planes are
just so noisy this was even before it
took
off a [\h__\h] oh well that's okay
um i' gathered information by listening
cuz again I
listen and by the end unfortunately by
the end I figured out something I think
his problem was that he was flying with
his uh wife and his
daughter and they didn't get an upgrade
and that absolutely soured their
experience and they came in here with
such a Negative feeling and she was like
oh my God I'm so sorry I will write
everything down that you're saying she
literally says that yeah please would
you mind I I really I would really
really love to take some time to write
this down a little bit later if you're
okay with that b blah blue kissing his
ass oh no oh no couldn't sit couldn't
get two more free
upgrades oh
no but what I was thinking
is a God damn it if I put the puzzle
pieces together in the
beginning I could have oh so kindly
offered at least one of them the seat
that I didn't want to have
and possibly get my money
back but I didn't put all the puzzle
pieces together until I properly heard
the issue at the very end until then it
was just like vaguely I thought I knew
what was going
on [\h__\h] I was even sitting behind him
like perfect no to get like his daughter
or like who would he choose maybe he
wouldn't even accept it because it's
only one and they don't want to leave
just one person behind and wherever they
were sitting
but I was thinking man that would have
been so so genius I could have could
have gone back to premium economy and
get my my my 800 bucks back [\h__\h] no I
ended up not cancelling because like
they they were not
really helpful um I can tell you all of
this in detail
[Music]
too and and at that time like the whole
week on it the whole it was like 10 how
long was I gone 10 11 days this whole
time I was like honestly in so much
pain I I was losing my
mind I got like two 90minut massages in
like one week in
Japan and was like constantly trying to
massage myself was to to to
know uh what's the word aail
h uh so I thought you know what they are
not being really helpful and it's stress
full maybe it's fate maybe I should just
take
it
yeah maybe I should just o
oo so I ended up just taking it I just I
just I
just try my best to ignore how much I'm
like paying for this oh wait ah I should
have waited cuz something was happening
oh
well yeah
okay oh all right okay I see
you oh push push yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's go ooh a pushy one aren't you
o are you sure you're not addicted to
business class now
no I like the laying down flat really
helps my legs like my shoulders are
always in pain my shoulders were in Hell
during the flight and also not during
the
flight but at least I could fall asleep
and then like ignore the pain like just
sleep for the pain you know that that
just means a lot that's
big one one one points pokey pokey
points poke
[Music]
points could be because of those
assets can I take what you can get yeah
I yeah I just gave up and I said [\h__\h]
you Austrian Airlines why are you so
stupid cuz like okay okay do you want to
hear the full story I told this in a
Twitter space more or less did I did no
wait did I not I I just tweeted about it
like
roughly you already know part of it
though in in my chitchat stream I told I
told about the first part of that
trip
m
okay okay so a rough explanation as
rough as I can
be I am not very good at it I
think yeah I obviously this is not the
Run cuz I'm not even focusing oh no who
knows you know who knows it's looking
bad I know I know I know I know I don't
care
uh oh sheesh
yeah let me let me tell
you why this
happened so when I
booked my ticket for this
trip um my intention was to fly premium
economy uh which
woohoo which was going to be already
kind of expensive on its own and I was
paying for for this trip by myself
because it was my choice to go to Japan
for doing a couple of things that I was
asked to do or to that I was invited
to
um yeah you know it's fine sometimes
sometimes it's okay bow bow oh Bow B
raid hello 39 isn't it always 30
minutes thank you b
b b
b you you can't right in the right
moment as I am starting my
story my first world problem story let's
go although I mean you know I I think I
think it's you know legit some some
parts of the story are like I have a
good reason to be complaining okay so it
starts with me booking my flight ticket
to Japan and I booked premium economy
and then when I was booking it I saw
something that I never saw before and I
think it's new because I find out later
that
the customer service has no idea what
this function is
apparently
Callie hi I'm trying my best while
telling stories I'm not focusing at all
we we'll try to focus later
maybe okay oh my God they're they're all
they're all bow
bowing yeah just in time for a prime
tangent okay and then I see this new
function it says like you can auction
for an
upgrade uh to business in that case I
don't know if it's also available if
you're like um
economy and you can like auction for
premium economy I don't know but I saw
it and I was like that's interesting I
wonder how low I
can uh set my bid and like it did say if
you put this is important this it said
very clearly and I checked it again and
again later on so I'm like very sure on
the terms and conditions of
this
um oh I stopped moving again okay H when
you make a
bid uh they there's a chance it will get
accepted anywhere like like a day or two
before your flight but if you decide to
take back your bid anytime
before it gets accepted anytime before
it gets
accepted you can take back retract your
bid and you don't have to pay you get
your your your pledged money back I mean
it was never uh charged yet I think at
that
point okay so I was like okay and I
thought that more people would be using
this function so if I put the minimum
bid surely I won't get chosen right so I
put the minimum bid which was like 800
bucks and I I just wanted to know you
know how it is for once like I thought
okay at least once I could do it and
then then then if I didn't like it I
could cancel the the the other
one but just for now let me let me try
it I don't think I'll get accepted
anyway and if I do then let's just let's
just have fun let's just let's just
enjoy Delux ah [\h__\h] the luxury that I've
just given myself oh you know
maybe it's meant to be if it happens
it's meant to be that's what I was
thinking
okay oh no anyways
yeah so I put my minimum bid
in and I'm like okay yeah nothing will
happen with this right cuz like you
could go up to like 3,000 4,000 and
normally an upgrade
costs at least it costs more than that
so [\h__\h] that's not I don't like that
that's not
good at least I think I I did pay less
than you would normally pay for it
mhm yeah and then before my flight a
little bit before my flight like a day
or or a day and a half before I
[Music]
get I get the yay you're in your bid has
been accepted YooHoo you're now upgraded
to uh business and I'm like okay
well um I guess I'm happy about it I
guess okay I'll take it y I'll test it
out and then I flew premium economy and
honestly the first trip was fine but uh
yeah I talked about it in detail in my
chitchat stream during my while I was in
Japan so check that out if you want for
detail I put I showed some pictures and
stuff Airlines gotcha yeah you mean you
flew business yes what did I
say what did I
say check the Vault please mhm um
but I didn't I still didn't think it was
worth the money oh we're ending it here
it
seems y That's
fine mhm I prum economy oh okay I meant
business
yeah 800 on top yes on on
top on top of what I already paid for
premium economies so just don't think
about it too hard don't think about
numbers too hard because it will seem
less worth it the more you think about
the numbers but it's still cheaper I
think than normally if I would have
bought business under normal
circumstances you know but don't think
about it too hard okay just don't just
don't think about
it don't concern yourself with the
details but I decided okay this was
nice it was nice to not feel
excruciating pain because I could sleep
through it in a flight for once cuz I've
I've been on this Austria to Japan
Road uh whether it be direct fight or
connecting flights a million
times
and I'm just I can't I can't I
can't it takes less time to go to Japan
it takes more time to go back
mhm anyway I I decided I won't do it on
my flight back because I didn't think it
was that worth it I think premium
economy is all right um
it's better in other airlines but it's
okay uh and I I wanted to save
money it's too expensive if I do 800 two
times that's too much that's just too
much okay you know I'm I'm I'm I'm
quite sometimes people say I'm I'm still
a little bit too much in the broken
mindset that I'm broke but I don't quite
agree with that I'm just reasonable um
you have to save money somewhere
otherwise you're going to be broke
um you know camp Camp yeah you know FR a
Frugal oh I'm
Frugal and fruity and you know
Frugal somehow this
sounds to me like something else
uh so I was going to cancel the other
one and I I I knew that as long as I
didn't accept it I could still cancel
it um I I surely waited unnecessarily
long to do it but I was still when I was
starting the process I was still very
much in the time frame of where it would
have been possible to do
it uh I flew on Sunday the 8 8th and I
started the process on Tuesday the 3rd
okay listen up this
timeline it's not completely my fault
okay so I I I I I logged into my like
flight details okay I'm like okay let's
let's see how I can cancel this
and like in the flight detail I could
still like change my seats and I could
do this and that but and it shows that I
did a bid but it didn't
show
um would you like to go there
no it didn't show how to get rid of the
bid you know and I I I honestly think
it's like on purpose they're making it
difficult on purpose
so I was I was doing on the phone so I
um maybe it was like you know maybe only
on the browser version although it looks
exactly the same um but then you know
they have like this customer service
help Chat thing so I started chatting
with that first you get treated by a
robot and then when you say I'm not
happy with the support they get you
human so
I I've had
airlines that were plenty helpful
through the chat doing things for me
through the chat understanding me
through the chat which aine was um the I
think fin air for example and other
airlines like the honestly
normally it
works so I started chatting with them I
explain my
issue
and uh
basically they're like I it's like I'm
do you want to see
it I took a screenshot of our first
conversation it was a short
one
but it already made me feel frustrated I
think I sent it to did I send it to JMA
oh
yeah let me show
you you're allowed to see it of
course
okay let me show
you ah okay let's start here okay so
first I gave them like a a general
explanation of there's no names of what
I trying to
do and then they were like kind of
repeating it but not really so I'm like
yes again stating clear I want to cancel
my upgrade bid if possible isn't that
like really clearly saying what I want
to do they
answer no I still said I don't see any
option to do do it myself I tried but I
couldn't see a way to do it so they
answer please be advised that all bid
upgrades are done on the
website would would you does this sound
like they're hearing
you would you feel like they understood
what what you were trying to
do
no right so I'm like I'm not sure how
that statement helps
me I tried checking on the website but I
didn't see a way to cancel the bid that
I
made and then she says so you would
upgrade with your Min one more
correct that's when I was started to
think like no no this is really a human
trust me that's when I started to think
like man they must not know about this
function
like what the [\h__\h] so I'm like no I
don't want to upgrade at all I want to
keep my original class that I booked
with before before the bid gets accepted
and I can't go back cuz that's the terms
and the conditions once it get accepted
I can't you
know go back anymore then it's fixed
then I'm bound to it and then they say
for all bid upgrades this is done
directly on the
website
um
um it the clim it's a
human cuz first first it's like a bot
but then you say are you like are you
happy do you need help from a human I'm
like yes and then it
switches but anyway obviously this
didn't bring me anywhere right so I gave
up cuz like this is this thing is not
hearing
me this thing is not understanding me so
I'm like okay maybe maybe maybe I can't
do it on my phone maybe I have to do it
on a PC this was on the third I was not
getting help from Austrian Airlines
customer
service uh on the third which was way
ahead uh way before they would accept my
bid um so I waited until I had access to
a PC I was traveling so it was a bit
difficult then when I finally had access
it was still before they accepted the
bid and still um how many hours was it
still at least 60 hours
before uh the
flight so later I find
out something that is important with
these 60
hours yeah
[Music]
um how did they not touch which
ones it's okay I'm not mad I'm only mad
at aan Airlines but I'm not mad at this
game um okay so I get to a PC and I log
in and I try to do this on the PC but
even on the
PC it's just the same it's exactly the
same I tried but I can't find any option
there's like a window for the bid that
shows you that you did a bit but you
can't click anything M so I I go into
the chat bot again cuz now I'm like
really certain that you can't do it here
I I didn't screenshot this conversation
but it was quite a bit longer I was
quite a bit more
like uh trying my best to get my point
across it took a while and I don't think
they really understood again they were
like I think jenma was watching the
conversation cuz she was there too
um so she could attest to it and also
they record apparently these uh chat
conversations too um but again it was
just not helpful they didn't seem to
understand what I'm trying to do and
what this is and yeah they don't know
their policies they didn't seem to
understand that I am able to can like
once I got them through the whole this
is a thing you have guys the auction yes
I want to cancel it yes it's a thing
after I got them through that whole
annoying section I tried to explain that
I am indeed allowed to cancel it um and
they wouldn't believe me so I was like
okay [\h__\h] this conversation I closed it
cuz this person didn't seem
competent I looked up the terms the
conditions so I could copy paste them
and was really certain of what I'm
saying is right I found the terms and
conditions I was indeed right turns out
I was still able to cancel it so I go
back into the chat B this time different
person but they seem to be sitting in
the same room cuz after I explained my
problems the person pretty quickly seems
to like know what's going on and like
just says yeah yeah we know but you
can't you can't cancel it you can't
cancel your bid and I'm like copy
pasting the terms and conditions and
they're like yeah but like okay well
please call please call the hotline so
they're pushing it to the hotline now
and I'm like
I'm in Japan this probably cost
money yeah like first they were still
trying to convince me that I can't do it
even when I was copy pasting the terms
and the conditions to them they were
still
like and and then yeah then they were
like just call just call please we can't
do it here if in any case let's say you
can cancel it we wouldn't be able to do
it here on the phone okay I'm like uh on
the on the chat I'm like okay [\h__\h] you
so they're wasting my time right they're
wasting my time I keep on saying this is
time uh sensitive oopsie Oh I thought
the uh grape was
coming I keep on saying it's time
sensitive I need this done now because I
know that I will be uh bound to it once
they accept
it so I'm getting stressed but I still f
okay I should be fine still so but I was
like I'm going to call when I'm um when
I'm back in the hotel and this this time
frame was really important though the
reason why I said I was going to call
when I'm in the hotel is because I had
my Austrian SIM card in the
hotel and the other SIM card that I had
in there for internet couldn't make
calls but by the time between the chat
we I already talked to three employees
who couldn't help me
and me getting to the
hotel we were suddenly under 60
hours and that's when I was S I was
sitting in the hotel room and I was
switching my SIM card and before I made
a call I I checked um again some details
I tried to find it again by
myself and I found something I found the
way to do it by
yourself
unfortunately it was a little bit too
late but I just wish that their
employees would have been competent
enough to let me know where I can do it
because this is the problem that I'm
saying they weren't even able to tell me
where I can do
it and it turned out to be like
relatively simple if you just dig hard
enough basically in the first yeah they
stalled me in the first email that you
get when you put the
bid but you're getting spammed of other
emails afterwards like they keep on
updating your your flight receipts I got
like four emails for updated flight
receipts after making the bid so it gets
like really like down down down
down so it's like in that email there's
a small small link where you can change
your bid but there's no way to get to it
through normal like clicks on the
website you have to go on the very first
email there's like one link and it says
here the terms and the conditions are
somewhat
different it's like it it's it should
still be as long as your bit isn't
accepted you're not bound to it but if
you want to change it you only can do it
up to 60 hours before the flight and now
it was 58 hours uh oh before that I
actually did still do a call one
call maybe that was like 59 hours before
the flight but yeah and then I found
that and I call the person again who was
by the way not helpful either on the
phone cuz the guy on the phone also
didn't really seem to know what the [\h__\h]
this
is then I called back and I said
yo um I don't I I I don't even
remember uh oh yeah uh no he didn't know
what it was but in the end he said okay
um like after me explaining everything
he said I I will bring this to like the
people who can do change it and ooh
finally something nice and they will do
it for you they will cancel your bit and
I'm like okay let me just confirm let me
just make sure so you're saying that I
will be going back to premium economy
for this flight back and I will not have
to pay the bid that I have made and it
will we canceled right and he said yes
and
then then I uh uh and he said there will
be a confirmation email for like when
this happened and I hang up the phone
hoping that this is for real for
real and then um I take out the SIM card
for a moment I think because I needed
the internet cuz the hotel internet
wasn't really working I take out the SIM
card and
I I I just do some things on the phone
and then and then like 4 minutes or so
after he told me it was going to
work I get an email this is what I
posted on Twitter it said your bid has
been accepted congratulations you have
been upgraded to business class and I
was like oh my
God
uh what happened I just talked to them
they said it would work what
happened now I'm bound to it cuz they
accepted it so I thought did he
misunderstand me too or did he put it in
wrong or did they think did they see
like this would be the rudest example
but would they have like seen that I'm
trying to cancel it and then they were
like quick quick accept it now accept it
now so that she can't go back on it
anymore
oh that would have been so
bad so I'm like what the [\h__\h] and I'm
like okay okay I have to call back so I
switch my SIM card again and I call back
and he's like oh yeah I was trying to
call you I couldn't reach I'm like yeah
I switch my SIM card but this is not
like what we what we discussed and he
was like yeah sorry so right
afterwards um I contacted the the people
who could do it but they said it's
already too late and uh and here he also
mentioned I think he did mention the 60
hours or something that he didn't know
about before though
mhm and I'm like yeah but like according
to your own terms and conditions even
within those hours as long as it's not
accepted yet I'm not bound to it and I
had like so many conversations with your
other customer service people employees
who could have helped me all this time
and basically I wasted my time because
you guys have no idea how this function
even works so is it really my fault that
all this time you weren't even able to
tell me that there is one website like
one Link in the first email that I get
where I could change it myself and if I
would have known that on the first uh
time I contacted you guys on the 3rd of
October then I would have changed it on
time and I wouldn't have wasted 800
[\h__\h] bucks on this you little shits
and he's like yeah I'm
sorry I'm so mad at this like this is
such a horri
customer service
oh I wouldn't even say that they were
purposefully stalling me they just are
not trained properly they don't even
know about their own like functions
about the they I swear to you they have
no idea what this auction thing is they
don't know seems to be
new yeah no I said I said all of this to
them to him on the phone yeah and then I
was like okay this is
[\h__\h] and he he uh said I should
write a complaint I was like yeah okay
I'm going to do
it um but that's then uh you know I was
like
um feeling a lot of pain on my body and
like I said I was going to do it
tomorrow cuz it was like late at night
but when I woke up you know I was again
in so much pain and I thought [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] I'm so I'm so done with it like I'm
just going to guess I'll I'll just
accepted it's not okay though it's not
[Music]
okay like all they needed to do is show
me where you can actually retract your
bid and they weren't able to do that and
stalled me until it was too late and
they took my
money it's would you say would you
say like sure in some way it was my
fault but they're not competent enough
to to tell me that like that's like the
minimum the bare minimum
no yeah one job isn't that what they're
here for tell me how to do it my god oh
no don't go up there hey
oh yeah that was on them like holy
[\h__\h] like there was so many employees
that I was in touch with and not a
single one of them could like tell me
that really
really yeah holy
[\h__\h] thank you guys maybe I still write
a
complaint it's too late now like they
might not reimburse me of course but
like holy
[\h__\h] but they probably won't care so
maybe maybe
this clip will reach them hello asan
Airlines let's tag them on
Twitter and they will be like I'm so
sorry no that's not okay like train your
employees properly my God you stole my
money because you don't train your
[Music]
employees y I worked in a call center
for 10 years I can tell you that the
call can tell you the call center
employees are the last to hear yeah yeah
yeah I can totally imagine that but like
the call center that for example I
worked with in uh when I was working in
a hotel they were also like
external but they were more competent
still than this I shat on them to 11,000
viewers yeah it's going to be more
Austrian Airlines it's going to be
[Music]
more my God was it Worf it Austin
Allin was it worth it
man and then I didn't even get a good
seat I tried the uh the lounge though in
in uh Narita Airport there's a uh like
two Lou lounges that you can use when
you're flying with business uh JMA told
me to use the A&A Lune that because it's
better there's the United was it
United and
the the ana launch it was okay I mean
there's some food there's
Curry and some some other stuff yeah
it's a big big launch yeah it's fine
it's
fine new system shouldn't even go online
without yeah yeah the employees should
be fully trained and understanding of
what those functions are like I can't
believe they didn't understand it and
then the first the first conversation
you you guys are saying it's a bot I
still don't believe it I just think
they're not competent but
those replies like it's so embarrassing
what they're
replying the [\h__\h] so
embarrassing yeah I know they run off of
scripts I know they like copy paste [\h__\h]
but like when when you're when you're
like tackling something that's Off
Script dude then you should go off
script obviously they didn't have
prepared the right answer
for this kind of case which I can't even
imagine that it's such
a uncommon
case people wanting to retract their
bids and not finding where to do it like
huh that can't be like that
rare don't you get fired for going off
SCP I don't think so if there's nothing
that
fits what you're trying to
say you
know just because they had the word
upgrade in them
H I would say the other conversations I
had unfortunately I didn't take a
screenshot um but aan Airlines they
should be recorded just for the record
you know if you want to check
them uh they they seemed more human than
that they were yeah like I feel like
they were writing their own answers
while still you know copy pasting some
stuff in there but it seemed legit to me
at least in those other
conversations
what it's
[Music]
fine but yeah you know after all this do
you understand why I was thinking damn
it I should have I should have uh given
the Senator's family
my my seat cuz I didn't even want
it see because of their Senator that
they said the person said you're so
important to
us basically because of me because no
because of their employees not knowing
what to do me being forced to keep the
upgrade that's why the senator was
unhappy so it all goes back
to the lack of support and
knowledge would you have gotten your
money back yeah yeah yeah I'm pretty
sure because there's like cases where I
heard for example like I was like
sitting at the airport once and they
were like hey anybody who maybe like we
over booked our flight we will give like
800 900 bucks to anybody who decides to
take a different route uh that takes a
little bit
longer with Lanza and then you get the
money
anybody who wants to do it you know they
do stuff like that so I'm sure they
can do that
[Music]
too
yeah yes yes Airlines do that they they
they try everything to fix their over
bookings and I'm sure they would do this
to make their Senator
happy now Senator is very very
angry because of you big
of
[Music]
you
well I got to sleep I got to sleep in
the
airplane food was all right I like the
food more on the on the first flight I
think
yeah yeah hey this is not a good run
either but maybe maybe I'll try to like
do some very focused runs after this
[Music]
one pictures pictures of my business
class flight are in the other zadan
stream chitchatting stream that I did oh
like when did I do it last Monday
actually one week ago I think
yeah there's a game going yeah where are
you looking
at are you back in Austria now yes I'm
back in Austria
and my cats were so
happy my Catos were so happy to see me
they're still they're like so
[Music]
clingy they're so clingy and so cute and
so fluffy and so happy they seem so so
so Bliss
H the mommy's
back yeah I I also I woke up so early
today I wouldn't even say it's jet lag
it's just uh I felt like like the air
was really stuffy and hot um because
probably the window wasn't open for a
long time my mom just I I told her to
sleep on my bed but she just slept in
the guest room where the cat toilet
is for some reason she prefers to sleep
there even though my room has a big TV
on the
wall that she can use to binge wash
no she decides to sleep in the well I
always say it's not that stinky you know
it's not that
stinky it really
isn't because the the cat toilet is
really good I I I spent three hours the
other day
watching even though I already have a
cat's toilet that I really that I'm so
happy with um watching 3 hours of like
really detailed really well well filmed
and and
documented
um well YouTube video of oh God
reviewing like pretty much every cat
toilet automatic cat toilet that there
is out
there I don't know why but it was
just
enchanting like the guy was so good at
making it interesting although like okay
at some point where he was talking about
the same toilet for 1 hour and it wasn't
even a good
one wasn't even like okay like worth
like at some point after after after 45
minutes I was like okay can we move on
to the next
toilet but still I don't know why I
don't know why I had to watch it it was
just so interesting to me
okay I didn't even feel the need to get
a different toilet but
next
toilet now it was it was um I think like
like four different videos that were all
like pretty long like 45 50 60 Minutes
of cat toilet comparisons
reviews but he's got like a million cats
and he was able to test it so
thoroughly and and it's so funny and he
had cameras everywhere and so you would
see them use it you know and he has this
one cat who is like a troublemaker in
terms of toilet going um but a big help
in terms of testing the
toilets o all right because this toilet
peace like like like Kell's ghost cat I
told her about
it so Kelly has also by my
recommendation I would say one like a a
an automatic cat lit robot but not the
one I have I think hers is like oh yeah
definitely like one of the cheaper ones
um but it should still work I was
thinking but the problem is ghost cat
yeah uh she told me
that
he when he goes into the toilet he his
butt looks outside the opening and he
pees and I think also poops outside of
[Music]
it so one of this these cats um from the
review guy also does that and he was
trying to solve the issue so I gave cie
some advice but seems like she still
uses her normal toilets as well ah there
she is she's still
listening so she's like you know
combining them I
guess yeah you know there's there's a
lot of lore to the robot toilet world
out there I've learned so much if mine
ever breaks then I'll watch the review
the fre hour review again and figure out
which one to buy
next but ghost cat is not the only one
basically was what I was telling her is
like he's not alone there's other cats
who have this issue okay he's not alone
in this okay other people suffer just
like you and other cats suffer just like
him did you see that the way it went
like P that was almost the
end
cat pooping support groups that's what
we really need in this world
Yes W this is a an awkward constellation
isn't it we have two paches we have two
pineapples they don't want to
touch it's getting
really claustrophobic up
[Music]
here
oh well you know I've been in situations
where it looked like it was ending a lot
of times and it was still like gyy
ah
continuing see never give up but it's
probably ending
soon
H yeah that's
that ah
oh oh yeah mhm
bye-bye oh 1,500 that's at least a clean
looking number your end game I know my
end game is
[\h__\h] okay let's try to let's try to
focus a little bit what can we
do when I focus normally in games I'm
often better at them when I don't Focus
right I think also other people have
experienced that with this game that
they're better when they don't Focus too
much and just just brain empty mode you
know but let's try to let's try to do
our best you know the problem is I have
so many things to tell you you
know but don't have to tell you all of
them at once right
yeah so weird to be back home again I
wasn't even gone for that
[Music]
long
for reflex based games yeah that's so
weird I do better with those when I
don't
Focus oh
yeah ooh EUR Vision yeah I got an
extension so we're still working on it
we could have been finished
already I I I would have honestly for
your revision it's not over yet you know
and I'm I'm really still hoping for it
because it would be good for all of us
okay for you EUR vision for
finally I mean for Germany Eurovision
for finally making some headlines again
and not about getting zero points but
about having an interesting act who may
get zero points but at least gets
headlines something new isn't that what
you want
headlines all press is good press there
is no bad
press
um what was I saying what was I going to
say oh yeah I I I'm still hoping for it
but I
don't it's just really I I don't have
too much trust in
them risking something like
that I know we can make it work but they
might also be doubting like how can we
make it work you know how can we get a
virtual artist on stage Etc but I
already have a lot of ideas you know I
thought about
it but yeah that might that might be why
they will just ignore
my audition possibly I feel like Austria
see I can the things of your vision you
don't need to be from the country that
you're applying for it would be
ideal but you don't have
to so and since I speak German and all
that you know I thought I can I can
audition for
Germany but I generally feel like
Austria would be more open for crazy
[\h__\h] like
this it's just Austria does their
auditions differently they're more like
you know they Scout people rather than
letting them
audition at least we get a new K song of
course you would be getting one
anyway honestly the song that we have
now wouldn't have been what I would
wanted to release next like I had some
ideas in my head um but since you know
we're going for the Eurovision I decided
to go for something else um it wouldn't
have normally been the next single that
I
release but this is
fine yeah but yeah I'm going to try for
Germany if it doesn't work out it's fine
I'll try again next year for Austria for
real for real this
time yeah we'll see we'll see I I really
want this to
[Music]
work but it's really only about how much
risk they're willing to take also I will
say I'm
vocally
not uh on the
level as most EUR Vision contestants are
they have weird songs and weird acts
here and there but
generally most of them have great
vocals I'm I'm not the type of person
who can belt like
crazy uh but I bring something else to
the table a great song something
interesting and new and refreshing
unique and decent
vocals and
dancing yeah it's it it would be
live but I know I know chances are very
high that they just you know turn me
down
so
so don't get your hopes up I don't have
my hopes up very high
either we'll see
we'll see we'll
[Music]
see is every why is everything so
orange not that I am complaining I
[Music]
mean
yally group
entry yeah I mean that could work
but no see I am the most European thing
that whole life has to offer so it's my
thing okay this is my
thing I am going to do this if
anything as a solo artist
mhm
dot yeah well the only European
thing
yeah see we can see that as
the one good thing about being the only
European make something good out of that
Monopoly that I have n need the
[\h__\h] the
apples why won't the apples
[Music]
touch
this is why Android is better what are
you talking about a okay I also
really prefer Androids yep maybe I
should have done that up here oh well
we'll get another opportunity
surely Bam
Bam [\h__\h]
this come on I need to be
saved from this hell okay we're going to
try it oo squeeze squeeze squeeze yeah
yeah touch touch
touch you little
[\h__\h] it's still too tight too freaking
tight
apple Mama Mia
[Music]
Mama it's
okay we're getting low and low okay okay
I was consistently off screen getting
1,900 let's focus for real for real cuz
I said I would focus and I still went on
[Laughter]
attention just wow
things okay okay so let's just let's
just
um talk about what's going on on the
screen I don't like playing games like
this but let's just say oh I'm dropping
a strawberry oh I'm dropping a is this a
mandar wait if that's a this is an
orange is this supposed to be a
mandarine or what is it the
anyway yeah like a
mea I think
it's that's
like first things first I'm kind of late
to even
like notice this wa this is we have to
set that straight before we go anywhere
else
okay let's see how far we get oh hey
when did I stop
moving
since how long have I not been Moving
kcki Co on show
tickle huh
[Music]
tickle what what what are you guys
talking about just say it simply it's an
orange and it's a
meon why give it such complicated names
what the [\h__\h] is a
nickon isn't that just an
orange P what the [\h__\h] is a Pon
again uh Pon I heard it before what's
the what's the German for
Pon find me the info on that find me the
Deets oh touch oh we got a peach already
early early Peach see my early game
strong a seed that's
[Music]
orange person is Kaki huhy what
happened Kaki what the [\h__\h] I have to
find a
picture I don't really see that much in
the
supermarkets no no
[Music]
bouncing
Man
Down uh let's put put it here and then
put no hey it did the thing again why
does it do that it's
like bamboozling
[Music]
me Gat Apper
nah firston is not a gat Apple cuz
that's a grenade
Apple no wait uh Canad Apple was what
was it
again I keep on forgetting why is it not
just grenade
Apple pom grenade pumu
grenade very explosive
pumu it's
[Music]
moving
no oh when I was
watching when I was watching Celly when
I was staying over at her place and I
was listening to her um even way after I
left the
room that was so funny that was so funny
cuz I was like out of the room I was
playing it loudly on my phone and then
and then and then she heard it and I was
like laughing so hard but you guys
didn't hear my laugh right she only
heard the music I don't know if she
heard my laugh or if the mic pic she
probably heard it but the mic probably
didn't pick it up but I was I was losing
it it so funny and and then and then I
continued watching it quietly more less
quietly and yeah just reminded me
because of the pomeg grenade she was
talking about at some point she was like
saying fruit names in in Spanish and
others right and then she was like
what's watermelon aquamelon
[Music]
but she was making fun of that like
somebody commenting
that but there's so in so many languages
like also in German it's really just
literally auua melon basically like
watermelon Vasa
melona so it would oo wouldn't even be
that far off you know you know what I'm
saying
[Music]
unfortunately it's not
P unfortunately it's not Pomo
grenade
Pomeranian
grenade wait what was it again what was
it again in English I forgot
already sand patila well okay well you
get this one okay it's not literally
translated but but it could be because
it is in other languages like German pom
oh it is pomegranate what did I say
before grenade
Apple that was
it I like
[Music]
that you might argue that I'm still
tanging and I'm not
[Music]
focusing but you may only argue that if
you want to go to the usual
room I can do what I want okay I will
fill the Silence with the words that I
want to fill it with may it be oh hey
there's an orange make him
touch or may it be interesting
tangents this is the waa
way a nothing wrong with chatting while
playing anyways right right I think this
is perfect this is the perfect zong game
right now for
me did you see that cute
bounce
[Music]
cute you know my mom you know what what
game my mom is absolutely obsessed with
right now and I was shocked at seeing
her play hours oh my
God I think I already told you a little
bit stard you
Valley stard you Valley now always
thought wo I always thought that was
like solely uh like a farming game but
wow I was
wrong and then my mom showed me her safe
files there were two that were around
100 hours then there was one with 172
hours and then there was one with 192
hours holy [\h__\h]
mommy holy [\h__\h]
mommy holy
[\h__\h] and she was just like like kind of
like brushing it off like it's not that
much 100 how long did we play Fire
Emblem and that seemed very long to me
also something like 100 100 something
anything that's over 100 is
long holy [\h__\h] yeah she would be like
streaming more than Kyla if she was part
of Hol
[Music]
life anything over 30 anything over 50
is long you think
so my Zelda playr was the longest but I
didn't I think my Fire Emblem streams
were the longest in total Zelda was
longer in terms of how much time I spent
on it but I don't think I streamed it
more than I streamed firm just because I
did so much off screen
[Music]
right Kyla Mama
collab my mom also really loves um
[Music]
Terraria Nissa do you want to play
Terraria with my mom bonding
[Music]
time well Emma RPGs are different I
wouldn't really like compare
[Music]
mmpg what the
[\h__\h] what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] I was saying I wouldn't really
compare uh mm RPGs with normal games
playtime because well I mean do I even
have to explain mean why the grenade
Apple well at least I know at least is I
guess exploding in the
air my
God I must go my people need
me grenade Apple what that how's that
Grenade song Go Again ah I would catch a
grenade for
I I would I how's the Melody I why I
always forget it I would catch a grenade
for you no cuz I cuz I would catch a
grenade for
[Music]
you my hand on the pl for you what was
that what the
[Music]
lyric
hey I'm
currently
well how am I going to start this
sentence I am i ooh I'm in the
midst because time is ticking like a
Time bump like a grenade Apple in the
midst of planning for my upcoming half a
year late bir concert guys
and jenma is
frightened before I left her I just once
again told her all the things we need to
prepare and she is frightened I'm trying
my best to make it like like
easy like put
everything
easily o overview for her
like this is what we need and this is we
need these these instrumentals we need
uh choreographies for these songs we
need to get new ones for these songs but
we also need to ask for permissions for
the original choreographies for these
songs if we can use them BL blah BL blah
blah you know a lot of things to plan
damn I'm trying to help her so cuz like
she's overloaded with other
[Music]
workma G but also me about it because I
always feel I also feel stressed out
about
it yeah cie made me
realize when she said like when she will
see me again roughly oh peaches peaches
peaches PES PES PES PES PES PES PES PES
they're moving closer thank you grave
for rolling it
over thank you what was I doing saying
oh yeah she made me realize that my next
trip to Japan is fairly
soon huh hey hey yeah that's what that
I'm trying to do thank you
Pineapple thank you thank
you yeah I think I'm not sure how long
the next trip will be cuz I want I need
to do some like dance lessons too so I
need to
calculate first of all I need to
calculate how much time do I really need
to be
there and if it's like
um any it's probably minimum two weeks
so you know what I'll do this time I
don't think I'll book a
hotel uh I'll book a like a mansion type
of place so I can try to stream more
easily and don't have to book the
streaming booth in our studio where I'm
I can't really be be
spontaneous okay oh no they okay this is
another like English Japanese Japanese
English thing wait wait wait
wait in Japanese they call um an
apartment even the tiny one room
apartment cheap one room apartment that
you you just call it mansion mansion any
small apartment like apartment and
Mansion are interchangeable in Japanese
okay
and then especially like there's like
you know weekly monthly and yearly I
guess Apartments AKA Mansions they call
it weekly
Manion and uh or or Mani Manion you
know and those usually come with a
kitchen and like proper internet and
Furniture um but it looks more like a
normal apartment
rather
than uh a hotel room there's no cleaning
either and you can start booking those
starting from like a week if you get a
weekly one I think mhm but not like for
only like three days I mean maybe you
could but that's not how what what
you're supposed to do like it's not
really common
yeah
is the PGM from the game yeah I wish
they could um add an option where you
can turn it off after hearing it
for 5 days you might want to hear
something
else especially you guys cuz you
probably heard it longer than I did
already if you watch other girls
streams if we could still change it we
just don't get like I could mute the
whole game and we could just turn on my
bgm but then you don't hear all the
popping sounds
well then you don't hear the popping
sounds so yeah I was going to probably
get a mansion this
time um yeah so then I can hopefully
stream more frequently in the next trip
cuz I know you guys are
suffering without
me and I also feel bad when I can't
deliver the usual content as
much yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah we truly are suffering the
most I always miss you when you go oh
man
[Music]
no sounds like you'll be really busy
with dancing anyway well no I
mean like I would say
[Music]
I probably wouldn't plan for more than
maximum 3 hours per day because it's
just like when you put in a new
choreography in your
head like you know just like in school
you lose focus after a
while
so normally we don't do more than two or
three hours
anyway so yeah I probably like a whole
week every day three two three hours
dance lessons
uh and then you know I go home and a
nice
dream
so not
bad yeah only so much you can or you
really like I mean you could force more
I I used to have um dance lessons longer
than that like 5 6
[Music]
hours
yeah but that's long time ago and
woohoo and not necessary now to do
that yeah it's like a big ass workout I
I used to get so exhausted by that like
o 6 hours and then often it would be
followed up by singing lessons another
one or two
hours yeah good times good
[Music]
times why is there no eggs in this game
they're also round pretty
round about as round as the strawberry
is I request egg
extension
expansion than
fruit excuse
me how do you know that for
sure well I guess you once wear one but
that doesn't really mean that you know
anything about your own body like that
okay you know nothing J
[Music]
know can we can we I need to
rewatch all the all the I don't know you
know like it's not only Hana who says
this stuff but hers is like the most
famous I would say and the
most like ah it gets it gets you the
most and I even can look like hanawa
with my cat ears and all
that never watched it it's so good man
watch
[Music]
it forever my
favorite I've only seen parts of it it's
so good there's so much
dialogue when I watched it for the first
time I had to like stop uh so often to
like
[Music]
read and there's like so much hidden
dialogue as well like not what they're
saying but like what's written on the
screen to
so interesting oh my God why does
nothing want to
touch
[Music]
you baste taste thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank
you I know I
[Music]
know
M making
me a little bit
[Music]
angry wish they finished the just the
story I still believe it seems like I'm
the only one I still
believe that they're going to put out
another season anime at some point I
know every time I say this they're like
oh but they're done and I'm like no just
because the most recent one is called OB
mon doesn't mean it's
OB they said there's more I'm pretty
sure I
believe I believe that there will be
more I will not give up
woohoo jump scare why are all my
failures recently because something pops
out I didn't have this off
[Music]
screen Cherry
catapult yeah
[Music]
if you reach 2K maybe you get another
season nah you
can't you I am a very realistic person I
cannot be teased
and what's the word for Ang again in
English uh fish
like that baited
[Music]
baited not that
easy oh yeah
yeah
Peach nice push
grape nice
push
still pushing don't know what you're
pushing it
for oh interesting interesting
development here ooh everything's
like I'm getting good
[Music]
[Applause]
fruits
[Music]
525,000 thank
you amazing runs of and this is my
perfect early game although not perfect
I had better early game
before and touch come on come on come on
P
[Music]
nice
hey
[Music]
you speak Japanese I speak Japanese I
speak the Glorious nongo
language
[Music]
yes about your back problems have you
tried
kinesiologist not someone who specifies
in that I think
no but yeah I I'm planning to go to the
doctor like soon but this time like a
new new one again
um and I'm going to be straight up
telling him I for me the most important
thing is not the like until now it
wasn't like getting painkillers and [\h__\h]
I refused
painkillers I said I want to get behind
the reason of it so let's get behind the
reason of it but recently I'm going
absolutely insane this whole oo Japan
trip
was
excruciating so I want to get this
like ringe that everybody talks
about I want to get
steroids I will say it and for that I
will even go to a
doctor a special one where I think I'll
need to pay more although no not really
probably but a v show that he actually
listens to me we have choices of free
doctors in like free types of doctors in
Austria like the general ones that
anybody with an insurance just uses and
they're like the cheapest ones so they
don't you don't pay anything normally
and then they they have lots of
customers so they don't get to take much
time for you then there's the Val
which seemingly you're
paying the same as the cheap ones but
you have to send I'm not really sure if
I understand the system but you have to
send the thing in to the insurance on
your own more or less and then
um I don't know it's I don't know how
it's different it's like a private
somehow like it seems like a private
doctor but in the end it's not I don't
know how to explain it I don't
know um but they are usually already
better like in terms of how much time
they take for
you what what what I guess you don't get
everything back but it's better than
than a private doctor where well you
could still get something back with a
private doctor if you send it in um but
not as much as with a Val choice they I
guess Choice
doctor doctor of your
choice so it's like yeah I
guess yeah how much you pay on your own
part I guess I don't know but vot just
like shouldn't be so bad in terms of how
much you pay out of your own
pocket uh I don't know it's complicated
[Music]
I think the system only exists in
Austria really really maybe in Germany
too
[Music]
though what's the thir type that's the
private
doctor yeah the most people use the the
first one that I said that the cheap one
that's just like takes any any
insurance unless there's no insurance
then it's basically the same as a
private doctor but like a bad private
doctor that's not really worth going to
then you might as well go to a real
private
doctor you know what I'm
saying I'm not good at at explaining
this because I don't really understand
either it's just how things are here
so man it's always the strawberries like
they trickle down and I don't know if
that's a good thing because I I feel
like it's always the thing that messes
everything up that I have too many
strawberries in the in between spaces
sometimes they touch each other you know
sometimes it trickles down sometimes I
get the trick trickle down effect no
sometimes calm down cute
skitt calm
down calm
down I kind of like taking care of don't
dump them in I
am I'm doing everything right see
almost almost we have two pineapples
okay is good it's good good all is good
all is
[Music]
well this is not
good you got that pineapple I'm going on
two one two
three stream my new single Pine Apple
from
po the mvy is up on
YouTube there's a dance short
[Music]
too I'm going two to free it tastes so
so so sweet go that way
yeah oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah keep
going in the oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
pineapple look and look at the
pineapples shaking they're trying to
dance but they're in a tight [\h__\h]
spot let them Dance Let the pineapples
dance let them
[Music]
dance oh thank you that's like a a sweet
Charming soft way of singing But if I
sing like that when recording it's not
like sometimes I feel like I want to
like it doesn't it doesn't fit for like
you know the songs but sometimes I feel
like I want to record a song where that
would fit it's like how new jeene
sings maybe
[Music]
partially you know I was I that new song
for EUR Vision that we absolutely rushed
recording um I recorded with Moy being
there she was like you know I mean we're
both in Japan we're we're normally not
ever in the same place so might as well
maybe you know have her be there and
give me some instructions if she wants
to
mhm and so she was there and she was
like she was she was praising me so much
uh and then and then and then later when
I gave it over to Johnny for mixing y he
was also praising me so much like they
were praising me more than usual Okay so
I think my singing in this mysterious
year Vision
Song is pretty I must also say like I
sang in ways that I normally don't sing
um
in most of the
time yeah it's uh I sang with a lot of
attitude and with a lot of
confidence normally no confidence now
yes
[Music]
confidence what the
[\h__\h]
oh can I put it
here o
moving no
[Music]
or is
it hi dony wony good morning dony wony
hi hi baby did you hear the
[Music]
meow
so
cute she's squid squatching the
tree chuny wonky my mom really prais
chunky
wonky for for being such a good Babble
Babble always just sleeping she was
praising her for just always
sleeping
yeah apparently um smoothie When I Was
Gone wasn't eating so well I was like M
that's weird normally she eats
everything that I give her she's not
that picky with wet
food um but it must have been cuz I was
gone cuz when I gave her the same food
she just ate it
normally now smoothie gets a little bit
weird when I'm not there makes me feel
bad
no she missed
me so my mom she said yeah this smovie
was annoying to her too but but when she
heard this morning when she heard
how uh oh no last night actually when I
was giving her dinner when she heard how
loud smoothie gets with me she was
shocked she was like oh smoothie was
already loud and annoying to me but this
is like even worse and I'm like yeah
this is
normal this is
normal but I'm I'm used to it and
because I woke up so early today she
couldn't even you know get that usual
midnight wakey wakey the Wawa to annoy
her moment squeezed in cuz I was awake
mhm so she only treats you this way no
she also annoyed mommy but not as much
as she annoys
me it's okay I love her honestly in the
end in Japan even without smoothie I
wasn't able to sleep for anyway
cuz cuz of the idol
meetings I need to maybe is this is this
something that comes with
age a not so steel
bladder
yeah but I thought it was later age way
later than
that yeah I'm not that old don't drink
all I'm trying to not drink that much on
on it's just like a sippy
sip sippity sip small sip
sip I I know that that's the problem
just drinking before sleeping but I like
like you know when I get when I okay
here's my
routine I watch you know like some
Netflix and stuff before going to sleep
I try to
W I tried to wait until the very
last moment before I'm falling asleep to
go to another to to
mhm I try to drag it down as long as
possible and also not drank like at that
point
anymore but I guess I got to how how
much time does there need to
be what's the science how much time does
a body a human body
need to work through
liquids two
massage your bladder muscle no
e various from person to
[Music]
person two
two I can't
my especially not when the air is really
dry I I can't I guess I'll just continue
waking up or suffering with excruciating
stomach pain no at night
yeah at least at least one sippy sip
right maybe maybe don't drink much
within those 2 hours and then before
sleep I can take one more small small
sip right right the small small sip
won't be my downfall
right
right you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] I never really have that problem
wow
ah Stone Benny Stone
Benny I'm not going to sleep with a
diaper you stupid diaper diaper
diaper you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] get your prostate check do I have a
prostate isn't that
[Music]
a isn't that a guy
thing yeah okay thank God see I know
anatomy
anatomy don't gastl
me oh cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
your little
shits oh
[Music]
man same same space waterfall just like
me for real for
real Pro is the man version of BBA
cancer exam
exam
uhhuh yeah yeah I I would say the the
the female version of it
is less intruding and more
acceptable cuz you guys get a hand up
your butt right
I am not jealous at
[Music]
all a camera sometimes e but I would
think it doesn't feel like the way when
you get a camera for your throat
woo um for your nose on your
fro
right he have you guys
had
um did you guys
um have this have this experience before
is this something you do as regularly as
women get
the the booby
test cuz the booby test pretty much
happens like almost every time when we
go to the women doctor
gynecologist
no
oh man you guys should do it earlier and
more more
often you're just hiding from
it we do it all the time I mean I mean
the booby
one after 40 is more
common
so okay you guys are very uncomfortable
with this topic I can see I can tell so
I will not switch to my holot talk
screen and interview you guys about your
experiences with
it just this
once no we're so waving
qued still here my dog always says I'm
too
young what the [\h__\h] maybe it's um you
know ostrich just has better health
insurance and stuff health care they
care more about my boobies
than they do about
yours that's a sad thing that's another
reason for you to move over to Austria
take care of your
boobies love your boobies make sure your
boobies are doing
well like honestly I I it does make me
feel a little bit
uncomfortable my gynecologist
ah she um she's nice and all
but she wants to check everything like
every time I go there even when I go
there just you know for a small small
recipe she wants to like go all in check
everything every
time probably for the money cuz she's a
private
doctor like she she checks
everything she she does the whole like
looking into my stomach
thing every time I'm like girl I'm fine
I'm I'm healthy don't no need to check
every single time but it's it's it's
like the recommended time anyway like am
like uh once half a year I
think is what uh science and doctors say
how often you need to check
everything for like whatever uterus and
booby cancer and all
that so it's really just the bare
minimum
ultrasound yeah ultra
sound wooho woohoo
[Applause]
wooho
woohoo you [\h__\h] go
[Music]
down Mario nah that was not
Mario e
[Music]
man come
on
[Music]
bu
okay
conate CH gr chill the
egg
egg go egg
[Music]
go just like
BF ah this is
[Music]
[\h__\h]
Nan the [\h__\h] what's with these explosive
fruits
huh the [\h__\h] I'm going to call I'm going
to call the
FBI there's too many explosives here
it's concerning
me cuz it's concerning
[Music]
me it's my concern
o I'm an explosive
fruit I'm going one two one two you know
there's this um Japanese idol group that
is produced by um jyp which is um
JY this a jyp meme sorry um is a
Japanese uh Korean producer uh Korean
Idol group producer but he made this
like Japanese group
and Yulia do you know the J
M with his auto tune uh do I wait I
don't I don't see that the road Castle
doesn't have autotune it's so
sad and um yeah it's
[Music]
called oh they released recently a song
that's called
coconuts recently and I just released my
pineapple song and I just felt like you
know there was so much Synergy there and
it's so cute and they also went with
this whole like summer Fame you know and
they go like Co coconuts it's so cute I
really like
it I really like their Coconut song
[Music]
cooc
I was thinking man they did this on
purpose right they they tried to be like
you know matching with me I release
pineapple they release coconuts both
summer tropical fruits for a summer song
okay okay I'll see you ni you I'll see
you can you cover it see I've been
thinking about this
Japanese songs generally are okay to
cover
uh they release music in Japan as a
Japanese
group but they're produced by Korean
label but I do think in theory it should
be
fine but yeah so I I was thinking about
it maybe for even performing it in a
Fredy concert cuz you know their songs
are cute catchy they even have some
English versions of their songs which I
would think would still count as a
Japanese
song cuz it's just the English version
of it and I think it would count and
then you know I like any kind of English
song that I can perform in an archived
[Music]
stream nii you not n you
it's n i z i
[Music]
u pom covered one of oh oh my
Nani
did you release an actual cover let me
look that
up P which one p p need
you you mean did she just sing it in an
archived stream or so because I don't
see like an a cover with Anna and
[Music]
what which
one
wait
what which are you sure this one
the I found one song that they did
together but this isn't this this
isn't are we talking about the same
thing 7 months ago this is no you get
you don't understand it's that
is
that does not need
you
uncultured
uneducated Idol
knowledge it's completely
different not the
same where's my there he is I'm so
disappointed
[Music]
yeah
I'm cultured swines I'm very
sorry it's okay but
damn
Dam
no you know
nothing you don't know a thing about the
things that I like ah I stopped
moving
[Music]
you try
really doesn't seem like you do wait why
do I why am I so tilted because of
you it's because of you
guys and that's a big oof that's a big
oof
[Music]
okay I am going to
concentrate I
suppose Justice
wants Justice
once H
English funny language
300 yeah
mhm just this once you will get justice
but only
once English
English I want the chry to go in there
please yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh oh oh oh
[Music]
appu
appu I listened to the
Shi song by the way for the first time
today oh my God the dance is so
cute I want to learn the
[Music]
dance that song has gone insane yeah it
took me a while to listen to
it
oh it's so funny yeah it blew up sheesh
and then I saw the 8bit drummer played
it
too
but this and and he also played that um
interet song and it made me a bit
concerned cuz like normally doesn't he
try like isn't he like really religious
and he tries to stay away from anything
that's like
y uh and the internet Y is like really
yby and the SEC song well kind of yby
too if you think about it he doesn't
know he doesn't
know yeah but he has as far as I know he
like Turned Down songs before that are
like sensitive in terms of the topics of
the
[Music]
song and for the song I Don't
Know But for I think for the internet Yo
song like the the the music
video I feel like it kind of gives it
away what it's
about more or less like not really in
detail but it's like you know it's kind
of
[Music]
yaai did you see my
short did you see my short also he only
did love rush and and pineapple so far
did people not recommend retrospective
yet cuz I really want him to play
retrospective but maybe we'll just
recommend it or you guys will recommend
it I mean when
um when
oh go
up when I put out a video for it
n okay ah okay he only does it with
video okay I guess that's not I mean
it's on YouTube with a link but I guess
it's not considered a
video okay okay that's fine all
right I really liked his version of Love
rush like for pineapple I surprisingly
didn't feel it as much as for love
rush I was surprised too cuz I didn't
think well this can't be the end hello
mus mus I didn't think hey I don't want
this to be the end that it would work so
well with
[Music]
the with the drums because they're so
loud and love vers is a sweet song you
know
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] don't say GG it's a good
[Music]
run
okay okay
[Music]
focus no
GG no yum one
GG
don't at least no ye yeah it was a legit
loss
[Music]
yeah cuz Every Time We Touch cuz you
keep plugging stuff of what what the I'm
just trying to do my best here okay I'm
just trying to combine things and
sometimes it just won't
[Music]
okay
sometimes it just doesn't work the
way you know otherwise the game would be
too
easy of course there's just doesn't go
ideally
[Music]
always big things deide little to
another maybe
maybe
[Music]
oh I'm not doing bad don't gasl me into
thinking I'm doing bad I'm fine and I'm
happy
okay I'm
happy I'm not feeling like this is the
end of the
world I'm fine
[Music]
this is my life doesn't oh depend on S
game for
[Music]
real ah don't roll so
far too much
Vigor okay anybody here who watched the
whale of Time
finale it was like actually so good
critics also say that the second season
is better than the first season so maybe
give it a chance
guys was so
good the last episode especially
damn a good finale really great finale
in my
opinion not giving it a chance after
that first season oh come on please do
it for
me do it for me
please I'd rather read the
books me me me me please if they change
the name maybe
[Music]
what I would read it instead no
oh yeah read it too
[Music]
but watch it so that we can talk about
it
understand I'm at season 2 episode 4
let's
go see I like you you're getting extra
points with the Wawa no hey stupid
Cherry
you think about y you're the best I can
always count on
[Music]
Julia who wants those point no you want
them of course you want them even my mom
like she doesn't she's
like she is so stubborn she loves Wheel
of Time Books and she loves all these
kind of shows you
know um but she's always been hating on
the
show uh like she gave the first season a
try maybe for like one or two episodes
and she gave up and she always
like you
know gets so mad and he when I talk
about Wheel of
Time um but what she is doing is
listening to reviews of the
show she also even already W oh oh
watched a
review of the final episode and she did
say to me and if you always put so much
weight on my mom's opinion then put some
weight on this she said she acknowledges
that the second season is definitely a
lot better than the first one and that
it's like genuinely good entertainment
and and a good a good a good product
[Music]
yeah
it's good she didn't watch it and she
won't for some reason even though she
literally herself is saying it's
good just by watching uh oh reviews oh
yes yes good
stuff but you
know my mom said so she kind of approves
of it you know kind of in a weird
way
well that's just rude that's just
[Music]
rude
shaking the peach is
[Music]
twerking now listen here you little
[\h__\h] see how they all just
refuse to just be nice oh there we go
thank you orange the orange was like now
you little
[\h__\h] listen here you little [\h__\h] just
like the orange would normally
do orange is the only one that I can
rely on here I love the
orange the orange is the one that like
pulls and
everyone's I don't know they they're
just you know they they're they're the
adults
here they're the extroverts here who go
to the introverts and are like okay okay
enough of your
introvertism get out of your freaking
shell and touch your partner
now it's a metaphor for me yes of course
it is what did you think it
was everything is a metaphor for me
[Music]
ah hey uh
stupid but it's okay we can
s
uh Salvage mhm we can sve and Salvage
and salivate or so anything can be done
really if you believe in it
m
mukashi
all
[Music]
right no it's not over look at
this it's
[Music]
fine
um hi
okay
uh
uh uh touch touch touch ah
[Music]
careful wrong one uh
[Laughter]
why
[Music]
why don't say GG to me it feels so
so what's the word don't you ha
[Music]
me what do the what do they always
say Patron
yeah no it's okay sorry I'm just joking
I'm just
[Music]
joking hey
he
[Music]
hey
what don't you li to me with your $
haircut who says that I never heard that
one
before who says that oh should have sent
the Cherry down there um it will get
there
eventually
yeah see Told You
So it got there it's a a
drag oh Dragon
Ball oh why won't you
touch come on yeah there you
go oh oh oh m
[Music]
interesting
interesting oh
[Music]
interesting doesn't that look pretty
decent so far strong early
game strong early game from the
[Music]
waha
they
say small left big right but eventually
the small ones become big too so what
happens then with to that
strategy see how it became big like what
what do you want me to do
theny oh oh
baby I have to make them big eventually
and then this happens so I think I'm
doing everything
correctly
pineapple I'm
going this game is great for promoting
pineapple is is cie the only one who
sings pineapple whenever she sees a
pineapple or are the other girls also
singing
pineapple I hope they
are stream pinea
nice hat thank you it smells nice
too I haven't heard anyone else sing it
they
should they're missing
out streamers love to fill silences with
random songs that match whatever they
just said or whatever is just happening
on the
screen don't we love doing that don't
[Music]
we because we can't think of anything
else to
say that
moment that's not just me no trust me
that is not just me many things are just
me but that is not just
[Music]
me trust me bro this D D Tanner is not
doing that but that's well I feel like
it's probably more of a girl streamer
thing she only does that of course she
does n thisa probably also everybody
does that come on come
[Music]
on
mhm here I'm dropping the small things
on the side for you guys just like you
said just like you told me to
[Music]
oh that's relatively small that goes
here
[Music]
too going pretty well going pretty
well hey all right Ricky do that you
quit you quit your
job why do I get a cut from
that thank you but be
[Music]
careful
um mhm
mhm
W hey
hello maybe we can get to 2,000 Ma on
but not the right melon we want the
watermelon I really like eating this
kind of melon though the this
one I like it more than the the one
that's orange inside
surprisingly doesn't that melon look
like there is a
no canop
calop
cantalope with
Tori because eloping with narissa
ravencraft
what no
okay oh oh oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
ah
M yeah
honeydew honey could you do something
for
me honey could you could you do
something for me could you cut the
Honeydew for me I want to eat it
[Music]
now
yeah oh you're so
sweet uh hey hey hey bring this Cherry
too hey
hey
[Music]
okay oh interesting interesting maybe
not the way you would have done
[Music]
it
m Cherry go
this is what Peak Performance looks
like I have my own strats
yeah should I put it here all
right yeah I was thinking about that too
ooh now these two need to meet would you
please I want I want ah I should have
put like a cherry there so that maybe
the lemon goes down to the the other
lemon then it meets the
peach
wait nah mukashi mukashi oh
well it's a that's not a pear a Paar the
pears that I know are shaped like a hot
woman's body
so that's a lemon to
me I I mean I've seen relatively round
pairs before but then they're
[Music]
[Applause]
no how do you are you assuming the Bears
race just now how do you know it's an
Asian bear maybe it's a lemon okay what
do we know we know nothing
n n
M calls it a
moon have you ever seen spherical
lemons
wow all right shut
up they are rounder than pears
[Music]
are you want to fight you want to fight
you want to fight huh fight me fight
me I hate
this now the lemons will never
touch
[Music]
man oh but maybe the peaches
will
well
how do we get the peach
[Music]
down pressure the peach peach listen
here you're being watched but I don't
know 7,000 something live viewers I am
pressuring you to do something helpful
here right now don't block the STW which
one you mean this
one yeah okay should I put it here or
should I put it then
[Music]
here on top right of grapes
yeah on the grape okay
ah it rolled over oh no it's shaking
everything's shaking this gives me a
feeling like something's going to pop
any
moment um we can put strawberry and
strawberry Berry then grape becomes that
and you know you know how things go from
there oh oh it's pushing it's going to
touch ah no it's not going to
touch it might touch
soon we have another strawberry coming
up so where does the Cherry go where
does the Cherry go where do the cherry
go I'm letting you backseat me for once
it's it's actually a miracle I haven't
let you backseat me until
now between orange and lemon orange and
pear okay let's see be careful
careful okay nothing's
[Music]
happening
um
where do this one
go where should we put that
one next to
Orange
[Music]
left
okay oh no woohoo oh okay ah ah
everything's trickling down in a bad
way okay okay okay there's so much [\h__\h]
down
there
[Music]
uh y oh I did that I did
that
wo come
on that was
[Music]
good is it moving no not
anymore I want the means to
touch anyway and wait it's it's it is
moving it is moving oh oh it is
all right okay nice
yeah
okay small SM art
SM SM
SM I want to put it
there go follow not like that okay okay
no
oh small small
[Music]
more
uh where go M middle maybe just or like
here just to combine them
[Music]
again
strawberry I don't care maybe it can go
down and combine with another
strawberry you know might as
well
touch we have a a a
car let's go with a gut
feeling thank you for trusting my gut
feeling oh we're making we're making
something else now all
right making something
[Music]
else uhoh it's getting full oh
moving should I combine
now
yeah combine
[Music]
and so still
moving I don't know looks pretty bad to
me I mean the Apple's still far from the
limit but there's so much empty space
there and then there's so much trickled
down small
fruit it's pretty
bad oh
oh should I try to push it
down it'll become an apple before it
reaches the bottom though
[Music]
probably don't [\h__\h] to push yeah not
with the orange it's too big to push
yeah that's what I'm thinking it will
probably just touch and become an
apple all
right
oh are things moving no not
really
um is this
[Music]
salvageable yes no no
yeah
the Cherry yeah the Cherry is
bad all right if you guys already don't
have hope anymore I'm just going to do
whatever and maybe we'll get something
good out of
[Music]
it this will fall
down
no
but this is the best I got so far on
[Music]
stream okay okay now this one will be
good this one is going to be
good cuz I have a
feeling I just feel
[Music]
it
yeah not sure if K or ban why does she
also always say p p when she said when
she plays this
[Music]
game
calculated solid start right my my
Beginnings are
strong but maybe one might say it's so
just because the beginnings are
[Music]
easy
hey
PES let's go oh let's go push nice push
getting
everything in
order currently I was thinking of
putting smaller things on one side again
but I change my
[Music]
mind
H I just want
to
um I want to keep things from going down
too
far like all the smaller
ones so you know I want to keep them in
reach to be
accessible too
far yeah did you guys see Council R is
not council is
anymore did you see that councilor is
not Council anymore council is now
promise I'm happy for them being like
their own gen now like they were
already like doing so many things
together
anyway have you noticed that like when
you pronounce it in
Japanese misu is
myth
English and then there's now
English
I I noticed this and it's like bothering
me that in Japanese it sounds so similar
in English it
doesn't yeah it's the pro
myth and myth it's like they're an
expansion of us or so I don't know
but it's weird cuz like in English it's
not like that at
all but I wonder if they noticed when
they decided on the name that it sounds
very similar in like the hiiki hippi got
kind so
there's and Advent you know like if you
if you list them up like
that uh like Advent stands out a lot
Advent sounds very
different and adento I
[Music]
guess Mis and P they're so
similar should we change Advent
to misu p
misu po something else that sounds like
that
a Mis put Mis soup or I don't know but
me it's Mis so soup not Mis
soup T oh oh that would have been
nice just call instead of Promise call
them
tiu
I don't know I don't know that doesn't
really solve the
issue reth actually would be interesting
because the re sounds similar
too REM for for
Advent no but I what I'm saying is I
don't want them to sound so
similar I just I just can't think of it
in
[Music]
Japanese
but it's nice I'm I'm glad that they're
like
officially
officially an
item
[Music]
ooh
oh an item
[Music]
yeah yeah I saw like
um
uh itss and bits B Bops of the collab
stream was really
funny really
funny what am I
doing okay I was like pretty much
playing brain empty mode
again but it seemed
fine
it's probably still going to go bad cuz
yeah I have a different feeling now my
oh hey I mean maybe maybe it's
fine maybe maybe brain empty is the way
to
go
mama going to leave this strawberry here
actually Oh see it's pushing things wow
totally on purpose I should have dropped
the orange before that though
sh M I was waiting for for things to
happen the strawberry was a good good
decision though
hello empty
[Music]
sty no thank you style oh no hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey you little
[\h__\h] a look at that mess down there
they almost they almost
touched they almost
touched come on yeah all
right
[Music]
he
stage one melon the
quiet yeah Oh you mean like cuz the
other one is stage two
melon this my actually I can't even say
this is my favorite melon I like both
like pretty much
equally although honestly maybe this is
my I might prefer it over
watermelon I love watermelon but
watermelon is just not even as filling
as the Honeydew honeydew is a bit more
filling and it's still
refreshing watermelon is more like you
know you you eat it when you want to be
refreshed oh [\h__\h] yeah this is not good
I'm sorry I'm sorry but we'll fix it see
I fixed it see I'm still fixing
[Music]
it I know I know I know not ideal I know
I know there's like so much [\h__\h] in the
gaps I
[Music]
do you put salt on your mmel no I
don't
no
MM never tried it I like the watermelon
the way it is but I I guess I I think I
know some people do that
yeah oh see but some people are
surprised but it's a thing
it is a
[Music]
thing man
man uh
why
ah
oh oh oh oh touch
[Music]
down
do where do I put
it I don't want to put it here because
I maybe I'll put it here at the
top
M cuz I also want to keep this open
still I
think on top left
Apple I'll put it here oh oh it moves a
little bit just a little
bit and
then
uh this one's a toughy
[Music]
too
the song has dug a channel into your
[Music]
brain when new beat box I don't think
you can call it
beatbox oh it's turning the wheel is
turning the melon of time melon of
time careful
now
ah Cherry oh wait for
me go Cherry go I believe in you I
believe in you too
Mikan danger danger
danger
[Music]
alarm
dangerous very
dangerous it's not over shut up it's not
over you want me to par
[Music]
it oh
ah can I can I put one more
[Music]
ah
dangerous
living living very very dangerous oh oh
very
[Music]
dangerous sad life
peing
[Music]
suffering
1,500 yeah but damn how much did I get
when I played at Call's Place those two
times my first
ever times playing
sua does anybody
know you got to check the archive go
go ooh 1,300 for my first try let's go
that's not
bad I want to get better
though you know the means look like
little little chickens little chicks
actually don't
they wouldn't you
[Music]
agree
I think they look like fruits actually
uh
meds wow I don't know what's wrong with
you are you
[Music]
okay orange looks like phoenixes the red
one's like chicken uh okay that's a
stretch but no okay they they still
remind of Ki yeah but see how is this
not a chick
chick a chick
chick oh there was no thought behind
what I just did just letting you
[Music]
know no go to the
right
[Music]
go
down
oh
catapult oh push oh oh oh W there's
something going on all
[Music]
right you know now that the season two
of Wheel of Time is done I think I'm
going to start the ooh Vikings
valala I wonder it's good cuz the end
like the last episodes last season of
Vikings was bad we talked about
that but I think people haven't have
been saying oh decent things about
Valhalla no not the
anime hey this is a decent decent early
game
oh see you you you you you doubted what
I just said for a moment right and then
then now you take back your words and
your
[Music]
thoughts it's a sequel yeah it's a
sequel I say that about every early game
well because my early game is always
decent pineapple
when are you going to watch Breaking
bed I'm going to purposefully not watch
it because of
[Music]
you quick
yeah oh oh
[Music]
should I let that
happen
h
ah
sorry ah now I can't reach all the
grapes
[Music]
anymore
M um St B
[Music]
go usually cool people like oh shut up
clut your
finger you keep you need to keep big
fruits on the side the middle of bad
position well if it wants to be there
who am I to tell it go away like it it
doesn't work it's not listening it's not
listening to me
[Music]
um
M ah no
Teddy oh maybe it was a worthy
sacrifice oh see all things
oh
see
[Music]
see don't let them pushy yeah I'm taking
charge I know I know I know things are
okay you have to you have to be in
control but at the same time you also
have to give them a little bit of space
to do what what they want to do like at
least let them think that what they're
doing is what they want to
do let them
think
let them
think uh and let them eat
[Music]
cake cold leader
handbook
so
[Music]
oh
spicy cuz I'm too spicy for your oh guys
by the way in my schedule that I
uploaded
stop yeah yeah yeah push it push it push
it push it push it push it Mom Mom yeah
yeah trickle trickle trickle baby
trickle I was fine with
that I want wanted this to
happen uh in my schedule you did you see
the
um the AOE
two double
twice uh one is a collab yeah but you
guys are
thinking the wrong thing it's not what
you think it
is you guys were like oh my God Sun Moon
Sun Moon
mm- M no not only it is supposed to be
the T the little small smaller smaller
tournament
oh you guys need to trust me more but
there's so much space there we can keep
on pushing the melon though maybe maybe
maybe yeah yeah it's it's MAA and other
people yeah
but I don't want to jinx it but I don't
know if it's like uh you know for for
like AOE we need to get perms and then
for bigger ones we need to get even
better
perms sometimes for big events we need
like special
perms I don't know if like so far from
the last update I saw MAA didn't have
like the the final perms to have this
happen um
um and now like we're still like
considering changing the
time so from my point of view where I've
planned things many times recently that
have been uh turned down cuz I was too
late it doesn't I don't uh I feel like
it might have to be moved to next week
if uh this uhoh yes
continues oh oh oh see the melon is
being pushed over there it's a good
thing is
it it will happen but I'm I'm not that
like MAA is still like really sure it's
happening I think
oh a [\h__\h] wow I thought I was dropping
this thing here all
right
okay
H Apple ready to launch no no no
wait so okay this is dangerous we're
making uh something down here Apple into
lemon supposedly W okay something flew
but it wasn't the Apple all is okay all
is
[Music]
good why are you not pushing the grape
over where it needs to
be why you got to to be like that
[Music]
okay ah hello stop stop stop stop to
stop
moving careful with the Apple I know
where do I put the grape on St okay and
then this goes here and strawberry and
then yep mhm and then this and then that
oh
oh sexy quite
sexy ah uh that's good yeah grape grape
grape yeah mhm okay all right this is
pretty good I'm cooking I'm
cooking just translated I'm cooking into
Japanese
I mean fruit
[Music]
cooking and should I put it here on the
side what you think it's closer to the
other orange that
way middle
ma Center okay stay in middle like you a
little now where would you put the
Cherry cuz I would just put it down here
to meet the other Cherry
eventually which is probably the reason
why things always like go wrong for me
no left oh okay okay
okay stay in the middle like
little say head back where does this go
here or here not so good I would have
preferred
different different fruit right
now
[Music]
okay I guess
left oh oh yeah we should have just put
it h what's
happening left
again a cherry on top of the Red
Apple I see like two people saying that
m
[Music]
M they give me something great during
work hours nice I'm happy to hear that
Cher on app death okay
de now this one I would maybe put here
to become an orange later than Apple and
so
on maybe the baby pit yeah it's small
baby pit yeah oh okay I hope it lands
where I want it to land I think this
this is good okay oh [\h__\h] it's pushing
it's pushing ah
uh
[Music]
M it's pushing out the baby it's pushing
the
[Music]
baby okay it's pushing back
inside
oh well it got rid of a few of the
babies in the baby pit
brief okay brief are sure the cameras on
I told you to take the
[Music]
video H okay let me pour some
water it was so ten over from the time
she put the first excuse me the first
one you mean when it was
empty nissa's
video okay I saw some people say
left
um I guess
here because it can't really land
anywhere else it'll go down here
[Music]
anyway uh what choice do I have
man off bye-bye Cherry
oh
oh interesting table
[Music]
turn I can't believe I've been cooking
for so long and we're still only at
1,500 what the
[\h__\h] it's definitely taking a pleasant
shape like an interesting shape better
than other shapes
maybe touch touch touch touch touch
touch it touch it you little
[\h__\h] all
right ah now it's bad there's too many
apples make them
touch doio oh wait why did I not putuh
what oh wait let's make let's make
something
[Music]
here
[Applause]
y
oh you were scared you thought it was
over
pineapple
[Music]
hey maybe
here oh that was more push than I
expected oh pach PES you little [\h__\h] A
oh oh pineapple pineapple I have downed
you still moving oh ich go ichy go down
ich go down no no ich go down okay well
what do you say about this I mean the
pineapple is really far from the other
pineapple give it a Bop push oh go it
e okay okay okay okay
riveting oh Cherry go down maybe meet
other Cherry
eventually
and nice and
nice is there something we could push
with the Cherry so that maybe we can
push the pineapple maybe but there's too
many things in the way I
guess yeah I I will beat my score new
record this is the Run let's go this is
the 2K run I want it to be the 3K run
too late now yeah
but where then where
[Music]
you blocked it with the or yeah well
well all we got to do is just make
another
[Music]
pineapple all
right
[Music]
can I push
it
yeah there it goes there it go
[Music]
no
well well well
well no it's not over it's not
[Music]
over yeah if I would have dropped it
faster I was like planning on it you
know you know uh yeah let's get at least
2K
please where should I put this grave can
it help me let's put it
here and then this here and then this
here
oh I am I'm I'm beating my third place
[Music]
score
we still have a lot of
space
[Music]
relatively oh
oh can where where should I put
[Music]
this should I try to push something or
is like just
left just left
okay oh record record new record all
right all right that's that's
[Music]
good I want to put it
there risky
risky I just want to go back back to 9
99 okay I I can I can put it there right
I I can put it there right I mean if it
works for you want for the one then I
can like then it's going to work for
don't risk
it okay
2018 and now I'm going to risk it hey
yay
yay new record new
record
Wow E
okay let's have a
strict
policy big right side smaller smaller
left
side hey hey hey strict
policy why are you on the right side why
are you mingling it's tingling my
senses poetry slam baby why are you
mingling it's tingling my
senses so
poetic it's too early to enforce my
policy you know we have time we have
time so much time all we have is time or
we don't you think all we have is time
but we don't that's the one thing we
don't have
really the one thing that we're lacking
in life is
[Music]
time there's not
enough oh
hey let me
move stop holding me
back
Sage CH I'm hearing words but I don't so
you agree but you also don't
understand typical chicken
Behavior you want to go down Cherry can
I push it does it
work hey and
[Music]
push so
true
[Music]
wouldn't you agree that
like sua game is like an artificially
created hype made by H
life like if it weren't for our streams
I don't think it would have uh come to
this
point even like Indies are playing it
now I find that very fascinating you
know it's a simple game
[Music]
it's a simple game but by like willing
its popularity into existent
existence okay maybe it started before
whole life sure but like I think like
you know with inho whole life we created
I mean I mean the the mostly I mean the
hype with inho whole
life like how does a a
game uh go from one person play it until
literally every person plays it like
this is not the case with every
[Music]
game not every game has this
happen and the thing is like it's only
in the Japanese Nintendo shop and it's
kind of annoying to get it like you have
to jump through some
hoops I bought the Nintendo uh pre praid
card in Japanese convenience
store it made a Japanese account but Cy
told me she could buy it with um just
like points from other games that she
bought so that's a that's a a way of
doing it that's actually genius I
already used up my points though so
I I couldn't do that
[Music]
Strat I don't know where to put these so
they're just going wherever Wherever
Whenever we need to be together I'll be
there and you'll be here that's the deal
my
[Music]
dear hey it's working see everything's
working but the peaches are too far
apart but if the if those lemons touch
then they'll become
peaches H and then they won't touch
because then we have three peaches next
to each
[Music]
other
he wacki
wa I love singing Shakira songs oh oh
maybe four peaches soon which means two
[Music]
pineapples hey that was an unexpected
combination wait wait wait for
[Music]
me
oh I don't know I'm not really following
the Strat right
[Music]
now she making my favorite fruit salad I
love fruit
man
[Music]
I could go the whole day just eating
fruit
[Music]
sometimes Shakira just made me join your
fans what Shakira Shakira told you to
become kfp doesn't mean Shakira is AK
kfp
NY
thank you
Shakira Shakira loves me what a great
Yelp review to
have speaking of reviews my mom she told
me she was like venting she
said I wrot a review [\h__\h]
talking uh some some place on Google and
it got
rejected she was so mad but she was like
literally sh talking like she was using
swear
words and
yeah
well mommy my mom does have Caren
Tendencies but like not like the typical
classic
Karen like American classic ter this is
bad there's so much potential down
there yeah
oh okay
believe
[Music]
believe m
now we have four [\h__\h] oh never mind
we have two
peaches four peaches became two
peaches hey you thought it was over you
thought it was over not
yet not quite yet my
friends oh still popping still locking
pop
locking candy
[Music]
shopping uh do you want to move no sure
sure about
that look it's my favorite Yellow
Ostrich streamer tanakak
caria was over once I started to tangent
hey no don't say that
[Music]
I keep on proving you guys wrong
wrong touch touch touch
touch okay it's
over or is
it
[Music]
tou okay it was therefore over all
right smart smart
smart hey wrong side
okay
oh ah hey M
[Music]
wait
MH mhm hey oh
oh do SC be think wa knows how cute her
way of speaking an accent all what did I
say but thank you I think that was is a
compliment
[Music]
right look at the
[Applause]
strawberry I want to ask how you how
what I want to ask you how to good Ian
uh how to become better at
English go to school if you're still a
student go to school
if you're not a student anymore if
you're serious about it take extra
lessons I just recently even though I'm
out of school took Korean
lessons or yeah buy our product H
listening but that's like on the base of
knowing Japanese so well
um but yeah there's many ways like use
English every
day find maybe a friend who speaks
English to you
like talk English
together um
yeah some people learn languages right
like Japanese for
anime I guess you could do the same with
like Netflix shows a little bit but I
don't really think it's effective oh
[\h__\h] I personally don't think it's
effective
oh ye
[Music]
oh con and I learned English from
American television oh yeah yeah yeah
her English is actually surprisingly
good she just she doesn't Flex it enough
like her understanding is pretty good
right like when I was like speaking
English and our collabs she seemed to
understand like pretty well
oh speaking is still you know smaller
smaller to of the
house I can't stop saying things are
smart
[Music]
smart IRL as well when I'm with jenma
the whole time I'm like pointing out
even when we're in in like a a normal
discussion
and like normal conversation I'm like
anything that's small I'm like small
smaller like small smaller break small
small small bite small
smaller uh I don't know
anything small small
suitcase small small
[Music]
time small small chance of getting into
EUR
Vision I can't
stop saying
it
wasn't there something with Sonic
today like Sonic some Sonic convention
or
so I want these peaches to
[Music]
touch h
viral quote
[Music]
machine there's a new Sonic game coming
up
again ah
didn't they release one last year or
this was it this
year what kind of Sonic game is at this
time there always is there always a new
Sonic is it like with Pokemon one game
per
year go go
oh all the corner 2K Kaku let's
go
[Music]
what's this big ass Gap there when are
we
dropping what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
massive about as big as the
hole in your sock
and in your box of
shorts and
in your uh uh your what's what's what's
it called again the thing you apply with
uh for
jobs could you explain what you did
between 2012 and
H could you explain H what do you mean
you just didn't feel like having a job H
what does that mean
[Music]
huh this this not good I don't like this
it should be good it should be good but
it's like
bad ooh I mean maybe the lemons could
touch oh yeah it's going there oh
oh well well well Color Me surprised or
whatever you
say all
[Music]
right yeah okay that shouldn't have gone
in the
middle three peaches two
pineapples M okay I'll send another one
down just so that I can push the Y yep
and then that goes there
yeah all right I
mean if that's how things are then
that's how things are like
this
m where do I want to bring the small
ones do I want to focus on one side now
it's kind of maybe too late to start
doing that
now there's like so much space on the
left side but maybe we want that for
bigger things
[Music]
it's not
over you guys are so
negative like look at that pineapple
party baby pineapple
hey I'm having a freaking pineapple
party and you're just like their
hoping negatively look at that melon
party now hey okay right side it is
right side is my trash
can oh it's moving
moving down hold on oh oh oh oh what's
going on oh hey hey hey
hey oh still moving
[Music]
okay did you see that little bounce pop
hey
you little shits we are so
back but if in like I was never gone
okay I never felt like I was
gone
wowers wowers
trousers
no no
no wait I'll wait I think it can it go
down anymore yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
there it is there it is yep
pop maybe not good nah too for it
actually wasn't
good why so many
[Music]
grapes
was pretty bad on the left side that was
so bad now was actually I will I will
admit that was really
bad ah this s not good ah okay
[Music]
fine
m
it's pretty bad right
[Music]
now what the [\h__\h] do I do
ah I thought I could land
[Music]
there are you happy now you jinxed it
because you guys were like it's over
it's
over you ruined
it it was
you hey chill chill chill chill
[Music]
chill didn't say
anything
okay then it's not you it's
them oh wait why did I drop it
there oh well still a lot of room
for
[Music]
mstic I stopped Tangen thing do you guys
think it made me better or did it make
me
worse
better
[Music]
really but is it worth it is it worth
the
sacrifice I don't
[Music]
know
no a made the Stream worse well that's
kind of like a little bit
uh strong thing to
[Music]
say hey
clean very clean which side is my small
smaller side
now say this
[Music]
side oh wait why did I do that should
have put it more like in the middle
maybe oh
well I'm going to build on top of
that oh hello there
peach when's the peach game coming
out that Pikachu detective thing came
out now
right I heard good things I heard bad
things but not I'm not going to play
it in
Spring
[Music]
o somehow I thought it would be
earlier much
[Music]
go I'm balancing all those small fruit
now not
anymore that's
okay I'll do it my
way I drop an apple I drop a grape and
everything's going to be
great just do it the Wow Wow way it's
the right
way they say it's over but no it's not
just believe in the
drop Drop It Like It's
Hot a hot
apple
Nice Nice lyrics
right I'm spitting she
spitting spitting out the
seats I yeah I'm I'm a
genius now actually while I was singing
I wasn't thinking a single thing about
what I'm doing and I am regretting
everything right now
so much moving all right
oh no no regretti
spaghetti come on come on trickle
trickle
[Music]
trickle it's fine now it's moving back
it's moving my small things back to the
right side are you seeing
this so many grapes my
God why do they have to fall down in
that order it's like they're making
[Music]
uh of
fruit uh
uh
thing
[Music]
why SK
yeah why do they have to
be okay I'm stupid but I'll fix it I'll
fix it I'll fix it I'll fix it I'll fix
it I promise I fix it see I'll fix it
look it's going it's it going down I
don't
know
okay ah that that bottom just looks so
bad eat
okay let's nurture it into
something that's worth
[Music]
it and no
hey not
[Music]
cool
[Applause]
[Music]
okay a
do
man oh my God it's already been 3 hours
40 minutes of me playing
this time just goes by
endlessly holy
[\h__\h] if I could turn back
time I would put the fruit down
differently
ah no no why
ah
[Music]
stay
ah no no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
okay
m
ah hey wait
[Music]
mother let's hear a tangent what I have
let me
think what do I
have uh without looking can I remember
do you remember do I owe you some
some
[Music]
something
a ah I want to keep some of the ID
stories for later cuz they will make
more sense
later uh no SLE
why I mean there's not much that
happened behind the scenes you
know I just uh okay I'll try I'll try
I'll try getting something out of
it um yeah so in case you missed it on
no senpai's
Channel we did a ASMR collab and I never
did ASMR before at least not
officially besides me sometimes holding
the
microphone um very dearly attempting
something
funny I guess you could call that
ASMR but yeah I've been to Anno to
senpai's place
before um for the Takami no F collab
that I
[Music]
planned and for this I planned it for a
long
time um you know you know you guys know
kind of how I stand with uh
ASMR there's Sometimes some types that I
can maybe understand that they could
even for
me
be nice but most of it for me when I
listen to it honestly it just makes me
cringe so
hard some types of ASMR like cooking
ASMR like the sounds of like Chop Chop
Chop on the on the cutting board stuff
like
that I I I like hearing
that and like and in environmental
sounds or or animal purring sounds and
whatever I guess
m raining of course yeah that's I guess
one of the most
common yeah like nature
ASMR can you even is that
[Music]
ASMR that's just Ambient sound isn't is
there is that the is that considered ASM
[Music]
more
oh depends on your
definition I guess
now you could put it into that category
now that it's a common thing
[Music]
ASMR
but yeah so I was planning to do that
because you know
like uh generally stream ideas doing
something special for the first time
always a good idea and then for off
collab ASMR is like like ideal cuz like
we couldn't do it as a non off collab so
I just thought you know when thinking of
collabs I could do with Japanese
members that's just like so obvious
[Music]
right oh yeah thank you for going
there
yeah then it does some ASMR stre for
members it's mostly aatu
oh yeah no do like specializes in ASMR
so she knows a lot of stuff so I thought
if anybody like I would love to also
like learn it from fauna for example um
um but you know it just kind of happened
first with n sen
by was easier to get to nor
but yeah
so I was looking forward to that
and and uh yeah uh she was kind of busy
during the day so I kind of arrived
pretty late like half an hour before the
stream and then we like she already had
most of it prepped but we set up the
last few things and then I saw she had
like my
blanket my birthday blanket I was really
surprised that like she told me she buys
some member merchandise that she thinks
could like she likes or could be
useful so you know not only my
merchandise of course but I was still
really surprised I didn't think like she
would buy my merchandise
H yeah made me quite flattered yeah
flattered and she said she put it out
because she knew I was coming like
normally it's not always out there on
her couch but she has
it
[Music]
yeah and one thing I always notice like
in uh When I visit whole life members
homes Japanese whole life members
they're always collecting
something I don't know how I didn't know
this last time but nor SEI is collecting
little
piggies I didn't notice that so next
time maybe I'll bring her some piggy
souvenir where are we putting the
grapes everything's like here for some
[Music]
reason yeah like smart smart SM smart
Piggies and she does have a lot of whole
life merch around her
[Music]
place
mhm yeah aan Piggy
[Music]
yeah and and uh n
n m m
no yeah we were preparing and uh yo I
saw her equipment for her ASMR room holy
[\h__\h] I don't even think all that is
necessary but
damn wo W that's like the most audio
equipment that I've ever like the oh
[\h__\h]
wow like her stuff is like next
level
wow like she not just the microphones
I'm like actually talking about like the
ooh like the um the sound equipment like
mixers and stuff like she has like a
million of them and I'm like is this all
being
used it depends apparently I'm I'm like
[Music]
fascinated that's crazy I don't think
fauna has that much stuff does she
like literally no has them like
stacked like not like mixer as like look
GLX R and of no like professional Sound
Studio
type
mixers wonder how it how that works like
what what why why a normal mixer can't
do the
[Music]
trick
M all right I mean what I'm doing is not
ideal but it's kind of
working father just has a closet a yeah
didn't she like say she's like in a
[Music]
closet I'm sure FAA would love to have
like one of those soundproof booths that
the Japanese members use those are
fascinating literally a room in a
room
I'm going to continue to try to push the
peach
[Music]
though okay
maybe uh okay now the apple is in a way
though so I might as well turn the Apple
into a peach too oh it seems impossible
M Casino
how hard is it not to cringe doing ASMR
in front of some yeah that also made it
more difficult I feel like I would be
better or more confident about it if I
was um
[Music]
alone yeah I was
H but
[Music]
D this is not good
[\h__\h] this run
[Music]
D but yeah um so we did the Asar and oh
she had like a lot of cool little tiny
small smaller smaller things
that would make interesting sounds I
found the the sizzling sound so
interesting cuz that was like some type
of like
foam
fuu out of a
spray can those thing do do spray can
thingy yeah then made like cooking if
you perceive it as a cooking sound it
can be like you know a grilling cooking
sound but you could perceive it as
something else too
[Music]
I gave her like so
much I was like you know we were we were
doing this whole yakin niku episode
because I was like feeling like eating
yak yakin niku and then I was like okay
let's let's uh let's um Grill some meat
and she made the the grilling sound I'm
like no way
then I'm like yeah let's do eating sound
that was just you know normal num n n
then uh a dessert
dessert wait wait oh then yeah I was
like dessert so she she literally just
brought out some like little snack that
she had in the
room and then I was like okay okay oh
already Peach then I was like okay now
now pay pay the check let's pay let's
pay the check and then uh we were trying
to pay with card making sounds but you
know there wasn't really much and then
oh yeah taking a a commemorative picture
so we took out the phone and made Pasa
Pasa Pasa
sounds there's like this whole this
whole
story that we created which I'm so sorry
it was so
stupid so
stupid I I just didn't know what to
do I I taught her more or less or showed
her how I make the frog
[Music]
noises mhm
mhm
[Music]
okay right side is the side that always
shocks to me everybody is always so
amused by my frog noises the purring was
also good the purring I don't know if it
was my throat or it just sounded weird
to me through the ASMR
microphone it's not what frog noise is
just frog noise have you never heard a
frog
before
[Music]
nice P I made him touch really
[Applause]
early
many
pineapp nice okay uh it's kind of in the
middle though I'll try to continue
putting things on the right like smaller
things on the right side
and building another whatever over
here come on come on go in there go in
there I believe in you I believe in
[Music]
you
mhm but okay this is kind of [\h__\h] to
what I'm
doing ah yeah this
is bad I'm sorry I'm sorry it's like I
can't decide which side but it just
happens cuz smaller things become big
bigger oh but this is good this is good
e we already have the pear or lemon or
whatever you want it to be let's make
another
one maybe maybe what I'm doing is
good you can't
you make apple now we need another
Apple e so early good early game good
early game though if we do this
right then it's a really good early
[Music]
game H right let me put this here cuz we
get two and we have the
orange small thing Apple there we
go should I try to build the same thing
on top of the
peach all
right ah hey hey don't do that what are
you
[Music]
doing oh
oh
uh what I what do
I I guess I got to make a pach out of
that thing then but it will be hard to
get them to
touch build on okay I guess we'll have a
backup uh then
although wait mukashi I don't want to
block it I don't want to block the the
[Music]
mean
um just just trust
me now I can drop it oh but it's
stuck
a okay maybe we oh just going to keep
things moving there we go all right hey
[Music]
e uh
yeah yeah yeah thank you that was close
uh can you guys touch oh well do it like
this okay and
[Music]
oh those um pairs could be so nice to
touch but that was my backup pair anyway
[Music]
so all right what's up nice hat thank
you Pineapple
hat pineapple is you know everybody
talks about wanting watermelons but I
just want the
pineapples I like that you and nor were
wearings yeah we had it
matching matching our dandel after the
stream uh I guess she was also feeling
like eating yucky yiku but we just
ordered Yakiniku bentos instead of like
going out to eat actual
Yakiniku yes
yes there's some movement still
happening should I push
[Music]
more ah oh oh oh oh
push yeah
yeah look at
that okay strong early
game
[Music]
e so we had uh Yakiniku while we were
talking about a lot of
things that were on my mind you know I
like to take the opportunity when I'm
with a stpy an experienced Senpai to ask
a lot of questions and
stuff so that was nice nice long talk
that we had and then I was going to I
was going to get my own Uber but see cuz
like last time when I was there um I
didn't have like uh like a good app that
I could get a taxi with so she called me
one back then um um and like therefore
she also paid for it but this time I was
going to get my own Uber but she was
like really fast like when I was saying
I guess I'm going to leave now and I
take out my phone and starting to order
she was
like she was like quickly calling one
again I was like e no don't but she
[Music]
did she did
it all right guys where now that the
melon is like on the right side should I
continue putting my smaller things on
the left
side or try to put BR put this pair make
it into Peach Etc and you know no still
right okay I was feeling the same
way so here we
go
m
hey o that was fast uh
[Music]
okay it's going to fall
down
I la I have to kind of put it there cuz
it's going to fall down
[Music]
anyway roll it
baby
apple now
what guess I'm going to put it here what
choice do I
have yeah no this is not good but what
choices do I
have it's going to fall
[Music]
down
oh
[Music]
e strawberry trying to make me angry
again
oh
look
oh oh I should have let it move could
have fallen down it will still go down
there eventually I'll force it if I have
to um I'll put this
here oh oh okay the pineapple can fill
that Gap too I don't mind that yeah yeah
yeah
okay hey it's not quite according to
Kaku what are we doing
now one more
pineapple one more pineapple
[Music]
please I know I know it doesn't want to
go
[Music]
[Laughter]
there
ah okay
[Music]
okay focus on the left yeah I'm trying
to I'm trying
to I'm trying I'm trying let's do your
first watermelon waa do you think I can
do it we're going very much like you
know like you know setting ourselves
some goals and like going after those so
I think that's like good a good thing to
do
[Music]
hey look at that we got the peach just
got to make another
Peach that has to go there
unfortunately oh
oh oh hey
oh will just be difficult to move but
wait if if I make can I make the grape
in the
middle maybe into a pig
there I I should try to use it that way
but this thing if I put it here now then
the pair is going to be
blocked go from the right okay let's see
what
happens okay getting
[Music]
closer yeah I mean once I make something
bigger
I see yeah
yeah
yes that's fine that's fine Apple
becomes pear when I make another pear
and then pear becomes Peach if if they
[Music]
touch uh not not much space but all I
need all I
need hey
[Music]
hey
no
hey hey did you see what happened it
like glitched over to the other side my
mouse my
cursor I curse
[Music]
you
I still I can still do it
see first
[Music]
watermelon
[Applause]
yay I'm going one two want to free it
tastes so so so
sweet
soy okay what now I guess whatever
happens it doesn't matter cuz we
accomplished
Something Free watermelons yeah yeah
yeah
yeah surprisingly yeah I'm still under
2,000 so it looks like the left side is
the way to go for for trash cuz there's
already like a bunch of trash there what
do you
think yeah build on the right right I
would say so too see look at the trash
look at the little
Trash grapes grapes are still considered
trash oh maybe I should have not oh hey
I mean I mean I
mean
okay automatic well what now the
watermelon is kind of on the left side
now I'll build I'll build on the right
side but even we have small things now
just just just let it happen see cuz
we're building grapes there we go hey
[Music]
55 can I put this here it will it will
it will just
[Applause]
squeeze
mhm grape
grape orange orange apple and uh n what
are you
doing
um touch okay okay
[Music]
trash we got a peach new
record how far can we
go
thinking of putting the grape here cuz
it's going to take too much space in my
opinion on the left
[Music]
side yeah oh
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
hey it's working it's
[Music]
working
M yeah I'm going to put the grape
[Music]
here
ah
ah yeah okay now grape is
[Music]
blocking
interesting hey 2,000 oh my God oh my
God that's like satisfyingly high
compared to everything I had until now
should I bake Bean shake or I've never
heard of myf before I think I've heard
of bean but I can't even remember what
it's
like 3K is reachable nah not with my
smaller smaller
[Music]
brain
hey well really not much I can you know
fix here
[Music]
so push it to the Apple push it to the
Apple
[Music]
M it's over it's so over can I can I put
it
here it won't or maybe here and then
push with try to push with strawberry
put the grap strawberry here maybe I
don't
[Music]
know yeah come on come on ah it does you
want to push that little
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's over there's no
way there's no
way
[Music]
wow oh wow okay it's over though it's
over you're saying the absolute limits
of the sua game right now how high can
you go with being forgiven
un
forgiven this is not
happening I'm happy with that maybe
tomorrow we can go for
3,000 I read some super chats now I
think m i we'll continue tomorrow it's
been 4 and 4 and almost a half hours so
we should probably cuz I got to read
super chats we should probably end it
here I that was fun but I I I didn't
expect it would be so hard to get
anywhere
o oof fre K
tomorrow I hope you guys enjoyed having
Wawa back
M and if you are like you know still
lacking the Wawa juice then stay here
I'm pouring out one for each of
you yum
[Music]
yum did you miss
me thank
you all
right
M yeah yeah let me before you guys all
go quickly show you the schedule also by
the way for members who weren't able to
download the wallpaper recently I think
if you tried a new updated link it
should work honestly the wallpaper is so
cursed sasuka Halloween
wallpaper um but please give it a
try
and
where's my here this
one I see that it's so good I love this
art cuz I told them like hey I need like
Halloween theme I guess again uh but
these are the things I already kind of
did so let's go for something new but I
don't know what so just any any kind of
concept that's not what we did before
so they went for chainsaw fast food
worker I
guess it's so good it's hard to see
behind the schedule but there's a
chainsaw there and I'm I'm slicing
through some
[Music]
stuff so we have S again today s again
tomorrow then resting day Tom uh
Wednesday because I have some stuff to
do so not really resting but you know
you
know got to be there
to um make up for when I wasn't there um
Age of Empires practice On th day
because on
Friday now here it says 4 a.m. but
currently it seems like it's going more
towards uh 7
a.m. um but who knows if it's happening
at all don't really
know wallpaper is copy gumy in ja yeah
yeah also literally like literally
translated wallpaper they also use that
for PC and
phone wallpaper just like in
English so I I think aoe2 the tournament
one might be a little bit in danger but
if it's happening it's happening
somewhere around that time and we have a
memb stream uh way after I'm hopefully
going to sleep in between and yes Final
Fantasy is really happening this time
I'm not promising or not even currently
not even like really planning to like
force myself to finish it
um but I want to at least give it a try
like I I I want to maybe make it a bit
more normal for myself to for long long
long
games
unless it's a tales off game not force
myself to like finish everything you
[Music]
know cuz yeah of reasons I just
don't um want to unnecessarily drag
things out anymore that are not that
popular on my channel but we'll see I'll
see how long it is you guys are saying
it's not that long what the hell
[Music]
okay H okay it's short not like tra oh
other FF games are usually longer
wow okay um yeah that's the schedule
things are happening this time for real
I planned everything ahead last week so
that the perms would be there on time
don't worry
doing it for real for real this
time so join
me should I read super chats
here change it up a little bit put the
schedule here behind
me like
this maybe will stay
here I need to I need to um update my uh
Halloween office again like at least
like put it back into my OBS cuz I don't
think I have it in my OBS it's October
it's spooky season T the spooky
season different oh yeah okay yes yes
yes yes yeah
[Music]
gladly
why you guys there we
go brainwashing
[\h__\h] wow I just really feel it now that
it's
gone don't get jump scared again
yeah yeah I need to set it up on my OBS
so that we can use it again haven't used
my normal like generally the office in a
while cuz I've been using the summer
backgrounds for a while m
okay so isn't it
nice just not hearing
anything suddenly makes me feel tired
though okay what are we going to
play maybe
this oh I'm not hearing it and audios
settings
okay is this
fine perfect
good anything is
fine uh personally I wouldn't even mind
not listening to
anything but then it sounds so empty
when you go into the stream okay
then wellow I haven't read super chats
in a
while no bgm is fine
too okay but I let me write it on screen
though like bring your own bgm to work
day ah
where do I put it where where where do
people like feel like they can see
it let just put it here and make it
bigger just listen to whatever you want
if you want
something
bye bring your own bgm to work
day why is it so
like like this doesn't
fit
uh
bring your
own
BDM wait it's
like
uh
alignment
center
there we
go
[Music]
beautiful
okay are people going to see this like
because the schedule is on the screen I
feel like people will not know where to
look but you guys know already what to
do
ow
[Music]
near
H
nah it's fine it's
fine
okay all right all right guys so where
am I reading the super chats like from
where do you
[Music]
know help me help me help me
t
t people don't read in general that is
true what the [\h__\h] add Block
Please the last BG freak collab aha oh
we're not that far
behind okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay so this
one okay oh well now it looks
really cluttered doesn't
itut uh oh
well B let's
[Music]
go Pinky hi kiaha I wanted to let you
know I just finished 2 years of
exercising every day oh shees
respect I wanted to thank you for being
a constant source of joy and motivation
and not just for me but for all of kfp
love you my oi thank you I think I saw
like on my Twitter
timeline something about that saw
pictures looking good you could compete
with those rugby guys that I saw on the
train yeah sh
this that is some insane dedication and
tenacity that I do not
have yeah crazy crazy good job respect
of course I'm guessing in order to
continue looking like that you have to
continue doing your workouts but maybe
not every day anymore maybe maybe you
can take it a bit more
easy unless you really enjoy it unless
it's not not like not you know too much
of a trouble to continue doing
it fi F yeah need to leave now thanks
for
watching muscle glows fast it
sucks funny the fast food R inspired
taking care of his
health
yeah
well well well
respect on everything you've done before
and good luck on your journey
continuing
yeah but be careful don't hurt yourself
than J Tracy thank you for the
red congratulations on 1.5 million Subs
K you deserve all the success your hard
work is paying off oh yeah 1.5 million H
it's it was very very difficult to reach
that but we did it I'm so
proud feels good to finally have that
five there instead of the four not going
to
lie thank you so much for being one of
them than soon you should be proud I am
[Music]
yeah thank you soon for for supporting
me me
m so many
timkin yeah I hope even the ones who are
like not actively watching anymore will
maybe check in again sometimes would be
nice you guys go tell them tell them I
can't tell them cuz they're not
watching tell them to watch me paty D
certain thank you for the pinky could
you give y a little sh or smooch it's
his birthday today but apparently he
can't send a Super Chat ooh I'm so late
oh oh I oh this was September
24th
uh Yoko are you
here I'm so
sorry I'm so late Mama
M ah I'm so sorry well it's not not a
red but you know what I'll give you a
sorry Choo
Chu happy happy very very very very very
very very very late
birthday damn it's already
October but well every day is a birthday
it's literally called Birthday not birth
year
okay it's called birthday so every day
you're
celebrating another day that you're
getting older in my
opinion so true so
true Lone Wolf gaming than you
soon ah this was about bers
SK I don't know if I'll remember
that make sure cie doesn't sell anything
uh marked as icy cuz that's what bibu
needs I think you need to tell her that
in a Super Chat she might she might uh
read it even if it's not you know a red
one she might see
it sty 92 D Mrs Lulu bef One D but why
are you saying it did she already sell
something by
accident and Mrs little beff sent a red
Super Chat thank you hey Ki waa I just
want to say I love you and your music
helps me get through my work days you
and the rest of myth are what made me
fall down the rabbit hole hope to see
more from you and the rest of myth thank
you thank you
[Music]
soon thank you I'm happy that myth can
help you with you know just everything
existing we're glad to be there for
anybody who needs us thank for
supporting us Smith right now if if you
guys are if if any of you are going to
Japan any anytime soon in Japan for a
short time I think it did say it until
the 15th so that's like a
week in akih habala you can see all of
myth on a big advertisement that's
pretty cool it's the advertisement for
the um the the the language learning
book and
audio I I'm also Bamboozled they just
like made it like start right after I'm
gone man this is not the first time this
is
happening yeah but yeah it's it's so
cute like the book turned out so cute
but the Audio I really want you guys to
listen to the audio too if you can
because uh you know it goes hand in hand
and it's like basically like a really
long collaboration voice
pack and yeah the book is so cute
there's so much cute art in
there
waiting for it to hit stores in America
in the future uh I wouldn't wait for
that cuz like it's literally that
wouldn't even make sense it's marketed
for Japanese people I'm just saying I
think it's still worth it for you guys
to get it cuz you guys can understand it
and it's cute and there's lots of you
know our voice recordings um but I don't
think it will ever make it to like
American bookstores cuz it makes no
sense you know you know makes no
sense would be cool if they could have
it like in like Anime conventions like
in combination with like some some
import uh little shop that Imports
things from
Japan it's in a New York store that
sells Japanese stuff that's so cool guys
okay if you have any shops that sell
Japanese things close to you where you
live and might be worth taking a
[Music]
look yes yes okay so with that
thank you okay thank you Miss lulup for
the
support please continue listening to my
music too
yeah for two pinkies AKA one red so
here's a
purple and congratulations on 1.5
million kada so I have a confession I
have a heart disease really that makes
my heart hurt and hard to breathe been
years gotten worse recently oh
no especially whenever I seet it gets
worse I went to the hospital doctor told
me to shut up and get lost what should I
do hey I was genuinely
concerned hey hey hey hey
heyy
sussy little
Baka
hey that's really
concerning
cuz y that could be really really
dangerous I have the same disease oh my
God just like me for real for
real no no
no m
M now everybody's like self diagnosing
themselves stop
it okay no more no more of these jokes
Hulu because I worry about you
okay how much time do I
have a Google says I'm going to
die Google
do I need to beat up
Google okay M well well well well well
thank you Honolulu that's really sweet
and FY but you really you really scared
me
hey thank you for the
support Nathan cotton with a rainbow oo
la thank you so so much it says hi atten
you may not have noticed but I've been
sending a super every stream I can catch
as lead up to my
birthday
wait no I remember seeing this but I
didn't get to say anything and I'm also
late for your birthday then
no
naan another one slipped through
no oh the timing I'm so
sorry that's such a bad
timing um I only cry a little no don't
cry let me let
me
yummy only one for my birthday this year
is a wa album wait no I already bought
that so all I want for my birthday is a
Koka Marathon wait no that was a couple
days ago how about some anniversary
merch nope already B BG free collab in
progress
Hipp hippopotamus nope Christmas you
also Christmas H what what does that
mean I don't understand this part what's
going on okay all I want for my birthday
is for my Kami ooshi to have a good time
and my fellow jimins to have lots of fun
and also maybe some fiscal
responsibility I think I may have not
reacted to your super chat in time but I
still did what you said I had a good
good time and I think the fellow jimins
also had a good time
so
so everything worked out perfectly all
according to
Kaku hip
hip hip hip hip hip
hooray that's how
you that's how you say that trust
me
Ray
yay thank you so much for the rainbow
and thank you for all the super chats
before that too I'm so sorry for being
late oh my God I'm so useless well thank
you hip hi hoay to you A big hip hip
hoay for Nathan cotton for being older
let's go let's
go
congratulations
hey see I'm doing my part with having a
good time the fow chipkin are having are
are doing their part by having a good
time you're not doing your part with the
fiscal
responsibility you're the only puzzle
piece that's left
Nathan okay but since you sent another
Super Chat I'm guessing you're not mad
at me okay oh that's good I'm safe I'm
safe from the anger of my team
nice okay and
wait stop everybody's bgm because I
think for a birthday rainbow I have to
do
this
um I don't think I can think of any good
lyrics
though happy happy
birthday happy
birthday to you w happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your
shoe happy birthday in your pants too
happy birthday to
you to my dear
Nathan I wish you a big one as big as a
hippo Tous hip hip hooray hooray happy
birthday to you happy birthday happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday
happy birthday in your plant too happy
birthday to
you you are so
patient when I need some
time next time time you'll be the
patient in the
usual room if you're not careful with
your fiscal responsibilities all right
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday to
you Nathan
coton what rhymes with cotton I don't
know but thank you for all the love that
you give to the
W hey thank you what rhymes oh sh What
rhymes of cotton yeah I was thinking of
mutton but like what the [\h__\h] do I say
about
mutton button cute as a na cotton cute
as a button that needs to be proven
though like where's the picture before I
sing that that has to be
proven
cannot sing that before I know for
real Na and cotton you will not be
forgotten cuz you're cute as a
[Music]
button oh I turn on mym oh
yeah
ah post picture of a
button no no
no don't you dare pull that kind of
prank on
me not
funny thank
you
ah thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank
you thank you thank you thank you so
much thank
you bring yeah okay I'll turn it off
hi where as cute as a button come from a
button is just plastic or wood
H I think because button is small and
small things are usually
cute and it sounds cute to say that
too H and oh
maybe I don't know
I don't know okay Nathan thank you sping
H thank you for the red super
chat thanks for na a chill dungeon
exploration Girls Talk Roomba hair
pulling stream
Roomba hair
pulling what big cat insisted on being
hell for all of it you have a whole of
10 kilogram cat for 4 hours
sheesh
damn 10 kill
gr whoa can you not like push him to the
side like have him sit next to you
like
o that is quite yeah a big
jungus oh that was when we talked about
the ghost cat incident
oh by the way when I was like sleeping
at Callie's place the cats like I I left
the door open and I I wasn't going to
have much time to
sleep uh like maybe
four
hours so I was like whatever I even if I
get disturbed by them it will be I will
be happily Disturbed and they um
especially like ghost cat was really
[Applause]
extremely shy that time but uh tutu was
as sweet as always she didn't cuddle
like into like around my my
my head as she did before but she did
like sometime during the night I woke up
because she was like purring walking
around walking with every step she was
like needing everything that was getting
in her way and then she she just made
way under my under my blanket and she
was
like going to my fies and I think this
is a thing she likes to do cie told me
about it before and she was like you
know going to my feet while while
needing everything and then
yeah so ticklish because like her fur is
ticklish and then she was like kind of
nibbling trying to nibble on my on my
toes and I try to hide them and she goes
after them
it's so
cute yeah and then she was like chilling
purring loudly inside under the under
the blanket next to my feet for a
while so cute
man it's so
ticklish hurts a little bit but not
really it's more like ticklish and yeah
painful she's so cute she's so small
though like so small
small definitely not 10 kilogram ghost
cat neither but ghost cat got really
really big like tall like
long cie thinks her cats won't grow
anymore but they're so tiny I feel like
they should still be growing but it it
makes me wonder like them being like
this old and still so
small maybe like the breeding in Japan
makes them generally like smaller than
they would be overseas I don't know cuz
they seem they seem generally very small
mhm compared to mine even yeah cuz mine
are ragd dolls supposedly which are
supposedly big but they're like normal
size
cats
h no anyway
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway spank cam did I give did I give
you a kiss
[Music]
[Laughter]
nothing happened okay and
then
uh uh let's read the FF zeros of the
death no oh I a strange color for what
what do you mean no no no oh ah oh no I
didn't mean Rago as in like uh the cat
race oh yeah right there's a I forgot
there was a cat race no I mean like they
they literally act like Ragdoll
sometimes you know when I put them over
my shoulder they just go like wobble
wobble
that's what I meant yeah of course
they're Phoenix
cats uh so fzero let me get the
thumbnail yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah they get they get like
that yeah yeah sometimes sometimes okay
wow I like this
thumnail
okay no shut up now
MO
oh thank you for coming to anime Toronto
too Toronto J D Trevor G oh no no not
the
name failed H cons you're not
failed I'm a failed hoodle collector but
you're you did your best
Consulting man Trevor
J
oh oh man I feel so
bad or do
I but that's uh three pinkies let's see
Alo waha first a little late congrats
are you
here on 1.5 million sub second I only
post a debuted correction cuz almost all
the H girls say wrong oh really I became
a bit of a pet peeve I'm good now they
do do they even
English I generally love when you say
things wrong
otherwise third I don't love you any
less just cuz you never finished finding
the hoodles or for anything else times
have just changed things from oh from a
promotion and scheduled changes two
years ago to a lot of Heartache
no wait you make me sad I want to hug
you I still love Wawa maybe even more
today than yesterday oh just goes up
like a never-ending spiral staircas oh
okay so it's
growing okay so just cuz I may not be
regurgitating bird puns
anymore and lurking more I it doesn't
mean I don't support you
okay how I tried commissioning W I might
do more too you
tried you succeeded right
who knows lastly random question would
you ever considered trying a week of
playing four to five different games
that fans vote for could be an incentive
if you ever go back to your charity
stream idea
oh but that that makes me think it's
kind of difficult to do that because
like if I just make you guys vote from a
pool of games that I choose okay okay
but then it's just like the usual but if
we want to you know make you guys choose
from anything then you know I'm thinking
I have to do this like the Family Feud
time cuz there will be like so many
different kind of suggestions how do I
even sort that
out uh bgm please write the note above
my
head I'll pay 500 bucks for Resident
Evil for
real divide into genres oh we could
choose five genres and then maybe one
game
each well I don't mind doing that in in
theory like the the whole making you
guys
choose but it's a bit difficult to set
that
up how do I make you guys choose
something also it has to be something I
have perms for but you you guys don't
like you could you guys could suggest
something from uh what others have
played before or anything from Nintendo
or you know then you know we have perms
for
it but okay I might I mean I might do
something like that whenever I feel like
I don't know what else to play maybe
when I ran out of some games you know
when I'm like oh man I feel like I
played everything I did it
all oh you an exile hi by the way I
wanted to I wanted
to that will never happen a second Ghost
Trick Ghost Trick I like that one it
looks
interesting oh
no wait
I just went on Twitter
and
artist drew
cie me too
please oh looks so good it doesn't even
it doesn't even like like when other
like artist mamas draw other members
like it's like so obvious that it's like
you know like for example coron empire
style but for this one it doesn't scream
noil to me you know what I
mean it's
more it's more
like I don't
know which I think is a good
thing
who yeah
M that one of Vera and me I saw that
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
kind of stylized differently yeah
maybe
maybe maybe they did it on
purpose oh it but even their like most
recent art of nowhere to S
by doesn't look so much to me like uh
like how she looks in the life to D
maybe they changed their art style a
little
bit oh
I feel like the
eyes kind of different oh well oh well
sorry I'm
um I'm doing something else here let me
let me let me go back to Super Chat also
yeah hook can draw you in different yeah
who could it too yeah yeah would look
kind of different every once in a while
anyway yeah so for games we'll see in
the future perhaps I can give that a
try uh and yeah aren't you happy we're
gonna play tails off again oh my God in
November although I don't know if I'll
be playing it when it comes out because
uh I might be in
Japan maybe got to wait a little bit
which gives you guys time to uh play it
yourself and you Trev G gives you time
to find any hoodles that are possibly in
the game if there are more
hoodles and then guide me to find them
without
failure hell yeah it's a
deal thank you trity I'm a bit re uh
reassured but also concerned so I hope
things get better for
you just so you know this this can
always be I hope it will always be your
happy place so make sure make sure to
take care of yourself and M M don't be
sad because waa sad if you
sad don't be
sad I know I know I know sometimes it's
good to be sad though you know let it
out let it all out all
out but I want to see you happy
again you do the same then well only
first you do
it J Monkey D Jim Tracy D mix Tech
Warrior thank you for the pinky I heard
you're getting into anime again well I
wouldn't quite say it that way okay not
sure what your type is but there's an
anime that has a redheaded strong
independent woman who has a hot brunette
Other
Woman what they boing boinging and
there's a petan one too it's called High
School
DxD H I've seen like stuff from that
[Music]
before
no looks like I don't know looks like a
harm to
me the
[Music]
script oh okay okay seems like you guys
wouldn't really recommend it either I'm
sorry mix
Warrior oh it is
okay maybe give it another try I I used
to watch harm anime is and kind of like
them depending on which one and in some
way back in monat is also kind of a
harm but yeah if if you have a harm
anime that's more like
B but even then nowadays I wouldn't I
probably wouldn't get into something
like that
anymore sukima yeah that's also har but
those those kind of animes you know that
I watched like years ago they have a
special place in my heart so
[Music]
yeah chable kid de 1269 register D thank
you Matt ver ssj fre the monster en mman
D Randy RJ Al 29 thank you for the pinky
hi Ki to answer my last Super Chat that
I don't remember now I was oess I had my
favorites like you and some others but
watching you at F Fest I was like that's
my oie oh I think I kind of remember I
was like oh you you decided to like me
at F Fest why how
why I see well I hope I can make you
proud and do more stuff like that at
third
best thank you thank you thank you for
supporting me and for opening your eyes
eyes and your heart for
me than
soon hi
smie hi hi hi did you hear that H what
what's wrong you looking for
something h no she's leaving okay h py d
Unwritten the Envy 63 known for
BS will action for the pinky I would
like to take this opportunity to
formally apologize despite being a mere
chicken and employee I foolishly koed my
beloved oian
C CE CEO in her first race due to my
reckless driving even if accidental I
deeply regret
this why did you have to remind me I
already forgot about this now I'm angry
again h
M you can hear the
sasm oh you think he did it on
purpose well he does say even
[Music]
if oh I drove it oh well well then
it's I I asked
for it's late I told you to put it on my
desk by so and so the next day it is it
doesn't matter when you actually put it
there it matters when I read
it this is your
fault your
fault your fault that I read it too
late it's just like the thing with the
airline and them you know being like
well you're too late now you may have
started the process earlier but you're
too late now so now you pay
love that logic don't you don't we love
that
logic that makes
sense taking it out of
him oh that sounded like me racing on
the
tracks yeah that's [\h__\h] dumb right
just proves as a as in a different
example just proves again how stupid
that is thank you for proving my point
green
welder that's what you were trying to do
right totally
totally yes many
varieties
[Music]
no what's
that uh what's that car brand again that
has like you know a circle and then
inside the circle it's like an l
almost Lexus oh see they're not like
that
uncommon um but I saw one on the street
that looked like a freaking race car it
looked really special that definitely
customized I
think that was my special car of the day
but I didn't post about it because I
thought
well you know can't really impress
people saying I saw
Alexis they're like everywhere
anyway oh they a luxury Toyota
oh not but it was really cool like I was
staring at it and I was like wait Kelly
Kelly we have to look at it and then she
was like oh yeah right you have like
some kind of car Arc going on and I'm
like yeah wait wait wait what is this
what's this brand again and then people
were like getting into the car and I'm
like oh yeah
oh they're literally getting into the
car right now seeing that I am staring
at them at their car so I turned around
quickly and we walked away
quickly what cause it well me seeing all
kinds of cool cars in
Tokyo
[Music]
smothie
poy hello oh she just ran in here and
she flop down literally like I told you
like a rag doll not that she is one but
she just flops down hi can I say
hi just give her a quick
pet
hi oh you like the
carpet oh she's
pring
y may I pick you up me
lady come on
yeah
she stopped purring and she just smacked
her lips did she hear that that was her
smacking her
lips cat smacking lips ASMR that's
pretty
rare that was
her she just stopped
purring yeah that was
her I was literally watching her do
it she's
like
cute that was a rare sound so I take
it she left the room H qes are 17 than
you soon M eight thanks for the pinky
don't worry T despite being Rivals we
both ranked out
oh that's that's that's not really
helpful I may or may not have aimed into
a wall when you were about to rank out
in race one wait does that mean you
tried to help me oh I guess so hey
that's sweet safe travels and have fun
in Japan thank you
oh you were trying to help
me you're the best thank
you we took over that game server on
that day was fun we should do it
again
Cruz avenge me Tiara
as oh I by the way this was about the
wedding I ended up
you know talking to her like like kind
of hinting to her about like hey I've
heard you do this at Japanese weddings
um is that right and then she was like
oh yeah but don't worry you have to you
don't have to bring anything you're like
coming from outside of Japan like all
the way you know and I'm like yeah I
knew she was going to say
that I did spend a lot of money just
getting there so I think it was
acceptable for me not to give her any
cash yeah my attendance was like special
enough okay I am the gift fair I think
it's fair I spent the most money on
getting there not only the plane but
also the shin
consen
mhm and
I need to go to Idol
meeting trash
can I love that you have that name still
Peter campy Dan imagination Arts Dan
Wiki Tunes
Dan uh Na oh yeah you make me remind is
that remember is that guy like did
something is there something new about
that guy who the the the Troublemaker
streamer in Japan who got arrested I
wonder if there's any
news do you guys know anything
no still being
held no news huh
okay yeah he's probably still just like
chilling in the cell
hopefully reflecting on his actions that
little
[\h__\h] oh he is going to jail for three
years is that like fix
now karma finally justice justice wants
Justice is
served that little [\h__\h] so deserved
wow
wow and
Japanese o Japanese jail
huh o it's I would say I mean I've never
been there but from what I heard it's
[Music]
different
damn so hopefully he'll learned
something from that this
[Music]
time Galaxy I
am
no pink almost for to send you thir
greetings this
[Music]
year
here did you want to send more than that
cuz it cuts off so suddenly and there's
no more after
that are you sure David ask you cuz did
you tried a new
link
cuz
like I think the new link
uh fixed
it the one in the Old Post works but the
new post was okay try the one the new
Link in the old post I
guess works but it's raw yeah just
unpack
it why why what's why is it so why
what's with this
wallpaper what's going
on okay if we get to the half of the
month I will try it again cuz you know
Giga file only has like rough settings
like 3 days 5 Days 7 days I think 14
days 30
days okay let's just get there and I'll
try to make another link and I make it
14 days
okay I don't know what the problem
is the like the first one was
corrupted but only I think only on the
phone right now
now I guess I don't know what the
problem is now just being raar you don't
like the
ra you downloaded yesterday on your PC
which one which one did you which link
did you
use the first link works the second one
is Ser what the [\h__\h] is it not the same
link let me
[Music]
check oh it's
not why is huh
okay if you guys are
saying the first one is fine then let me
replace the new link that was supposed
to fix things with the old one that's
also a new one somehow I don't
understand okay and is this now raar
yeah it
[Music]
is
oh
uh yeah yeah the r should be fine you
just have to right click um I think even
if you don't have RN R installed doesn't
it just automatically like use like the
like the zip uh Plugin or
whatever like basically unzip it yeah
yeah yeah
yeah that's what I thought okay
good maybe on the phone it's not so easy
but
uh uh how did we do it until
now isn't this how I do
it I'll I'll do well as I said when we
get to the middle of the month I'll do
it again
differently still zero are you sure what
why are you done downloading this on the
phone or on the PC right now let me
download it
download it's corrupt on my end I'm on
PC n and you tried the old one the new
old the one in the older
post oh yeah I already downloaded it
before and it worked now I have it again
well it it
works it
works
weird yeah I just updated it
again anyway okay back back back to
business are TV cuz I like watching you
well I mean if you put me on your TV I'm
basically your TV smart TV I'm going to
make your TV into a smart
TV trust
me my highest score what was my highest
score we got to like 2, something 400 or
so surprisingly low even after all these
hours I am a shame
AED but well Cali has played it for
hours and
days and still didn't get to free Cas so
I guess it's it's quite normal to
struggle okay uh what was I
umy I read this I
extar and but wait I feel like I didn't
really go into the
[Music]
like
and then by you
soon I I'm done with
this let's
go
oh yum
good
plan love Rush had a few super
chats the premiere oh my God most of
they're like most of them are
unknown a you just wrote the the whole
lyrics super
chats is
this oh my
God it's literally the complete lyrics
you must really like the song
W better sing the song then oh my God no
I'm not going to sing
it no this too
much it it it adds up to a red it it
does
it wait 5 10 15 20 it
might 25
30 but that's like
cheating 35 40 for I can't count man
it's probably a red
one but it's
cheating doesn't count no don't believe
with a red one there's no way you could
write this much and make me sing a whole
song Thank You unknown for being
understanding oh I hear
smooy she doesn't do really love us I do
but if you want to hear it you should
stream the song on YouTube just listen
to it on
YouTube you know what I'm going to do
right
now I I don't know if it really I
wouldn't really say it had like a huge
effect on
it but I'm going to change it now from
PV to
MV
okay are you happy now
algorithm I can't believe people
wouldn't click on it just because it
says PVE I like literally can't believe
it like you should really just click on
it okay done it's now an mvy not a
py okay so guys do me a
favor let's get love Rush at least to
100K cuz otherwise it's just sad so if
you guys have some free time please
stream love Rush on YouTube a little bit
I would really appreciate
it thank
you thank you please please please
uh so what do we do here what do we
do thank you uh 22 times okay I'll say
Dan I'll say Dan 22 times at least Dan
Dan
Dan D D all
right that was
easy
if it's playing on Loop I don't think so
like
um it's hard to say I think you might
have to play like a full video in
between and then go back and play it
fully and maybe even stay in the
tab the Sai Dan K D Cru Dan The Gamer
cre Dan pandon aess
Dan dley Dan Alvar Dan Tracy danash
seven of evil danash jish monkey d space
waterfall
prodction
yay oh the outfit by the
way um the outfit isn't it so cute for
love rush I gave like basically like two
or three examples of what I wanted and
like she combined it basically I really
really like it it's so pretty it turned
out so
cute
right yeah okay
paragliding challenge super chats we got
a
few cute cute cute
cute and thanks for the pinky hey got
some questions any update on the sve
sword
[Music]
PNG
oh yeah yeah
no
uh you would think
[Music]
so okay um um how hard can it be right
you you you would think
[Music]
so
um it's uh it's
complicated but I do think they forgot
about it at this point um I already
reminded them a few
times let me see if I can
find
any where is
the see okay
[Music]
hey okay they definitely forgot about
it okay okay thanks for reminding me to
remind them how does the new hair for
your casual outfit look from the
back I don't know just the braids just
are tied together in the back that I
would say I don't know I don't have like
a a drawing of it but it's nothing
special I think one could an artist
could probably just come up with it on
their own it I think it's an easy
guess uh and speaking of have you
noticed your blouse in that outfit has
been way less SE ah I saw this and it
really made me wonder I
don't think so I don't know I looked I
tried to look at it and I'm not sure
I don't
know it did it at least didn't really
bother me you swear okay where is the
proof where are the pictures I told you
to get
pictures where it's noticeable cuz I
tried to compare it and I didn't really
see anything but I was just looking on
my
phone someone made it side by side oh
really okay show me now send it to me
now on
Twitter is this true
that's
crazy that's
insane I don't even know what to say
like cuz like getting anything fixed
really takes a while I might just keep
it this
way I don't know they seem more safer
now I don't even notice the blouse right
now yeah you know especially because we
can take it off now I don't think I care
that
much
um but yeah here I'm refreshing my
Twitter I I am
waiting I don't see anything
yet go
go I really need to go idle meeting that
you making me wait
[Music]
why St not there oh my
God just
go
okay but stay okay I was forc myself to
wait because people
leave okay you better stay don't God of
amiibo I Am timing you
out that is not
acceptable
it's just us and the chainsaw now are
you scared you should
be hello what do you mean quiet I was
muted now I'm
not
okay
um yeah thank you also you listen to The
Voice pack thank you yeah I I was part
of the end of Z voice
pack which reminds me I have to record
one like another one really
urgently I think the deadline is like on
the 11th
Maybe I think so right let me check my
deadline where is it here this
one oh no it's
tomorrow that's
fine I'll record it
tomorrow r no bgm please read the note
above my
head bring your own bgm to workday
fancy thank you
for rent
money oh this must have been after my
Twitter space
right oh yeah wait it was I had this
open during my Twitter space Oh yeah
thank you oh my God I actually have to
make uh more big payments and this by
but I think somehow it will be
Dau but because of that I would have
also preferred to not pay for business
class
again oh well if it isn't the
consequences of my own actions and the
incompetence of Austrian Airlines
customer service a thank you
doll it's a big
help do I need money for food no because
my mom cooked for me so I can eat the
leftovers I'm living on
leftovers thank you FL of fetty very
very
kind you're leaving where are you going
where are you where do you think you're
going yeah she cooked me for breakfast
she also made me kashman which I always
love to have when she's here I always
ask her to make
kashman yummy so good GD thanks for the
pinky get a new tax account at kiar dot
do dot no no because it's like so
annoying to
like no it's fine Sky thanks for the
pinky almost bankrupt fun let's
go thank you AO dang Ultra Noob d h
d mic thank you for the pinky just got
reborn recently o
congratulations show yourself are you
here I want to
see I want to
see also I think I have a meeting with
her soonish I got to get some
documentation
going before that
o wait you're not
here man okay show me next time show me
your beautiful reborn self next time
promise
promise H the koala Universe the gameer
Jim Tracy Dy D studio raing with the
pinky
[Music]
ta tati thank you for the red jet taii
still here taii doesn't disappear huh
like I think I would think he's gone but
then he proves me I'm wrong really nice
thank you
Tai thank
you and space
[Music]
waterfall okay and
then oh okay still have a a bit more but
maybe we can keep some for
tomorrow I still got to read the Japan
chat ones a few from the other Vlog and
ID collab but that's not
much yeah let's end it here I want to
eat something I think just chill chillax
with my
cats you added me okay let's check out
the comparison thank
you let's see what science
[Music]
says
I don't know well I wonder if it's just
because of the
angle but
yeah well do we have another old
one was it really that bright
[Music]
before I don't know what am I looking at
um
well old new
[Music]
wait I make comparison now how about
that I'll try to pose the same way and
then we can be extra
sure that they did
that but I don't know if I'll really
request them to fix it because
I um like it's it's just
annoying I don't want to annoy them um
even though it shouldn't be like that
but
still
[Music]
H I keep the Hat
though and then let me put a white
background because that
way you can
judge it better
maybe
okay
uh
yeah okay yeah
wow
wait I'm like a little
bit
higher wow okay
[Applause]
screenshotting uh
cheese
okay
oh okay science for science
now let me get rid of
the white
background
and I moved my head by
accident bikini had a darker
Hue I don't know I'll just tell them
let's look at this and see if they want
to fix it maybe maybe
maybe slight difference but still
noticeable it's not a big deal I would
say you can see see it on the sleeves
too yeah I guess
[Music]
so
true
[Music]
Maybe that's so weird how does that
happen oh well okay uh that's it thank
you for showing
me you don't see it much anyway it's
fine it's
fine maybe I'll just ignore
it yeah just like a small bit like it's
not completely not transparent
anymore but yeah thank you guys for
watching if you want to want more than
tomorrow is more s games I'll see you
there and nice to have you guys back
nice to be back and the German we say
Alin
byebye Cho see you tomorrow good night
have a nice day or evening
[Music]
bye-bye