[Music]
Mr. Orange and the idol Vtuber
interview interview
It's Takanashi Phoenix's character from Horror Men Gush It's
Orange
It's Orange
[Music]  I
'm late.
Excuse me
. There's a reason. I was busy.
What do you think we were doing? I
wonder what the two of us were doing standing there.
Autumn kicking, oh yeah, right now, Nenechinchi. I'm
asking you to come to Nene's house. Hey, let's
do this.  No, it's
Benetintine. Yes, it's
fine if you have a penis. Danger,
danger,
yes.
M away. Well, that
's right.
Nekirari-chan took a look at that family.
How was it? It
was cute, wasn't it? Everyone, uh, there's
something
wrong with insects.  I don't think it's that big of a deal,
but
seeing it so close up for the first time in real life made me
a little disappointed.
[Laughs] It's about the
size of my palm.The
thing with the long wings makes me
wonder what a flower flower is.
But I took a photo. I
want to post it on Twitter after this. It's
crazy. It's
Geo Guesser today. It
's popular. Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, I
named the bug.
[Music] Hey,
bug
. You're going to die soon.  It's a relatively short time, so why don't you give it a name?
Right away means it's
only 3 months, but I
've given it a name. I want to live a more
meaningful life. Well then, I
can't give it a name for that hairy thing.  Hmmm,
that's right.
Mofurun Mofurun is cute. Well, I'm
going to fill it up now. When I saw the bath, I
thought it was a dangerous cloud, but it
turned out that it looked like a giant spider, and its legs were really fluffy. Moreover,
when I opened the box, it was a bit stinky,
but that's just how it is.  I felt like those insects were
out in force.It's so
funny.They really have that kind of hobby.I
thought my house was interesting.I was a little
disappointed, but I thought it was interesting.
The smell
is better than that of a dog, isn't it? It
smells like a natural smell, is
n't it
?
[Music]
I
leave it here, and I
don't even try to meet the dog. It's
on the floor.  What will happen if you put it
fly. Flying flying and going somewhere with
feathers There are wings There are feathers.
Well, if you
say you're an insect-loving Esuke, then let's
talk without a box.
Let me be free. Do
n't let the insects be spared as they fly, so I'll scatter
them all over the room. That wouldn't be a good idea,
right? If you do that, you'll get scared while flying.  You
know, there's a room dedicated to insects in the forest, I
guess. I'd like to build a house
somewhere hidden in the forest.
Well, if you lived in that kind of place, you
wouldn't be very happy. Inside the house, there would be trees and things like that.  Niaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa(aaaaaaa(aaaaaaaaaa(2002010100010100010202 For_ for_ for 2019)” I see that it is
possible to enter the house. Well, that is
also
possible.
Hurry up and play a game.
Today is a free showdown, but when I
look at those Japanese members, it seems like everyone is only looking at Japan. I
don’t know.  Well,
today I'm
going to take Neji overseas on a
world trip,
but the
screen is all in English, and it's already
possible because it's a Pore account,
but
please leave it to me.
[Music]
Where in America will it be?
To be honest, I don't understand why America is serious.I
really don't
understand.I really don't understand.It's
a little bit like this.When I'm in America or somewhere like that, I always have that
mouse in my house.It's
okay, but if you're concerned about something, let me know.First
of all, where are you?  Let's go,
see more
. This is where there are signs and stuff. First of all, you
can see it here, but that's all.
Well, this is a street name, but it's a
scalpel injection. Oh, I know it's
Massachusetts embroidery, but that does
n't necessarily mean it's in Mastille.  Okay, I
see.
[Music]
Well, the road is pretty wide. Let's
walk.
What kind of place is it? Well, it
doesn't feel like it's flourishing,
right? It's like the
countryside. It's not that big of a country, though. There's a
swing at home.  I like that dog.
There are no shops.
This is a residential area. There are
a lot of Americans here, but most of the American fans
have cars.
Unless you live in a big city, it's like that.
And they do
n't leave their cars on the street.  That's right, don't stop at home.America is
so big.It's so
big.That's why America has a free final.Even
though Rain-chan will understand right away, we wo
n't understand.There was a mistake.
Also, this is a
school. Ah,
that's a P Clinic. Oh, I see. The
name of the store
is Domino's Pizza. The
name of that place is often found in Mizuno.
By the way, this is a phone number. I
think it's Savenate, which is an area code.  That's right, I'm sure
there are English viewers,
right?
Ah, what, what, what, this store is
like a goal.
Red Line
Card. They
said it's somewhere in America. That
's right. Please give me more hits. Oh,
but wait, I'm back around here.
[Music] I see.
[Music] I've
never had tacos.
Tacos Takahashi. It's
American soul food.
Hey, there
are a lot of sports shops.
[Music] It's
becoming a mountain. This place is a
mountain. If you're an
American, you'll understand by now.  Yeah,
uhh,
hint, hint, it's
not just American food. I know that.
Tacozo isn't American food, but I
feel like everyone eats it because it's soulful.
Hey, it's spacious.
Wait, this is the phone number. This is the winning phone number.
Now, I guess I should pull this out a little more. It'll
disappear as time passes. It'll disappear. It'll disappear.
It's a photo that was taken at a different time, so it's okay.
Wait, where is it? It's
blurry, blurry, but I
can see it a little. It's a
shame, what's this? It's
my own sex.  OK
[Music]
Wait and find out,
America. See you
soon. It seems like Montena. Montena. Where's the problem? I heard it for the first time. How close is it from there? That's a big, wide, big camera. OK, come on, let's take a little walk around here.
This is also important here. It
says 15910, so I have to remember it
as the name of a road.
It's Surface. That area code is the same.
So I've already got a rough idea of ​​what's going on there,
but I do
n't understand anything.
But Mt.  It's along the side of the mountain.
It's close to the mountain. I wonder if
Yamato is
home.
JS I don't know what it is, but this looks
like a sport. It's not like skiing.
Hey, it certainly
snows. It's
quite far north, in the north of America.  The
weather is really bad, okay?
OK, what?
[Music]
[Laughter]
It's a shop. Somewhere, they changed the name of this place.
Wait, it's becoming a big city.
Really? Let's go a little further into the city.  Let's
see.
Wow. The
gas station looks nice. I have
n't written anything about it. Hmm. I haven't written anything about it.
Hmm. The one on the left is [Music] Well, I already know that it's popular. Give me a little more detail about the address. OK. Oh, it's
a little blurry.
But I do
n't know, but it's perfect. It's a batch battery. It's a bit like the name of a place. [Music] Look, even if you don't know anything, if you look for it a little, you can
go there. That's great.
But I walked a lot, so it's a bit
far.  That's what I think, but let's just put it around here.
OK,
that's
nice. It's amazing. It's about 800 meters away. It
's really close. It
's a square. It's a city. That's right, America. That
's the way it's mainly made. It's
ok to have them do it a little earlier.
[Music] Do
your best again, that
's it. You've
come to a forest-like place.
[Music]
There's nothing, so you
have to look for something.
Aim for something big. O Cy Fresh. What does
it mean?
Road  That's the name of this shop. Let's go to the shop
okok. Let's aim for the big one. Okay, that's
terrible. First of all, I do
n't understand this.
[Laughter]
[Music] Looks
good. Hmm.
[Music] It would
help if I zoomed in.  But I haven't written anything
[Music]
Please zoom in a little bit.
Eh, it's
better not to do it now.
[Music]
That's a little bit.
If you said the price, you would have cropped it out. Ah, that's
right.
Isn't that there too?  It's okay, I protected you, I
protected you, I'll protect you
After the car shop [Music] I
look at that sign over there. I think I should look at it,
but I think I should change my phone number. Or
should I look for my phone number? It's
written there,
but
[Music]
Hey, America.  It's so
big, it's so big
[Music]
I do
n't understand that. I don't understand it
too much. Can I
see it? If I can see it, it's like, oh, here,
this way, it's the seaside. Even if it's like that this time, it's the North Color Liner's Surfist. There's no side around here, it's the sea. It's the only
phone number that's ever used.  Apparently, it's
better, better? By the way,
what does this mean
?
Eh, well, this is probably
someone else's photo, but when I
translate it, let's
mute the microphone for a moment.
[Music] I
see. That's the name of the store.  I don't
know why they chose that name, but it's
slow and effective. I wonder if it's a
gas station.
[Music]
Even when I get close, it's all fur. Hmm,
no. [Music] I wonder if they're putting in a car. Doro's is
making them.  Not yet
[Music] It's
a bit, you
should look at the details
Dangerous spanion
Espanol Spainon can speak
Ah,
uh, that's Kaito-kun, please go home.
uh, kind
uh, this. If it was
an American or something, I wouldn't be able to find a store.
And the
type of metal and the
type of fire are
different depending on the location.There
are stores that don't have a store, and I can
understand it quite well with wood etc.
But I don't know what
it was like yesterday.Oh yeah, the type of fire yesterday.What?
Hint please hint pudding It's okay.  It's
not quite a rock, it's just
one more thing.It
's an authentic Mac, it's different from the American Mac.The
taste is so
healthy.I
guess it was Japanese health.I don't think it can be called healthy, but it seems like it's not very
filling.And
sugar.
There are so many traffic lights. There are so many traffic lights. I'm from here.
[Music] It
might be true, but it seems like there's more to it than that. The
size of the carpasage is terrible. Are hamburgers big in America?
If you order a small size drink, you'll get
something like this.The
small size in the US is the
L size in Japan.Hmm, that's right, it's a
good deal, but I think so.That's
helpful.It's true that there is a KFC,
not a KFP
store.  Please change the name of the store that doesn't have a name on it.
Just to confirm. I wonder why. I
want you to write it down.
This is difficult.
[Music]
This is a
battery
shop. I
think it's the one from earlier. Hmm.
Well, let's
go. Let's go.  Let's go, let's go,
teleport Oh
, wait
, but I wanted to do it all the time. Hmm, no, I don't really understand this. It's like a sign. It just
had that speed.
That's the way it works. But
even if it's written here, I wonder how far away it is.
Hey, I don't think it's that far away, but then I can't see
the surf. Oh, no
, that's it. But I haven't seen the ocean, so I'm sure. It's in the city, so you think it's nice to be down here. Maybe it's not right,
but it's almost there.  I
think it's close.
What is everyone doing? What do you think of this
number
?
Oh yeah, it's
probably
erased here and there on the road, but
87 is up.
There's 87. I
think it was 70 when I looked at it from a distance.  Yes,
that's
true. Where did you go earlier? Okay, it's a long way, isn't it? It's 70 years long. It's long, and it looks like a crane. In Japan, it's the image of a seaside place.  It's like lifting something up. That's
amazing!
This one is seriously facing the sea.
There's just a little bit more written like this. This is
this, this is this, this is that factory.  That's
right, it seems like they're stabbing it on the side of the road. They're not pasting it on the wall. After all, it's 87 again. If it's true, that hole is basically 87. [Music] This one is ok, so it's
perfect. I don't think it's necessary to make it clear,
but just a little.  It's a winter scene. There
are
41. 41 is along 70 streets, so I thought I'd
do this for a little while. Let's
go. When you
look at it like this, it looks far away, and it's
really real. It's true, it's like the
Fire Out version.  It was
below, that's true.
Someone wrote in the chat that they
wanted to go to Bangami. I
went to Enoshima, and at this Bangami beach, it
said that there was a beach in Enoshima, so here
it is. [
Laughs]  It's
safe to say that this is worth it,
isn't it? It looks like a school,
isn't it? Hihiro: Yeah, but it might not be a school. Go around a little, look around,
look around.
Victory, this is what Pringus is doing.  This building is
currently in a large area of ​​mud, so you
should take a good look at it. You can ask if there's anything written on it. Is
n't there a name for this building?
Hmm, it's not really listed.
Take a look here and there.
OneWay
Donotenter That ca
n't be helped
I'm
bored
38 yen I
don't need this I don't need this
[Music] I
don't see it very often Oh
Quick High School I see I
heard you click somewhere for the first time
Hey, but it seems like a
peaceful place It's
calming.  The
tree is beautiful The
baby really fainted and died The
unconsciousness has changed Ah wait
414 Oh, I got the phone number so I'll get it soon
414 I do
n't know but I'm looking for this
This is helpful I'm
infected with a virus Oh the
sea This isn't the sea but it's serious  There are
so many ponds, it's such a
nice
place
[Music]
Wow, that's
okay. Oh, but that's the high school I just mentioned. Yes, the
Scott card is
really good. This is American.
Even if I go alone, I can do some sightseeing on my own.
Yeah, it's really good, don't get lost, right?
[Music]
You know,
that Morita
has S and MVBA written on it. That's
right, this is what I
want to see in order to study.
[Laughs] It's
great when I'm going abroad.  It's kind. It
's not a kindergarten. It's
not a kindergarten. It's a park.
[Music] A
signboard.
It's a place that's being invaded. I wonder
if it
's the name of a town, but it doesn't look like it's by the sea. Hmm, there
's tennis here.  On the right side,
tennis Japan,
American Denny's
is not delicious at all.
[Laughs]
That's right, it's delicious. Denny's is
delicious even when delivered to your home. That's pretty good.
Oh, there's a restaurant in America,
there's a restaurant in Japan, and the
one in America is pretty bad.  I
heard that. Hey,
but the 7-Eleven in America is
full of poop.
[Laughs] It's full of
poop. I want to go to Starbucks. There are a lot of
hotels here, so I haven't written a few photos. Hey,
this is
n't a phone.
Hunting, oh, here, there.
Look at me, I don't think there
's anything wrong with that, but it's not written there
.
[Music] I can't
use 88. I
can't use it. I'm
making
that toll-free call. Wait, wait, that's not 200. Is it
713?
Wait, wait, Hussen.  I wrote it on a sticky
note
71 I
know, I know, it's
here Ok
Stop I've
heard it before
[Music] I do
n't know, it's from America, it's pretty
similar in shape, it's
almost the same
Texas is amazing I
went to Uny, Adeka  This place you can see,
it's true, I've discovered this place, but it
's kind of an interesting shape.
Texas. I've heard of Texas.
Houston is
on the ocean.
It says it's nice. If you're a nice person,
this is it. It
's on the ocean. I
need some hints.  Even if it's just a little bit, I've
already figured it out. I wonder if I ca
n't find a park or something. It looks like a park earlier,
but it's
small,
so I don't think it's possible.
[Music] I guess
people aren't walking around anymore, huh? I guess there
aren't that many pictures of it. After all,
everyone is in
cars.
There's a lot of phone numbers that I don't think will ever be deleted.
[Music] Let's
make some more checker PVs.
What's Texas? Have you ever heard of
Texas? Texas,
oh well,
penetrate the
whole French
[Music]
Osmosis City Jachintou  Jachinto,
Wow,
this is great, isn't it?
That's all I understand.
Wow, that's
amazing. Mango
is really good. By the way, it's the fifth and last in America.
Let's go squid.
[Music] I wonder if it's
completely
okay.  There's a cover. It looks difficult here. You can't
go there
unless there's a road. It's like a
campsite. First of all, let's find a big road.
That's nice. Each house is big. It looks
a bit peaceful. Do your best. So,
the world I've seen in Icarly.  Ah, I
see. It's true
that it seems to often appear in those American TV shows.
Comedy dramas.
This is the big road. I
said I'd leave it to you once again, but
this is a school bus.
Oh no, this is already there.
Eh, this is this, this
is Kenchi, May is some kind of place Hey,
money is definitely a place.
MA was
supposed to leave it to me. Let's
go here,
mamams. It
's a novel. Okay, then I'll leave it to you from here.
Okay, can you find that?  The name of the place
is Canyon Findy
in
K or K.
[Music]
No, it's like a different place.
No, I
don't know. If it's a small town, you might have to zoom in a little more to see it.
Well, it's a little hard to see, so I'm going to
change this. Hmm, I
think you can look around Ao and A a little more. Let's
look for hints. Hmm, I
like the big mom on the road. It's
quiet, isn't it? Yeah, it
's quiet.  Hey,
do you have a phone number? I
don't need it anymore. I've already figured it out. Even with a phone number, all I can do is get an interview.
Ah, here it is, massachu and embroidery.
That's right.
[Music]
No, this is the
one who forced himself to find Venus.  That might be a good idea. Yeah, there's a
pop-up on the map.
Venus. I'll help you a little.
Hmm, help me
out. OK,
OK. [Music] [Music] That's true.
Berlin, sometimes I keep repeating my name.
Hey, there's something like this in a city like this.  It doesn't feel like that,
right
? It's definitely greenish. I know that.
[Music] It
must be green.
's H. It's a response.
Really, it's
not a gaze, it's a response. I don't know. It
's a response, but it's also negative.  I haven't seen it. It's
okay to reply, but I
haven't found it. I
know it's
Harvard University,
but it might not be this one.
Maybe they're just in the same place. The
same name doesn't mean it's there, but it seems
like it's there.
Harvard University.
Where is
Harvard Elementary School? Harvard Elementary School.  I think I should go to elementary school. You
're too old.
No, I'll skip a grade
and go back soon. Shun-senpai went there, right? You're a second-class
graduate. You're an
elementary school graduate, so university is different.
Well, Shion-chan, I'll give you university.
Oh, why is this so good? It
wasn't in the middle of town, so I guess it's somewhere around here. Let's
do that. Ok
A.
OK, where. Ah, you were
playing a really naughty game, right?
That's how I tried it.
[Laughs]
There are a lot of other things you can do too.
Back button  Where's the back button?
[Music] It
was my first time playing such a naughty game.
I thought I'd give it a try. It's New Year's Day, so how was it? Yes, it was naughty, so I watched something so naughty. Everyone in my house seemed to be happy.  Right.
[Music] Even
though it's night, there's a lot of people, and they're
all feeling naughty.
That's right. It's amazing. It
's in the middle of the city. I'm
not from Germany, but I can
speak German. I
think I understand the general idea, so let's go and see it.  Let's
see,
this looks like a parking lot.
Wow, Germany is like a
big city, but I'm also looking for a phone number.
Hmm, I guess I don't need it. So, what are some other
hints? I
feel like it's S, I can't read it at all, but this is it.
Essen-like S5 Essen is amazing.The
image quality is terrible, but it
looks like S.Hmm, the
gas is bad on the left side.Ah,
that's
[music]
.I
know, but the
location and here and there are similar to loaf.By the
way,
other than that Japan, it's the best in
Japan.  It's a place where a lot of people gather.
Well, I guess there's a reason why,
but it's been a long
time since a lot of Japanese people lived there, so
there are a lot of restaurants
, Japanese restaurants, Japanese stores, Japanese
hotel chains.  Yes, I
can understand Japanese.Heh, I
guess there are a lot of Japanese people there.There
's an area where many Japanese people gather, but I think we can communicate pretty well there.Heh,
don't look for it, let's do this.It
's a white birch tree.He's
there.  There's a dog too. It's
cute. It's amazing. You see,
in Germany you can park your car on the road.
Well, if there wasn't a parking lot, this would
be pretty normal. [Music] There's
no big road. I'll still look for it. It's still peaceful.  Yeah, I guess it's a
park.
It's a nice place. There's a lot of people there.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on. I want to draw some graffiti.
[Music] There
's a lot of graffiti overseas. I'm used to it,
but I
came to the store.
Wait, wait, what's that?  Right now, here,
over there, it's a
little too detailed. I
don't know, but sometimes I
write concert hall names on posters like this.
[Music]
Can't you see? The image quality is terrible.
Other
maps are better.  No, I can't
read it. I wonder
who it is, so I'm writing City.
Sorry. Ah, it's amazing, it's artistic. It looks like something was actually written here.
But the
image quality has
no choice but to improve. But this is the main street. That's
right.  Hey, I don't understand, Coca-Cola, I
want something that I can see clearly.
[Music] I ca
n't see. Oh, by the way,
something happened to me while I was sleeping. There was a
country in Europe that I wanted to go to, right? It was Spain,
right? I want to go to Pei.  I'm going to go later. I'm going on a
world trip today. What
shop is this?
[Music] It's
too difficult to even do. Ah,
but I don't
understand. The
game. It's a bit narrow here.
Hello.
That's the name of the place. The
name of the road. This is a one-person car.  It's
cute.
There's a micro or micro in Japan. It's cute. I want
to
ride
it. I want to ride it. You know,
there are a lot of them in Germany, especially the
buildings. I don't want to ride on them. I
don't want to be exposed. Things like
that here.  Yeah, I'm back, that's right here,
hmm, no, I'm not home, back The traffic
light is a little different again. You're
fluent,
licking What's the language? What's going on fluently?
[Music] I
wonder if I
change it into a car, it's still in Berlin It's here, but it's
a bit like Berlin's window park.  It seems like it
's around here,
but it doesn't necessarily mean it's really there, so I'll
drive around a bit, OK.
Take me.
[Music] It's a
car.
This looks good. Bus stops here and there. Ah, the signs. It's been
4 years.
[Music] Something like
that here, that cut.  I don't
like it, but I'm starting to understand
[Music]
Unko spare version I can
understand Bell Berlin. It's
over there in Veronie, but I wonder if it's
really that weird. I
want it on a signboard or something, not on a car.
[Music]
There's something posted on it.  Advertisement for the Aoba Bath An
advertisement for the bathhouse is right in front of me. It's huge and
stagnant. It's
moving in an instant.
[Music]
Ah, but there's something like this. Yeah, it's
really big.
The road is
[Music]
And the phone number.  There is, but I won't look into it this time.
[Music] There
are a lot of cars. I
guess I feel that way. I feel like the city is a little different compared to America. It's like a town. I thought there was a little less nature here. That's
right. Nature, too.  Oh, wait, I
think this is the name of a city, but I've
never heard of it. I've never heard of it. I
don't know. I don't
know.
There are people who say it's 100% Berlin.
Seriously, I'm
finally going to do it
in Berlin.  I wonder if the
city feels like Europe, and even if it's free, do
n't think this is Europe.
There are better things out there. It's
really still a little different. It's a little
different. I want to see the
let'sGOOK
[music]
and this.  That's fine. It's already drumstick.
What's this? It's
really busy. Is this Europe? I
guess I can guess it just by doing so. What's the name of the forest? It has to be hard pack. I ca
n't get it, but
it's only in the front and back, so it's
everywhere.  I can't go, I'm locked up. Well, on
Friday, I did
n't know anyone, so I asked them. Well, they don't
know.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well, then, yes, I
came to see you. It
was Frankfurt.
Frankfurt Frankfurt food
This is apparently
it.  Frankfurt, yeah, it's the
name of a place,
huh? It's a
political name, but it
's also the name of a place. Hmm,
next time, please choose a proper place.
Over there.  I
know, I
know.
As expected, it became very popular. Thankfully, the members of the English English group. After all, not everyone understands it. The
boys in my class were happily singing it.
Here,
it's so cute. But here, it looks like a big match.
Germany, it's big.  There are a lot of towns, aren't there?
Unlike Austria, there's only one restaurant. There's only one.
[Music]
That's what it would be like to be a free guest of Austria at Ospa. The
location isn't fixed, it's fixed.  Or rather, it
's all the same because it's limited.
[Music] I
'm kidding. It's a
piano.
Famous
classical music
composer Mozart was born in
Lenovo.
Computer responds to that.
[Music] I wonder
if this is a tourist spot. It doesn't seem like it's a
tourist spot.  I don't think so, but I think he's pretty
central in the
city. He's making music somewhere near the seaside. I
can't go here, it's too small. He
wears terrible hats, like knitted hats. I think this is written in the advertisement, too. It's a
bug.  Let's
go that way, so we can't go
that way. [Music] It's black. It's OK. It's hard mode. It's hard mode. There's no hint. There's no hint. That's all we have. [Music] Something like this.
It's the name of a road overseas.
[Music]
For
example, Japan's strengths are completely
different.For example, I think it's written in a different system.For
example, ``Hanopass only''
means something like, ``Tokyo, Tokyo'' street, but that's why.
This doesn't necessarily have to be Tokyo. It's
meaningful. It's true. It
's not. Hint
[Music] It
's rough, but it's not so rough. It's just that my
current analogy has landed. I feel like I'm trying to get into
this building. [Music]
I don't know. This is a typical German
town, so I
don't go there very often.
[Music]
Police. It
's a hospital. The
name "
hospital" reminds me of the name of the town,
right?  It's
been erased. It's been erased.
Hard mode Hard mode Can I
pass here?
Please
let me pass. I can pass there. I wonder
if there are so
many people. Summer is already here.
[Music] Looks
like a flower shop.
[Music] A
crazy bicycle.  It's stopped. It's
not going well in America, so
it's difficult for Germany, but for some reason it's like that. It's
probably a little like Japan.
There are a lot of buildings, and there are a
lot of cars. Let's
go with everyone, Berlin, Berlin again.
Eh, Berlin.  This is a pharmacy uptake.
It means a pharmacy. But if it's a pharmacy in Berlin, it's
not Berlin. I wonder
if it's going to turn into a shoot again. It's okay. It's
close. That's a
joke. It's a really
good road.  Okay, let's just keep going for a while and leave it to you.
[Music]
You know that, yeah,
German highways. Yeah,
that speed is
freedom. Even if it's
fast, it's
fine. There's no limit.
Hey,
this is, ah, that's
helpful. That's helpful, but it seems like I've gone too far.  Let's
take a look at Zoom 2 If
Humberschbeck is the closest, it's OK.
Ok, I
have to find it, then it's Lube.
Eh, it's
close to the sea, but it's 2000m away. Well, what
if? Leave it to
me.
65 I'll
watch the kill. 65 It's quite far away.  But
maybe it's just half of my strength. Oh yeah,
what do you mean by refuting? It
doesn't mean driving a car,
but it's a road anyway, so let's go and check it out.
Eh, I
want a number. Number
mud.  I want the number 25, not 25. I didn't
see it. It's
2524. It's been
25 days since then.
There's a rainbow here, but it's still
very close to the road.
]
[Music]
OkOk
NEXTisSpain's I'm
excited, but Spain has no
choice but to do its best.
Go here, go here, go here, go here,
go here, let's
Stain.
[Music] It's
natural already. Hmm,
turn off your LINE voice, OK.
Looks hot.
Watch it once.  I wonder which one is here? It's so cute.
There's nothing natural about it. Is
there a tomato? There's a tomato, or an olive.
There's something called an olive. It's a good tomato. It's all the
way, all the
way. I'm still going all the way.
[Music]
This is the kind of place where I found myself.  I wonder if it's
going to be a too random animal.
Just look at it. But it won't stop at this type of leaf.
And it's on the ground, isn't it? On the ground. I wonder if
this is really a forest.
How far will it go?
I'm
really giving up on it, but there's something like that. A
sign
[Music]  ] I ca
n't read it. I guess something has ended here. If
it's an insect, then
this probably
means taking that
nice trip.
Then
[laughter]
No, I
don't understand Spanish, but I
'm in Europe, where I hear things like that quite a lot, and Spanish is quite similar to Italian, so
I guess it's okay to say sorry, so I guess it
was in a place like this.  Well, I
guess that's what it means, I guess
. There's no main street.
[Applause]
The concept of a main road is gone. And so are the
houses.
But if you've come this far, you'd
better go straight.
Trust me, let's go.  -There
's a building, right? It's coming, it's
coming. Come on, it
's a cow.
[Music] I
guess skirt steak isn't just noise. It's a secret, but I just learned about it for the first time yesterday. It seems like
skirt steak can be eaten anywhere, but I
heard it.  Yes,
but I've heard that if the person at the restaurant
says it's entwined, it's like skirt steak.I've
heard that if the person at the restaurant decides that it's skirt steak, it's okay to serve it as skirt steak, no matter what part it is.  But it might be a lie. It's a
scam. Boyfriends and
girlfriends can
say anything is Calvin. If the
person at the recommended restaurant decides that this is our casual place, then it
's Calvi.
[Laughs] I wonder
if it's Main Street Boulevard or this is the ranch.  Let's
move on. There was a building after
all. Here we go. Go
forward until you find a sign.
[Applause]
Maybe it would have been better to go left or right over there.
But,
there's no houses around here. There are cars.
Only cows.  No, I don't
know [Music] I don't know. I've
been to Spain once, but I
wouldn't go there the first time. I don't know if I went here once. It's
not in the city.
Where are you? I can't connect to Wi-Fi here.
But I
can't see the map, but
there's also a horse.
This is a small horse.
[Music]
Oh, look to the left again. It's
cutely resting. It looks nice. It
's a sign. I don't know.
What does that mean? It probably
means a lot.  I don't
think so, but
there seems to be someone who knows where it is, and even if you're a genius,
you're
not a cheat.
There's a basketball goal. It
looks like it might be interesting.
What's the
hint? There's a guy
in a certain place who
speaks Spanish.  No,
there's a town, but it's so far away that he seems
to
have figured it out.
[Music]
My brother here, you know, you know,
my brother has
been recently coming from around here in Austria, going
from around here,
through Switzerland,
to Ryoko, or whatever...
[Music]  ] I've been
walking so far. The three months I've been
walking have been amazing. I can walk in just three months. On the
contrary, I wonder what they're saying. Oh
yeah, that's right.
This
is a work in which I walked through a tunnel as a standard pilgrimage.
Apparently it was difficult.  That's right.
[Music] I
was just saying what the name was.
[Music]
That
's the only place I've heard of it.
Actually, that's all I've
heard of it. It seems like it's
somewhere nearby,
but I said something like it's on top of that.  I wonder
if it starts from the north. I
didn't say anything when I saw Calcion. It seems like it
starts with G.
[Music] Hello,
there it is. Where is it?
[Music] They do
n't seem to speak Spanish there. That's weird. I
wonder what language it's in.
Probably
Portuguese.  It's
not there, but it's close to something like this,
so I guess it's a mixture of Spanish and Portuguese.It seems like the
name of the area, Galician.Oh,
Court.It looks like that.I did
n't see it written there, but I
saw it written there.  It's written on
it. It's
not on the map.
But there are quite a few
owners. Eh, I can't even find the region.
Galician
If it's a region, it's changed a lot
[Music] It's
not difficult. I don't
understand it too much.
Randomly yes.
I've given up. It's not that bad. I
want it to be placed in a better place. I want it to be placed in a place where it's easy to understand.
Even next time, it'll be better than before. Here we
go.
Okay, let's go. This time, the
trees are interesting.
This one is
a little different. I wonder
if it'll end. It seems
like something happened.  It's kind of
warm in
Spain. I
drank the fields. Is it warm? I wonder
what kind of fields it is. Don't
push me. Eh, I
don't know. I
'm moving on. I wonder if it's
grapes.
[Music]
Really? The
futon seems to be a little bigger. It
feels like it's a different shape
[  [Music] The
letters came out, Pearl Spider.
I don't know.
Is this just the name of a building? I do
n't get it at all.
But it's nice to have stylish letters.
[Music] I
want a bicycle, and
walking is definitely
not enough.
Left or right,
right, go left,
left, left,
all the way,
Spain. It's
on a different level. They're
always plowing something.
Hmm, this is just speed.
[Music]
Done. This sounds
like the name of a place, but it's the sign.  I do
n't understand it at all, even if you say it like this, even if you're a related person.
[Music]
Española
On my shoulder,
uhm.
[Music]
No, seriously, I might have
paid to be a guide to Spain. By the way, I
went to my house.  I
used to go to Venice, Valencia, Manesia, maybe Valencia, and I was playing alone in the sea around here. I want to go to Steems again.
No, I don't know, Spain, seriously. I'm
going to Japan. I do
n't know, it's too difficult. Yes,
yes.  It seems like it was
close even though it was a bus. That's true. Hmm, I don't know.
If it were here, it would be a little crazy. It
's possible. It's
possible. If it's possible, by the
sea, by the
sea.
And it doesn't look like a small town.
Christmas
tree
[Music]
Location  In front of this, this is,
um, this
garden, isn't it? It's like an
island called Canary
Islands. It
's an island, but it's not like this one. Is there another one? It's
like a Spanish island called
Sunfresh. Those people
went there. This
is Tena.
[Music]
Eh, wait,
wait, wait,
this is probably an
island.  After all, it's over there,
this way, this way, that way. I wonder
if this is the right place.
Where should we go? Hmm, it's
by the sea,
so let's go somewhere. Here, around here,
no way. Wow, that's
5 km.
This place is
surprisingly popular for vacations.  I wonder
how big all the islands are around here Are we
going to go home? Let's go to Japan. Japan felt great. Right now, it's amazing.
Well, as
expected, but if it's Japan, I don't know. I'd
like something like that.
[Music] Let's go to Japan,
too.  I tried it, but it
seems difficult, and I often end up in Okinawa.
[Music]
Let's just say this and that. I'm
still talking on LINE. I've
come to Japan.
There are quite a few mountains in every prefecture. There
was a prefecture behind me.
Akita Prefecture has been confirmed.
Where is it? I'm over here on the left. I
can pretty much figure it out. I'm tired of it. Generally speaking, the
top is the bottom,
so I still don't know. Even if they
ask me to get a dome run, I do
n't like it.  I don't know.
Where is Michimura
? Is it Akita Prefecture? Let's take a closer look. It's
already very humid. I feel like it's an
experiment. It's
humid, but it looks cool.
[Music]
Oh, it's a
doll sign. I
can't understand it, but I can read road signs. I have a
license.
Why are you so surprised? Do
you really have this paper? Since
when did you have it? You took it right after you graduated from Goldway High School. Have you had a
drive date yet? Well, I'm
going to drive with Nene.
When was the last time you drove one?  Ah, it
was about 3 years ago,
no, I
don't like it. It's not like I don't trust the area around here. Route 105. Eh, I haven't driven
for about 3 years,
but if I suddenly start driving again, I don't
think I'll be able to do it. I don't think I'll be able to do it. I want to
go to the driving school one more time. Eh,
but  I guess there are some, like
convenience stores, etc.
But are there any Japanese people who can drive well
even if they haven't gone out for a while? Well, I don't think they need a car.
If you don't have an image, please let me know.
Everyone, I'll
take them with me.  I'd like to do some kind of drive in a car.Usually,
Klee-
senpai is like that.Senpai is
also like that.I
see.I see how weird he is.  I'm sure you can do it. You must
be the one being driven. You
don't always ride in the back, so you
probably drive yourself because you have free time. 105
[Music] It's
confirmed that it'll be on Route 105, so it's around here. Come on,
try pushing the pit.  Okay, let's do this room.
No, no, no. Next [Music] That's right. It's
not Tokyo. It's not Osaka. It's
not Nagoya.
[Music]
Hey, I don't
understand.
[Music]
Kirara
Let's ask the people at the local houses.  To this person,
I'm sorry, where are you?
Stop Asahikawa,
Hokkaido
Asahikawa is probably
only in Hokkaido. It's called Asahikawa,
right here. Yeah, probably,
probably. Wow.  So, it
's a cold place. It
doesn't move.
Wait, it felt cool. I wonder if Toko
Toko Town
is there?
[Music]
[Laughs] I'd
like to interrupt a little more. It
's pronounced "man." It's
written in Roman letters at the bottom.
Talk  Let's
just talk about it. It's
really big. The
Japanese garden in Hokkaido is amazing.
[Music] Eh, I've
never
heard of it.
[Music] The
region name is a little more
general.
Hmm.
Post [Music]
Where and
where can I find it? It's
probably very detailed.  That's what I think. Is
there someone who said it looked like cheese everywhere in the post
? It's the house around where I saw it
[Music] Oh,
what's that? 17
[Music]
Nice weather, nice weather, 16 Ah.
Very, very detailed
[Music]
21 tablets 19 are here.
6th graders are
wide.
[Music] Where is
101213 at 14 and
15? If
15 is 167, it's 17. I'm going to
get a lot of points. I'm going
to specify it.  -
[Music] There's
only 16 and 17.
[Music]
5 I've
already lost the lock. Hey,
1616th Street.
[Music] If you
go down the road, there's
only 17 and 16.  Was
n't it something
? It's an early respawn, I'm sure 17 I remember the bus stop just now. This guy is a genius. 17 I want to find him. It's like Kirara. There was a killer there, Kirara. [Music] It doesn't matter how far you go here. Ah, that's
amazing.  - Yes,
this is good. This is definitely suitable for collaboration.
Game-chan, this
is a city. It
could be Tokyo. It's a really
big city.
[Music]
Wait a minute. Let me know when you've finished hinting. I
have to go, but it's fast.
Along the road,
maybe [Music]
If it was a
city, you could probably tell by Tiara [Music] Bookstore street What's in focus? I feel like there's a word that I've never heard before, but I feel like it's something I've heard. Maybe Tokyo.
Fish. Not Osaka. That baking soda.  I've
lived in Eisaku, and I know
more about it than I do. I liked it
quite a lot.
Oh, there's a blue one, there's a blue one, oh, it's
nice. What's the
hot water here? Shrimp to Fukushima. Shrimp
Fukushima.
Amo fish.  Yeah, there
was Fukushima nearby. I wonder if there was one. I feel like there were two Fukushimas. I don't
know if it's Fukushima. Wait, but it smells like Osaka. Oh yeah. I think it's Kanto. [Music] I've heard something about it.  Let's move on a little bit. Let's go.
[Music]
Please tell me something. The
letters are small. It looks like there's a
station. It looks like it's in front of the station. I wonder if that's
wrong?
[Music]
Seriously, it's 7-Eleven's Doria Ski.
After all, it's Fukushima somewhere. Kushima
is a military commander.  I wonder if there is one?
[Music] It
's not the Loop
Line. It's not the Loop Line. It's not Osaka. I searched and searched for it. The
Loop Line. There
was an expressway
there, so I guess if Fukushima was around here, what would it be? I
wonder if Osaka city is that close.  After all, it's Japan.
Everyone in Wrench's chat is very knowledgeable. That
's right, as expected,
everyone here is
helping out.
Osaka also has Fukushima, after all.
[Music] That's
great. I want to go to Osaka. Let's go. Let's
go! I
want to defeat Block. I've
gone too far.
Well, I don't know. I can't see it
either.
But I think I saw something like that when I went fishing. I
want a train to Fukushima. They're
looking at me so much. They're
so over here. I have a good attitude. Oh man, where are we going?  I wonder
where we're going.
This is juice.
Fukushima 7-chome. It
's cool and detailed. It must be Osaka. I wonder if it's
in Osaka city. It's probably to the left of the way home. No, it's so
fishy. I want to
go there every time. I don't
know where it is. I don't know. I want to
come.  Where is Osaka? I do
n't know. It's cute. It's next to Osaka Station. It's Osaka. So where is Osaka Station?
Fish and vegetables
[Music]
Umeda Oh Umeda Umeda?
How
about that Shinkansen in Ueda? Answer.
It's along the road.  Is this around here
? Yes, it's okay. I'll go.
Don. You've already
helped me a lot, but it's the
best. There's
still more. This is the countryside of Koi Ah 4. Even with this, it's just too soon. Here,
that neglect.  Have you ever been
looking for a dollar like this? I
wonder if I'll have to waste it
for a while Yes, why is it here? It's like that when we were in the city It's
scary, I'm all alone here
Orange
Orange  I'll grow oranges here. I do
n't think we'll have any fans here. They
won't come to the concert. We'll
do it in the mountains.
[Music] They couldn't let us
into the venue, so it might be a
spin. The
pin is like this.  Don't you care? It's
very humid.
[Music] It's
humid. It's really
deep in the mountains. There
are no signs at all.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well,
is there anyone else here? You must
be a genius.
Local number 3.
[Music] I have to
go back and zoom in. That's
what I'm reading.
Nishitani.
Below is Nishitani. Kumangu Tahara.
Ehime is Ehime,
eh.  It's
too early, it's too
early, why? It's
scary, scary. Is it
local or Japanese? It
's a scary world. Is it Ehime? What prefecture is
Ehime? Ehime Prefecture
This is it, right? But I often listen to it.
Ehime
[Music]
Aichi
Aichi Prefecture
Aichi Prefecture Ehime.  I don't think it's
there. No way. [Music] Over here.
Shikoku, Shikoku. What is Shikoku? I don't
know what it is. I'm sorry.
Ehime,
Ehime. But it's Shikoku. I've
come to Shikoku.
[Music]
Ehime, let's look for it.
Coach
Okayama
Himeji
Ehime.
Only the princess is in Roman letters. I
see, so I look for a little more detail.
After all, I'm particular about it. Let's get down to it.
Ruu Yamashita, I really like Amelia-chan here. Yes, you're right. There's
too much nature.
[Music] It's
dark, it's dark.
There's a snake that I can't answer at all.  Yes, we have
been walking in the same place for 10 days and haven't seen anyone who hasn't had a drink of water.
After getting lost, I wonder
if there are still people who came here earlier.
I wonder if I'm done.  Are there only us
left?
Don't think about it. I
think there are more. If I
don't keep walking, I
think my brain is going to go crazy.
[Music]
People - they all still exist.  Is he still alive?
[Music] What
's his address just a moment ago when I thought it was over? It's in Ehime. Yeah, something like that
. Now I can see
Nishitani Nishitani in detail.
Wow. There's a place with Nishitani. That's how I read it. [Laughs] It's
in Mt.  I was inside. It's still Kuma Plateau. It's
white.
Okay, the next one
isn't that far away.
[Music] See you
again, Toy Mt. Takasui. Maybe it's Mt. Takasui. I
guess it depends on the perfume. I'm going to
go back
down the mountain.
Wow, the scenery is amazing, but I
want to go to that kind of place in Japan. It
definitely looks like Japan. I
want to go to the mountains. So let's
go
for a drive. It's definitely tough when you don't have a car, remember it and remember it again.
There's a place called Jigokudani, which I think was Gifu, and
there was a monkey in the hot springs, and
Yame-chan really wanted to go there.That's
right, it was a really nice place.The monkeys were
left to roam.That's
what I said.  I
didn't
say that. It happened before. I should have told you the truth. I wanted to
go to Jigokudani. It's lonely to go alone,
and it takes 40 minutes without a car.
04 Area code:
Well, it's
Tokyo, so
maybe Kanto.  Hey,
can you tell me?
Saitama,
Okutama,
Kanagawa-san,
Chiba-Saitama, I still do
n't know which one.It seems like I can't figure it out just by looking at 04, so I'm
coming to a bigger city.The
car license plate number is basically umm, it's
too simple.I'm
sure it's correct.Hey, I
watched a little video last year.  But a
video of a solo trip to a hot spring in Hakone
Aaah
Pyramizodori
Hiramizo Dori Reimizu Dori
[Music]
Tiramizo Dori The locals are so
detailed Komaki It seems like they'll
come out when it rains
Don't Google it
Raise your hand only for locals If you're a local  You look
so happy.
Orange is my hometown. I'm
here on Hiramizu Street.
It's the free final, but I
feel like I recognize the smell. It's
like the same atmosphere. It's
amazing, isn't it?
Skeen, the hot
springs that suddenly appear in places like this feel really good.
Yeah, it's pretty close, oh, my hometown is
on a country road. It's
really good. It's not like I work. I see.
Everyone's okay. That orange is Japan. I'm going to do a
live house tour that goes all over Japan. That's
nice.
[Music] I've
been feeling sorry for you lately.
On TV.  I
saw a professional girl putting it up and there was a really cute girl,
right? I
heard that someone wanted to see that much of Ikusabata station. I'm
going to Ikusabata just to see it.
Stop early.
[Music]
Tokyo,
Tokyo. It's not in Tokyo, is
it? It's in the
countryside.  Actually, it's
Ome City. I'm
not sure if you've seen it. Maybe,
but it's
better than Kanagawa. It's definitely a place with greenery. It's
on the left side, and you
'll get powder in your mouth. I think it's on the
top left. Is it
somewhere like Hachioji?  By the way, there's
more greenery around here in Hachioji. [Music] There's a lot of greenery over there.
[Music] That's
true. It's amazing, but I don't know how far it is.
[Music]
Well, I'll
go there.
Okay, I do
n't even see the name of the street on Hiramizo Street.
[Music] It's probably too easy to
choose a mountain because it was sponed in a mountain.
Eh, Mizuyama wasn't even mentioned, right?
Eh, let's
do it here.
OK, let's go here. Then
[Music]
Let's go for the
last time. It's the last one. It was the last one. It
was amazing. I was able to travel the world so much. Japan was the best.
Congratulations. I was able to see America, Spain,
and Germany.  Well, I'd like to go to Germany too. Yes,
Germany is
good. Hmm, but there are some good things about it. The
more English you speak, the more you
speak German. I'm good at English, I can do it.
Generally speaking, if you can speak English, you can communicate.
Because everyone can speak English,
English is
not their native language.  But you're talking in English, so it
's English, but you've forgotten one
important thing. The
role is over. I'm
definitely
crying through my earphones. I
thought I couldn't do things like memorize words in English, but the other day I was with
Ame-chan.  When I heard Keala-chan talking, I
thought that listening was really difficult when I was in Japan, but I wondered
how I could study listening.I
can talk to her every day.
[Music]
There's such a thing as English conversation.  Maybe it's
like going to class, or watching
English programs with Japanese subtitles on free internet every day.Once you
get used to it, you can
watch English programs with English subtitles and
read the subtitles.  When I watch things, I get
better at both listening and reading, and
listening while reading
also
makes it easier to listen.
Watch it with subtitles
[Music] I've
seen it quite a few times.
Well, I know the gist of what it's about.
Okay, now go
watch it with English subtitles. Oh, I see. I already
have the Japanese content in mind, so yeah.
Well, I see, so why not watch something like Disney
with English subtitles?Let's try that.The
English will probably get a little better.Listening.But
one thing is still important.The important thing is that there are
n't that many Japanese people in Japan.  Be
confident. People
say you can't speak English,
but you have to
get over that
and try something. Well, it wo
n't get better, so it's important to just talk and
see it. Come on, I
want to see beautiful scenery like Austria.
[Music]
Personal  I recommend
Greece.Greece is also
in Europe, but it's
cheap and
clean, and the people there are
really kind.Heh,
when I went to Spain, I
had a little trouble with English only, but
in Greece I didn't have any problems.Heh, there are a
lot of easy-going people.  It's an
article on the internet, but I saw it. It's amazing. They're so
helpful,
open
and friendly. I think they're still friendly with Spanish people, but somehow I
wasn't that good at English. I'd
also like to go to the Netherlands.
[Music]
Like Hungary.  I'm in Hungary, so
just
come here and
take a plane or train from Austria.You can go to Hungary by train,
like I said before, or something like that.You can go to the Netherlands by
plane for an hour,
and from there, it's like an hour or two, here and
there.  I can get there in 1 or 2 hours,
really. I
've said it many times, but I'm scared to go. I'm
actually going to get my passport. I'll have to get it already.
Then, I'll
come around the fall, and it's
not early in the fall. That doesn't happen, so it's January now.  It's
warm and cold in autumn too.If you want to go on a vacation, it's
better to go in September at the latest.Hmm, let's
go to the sea in September.Yes, let's go to the
sea in September.That's it, I'll be waiting for you.So,
today  Chiara-chan came to my house.
Well then, we're
going to go out for some delicious, delicious food.
Well, I guess there
was something I wanted to do.
Let's go on a date at home.
See you soon,
everyone
[Music] See you
again
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
getting a little nervous
[Music] I've
already
had some regrets, but it's okay today.  Maybe,
please
[Music]
There's a fog
It's funny, but
[Music]