[Music]
uh
yo guys do you hear me
[Music]
oh hi guys welcome
and um actually i don't know about you
guys but here in japan
it is christmas
but um i feel like uh we shouldn't
we shouldn't really like i have a lot of
streams planned today
and tomorrow and i have a christmas
karaoke coming up so
i think we can the whole the whole merry
christmas meeting let's do that in my
karaoke stream
okay let's take our time we don't have
to do
[Music]
let's celebrate it uh in the christmas
uh singing stream
yeah well christmas eve but not real i
mean it's uh here it's
2 2 p.m so yeah
i personally always celebrate christmas
on the 24th
and the evening but many others do on
the 25th
like i mean okay celebrate them
celebrated on 24th but open the presents
on 25th i
open them on 24th but anyway um today
we are playing for the first time
on my channel i personally have been
playing sims
since sims one i've been playing it
since sims 1 was out
and uh yeah i basically grew up with
sims
but today we're playing sims 4.
i'm excited because i mean even though i
for many years have been only playing
sims
once per year maybe still
i am very excited to go back
and it's still a a game that is very
deep
in my heart
and i mean this is not gonna be like a
weekly series but maybe a series that we
can continue
every once in a while i have to say one
thing though
i wanted to because i whenever i play
sims
i get like a [\h__\h] ton of custom content
normally but
i even yesterday i was very busy even
though i wasn't streaming thank you for
the red super chat thank you
even yesterday i was kind of busy let me
get rid of that pinned comment
every time i i get out of the window the
audio stops don't work don't mind it
um but yeah i didn't really have time so
i only have like
five custom contents
but i made sure that i got myself some
feather earrings i have to say
once again i say this again and again
but my my feathers are not earrings
but in the game i got them as earrings i
hope
i hope they work because this is the
first time i start up the
game now here on this new pc i hope
everything works
[Music]
i think papa also likes what sims 4 is
on sale 88
off on steam ooh hashtag not sponsoring
anyway so our goal today is make
uh me and cali for now only me and
callie maybe in the future we'll get the
other girls in there as well but for not
only me and callie
and then we get a an apartment or a
house i guess
and then we will try to we will not
start i will not make them lovers from
the beginning
i will not marry them from the beginning
i will try my best to make it happen
with my godly skills controlling them
thank you for the red super chat are you
going to have a cat of course i'm going
to have a cat obviously
by the way i don't have oh god there's
so much to talk about but i don't have a
i don't have every expansion pack i have
a bunch of them
uh i didn't get every expansion back
because i don't even like
every expansion pack i'd not not because
of financial reasons
but because i don't like many of them
so let's go it's been a long time
i feel like it's been over a year for me
the last time ea is telling me the last
time i played the game was in 2019
[Music]
i play it like once a year and then i
get really into it and then then i don't
play it anymore
so yeah let's get started sorry for all
the talk
hi would you like to create my study or
whatever
let's say i don't even i am a young
adult maybe i don't know when watching
tv i mostly
pay attention to it thank you for the
red super chat thank you for the other
super chats as well guys thank you merry
christmas everyone
it depends it depends because
next question one of my thoughts on
aliens
they walk among us because there's eofy
senpai
acting is a means to
i don't know how much voodoo
do i do to my friends for my own
amusement what
some some of it sometimes
so i guess friends we're trying to
create myself huh i get asked out on a
date what's my response
it depends on the person but
my interest in politics is politics is
uh
[Music]
none of these answers really fit to be
honest new question
what's the most important thing to me my
cats
does my i guess that's family that's
family right my cat
my kids are family someone is wrong
what do i do
ah tweet about it
i i can't i cannot hold myself back
surprise the paparazzi are here of
course they are of course they are i
mean her life is famous what do you
expect
um i would hype my latest uh project i
would i would hype up hollow talk i
guess
which is by the way this weekend what's
for dinner
[Music]
burger i guess a free course meal
how do i act around groups of people
i'm sure everyone's happy yeah i tried
to
make the situation not awkward
[Music]
well they're adding like a lot of traits
but we can still change them
what do i do to cheer myself up oh
be mean to ultrasound what the hell now
spend time with my cats but to find
success
i don't agree with any of these i see
computers as
a tool for world domination that's
literally what i'm doing right now what
that's me
that's not me okay so
first of all uh what i guess we just get
this it's hap it has been a long time oh
my god not my first time playing sims 4
but
okay where do we start let's see if they
got oh
they did get my custom content hello
i am very fair although maybe
yeah that that's i think my skin tone
but it looks a little bit different on
that monitor
oh my two monitors have a different
different lighting i'm not sure what's
real
how do i change my my gender got it
why do i change my gender
hello my name is kiara
okay wine caps look though
[Music]
um
the diamond top left ah thank oh yeah
yeah thanks
the the whole layout of sims 4 is so
minimalistic somehow it's kind of hard
to
whoo that's female me
are you sure about that
which which sounds like me i believe
does that sound like me
mora hey maury you boza
maury is bowser what
does that sound like me maximum birth
okay makes sense
just speak again
yeah that's probably me i guess oh look
at what they what they
they say i'm a genius they say i'm
family oriented and i'm a foo
well that that sounds absolutely like me
[Music]
what is that greg gracious greg
gregarious what does that even mean and
i'm a party animal i mean
not no that's not that's not really true
how that changes let me change it
it won't let me change it because i got
went for that story
ah i'm going to change it thank you for
the super chat
where are my sims sims people
corrugation regulation gregarious means
talks a lot oh you can't change it
what you can change it with the story oh
come on god damn it okay but look hey
our scale is cooking
starting from above average oh
and we can write oh okay well okay
that's okay it's not a big deal
okay so i bought i i got one hairstyle
dlc that's
i was hoping that that would look like
my fluffy hair does it
unfortunately it has no um
uh greg greg gradient gradient it looks
close enough no
oh kind of edgy but
i think skye kind of i didn't have much
time to
check out the uh cc i will get more for
next time
there's pink too that's cute that color
oh wait she has pink eyebrows now now i
think
[Music]
um
maybe maybe i should commission someone
to make my outfit in sims 4 in my hat
and everything maybe i could commission
someone i wonder if that's expensive
okay so basically that's for everything
okay good
okay now the eyebrows pleasing in a
normal color
and maybe more if then i have very thin
eyebrows
this is gonna take a while since four
artists i'm gonna commission you
and what are my eyebrows
[Music]
oh my god anime eyebrows don't look
good on normal people
but i see i feel like it years ago like
10 years ago people would actually do
these kind of eyebrows and they look
ridiculous let me just tell you they
look ridiculous
oh actually oh it's fine
but the whole face situation that we
have going on here
is uh not very let's take the basic main
face
that's much cuter that's the
okay that's the or maybe that one
let's start off with that and work with
that let's try
if we i have did i download eyes no i
didn't
i didn't but it's okay they have purple
eyes yay
okay let's make our eyes big how do i do
the
oh how do i make them bigger again
ah extra big animal eyes
well that's a bit too big that's kind of
creepy though
okay okay okay okay and
it's really been a long time i i am not
used to this does this look
wait why did i change the eyebrows what
the hell
this is look does this look like me
i mean that looks like me don't you
think
i mean that i under the nose and all
that
i have a small nose every oh
we all have small noses somehow
there's literally no whole life girl
with a big nose
mom small tiny nose
this is chris kiara what's wrong what's
cursed about this
name
this is cute
this is cute i don't know what you're
talking about
what else can we do a little face
oh wait oh my god
oh wait she has freckles now that skin
tone came with freckles
i don't know look that's look that looks
like i don't know
should we use that or should we just use
my father i'm pala what can i do about
being i mean that looks okay
let's go with that vampire
you look like a neat that hair screams
just got out of bed
what my hair always looks like that
all right all right all right all right
all right uh i think we did that we
don't need a
i mean wait actually we need a hat but
i think the hat uh automatically gets
rid of my hairstyle
right and they don't have the perfect
hat i need i need to commission someone
for a hat
i think it yeah kills my hairstyles and
i'm not even going to do that i don't
want to look it up again
accessories doesn't have my feather
earrings what do you say yes
yeah look
wow i mean it's covered up by by the
hairstyle but
she had a 3d model debut i got them
earrings yum but by the way for
the record my feathers are no earrings
no no no no
no no they grow out of my
out of my skull but okay we got that
that's pretty accurate now
don't you think
stop looking like that your expressions
are weird
okay makeup no where do you have mac
makeup how fancy
ooh ooh
i mean i i like to wear makeup
i like that black makeup
now what are you trying to tell me
kiara mac makeup
wow no no no no
i want eyeliner now you
that looks cute
stop stop making those faces
and then i need some blush
what's a good blush and they have mac
blush
my blush is kinda like that baby
how cute hey look it covers on there
[Music]
stop it i look beautiful
what why did we huh that closes
i don't i have a i have a choker do you
guys have a choker
i mean clothing-wise we probably cannot
recreate myself much
oh so i see no choker what the hell why
is there no choker
what ridiculous i need to get some more
cc
well here we were here yeah uh lips
i don't wear anything on my lips my lips
are beautiful the way they are
face paint no thank you
no no no okay i think we can that looks
like me
i think that looks like me monitoring
you guys are too strict so now let's get
into clubs
um what would kiara
wear casually
[Music]
good question i mean that seems pretty
accurate
not
but no i think i would wear something
more um
that's cute hey come on
that's cute i mean it's kind of
winter outside now but we can set
something for cold weather and for hot
weather
your arms are crazy long that's true my
arms are so long make them smaller what
the hell
how do i
wait how did i
can i can i change that
can i do that now that you say it also
can i make myself like taller
oh yeah oh got that booty
i want to make myself taller well then
i have some hipster
[Laughter]
[Music]
is there was there no way someone
someone who knows some stuff style looks
body body
what it no it does not it bodies oh
is that like do you have to choose from
these
no height or arm sliders what
they definitely had height before
in sims 2 or sims 3. what you tell me i
have to live with those arms
what i won't figure
you can do that
[Music]
booty booty dumb yes
yes okay maybe not that much
that's okay
much maybe not maximum cali has maximum
loops i have almost maximum boobs
i think i can do something with the
shoulders as well
yeah yeah yeah
the [\h__\h] are those hands though
but maybe we'll find something better
let's keep on checking
[Music]
what could we go for nanyukio
there's so many clothes even without
custom content
[Music]
no nothing speaks to me as much as that
sweater
oh yeah there's also different varieties
of each clothing let's see what this one
oh orange okay
now we're talking
yeah let's go with orange or or that one
i like that one should we go full orange
or should we go
with the stripy one
of course we show my belly of course we
do
full orange stripey stripe stripe stripe
stripy oh i think people want the
strappy one
good choice now let's go for some for a
minute do you have a mini mini extra
mini skirt that's
shorts i need a mini mini mini mini
extra mini skirt that's
awesome i mean close enough but actually
it even has a belt
no orange what do you mean you don't
have orange what
those are cute though
no not short enough
oh i need extra extra shorts oh
those are cute but they don't really fit
the top
oh that's also not a not a skirt but
almost
you have it in orange that's not orange
oh i'm trying to not spend
two hours here so
we want a skirt please a skirt
a skirt i need a skirt
oh that's not short enough
that's also not short enough
that is short enough but that's not why
is that in casual
why
okay that's that's it they don't have
like
they don't have skirts of my size for
some reason
of my length okay well let's go with
that maybe
they also have no orange dough
but do we have maybe a dark blue or like
a maybe a white
i have no white
does the other one have a white where's
the other one
and i just saw got it
i love sims 4 music i love sims music in
general
wait where did that go i can't find it
anymore
ah this one i made it black oops okay
let's go with let's go
but that doesn't okay you know what we
don't have to recreate
this completely oh
that's perfect pumpkin
dark oh
i think oh actually the gray one
actually that looks cute
kawaii
that's really cute and it shows my booty
it's the the the right amount of
shortness and it has a belt it has a
belt and the colors of the belt speak to
me
faking the chicken yet yeah yeah you're
right actually but then the calves look
so small
yep that that's actually yeah i made
the ties and the clothes bigger and now
now it looks better
i said the hips what about the hips
though yeah
well not that much
yeah i mean that oh
that body yes
what would i wear to a formal thingy
uh what uh i don't wait
how do you go to like full out here
oh there we go okay we need a a pretty
dress
thank you guys for the super chat thank
you
pretty dress oh that's that's kind of
fancy
[Music]
like for what occasion would that be let
it go
it would be probably for
[Music]
maybe for a whole live second fest
if i was on stage i would be wearing
something like that maybe
nothing here looks like an idol dress to
be honest
nah the real spicy part of
this stream will be when we get into the
game actually
so please bear with me while i'm trying
to that's cute
i'm trying to make myself here
that's cute i like it it's sparkly it's
golden and sparkly
yeah whatever we're just let's just go
with that oh wait shoes
no no you're not wearing those you're
gonna
what the hell are you wearing oh my god
uh wait a second what
what where just tops
yeah uh under here here here okay and
sporty what
what do i work for uh aware for my
workout
please not not so yellow please
hmm
no i don't like the color oh maybe that
color
and then for the bottoms
[Music]
i mean that's all right to me what's
that
that looks cute okay whatever
can i make myself naked i want to be
naked when i sleep
but i don't think we can do that so the
closest thing would be
something like that
um
close enough
to think a little bit of piccolo senpai
every now and then i think i'll
go slippers i usually don't like wearing
slippers but
in this case i i i need to get some
piccolo senpai into my bed
so this is a party outfit you call that
a party outfit
you ew disgusting
let me show you what a party outfit is i
like the party outfits here
they look cool
[Music]
outfit i like i like something like that
like that i like that no
those colors look so bad together
i mean no actually no she has to wear a
dress she looks
weird that that does that does not suit
her
body shape
i like that one that's cute
you guys probably don't understand
but believe me it looks cute and it's
comfortable
it has a bit of a hippie vibe though
i don't want the pattern i want um i
mean this
is cute but nah actually now i don't
like it anymore yeah
now i don't like these outfits anymore
party party party
freddy can i just go naked actually this
one maybe
yeah get cali to see my
my body line my sexy bloody let's just
go with black blackest
black sometimes simple is best but we
need some sexy shoes
oh sexy shoes
by the way guys no one ever told me if
the pgm is fine
is the btm like a good volume
is it okay
i'm good because i'm low ah
okay i i made it a bit louder
so you can enjoy the sims 4 music
to its fullest
these shoes maybe yeah okay i don't want
you guys to judge me
for my choices
what that's all you have for swimsuits
let's go for
a two piece then
[Music]
i need more swimsuits why is there
barely any swimsuits what the hell is
this
where is the fitting uh
bottom and that's it
that's cute and now for hot weather
when uh because it sims for the people
who don't know there's like hot seasons
and the cold seasons
if you have the expansion pack for it
and so your sim
will automatically dress this way if
it's hot outside
oh do we have even even shorter skirts
now no
i feel like my basic outfit was close
enough
actually i want a dress i want a dress a
cute
sundress you have something like that
that's cute sometimes i like to be girly
you know
sometimes i like to dress a little bit
girly actually that's really adorable i
like the orange color
where are those shoes look at those
shoes i will keep them that's totally me
yes i would wear shoes with a cat face
on it yes i would
wait a second she has been taking off
the earrings for every outfit except
this one
how dare you oh god we have to get the
earrings back
uh accessories
uh where were those again
ah probably not not there how do i get
here though
uh oh by the way how let's add her some
some fancy stuff
are they a bit confusing you have to
click the face okay
thank you sims people who understand
sims 4 thank you it's been such a long
time i've been playing this game for
like
a million years but where my earrings
got it am i blind do you see my earrings
they're gone maybe they're only for
casual
ah remove from okay
ah okay now i have to do that for
literally everything
oh my god why why why are you wearing
glasses
what kiana doesn't wear glasses
no no no no and
forev for working out why would you wear
glasses suddenly that's so random
i mean nothing against glasses classes
are cool but
i don't wear glasses
i'm getting the hang out of it guys
so who here has played sims before
glasses are really versatile
have you guys played sims before me me
me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me oh i
see you guys
okay that was the wrong question the
actual question is
who here has not played sims before
everyone raise your hands now
now this is what i want to know me me me
me
what what in what world
were you raised in what that is
unbelievable
[Music]
okay okay so we got that finally we got
that down
now back to winter coffee because we got
that okay okay okay
we do clothing i like stupid christmas
sweaters
i like those
you have different patterns now
but that's not enough choices i need
more stupid christmas sweaters what the
hell
do i have full outfits too that's cozy
but now
that's all you have what oh wait this
one is cute um
okay i don't know why you need it to
take off your patent snare
but i like your spirit i like it
and those those sweaters look cute oh
which color should we go for
i feel like cali would wear that
maybe we should get matching christmas
later so i'll i'll wear i'll wear this
one
um i'll wear the green one and she can
wear the pink one
okay i'll kill you
this is my game i make the decisions
here okay
cold weather you think in cold weather i
would wear
um pants are you kidding me
ridiculous i wear a skirt with tights of
course i do
so give me a skirt any skirt is fine
it can't be a skirt that's a bit longer
that's okay
but i need my tights with that
so for example that but then you can
as far as i know you can put on tights
accessories
yeah leggings yes
yes yes yes yes yes
i mean they should probably be warmer
those are see-through but okay
maybe they don't have black oh let's go
with those
or yes but just just for the purpose of
being sexy
that's where those tights go and then
some proper shoes not those shitty
shoes i like those
[Music]
i like that outfit
my personal taste please don't make fun
of me wait i love those
those are comfy i know there's so many
people who hate those shoes
but i love them they're so comfy
oh people hate them why do so many
people hate these uggs
why eggs are so comfy i'm going with
that i'm going like that
they're so comfy yeah you're not
supposed to wear them outside
lies that is not true
kiara is basic you are basic you are
basically see she's happy
those shoes make her happy uggs are fine
i always bought like a like a cheap
version of it
and then after two months wearing them
they would look disgusting and then i
would throw them away and every year i
would get new ones
anyway i think we're done with kiara no
is there anything
else we have the outfits uh
i think yeah we have all outfits is
there anything else i was able to do
i changed dosing oh walking style
no not snooty
that's that's how maddie and senpai
walks
mommy said if i walk like that
oh yeah that's how cali looks
that's how i walk
oh like that i sometimes i walk like
that
[Laughter]
i want to walk like that okay but cali
sometimes
can walk like that but sometimes kelly
walks like that
so i'll go for i'll go for the bouncy
one
yes okay i think that's it so now we
make
oh what's that add a similar story
should we do another story one let's try
to make one that's like
cali okay these questions are for cali
there is a going away party for for
kiara
what do i do what would you do
what would you do if because i'm
probably gonna have a going away
party i'll probably gonna do that
and invite only kelly she would buy a
gift
i feel like she would also cook for me
if that was a possibility
but yeah i should probably buy me a gift
yeah
oh no why would you make me think of me
going away already but this is not
happening in sims 4. in sims 4 we will
be together forever
and not even death can pardon us because
she is deaf
and i have a funny idea in my head that
we will try out later in the game
acting is a means too
do what do you guys think she would
answer
freaky
[Music]
you sure about that guys
i don't think the next question my
favorite type of people are
oh what do you guys think
good people are interesting i mean dogs
no she's more of a cat person now we
know that
good people or interesting people that's
a stupid question
interesting people okay
it's lights camera what is this question
what kim
what oh what do you say at the end of
the sentence i mean
if anything she would say action that
comedy i mean who says that what
what who says anything but acting
it's my friend's birthday what do i do
for them oh another question that is
like what does she do for me
and when it's my birthday i think she
would take me out uh
on the town and go somewhere with me she
would go on a holiday or vacation or
something with me
what friends i am her friends
i'm more than her friend what friends is
no no no no she has me she has me
she has me now
no no she goes somewhere with me if i
could be remembered for one thing what
would it be oh
all the items but like um i mean her her
songs and all that
it must be this one and i think that's
what she wants to be remembered
with as well
a friend trips and falls in my home
what's my reaction
that's difficult i think she would
ask if they're okay though and like
point and lab what why laugh if it's me
you think she's that mean
[Music]
she doesn't she won't do that she'll
she'll help
i believe in the good side of kelly
what role would i play in a criminal
heist all
okay now this is interesting
i it could be the mastermind the muscle
you mean the person who kills the people
that's true
someone ate the last glass of my pizza
[Music]
okay okay surprise the paparazzi is here
i had the same question what would she
do she would sneak out the back door i
think
i think she wouldn't um i don't think
she would wanna yeah
yeah i think we all agree on that one
the best food is
uh
i think she would say prepared by a chef
though because we like getting some
fancy food together
yo kelly at least you're not male like
me
i ended up being male 1
okie dokie um so
let's start off with oh wait how how do
i
uh wait first of all let's do her
yeah kelly what voice
[\h__\h]
she has a little voice tell
me
[Music]
don't you think
close enough oh she's by the way
creative yeah
good yeah and active
active i mean she's a workaholic but not
active in the way
that they mean active
friend of the world and gregorius
oh well whatever you say whatever you're
saying her arms are also
extremely long also let's get oops
no oh you can do that as well right i
have to make my
yes thank you hips
yes boobs yes
booty yes
but boobs they they have to be yes and
that booty
looks okay in the dress right now but
probably crazy
and in any other any other way okay
so we start with the face
let's get her like one of those basic
faces
and then do that from there uh so
we need they don't
really have like the purple eyes could
be pink eyes so i guess we have like uh
the same eye color let's see if i have a
if i have a fitting hairs oh that can i
do it with the same hair color
no and then this one i guess
oh wait ah
that pink now this pink yeah that's
close enough like
unfortunately i can't get it any better
than that i think
but she kind of needs longer hair i'm
i'm gonna download some
custom content eventually it's a nice
pink doll
not exactly as kelly
oh no the other one was better right
this one is it is it better
one is better right give her another
voice
what that's accurate i think
first one is better okay okay that ain't
pink to me that's
i mean as pink as i mean the other pink
is this one
i don't think we want to give her that
pink it has to be this pink i know it's
kind of purplish but oh well i like the
it has some kind of like holographic
effect if you know like more like a
metallic
effect i like that okay we're about to
hit the one hour mark oh [\h__\h] just take
so
stuff like this takes so long
okay let's see so she wait she looks so
cute already
wait we didn't do her her skin color
wow but that looks good that looks good
with the hair color though
she she is very pale though just like me
[Music]
no i think it looks okay she's paler
she's actually paler than me i'm not as
pale as she is
right okay and then
actually yeah looking cute let's get
those eyebrows
thinner yeah cute she looks so cute
yeah cute very cute
very cute cute
i feel cuter than me
do i still look weird to you guys
stop stop moving stop stop moving stop
stop moving stop moving stop moving
i wish you could tell them to stop oh
there we go
we're finding those that that jaw
i'm scared oh come on
you stretched your face really
i actually haven't have quite the round
face stop stop moving
so wait a second where why
why is she so much cuter than me oh well
let's get started with um why did i do
it i'm not ready i can give her makeup
i forgot the makeup um
okay what kind of makeup
[Music]
something decent that's too
not standing out too much
[Music]
i feel like she would look sexy with a
lipstick
oh that looks good
oh
cute wait can i give that to myself as
well
i don't like my lips why not
lipstick too after a while
i want that too i want the same one
she's so cute
she looks like what bdsm
what do you have to do for every outfit
i think
possibly which we want that we don't
need them they're mostly in their casual
outfit anyway
um cheeks
what that's a bit high up what the hell
this one
cute okay let's go with that
yep okay clothing wow those
wait that was waist is a waist looks a
bit crazy
okay so what would callie wear
in casual to be honest
i what do you guys think she would wear
would she wear something sexy
or something like just
like something like that
what do you guys think actually
i think she would wear that
think she would
[Music]
emo clothes oh should we make her like
super edgy
[Music]
adidas jacket sweatpants actually
she needs some sweatpants
ah
um why do we have better sweatpants than
those
no i want to make a sexy cali i want to
make a hot
sexy cali um
give me a sexy cali come on
i mean that's pretty edgy oh god those
boobs
oh my god
kelly that's not natural oh oh this you
can change
that too yes they gotta be a bit droopy
a bit droopy you know that's much better
[Music]
i think she would actually do that but
wait why do i she has
she needs thicker ties cha top pies just
like me
not ties oh yeah oh yeah oh wait
actually
actually i like this kelly i like it
she's like on one side she's sexy and on
one side she's wearing like
rough rough clothes like she doesn't
give a [\h__\h]
i like this combination
[Music]
shoes shoes shoes shoes
cowboy boots
uh she would probably not wear high
heels in this outfit at least so
[Music]
actually that seems accurate
i love making cali in this game this is
fun
thomas j okay so next is formal
formal can be
nothing too crazy for kelly although i
would love to see kelly in a dress like
that hmm
[Music]
nah callie would never wear that
wedding dress
do you have that in black me too
what the hell are those
no no no
to watch it
[Laughter]
okay actually like that what the [\h__\h] is
that necklace actually wait a second
that necklace might
might suit her how do i change the
necklace
i i wait is the necklace part of the
dress
is it where is the dress again
no it's not part of the dress how do i
change it again
was it here oh yeah
yeah we don't want it oh let's give me
some pretty earrings you cannot see them
but
yeah you can literally not see them does
cali have earrings
wait we need skulls are there skulls no
i need skull earrings
oh man close enough
oh wait what do we do with the shoes oh
shoes shoes shoes
i guess she would force herself in some
into some nice stilettos or something
like that um
oh yes this is this is where the sexy
cali is coming out
no sporty where are the adidas pants
where are the nike pens
[Music]
yes yes the top though
now that must say something like uh
my chemical romance just imagine it
saying here my chemical romance
or is there anything with a skull though
is there nothing with a skull
no that just says my chemical romance
yes that is kelly
and now for sleeping i want i want her
also to be as naked as possible
so we'll just go partner next time let's
go black with her oh yes
oh yes black yes
yes italian black laundry oh
yes
okay party party
party bunny bunny let's see what
what is she gonna wear for a party
[Music]
do you guys think she would wear a dress
or
not actually that looks
[Music]
oh those
those leggings
i mean i can't see her wearing those
i can't see it
because they kind of look stupid or like
that
yeah wait a second yes yes
hipster cali yes
nope ain't hair eh
i like this hipster cali on those
glasses
no let's get rid of those glasses i
don't want them
oh my god no i don't want those
no you
sunglasses i guess so we can give her
some sunglasses
do you think she would wear sunglasses
like that
or oh yes oh yes
i think that's more hair type of
sunglasses now
yes yes other than that we don't have
um that much choice
definitely okay look at her
now i i feel like cali can wear
so many different kinds of clothes
shoes should we make them oh my god
no no come on
again
what are those you
i i kind of i kind of liked the pink
shoes that we had before i kind of liked
those
because they kind of stood out a little
bit like these
i i kind of like those like half boots
what do you think
tim's what are tim's again what are
what is that do you mean timberlakes
what is that
i like them okay okay now swimming
wait i i did go swimming with her
already so i know what she would wear
but we don't really have that here
so we have like a bright pink
but then we would be matching oh
that's oh my god wait
your body scares me a little bit
yeah yeah
and do you have the right color
oh yeah that's uh that's about the same
color as she was wearing when i went
swimming with her
her legs are so thin
[Music]
really it's already maximum
it's already maximum there it can give
her even
thicker thighs though okay
so for the hot weather let's see we're
almost done guys we're almost done
um hot weather huh
i think she would also wear some hot
pants though
like dolls
[Music]
oh what are you guys just a hoodie in
hot weather
what oh she will die
try to fix her arms what what why i
can't make them shorter unfortunately
jeans
oh maybe yeah maybe a long
skinny jeans something like that
all right but this is oh it doesn't give
me the option
because i'm here to protect her pale
skin
no no no no yeah yeah
maybe
or shiny pants would you wear shiny
pants
i don't think so
oh i think we can go with some ripped
jeans
you think the arms are so skinny i made
them a big bit thicker there you go
and then for the top
[Music]
it's it's hot outside though guys
consider that what would she wear
as a top um kelly kelly kelly
kelly kelly
that's cute
i tanked up a hoodie tanked up yeah i
think
[Music]
yeah actually yeah she would go
ah there we go there we have the skull
that looks so lame though that looks so
lame
[Applause]
[Music]
keep it okay it's stuck yeah kelly is
often very dorky too yeah
kelly's such a such a
like not complicated but she has so many
sides to her personality
and i thought we will get wait what were
those shoes oh
you you oh my god no no
oh wait that outfit looks horrible but
she will only wear it
in in very hot summer it looks horrible
though
oh my god
[Music]
oh yeah this is cool with that
okay so matching sweaters i thought she
would wear that that's cute
sweetheart in the pants
i gave myself a skirt with some leggings
what about cali oh my god
would she also wear a skirt or do you
think she would wear pants
keep it bottomless
pants okay
don't you have like sexier sexier pants
than that
i don't like the pants in this game
um
[Music]
look at those stud belts study study
studded belts but we can't see them
because she's wearing the sweater
i don't like the pants
[Music]
give her leggings leggings
thank you for the recipe merry christmas
to you too
thank you thank you pinkerton
[Music]
leggings
wait it's cold outside right
um i personally
um have to say one of my pet peeves
is seeing girls outside
in almost or a little bit
see-through leggings where i can see the
line of what they're wearing
and all that and like i can let you see
every detail
that is i don't like that i know you
guys like that but i
don't like that
and where i'm from so many girls wear
those leggings where you like literally
see everything
it disturbs me
i don't like it you guys think i would
like it i don't
but i don't know for kelly i don't know
actually i mean i see the line of a
panties there
but that actually looks okay
[Music]
what do you guys think she needs some
boots though
oh yeah what are those
oh hell no oh but that's that's cute
her feet are so tiny though
what do you think about dolls is that a
weird combination i i guess she maybe
needs pants after all
or she would wear them on top i don't
want her to wear them
[Music]
oh yes yes yes now this is something
somewhat accurate
now she looks like kind of like too
thick
perfect perfect this is good okay
we're finally done we're finally done
guys
okay okay um one more thing maybe
should we get ourselves a cat or should
we adopt
let's adopt the cat later let's not make
one let's adopt adopt not shopping
what's her name
i think we're done i think we're done
but did i do
what did i do is something wrong
oh maybe
[Music]
okay now i think we're done
can you check over it
not still wrong
god damn it
hmm
now this has to be right come on i used
all my brain cells
did i get it right now is it not
california maury no
what oh it must be
kelly okay
now let's start because this already
took like how much one one and a half
hours
california
enough we i'm not ready oh my god i'm
not ready to start our life together yet
oh my god i look inside
this is a bad photo oh hey our household
name would be takana
now it would be takamo
mori
[Laughter]
oh i mean it looks cute don't you think
randomized for it's red oh
oh my god it's so crazy
oh god
[Music]
okay sure let's get started oh
yeah where should we live i have a few
expansion backs so
we have a i think we would probably
first in the beginning
i mean we would probably live like in in
the
in like a you know
a city city type of uh place
and then we can get an apartment yeah
but we need
now the question is should we like
treat us a little bit of money and you
know
get the place like nice
like decent or should we
like not cheat at all but then we have
slow progress
yes yes yes yes of course i love how for
sims
people don't care about cheating because
sims just comes with cheating
but i i don't remember how you would
cheat before moving in somewhere so i
think we have to move in somewhere first
into a cheap
place uh can we afford that
oh yeah we can i left you before in
another sims gameplay
that looks like we can't and there's
even two
live uh two sleeping rooms
[Music]
eventually we want to get to the
penthouse yes but we have oh
wait can i already give us money now
what was it again model load
uh cutting those are old ones i think
what is the new one
[Music]
i think we have to move in first thank
you for the red super chat
thank you so much
i can't do anything
i think we have to enable
do i have to capstock
oh free free real estate on
now this works as well
let's go straight to the penthouse
where's the pandas i'll do apartments oh
that's so big though
oh that that's the penthouse okay i
guess we're moving into the penthouse
only the best for takamori
[Music]
for uh i think we'll start furnished and
then we can like
change things up a little bit
let's go oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah
my life love cali is starting
welcome to taco bonnie
and sims 4. hello
so how's your day going kelly where it
look so cute together
oh they they have to move to have a
conversation
i got the voice that's nico's karen
chill brought some bombs
[Laughter]
of course i acquired a charisma skill of
course i do
um by the way
[Music]
we need to afford this plan okay we
can't afford being kicked out
wait wait
[Music]
uh come on cannon don't watch tv what
the hell
you gotta flirt with gally we don't have
time to lose
[Music]
oh wait i wanted to get out of the bad
one
okay wait a second so how does our
apartment look anyway
what we have a basketball court
what what on earth
we have a basketball we're not gonna use
that we are not gonna use that even
and we have a is that a she shower
i think it's a shisha interesting
interesting we have a little a tiny
balcony
interesting
one bad room of course with a computer
because we all stream from our bedroom
oh interesting whose room could that be
could that be my
we have to change the oh that looks more
like
yeah yeah i think we have a big
difference in that that's kiara room
and that's kelly room oh yes yes but
we'll change it up
also cali has like a huge tv now so we
need a huge tv as well
and then we go uh how do you go upstairs
again
uh wait a second i haven't played this
game such a long time
i'm confused
upright ah thank you
and wow wow oh yes that's uh
kelly's favorite place in the apartment
i think
a piano no one plays the piano but sure
el or does cat cali doesn't play the
piano does it does she
oh a nice area where we can eat
the bathroom looks okay oh yes this is
about the size
that's pretty accurate yeah kelly's tv
is pretty much that size i'm not even
kidding
i am not even kidding it's pretty much
that size
i am not kidding
[Laughter]
i i was like what oh we have another
bad room but okay so first we maybe we
use the bathroom at
the bathrooms downstairs and then we
work ourselves our way up to this room
together tv is looking good
but i would personally probably
move that a bit to the back um
should we add some things now or should
we just get our relationship going
where's the kitchen by the way
did i miss the kitchen is that the
kitchen
oh we have some fruits we're being
healthy
the kitchen looks nice though
does does ever does she also have a pc
in her room
yes she does but that's a hope hopefully
that's the strongest pc that there is
but that's not a game of girl chad do we
have a gamer girl chair
we need gamer girl chairs how do we get
a oh my god this is uh
wait a second we go we go
maybe here yeah
where's the gamer girl oh the queen's
dining chair
oh yeah
i want that one
but it's i have to unlock i know there's
a cheat for for unlocking it
how do we unlock it is someone does
someone know the cheats
[Laughter]
come on
come on like
unlock all objects
it's not i mean i see this one it looks
well
oh oh or that one oh well okay
i'm okay rid of that one because that's
a shitty chair we need a good chair
we're working on our pcs
it's our job so
oh my god i can't work with that chair
what the hell
um but maybe i want the white one yeah
okay one day i'll get that what do i
have to do
unlock by reaching level four of the
esports career
we can do that what job should we get in
this game
too well let's go back to living mode
hey y'all how's it going you two
are you guys hitting it off let's share
some brilliant ideas
esports it seems it seems close enough
because then basically
they're making money for gaming it seems
close enough
but cali could i think i want kelly to
be a musician
i could also be a musician oh
just in a brunch
merch are you single kelly
the important questions have to be asked
here
are you single cali
full blade kelly's place
where you go did you tell me she's
single
kelly kelly stop okay okay this is
this is where this is where it starts
they always wanna
they always wanna you know watch tv for
god's sake
new beam hold
both watch tv oh what is she doing
play a party frenzy what what is that
what's party frenzy oh you're gonna oh
she's going straight into gaming
oh i think you should join in
how do you join
oh yeah this is how you bond gotta play
some games together
and i mean we're we are probably wait
what what are you doing
why did why did you not you're too late
it's over now oh you're going to work
kelly is going to work out what
what i may we have a work look at
we can barbecue wow look at that oh my
god that looks amazing
coconut
that's not like you that's not like you
we don't we don't read books here in
this house
that's not that's not what we do we'll
go swimming
yay now swimsuit cupboard
[Music]
that water looking good oh so we're both
doing sports right away now that's
interesting
interesting choice no no i'm not gonna
remove ladder by the way i think in sims
they can go into the pool without a
ladder so i think they can also go out
of the pool without a ladder
as far as i know i think
no we don't talk to any other human
beings
the only human beings that we're gonna
talk to is ourselves
okay so um
we should probably get a job
uh so let's go down can't we
what the f did you guys let yourself in
to my what the actual [\h__\h]
kelly we need you to kill them
what on earth callie those are rude
intruders [\h__\h] off
rude introduction
rude introduction that's totally
something callie would do
if they if they just go into our house
like that
send home sent home bye-bye
why are they becoming friends somehow
leave stop talking
what's chatting oh my god clever
no i told them to leave
panaroo just
your mother is a llama
and your mother is also a llama
where are you going oh my oh my god
did i just go am i just i'm just
chilling at the toilet
okay
no no
go away
you came into my house just like that i
don't like it oh wait a second
what's it here there we go all right
now they're gone i think it's only you
and me
go on only you and me and now look at my
sexy body oh
do you like my sexy wow
discuss fine cuisine as we always do
stop watching
tv stop it
let's talk about cooking oh man i just
thought there was another intruder but
it's just a night
is that one of our sims protecting us
[Music]
callie wants to get to know kiana
says here hungry artist already says so
automatically do i have something
commercial we already have jobs i'm a
commercial
spokesperson it says
and there we go one goes to play skim
scuffle and the other one plays
playstation 4. what the hell
yeah if that seems pretty accurate we'll
just uh
play games seems pretty accurate
and you're playing playstation again no
yeah
that makes sense why are you i went for
a swim
i'm not in my aunties i'm in my swimsuit
hell iop is creative inspiration comes
to
creative sims often but creative
activities are ignored they're emotional
oh
and okay well is that crazy what she's
doing creative now
anyway she's a hungry artist she needs
to reach level four of the painting
skill
but i want her to be a musician
which is why i will buy her a guitar
i think guitar is here or like a
microphone
oh yeah oh yes yes
wait is that a cuddle okay machine
what is that what is that
we have a look at machine so we don't
even need the microphone i guess but oh
well
how do we how do we move that again
we have a karaoke machine oh my god
i love karaoke let's sing let's see what
wait do we have
did i learn more genres later on i
wonder because i want to
see her rap come on kelly
let's see you sing here
level one of singing skill it has begun
[Music]
yep
oh yeah
[Music]
on kel we have to watch that
show what do you think of that kiara
what do you think of kelly she's
laughing
wow good job she says
no one more one more when we can sing i
can sing a duet
country with with me oh
oh yes now this is what i always dreamed
about
[Music]
[Applause]
gonna clip this and upload
[Music]
it's me singing
that was amazing uh-huh
can we sing more than that no it's
always the same song for now
kelly no no no no she wants to cook what
no you have to practice more
come on i'll i'll i'll cook gretchen
[Applause]
this is real life this is real life
wait maybe i should get a career as a
cook instead
there's so many possibilities but look
at that kelly
we have to make this a reality us
getting a penthouse together
and then like grilling on top of our
penthouse
oh my god she did it we have corn yes
with corn yes
oh my god that's oh i'm getting real
hungry now that's literally what i want
to eat right now
are you how is it
what what is it how is it she's uh
callie reach singing level two you know
what i'll be the cook and callie will be
the singer
i have decided that that's oh my god it
looks yummy
just thinking about kelly what are you
going to do
chat with calliope okay
let's go coin
what's she doing what are you doing
you're just standing there you
grab oh i made a hole i made it for a
county as well how
nice of me
you want to grab that food just gonna
grab the food that i
cooked the grilled chicken
yum oh we have so much oh my god this is
paradise
chicken
am i coming down we should have just i
should have just stayed downstairs
oh this is lovely we can sit down and
have a talk
that didn't sound so good from singing
karaoke oh callie it's okay don't worry
about it
why are you embarrassed no
[Music]
kill bubba are you okay this is kind of
awkward
[Laughter]
wait and she's also they're both
embarrassed about singing badly
no don't worry about it
how about how are they doing by the way
they're doing fine
callie needs to go with pete she needs
to go to an idol meeting
are you going to the idol meeting now
yes
the way she walks let's watch her doing
her idol things
what are you thinking about you what
what what what what's going on
what are you do you want to wear some
clothes maybe
uh i guess it's suits he's also buried
what's going on there what
why am i
why are you talking to an angry naked
stools
why is he angry anyway
no no no no no no no now you go back up
to your house and never leave it again
[Music]
how about we where's the tv again
we have a tv here too we have two of
those huge tvs
let's watch a cooking show because i
want to be
the owner of a restaurant oh wait do i
have do i have that expansion pack uh
installed i wonder
actually kelly you know what you're not
gonna play games again
we have to do some progress here you
know how about
you practice singing on this one don't
worry about being bad
we go better you can become better
you're already bad
but you're already good
in in in real life so
don't worry
[Applause]
should i help you it's though a deer
a female deer red a drop of gold
she's giving in her best she's trying
and i'm just
oh my god but a tv like that in the
kitchen up there it's very interesting
design
[Laughter]
oh
is your neck fine that's gonna that
looks like it will hurt after a while
what does kelly want kelly oh you wanna
watch kelly no no no she's embarrassed
right now don't watch her
no need to watch it by the way we should
put the chicken
uh inside into the fridge
uh put away there we go
okay did i just hear is
no i hear birds oh
cute okay guys one more thing by the way
since it's uh
almost christmas
should we keep that basketball court
let's say it's christmas in game as well
so
how about we make like a little
christmas section here
as far as i know i have some something
like installed
that's like christmas related
i wonder
christmas oh i see i have a christmas
tree
a second camera i'll go here
should we have it by the piano so that
uh cali can play the piano and sing for
me
well i play the piano and she sings or i
sing and she plays the piano
wouldn't that be lovely now what else do
i have like a driver
oh where is all the christmas stuff
i can i oh yeah i can filter down by
the right pack oh see i don't have all
of them
but there is a there should be a holiday
thing yeah
well that's it
what is that
i want i want like all
why do i wait what oh
look at that but by the window it makes
absolutely no sense that looks cute
though
karaoke machine is in the way bar is in
the way
uh we can put it here maybe instead of
that
whatever that is and it's a tv stand oh
let's get rid of that window too
and then put that that's so cute oh
it's cute what else do we have
[Music]
oh wait that's so cute kawaii
let's decorate everything
that's cute
put one here as well oh yay
[Music]
yeah getting into the christmas mood
i'm not spacing it out correctly
probably but i don't care
i don't care yay i don't care about that
side
takes too much time and something nice
above that would be
cool though do we have anything oh
what's that oh
how pretty oh
we have some light flip-flops what
that's probably for australia
oh what should we use maybe that one
yeah how pretty
where does that go here
and here
what's that it's a log display
beautiful let's get rid of the other one
oh yeah beautiful
what's that ground what ground
candles oh
four festive candles i like those
candles
let's put them here and let's put them
maybe some in here as well
and some here lovely then we have some
oh we have what what is that what that
looks cute
[Music]
why did we put that
here oh i love decorating for christmas
unfortunately my i'm not decorating
anything at all right now
like in in my actual house because i'm
like i'm just gonna throw it away later
and who am i decorating for except for
my
for myself
cute have you guys do you guys have your
tree up do you guys have a
uh a christmas tree up right now
because i don't i do yes yes yes
yeah oh how nice
no no many of you also don't why do you
not have one
because you guys are not having a big
celebration this year probably
that makes sense
i could ask you the same thing yeah
because i'm just staying at home and
streaming
oh wait there's different ones ah just
that i see
oh and that's cute i'm not saying with
no one
staying at home watching streams that is
a good life choice i must stay
what's that stupid thing
good life choices i appreciate that you
guys are watching my streams and i'm
streaming for you
all day and tomorrow as well so
i i tabbed out goddammit
oops no nobody else is having a nice
christmas together guys wait i don't see
the chat anymore
there it is a very potential christmas
is what i'm looking forward to
[Music]
what else should we do uh do we have
anything else
no chairs what are those holiday wall
speakers
listen to holly music wait is that gonna
play holiday music specifically
[Music]
where do we put it where do we put it
i need the walls up
let's put it everywhere
i hope i don't get copyright striked yay
about generally all music in sims is
like
sims original i think unless it's like
covers
with all right like originally real
songs but then covered by
some uh in simlish
anyway should be fine should be fine
okay let's see if we hear that music
enough decoration
callie keep on practicing keep on
practicing
[Music]
christmas what about what
oops i missed it oh god i have too many
now
it's so christmasy there's christmas
everywhere
you guys speaking of christmas music you
know usually
up until this year like i would you know
work somewhere and uh have to commute to
work and all that
and every time i would do that i would
like around christmas season like one
month before christmas
i would already hear like christmas
music everywhere right they play
christmas music so early everywhere in
shopping malls
on the radio on tv at work
as well but now
i've i've in the last one month i've
been outside maybe two times
so i haven't heard anything like that
i it's so weird so to me it's like i had
no
like holiday christmas feeling
right like i know people get annoyed by
christmas music playing everywhere but
to me that's like the
thing that gets me into the mood and
makes me feel like oh christmas is
coming soon
right and now it's like what it's
already christmas
today is christmas
what i have i have yet to hear
last christmas somewhere and and that
just
that oh my god that's just like
no way it is christmas now
so yeah to me it's like not christmas
until i hear
uh last christmas somewhere but she's
sleeping oh
you're sleeping in the right room how
did you know that this is your room
i didn't even tell her i put a mistletoe
is there a mistletoe
no there's no mistletoe
there is no mistletoe by the way kelly
do you do you need to sleep
oh she she almost has that point let's
get it
and then she can sleep you gotta work
hard she's a workaholic
and now you can go sleep you probably
want to go to sleep by yourself no
no okay she's energized she wants to
stretch
okay you do you kelly if that's what you
want wait
oh that's a good idea kelly i didn't
even think of that oh
oh thank you for the attention for the
super chat thank you
wow that's so cute i wish i had my
house decorated like that oh and she
goes for an energetic pee
[Music]
i think you should sleep now kelly i
think it's time for you to sleep
no no no no no your room is down here
callie
you're
are you trying to sleep in that bed
or did you try to sleep in that one but
the color looks like she's
i already canceled it but
what kelly what for real dolls
anyway let's sleep here let's just sleep
here for now
but how sweet she's she's trying to you
know get close to me
oh cute ah
it's our first night and we're still in
separate beds but that's okay
we gotta take it slow we gotta take it
easy good morning kiara
looking good she's very happy and she's
wearing her pecora slippers
where are you going
warmest oh that's cute that's there's
such an interaction
i should start thinking about further
education no i'm becoming a youtuber
oh burn money oh yeah let's burn that
money
isn't that illegal
[Applause]
oh my god oh
that's so funny well can you do
something with that
snowman no
i'm going for a pee um you guys like
that
this is um of course i don't go
to do such things i don't do this
i go to other meetings
not you should eat something
cook eggs and toast yes oh eggs and
toast i want
i want to cook something too i like how
she's like to cook here
[Music]
so when cali is awake she will have
fresh breakfast
i think she's probably cooking for two
burning our super chat
i'm sorry that wasn't me that was kiana
and sims but this is totally the reality
of course because i wanted to be real oh
my god
oh my god
did you mess it up
it still looks good quality excellent
excellent that was excellent
grill plan what the hell you just cooked
something
you just cooked something but apparently
it was just a serving for was i was
serving for one
yep why does she want to cook something
right away
again excellent
yeah using all those eggs that i have in
in minecraft you know
you gotta do something with those eggs i
have to way too many eggs
so today after kelly finally wakes up
our goal is
to make these two get a little bit
closer you know
we gotta help them with their
relationship a little bit
she's like super focused money to burn
oh anything cares about is simonians
this neighbor deserves a better class of
sim and kiana is going to give it to
them
it's not about the money it's about
sending a message
it makes total sense that
would you like to cook something for
cali though
uh cook
oh can you use breakfast oh yeah mac and
cheese nah
let's make her some scrambled eggs with
bacon
but don't eat it don't eat it okay this
is for cali
what cooking is
she was up all night practicing singing
after all
okay don't eat it don't eat it yes okay
very good so this is for cali let's just
leave it there and she awake soon
almost okay so what do we do
maybe we can
[Music]
maybe we can find a new job finding job
can we become a cook
i mean i'd prefer to have no job but
oh well could be fun
oh should we do that is there a normal
cooking career as well
are you kidding me that exists they have
a hi
i'm here hi i'm there i can become a
fast food employee
can i become the boss of it as well
i can even choose a shift i'm not going
to wake up early hell no
let's get that job it's perfect
yes i probably had yeah commercial
commercial spokesperson
quits her job and goes to become a table
cleaner at kfb
uh yeah it seems seems legit makes sense
[Music]
are you okay with that no we are okay
with that we are proud of this choice
please stand so ever okay
can i still have a wink wake up
goddammit
kelly doesn't sleep so long kelly sleeps
five hours and that's in
wake up oh she's super energized
okay so there's food for you made by
your soon-to-be wife
she's looking for my company
she came into my room to eat it with me
who likes zerf zombas she's
[Music]
destiny deeds have alienated you from
polite
society but we don't care about all that
we value results
you're a criminal at heart i can see
that in you
so i'll extend you on offer what the
hell
we should have picked that up i was busy
reading
that was for callie right were they
offering her a criminal job
no who the [\h__\h] are you tristan i don't
know you
what is she doing oh she's going to warm
herself again okie dokie
so kelly how how are those scrambled
eggs that i cooked for you
the bacon that bacon
[Music]
i'm getting with you i haven't eaten
anything yet
hi you need some hygiene why are the two
showers
why can't we just like shower together
and there's golden towels wow
sizzling bacon
i need to cook more by myself also the
music is annoying me now
[Music]
can we get rid of the music what are you
doing
watch sims of the dead oh yeah that
seems something like that kelly would
watch
however no
kelly
let me propose something to you it might
sound crazy
but you and me is she talking about
fubukki senpai
did you not like the idea share personal
life guys we have to get closer
what does our relationship look like now
you guys don't see it
but we're we're getting there we're
getting there we're like
like almost best friends
i feel like we don't have to become best
friends now in order to
do you know stuff
you look sexy she accepted my
compliment okay here we go
what about a pickup line guys tell me a
good pickup line
tell me a good pickup line tell me your
best pickup line guys
go
tell me i don't have any
are you an angel because yes your eyes
are like the universe oh and that's
something i want to hear
are you kiana because you're dead
oh that's cute
you are my reaper because you take my
breath away cute
are you the grim reaper because you are
dropped that gorgeous
oh them clothes would look better on my
floor
if i could rearrange the alphabet i
would put you and i together oh that's
so
cute
ah another one wrote the same thing
don't copy each other be original guys
what did it hurt when you fell from the
vending machine because you are a snack
i thought you were going for for the
typical one did it hurt when you fell
from the heaven or blah blah
are you a torch because you light up my
world oh
it's cute lloyd those are some good ones
but i want to ask her i'm already doing
it right okay
are you kiara because you are 10 out of
10 girls
oh yes i am oh
kelly don't leave the room no don't
leave the room
free but nia floof
purple turret bernard
[Music]
oh
numbers
she wants to do it see wait i don't even
i don't even have that option do i no i
do
but i want it to come from her and i'm
only inspired she
is flirty how do i take screenshots and
how do i take screenshots and sims this
is the moment guys
how do i take screenshots what was it
f12 i know that doesn't do anything
doesn't it normally do like a uh
no no that you can take screenshots in
the game though
let me google screenshots in
sims 4.
how to how to
c it's c guys it's c for camera
who would have thought of that huh you
guys didn't think of that
yes yeah
alrighty we are ready to take some hot
screenshots
but wait can i change the can i get rid
of them
oh well never mind let's just do it i'm
ready i'm ready
although i kind of want to go to
something where it's
pretty oh that's got it let's go to the
tree or here he's also pretty
go here and go here
okay we have arrived guys we have
arrived
[Music]
let's start with his hands slowly slowly
it's a steamy exchange
bye
i want to cherish every moment now
can i get oh my can i get rid of the
layout one second
google how do i get how they
uh is it free camera remote tab key
got it
there we go okay i'm so nervous guys
i'm so nervous
i forgot how to ah wait a second
oh it's okay oh my gosh guys i'm so
nervous i'm so nervous um
i need to get a better angle
[Applause]
how do i
okay slowly slowly slowly guys
[Music]
oh
i think i got a good screenshot and i
can't move properly anymore
wait a second ah i messed up the
controls
we did the kiss though guys we did it
i can't move with a wasd anymore what
did i do
we kissed but i couldn't cherish it i
was too focused on taking a good photo
and now she just wants to watch tv
no no no no kiss more
this is too quick this is too quick just
uh
let's just kiss normally again okay
i feel like just you know
wait a second like my controls are not
working properly anymore
one second uh
how did i mess up all my
controls
close your cup zoom
saves your camera position because
you're saved
anyone know how to
press e again i didn't no it doesn't
work anymore i can't use uh
wasd and i didn't i can only
god damn it this kind of sucks now
maybe it's capsule oh
oh wait i know i think i know why
um i don't know no i know that okay it
works again i know why
it's because of the stupid japanese
keyboard setting
yes yes yes yes
all right okay
let's get it let's get a good one
what is that express
oh what is that
is
i can't even get a crude screenshot
because your kissing looks ridiculous
oh my god but okay i'll go with it oh
um
[Music]
oh yeah taking those screenshots
um
let's give myself a rose from kelly
i like flowers
what is what is keanu doing with me
thank you yeah let's pose for her sexily
hey oh wait that's so cute
it gets this cute though
that's adorable i'm doing my my verb
mating calls right now that's so cute
oh wow you got them poses wait kelly
wait we're not over yet
so she's just let's keep on going
embrace yeah let's just let's just
softly embrace her
in front of the christmas tree oh it's
cute
oh that's cute though yes
i'm getting the screenshot material for
next time
oh it's so cute
okay
oh she's happy her face looks a bit
weird though
and we love each other see this is real
you guys
why would you think that takamori is not
real it's so real
oh
oh yes let me whisper something sweet
into your ears
what should i what should i whisper into
your ears guys seductively
what should i say guys
i know something
oh my god cute
who's michelle who is michelle stop
talking about michelle
she wants to watch you kiss me she wants
to kiss me
she's kissing me
oh
i am very happy i feel fulfilled
now let's ask i think i i i will ask the
question
caress cheek i i think she would like
being caressed on her cheek
[Music]
oh cute her eyes look weird
oh
dads
i am so i need to um hydrate myself a
little bit let's drink something
[Laughter]
i'm glad that we are all enjoying this
together and shipping this
cap no no no
so so now i wanted to actually i wanted
to ask you a question
don't
[Applause]
[Music]
is officially a thing now
yay
[Music]
we have done it success full success
amazing
congratulations thank you and we made it
before christmas ends christmas
[Music]
i got a girlfriend before christmas
because christmas in japan is horrible
if you don't have a girlfriend or a
boyfriend it's horrible
it's just horrible no i did it before
christmas like on christmas
that's even better that's like just so
wholesome
well
[Music]
undying love is kind of ironic and very
fitting
[Laughter]
[Music]
the time cannot stop us because we are
both timeless why are you walking away
what's up what are you going tally is
very confident where's kelly going kelly
has to pee
use and what what
[Music]
yeah yeah there's a concert in the
toilet
[Laughter]
what on earth is going on
anyway how about we make a nice
christmas
dinner by the way i'm i'm kind of like
i'm not sure what
where to end this today because i do
have a stream coming up where i want to
read marshmallows but
who the [\h__\h] are you uh but
i still have to like uh open my my
marshmallow and then and then go through
the questions and all that
so i'm not sure where to end this i need
some time to prepare the japanese only
stream tonight
which is in in three and a half hours
oh my god what do i do anyway
that's coca let's cook a nice christmas
dinner
actually winter cake cookies
what i need to cook it let's make a cake
yeah a christmas cake
end with a proposal don't you think
that's if it's too quick
i don't know
okay i will make a nice cake for callie
and then and then maybe
maybe we can do it
i hope i don't mess up the cake
[Music]
you're baking a cake you're not you're
not supposed to play basketball right
now
you're baking a cake stay focused
stupid i have to cook the cake you bake
the cake
callie's in her room very good
no no no no no oh there we go
oh there's a some green stuff on that
cake which i'm not sure
callie's already coming cali has callie
has seen
where the cake
a second is a screenshot oops
with kelly kelly in the background
there's some random dude in the
background i don't know what he's doing
there
cake it's cake time take a piece
sorry about counting no no no no working
out you gotta take a piece too
let's eat that together
oh how nice they chose the same spots to
eat together again
are you thinking about herself
yeah and never screenshot from that side
[Music]
merry christmas kelly merry christmas
oh merry christmas to you too kiara
thank you for the cake it's tasting
lovely
kelly kelly i actually have a present
for you
if you're ready
i have i have a present
stop watching those please stop it just
go there
do we have something to play some music
just got those christmas speakers in
here
turn on
[Music]
romance oh yeah
it's kind of different that's not what i
was thinking about but okay
no no no no no no no no no no no
uh close enough so how about how do we
do this
i guess we just um
bring her over here
why are you leaving the roof are you
gonna offer it to her face
just gonna talk with her about it first
do you wanna do you wanna go upstairs
kelly
yes yes always she's feeling
she needs to pee but that's okay oh
we're already inside each other
well kelly is faster than me kelly's uh
ready to go
romance some memories too oh
oh me not jumping
to the cupboard
[Music]
it's just a game
i'm very much winning yes
oh wait can we like the the plum bob is
con actually the orange is fitting but
i want it to be more positive
let's go
oh yeah oh what what
well that's all we got to see guys
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Laughter]
oh i think i need to sleep oh my god
how was it kelly
was good oh i see i see kelly
peak content i have to say
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah that was um
that was that um
and
[Laughter]
thank you for the super chats thank you
thank you
and i will um have to eat something and
prepare my next stream which will be in
japanese only in two and a half hours
so i'll probably move my japanese only
stream to one hour later i need a little
bit more time to prepare it
um yago is crying right now why won't he
be crying
i think yago also ships takamori
he also appreciates the takamoni yes yes
yes yes
so i hope everyone enjoyed this i want
to play this again soon maybe in january
um but
this will not be a weekly series as i
said before
but um we want to get a cat and we want
to make uh
children obviously
[Music]
right now but thank you very much i'll
see you in the next stream
and tomorrow i have an unarchived
christmas karaoke where i prepared
many songs and i prepared a stage for
you so i would be very happy if you
would comment on archived so you better
come
check out the schedule thank you guys
thank you thank you
thank you for coming today we'll do it
again soon
[Music]
see you soon and in german we say auf
wiedersehen thank you for the pinky
thank you thank you thank you i love you
guys
what a good stream
[Music]
you