[Music]
thank you for
accepting the collaboration invite even
though i've only been in here in in
the whole life for one day thank you
very much oh my pleasure i i
i'm excited to stream with the the
newest member of hallelujahn
thank you bye i respect you so much
it's such a pleasure it's such an honor
to play with you today
so uh oh my god wait what
andrew oh my god wait my stream is down
for a second
oh okay i was like what what
youtube is kind of like uh youtube is um
bullying me recently i think youtube is
uh
youtube needs a vacation and they're
starting to uh
get a little tired but oh wait no
is it started now wait a second
today yeah i think now and now it should
be yuck
wait am i am i on guys am i on
it
sorry sorry you know youtube is bullying
me i'm here now i'm here now
there she is the lady of the hour
absolutely not my fault
once again for my viewers i would like
to say gooda senpai thank you
for um except accepting my invite to
collab with you
even though the one month collab band is
not left to the end
and once again it is my absolute
pleasure to play with you chiara
yeah yes yes i'm yokoha you miss
uh it made my heart it made my heart go
flutter flutter and i felt
very rosy right in my cheeks and my face
i'm not i'm not used to it yet but i i
i think i'll be used to it soon maybe oh
okay we'll see how long i can put that
act out though
all right so today we're playing mario
kart
yeah which we are both totally
professionals at right
oh yes prepare to be obliterated
i still i don't really know what that
word means but you you do use it a lot
don't you
yes obliterated it's like uh the tnt
in minecraft when you set it up
when you set it up when you when you
make tnt go boom it's going to
obliterate
the stone around it destroy it
yeah yeah okay
so by the way we're playing um on both
we're streaming on both channels so you
can see both
views and we are doing you guys the
absolute
favor and honor of being able to play
with us
no nintendo switch boys and girls
uh wait let me copy that and post the
code in the chat once i
join myself so that we uh have space and
they don't join before us
are you ready to hide the code i am
ready to hide the code shall i begin
yes let's join okay
hold on hold on i have joined
uh no no no no no yeah
wait oh god i wonder if my people are
wait wait i wasn't able to join
hey what why are you in are you in no
i'm still putting the code in i'm slow
okay okay good good good good
wait if you you were already in my room
though it should be in your list of
previously visited uh tournaments though
oh god there's someone in there that
looks exactly like me i don't know why
okay wait i'm here all right i will join
join yes yes um
yeah you probably should join quickly
because people know the code from
previous tournaments
i
oh
[Laughter]
oh my god it says
guys wait for me wait for me
it hopefully hopefully doesn't stop
the time i first saw you in the game
you look ridiculously adorable
okay we're starting right away i want to
go for sunshine airport
do you know which one is me there's like
three freakiest looking like me do you
know which one it
is uh yes it's the one right next to me
no it's the one with the purple eyes
[Music]
yes of course i'm from australia by the
way totally ignore it i mean that's a
that's the flag of australia don't mind
it that's the flag of australia
yeah i didn't know australia flag looked
like that
educate yourself i guess i guess i need
to go back to class
yeah let's go get up
[Applause]
[Music]
um i'll probably be cursing a lot i'm
sorry
that's fine i'm sure
[Music]
own us anyway we should work together
oh once i win this one
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
we played we played one game before this
and
uh pulled out the japanese that you
learned from me what did you say goodbye
[Music]
small
we're pretty much on the same level
we don't seem to have much of a much of
a space between us
or we're always almost always around the
same
spot
[Music]
can't you like jump off the the things
you can like
dump up the clip like when you when you
like do a
jump you can uh oh
see i don't know how to do that let's
use to shape the lead controller
well if you have that if you have what's
it called again
now what's this fancy thing
that was close though that was really
close wait where are you
oh pretty close pretty close
[Laughter]
nice one nice first match
oh apparently when you go off the jump
you press one of the r
buttons and it makes you do a trick and
you get a speed boost you get a little
oh by the way guys so that would give
more people a chance to join
please leave the room after one match
thank you
thank you new people can come in thank
you
also fake kiana you also have to leave
thank you bye-bye
my mom oh nice everyone follows the
rules that's what i like to see
oh a new one came in hello friends
which one would you like to do next i
think people are gonna
they're probably gonna vote against us
but you're gonna go for random oh what's
the code should i put
oh yeah i put it as a pinned comment oh
okay
i i i have not done that i am sorry guys
oh there we go there we go oh i think
we're already full anyway
okay i'm gonna go for a workout
nice neck hold on hold on i'm posting
i'm posting it
eat your rumble i'm ready
i love how you look at the what's it
called amiibo
amiibo a meme amiibo a me a me i think
it's just a me
you look like you look like
doesn't it look just like me it's a
spitting image
looks exactly like me even the body size
is perfect
i just pulled the slider all the way
down
[Laughter]
gotta be realistic right so people will
recognize you
i mean of course
hey watch it link
where are you put on i am i went down
i'm down
by the bottom oh hello
oh hi is that you understand
[Music]
i don't know how to drive okay that's
good me too
neighbor in my car nor in real life
oh yeah i'm playing for the obs screen i
don't even know which
uh which what is my placement
i'm also playing oh no i'm playing
julian
i must be number one i must be number
one it makes totally sense because
people are in front of me that means i'm
so fast
that i'm catching up on the people that
are last oh
that was me oh maybe i am
not i'm not actually down
she was uh better than me but you're
gonna you're like pretty much
the same as me you're calling me bad no
we're both fantastic
i gotta start my dominance
[Music]
look at my butt look
[Applause]
oh
are you kidding me
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh well guys it's i'll leave it up to
your imagination what what placement i
have
always look this guy with a big crown
look at this nice one nice one
next group please who wants to challenge
these
professional mario kart drivers who
wants to go in who will
be humiliated
[Music]
thank you
what was that you showed me before we
started this street
the turkey sound yeah i thought
i'm practicing it but um
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait you're doing like is it in here is
it in your throat when you do that
yeah i'm not sure what i'm doing can you
do a turkey sound
a turkey where i'm from sounds like ah
that's way so cute
[Music]
sounds more like
[Laughter]
oh
what was the suffering where is
suffering turkey
do you remember anything besides the
second
that i taught you a new room oh my
goodness i'll fix it in a second
hi you remember any other japanese that
i taught him
let's see
ah kitty
[Music]
but it's okay i i didn't expect you
hold on i'm concentrating i'm getting
sweaty
hmm no not in that way
wait what
[Music]
[Applause]
no
[Music]
wait did you send someone to me and did
nothing hit me though ah dang it yeah i
sent her a
clap okay i'm gonna wait
in front of me and then i'll shoot that
on her
no don't do that i don't know
careful
[Music]
the combat okay one second let me fix my
image
let me get back to buddha's room once
again
okay let me find kawada
no i gotta cheese
oh is it pronounced gouda in english
yeah it's spelled g-o-u-d-a
oh yeah
that sounds that sounds even more like
you in english than gouda cheese yeah
exactly
[Laughter]
okay new people come in and challenge us
yes
turkey sound completely messed up my
froze
i'm sorry
oh it's okay i like trying new bird
sounds and
i learn a lot of things about myself
when i do that
ah a journey in self-exploration through
birds yes
yes like a cuckoo cuckoo bird
oh that's cute what the hell thank you
i'll add that to my
real pop wait
[Music]
hey don't quote me on that guys rep
repeat
[Music]
oh
soon tm hold on i'm getting tricked
shrek i'm getting ripped i meant to say
shark and rape
what's going on are you like behind
are you 12 right now yes
nice
you know how you can see a glass is half
empty and the glass is helpful
now if you see it as half full then
you're number one right now
technically that means i'm about to
laugh everybody so you better stay in
the front end
[Music]
right now you're far away from me
hi oh no actually oh never mind
[Music]
i love it
oh that was
[Music]
oh
yep
oh man hey i got the crown though
why do i have the crown you'll have the
crowd
because you did better wait no actually
why
is that what's up
i'm back with the shark
because it reminds me of the gamecube
times oh
i chose the i don't know what i chose i
just closed my eyes
you chose the difficult looking one
oh there's one one person that looks
like you but it could also be a piccolo
fake
that looks like is it the tall person
yes
would you say that looks like you um um
are you you aren't like when you're
wearing the crown i can't see your
pictures but that is you right yeah i
have the crown oh
okay
her fans are like really strong though
[Music]
they were representing the glass empire
after all
[Music]
what is the road i chose i gotta do i i
gotta do good in this one
so full i'm so slow right now
i need something
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh i like how this mario this tanooki
mario yells
oh god i'm just using them the catfeet
which could because she's
cute i like my wife
actually surprised she's alive but i
eliminated her previously
layla i was like yeah i might have uh
eliminated mario's whole family in my
super mario sunshine stream
yeah but they like to respawn so it's
all good it's all good
it'll be okay i'm sure
do you see how far away that uh fan is
from all of us
please don't let me please
a mustache
who dares who dares to touch a phoenix
i do be ghosting no no no no
where are you going
[Music]
you're second i'm dead i'm gonna lose it
ridiculous
where are ya'll
ah i had it all i had it all in that
moment and then i lost everything
but i love how we're on the same level
that makes it feel very
comfortable for me it's more of a
challenge that way
yeah more chances for us to see each
other in the race
and we can improve together of course
that's what i called it thanks guys
thanks guys good good round of applause
[Music]
well obviously because we are the best
in here
obviously we are the queens what is that
alien
over there oh my god it's kinda cute
i like it i like how really creative
some people can get with the me
creations
it's really impressive i think
i'm very nice of yogurt
did you play the newest animal crossing
i did i have about
uh just under 200 hours i think
what yeah is that a lot but i played it
a little bit in the beginning
like maybe for a month but i quit um
already
yeah i did too uh
i'll get oh to animal crossing you know
is also playing it i think
she played it one set on stream i think
um
i mean yeah i'm done
[Music]
[\h__\h]
that's a fake australian flag look at my
black that's an australian flag
it's australia minus the l
now there's a little bit more than minus
the elf
us australia
you're close enough close enough but i
don't feel smelly right now
hey i'm from australia mate hey
good night mike i thought i could block
that dude
come on
you have a shrimp challenging you go
i must win can you can you beat him
for her assad
must be uncertain maybe
you're saying that like a like a
politician dominance
might be assertive under those
circumstances
may they beat me in this match
failure is not an option
where are you by the way i haven't seen
you for a while
bye bye bye bye
[Applause]
[Music]
i was too focused on finding you
okay
mommy i'm just chilling on the beach
oh isn't it nice i missed it i want to
chill on the beach
yeah right yeah come on good night you
tell me
yes what the hell what is this timing
oh come on what would be a nice
oh beach destination
ah somewhere with really soft sand
because sometimes sand is uh
not so soft and it hurts your head yeah
oh well if you if
you say look how we both
10 friend 11.
[Applause]
good job good job i like you
gg everyone there was only one person
worse than us and that was probably on
purpose
they're probably divorcing us on purpose
people often when i when i stream mario
kart
my fans often like to uh wait for me at
the finishing line
that's really cool kind of them yeah
they literally have there
they have their job on the line they
lose their job if they don't let me win
so
with their job yeah everyone works for
me
they're my employees at kfp who is
lifting
my memories are my employees and they
lose their job when they when they don't
let me win
and you don't want to lose your job in a
time like this right oh
i'm going for a rainbow road on purpose
even though i hate it i hate it
so if i if i win does that mean that i
get promoted to
uh store manager
no you you get promoted if you let me
win oh
that's how it is that's how it is
so do you want a promotion go get it
[Laughter]
hey there's another impeccado fan in
yeah exactly that's what the name says
i can't rule like when i speak german we
roll the rs but i can't roll the r when
i speak japanese i don't know why
are olga
right that's like it has it needs a
little bit more l
in there right i usually when i roll my
arms i do it at the very tip of my
tongue
[Music]
it's all right once you figure out that
tongue roll it's gonna be
game over that's all it takes right
that's all it takes
you're going to be going to roam your
eyes i see you fighting with that nose
daddy with that peculiar fan
[Music]
oh
turned on and off the line man it
completely messed up all my lights in my
apartment
on y'all
this map makes me feel funny huh what
i can't kill you you're too far away i'm
sorry
[Music]
come back to me i see you in front of me
anyways
i like how we always feel closely each
other
it's so nice how we both suck i love it
how are you able to play i have to
concentrate so hard
probably if i would actually stop
talking and concentrate i would probably
be
much better at this game
[Music]
wow
are you behind me yeah now yeah i was
next to you for a second
but someone hit blue with their goddamn
shield
[Music]
we gotta do a follow-up on that japanese
lessons and teach you german instead
maybe you
maybe you remember more german yeah you
remember the japanese that i told you
yeah that's good yeah
you're so far away from me why are you
six and i'm telling you what the hell
cause i was getting sweaty while you
were talking
i miss you come back to me
let's go for cheap gym beats
i haven't played i don't think i've
played the water park one before
is that the tip tip beach i know that's
something no this one there
it's the i don't know it's got someone
below it you like roller coasters
ah i have to enjoy roller coaster but am
i wrong
um i need a lot of pushing to get on the
coaster but once i'm on it i have fun
but oh okay it's just if you flip your
arms
no i also when i'm on a roller coaster i
like
crunch together and look down and i'm
like my arms like pushing against my
head and like
and then at some point i stopped
screaming and inside i'm dying only
there was one time i was on this i was
on a roller coaster
um and it's one that like pulls you back
like a rubber band
and when you're supposed to i didn't
know this but when you get pulled back
in one of those
because of the pressure when you get let
go you're not gonna be able to breathe
in so you have to take a breath
before you get uh before it goes
and i didn't do that you don't worry
what happens if you don't breathe well
when i did that i couldn't catch my
breath so i started panicking because i
couldn't breathe
and it was dark and my eyes were closed
did you die did you die well i know
how long could you not breathe it was
only a few seconds but it really felt
like a long time wait why
why on all places are we on the rainbow
round
it does happen
oh i remember this i remember something
like this
is that's actually the rim no that's not
the rainbow road i think there's like
two roads that keep on like uh
thinking this rainbow rod but it's not
uh-huh
[Music]
me no oh no you're not how did i catch
you if you're behind me
hey where are you what place are you in
i don't know i don't see it because your
head is covering it up do you want to
move like a little bit to the right or
left that's just kidding
[Music]
can you tilt your head to the very left
right now
oh no i still don't see it
i only saw the th something so it's
probably not first
probably not second and probably not
third it's third
or second when you're behind me
time for the grandchild soon
come on
[Music]
climb up not a chance not when i'm down
here
did you fall down the edge oh no no i
have the this is i think i have there's
like a thing that keeps you from falling
off the edge yeah
i have it on too but it didn't save me
one time and
i fell down anyway oh maybe there's like
certain places you can fall down
[Music]
uh
okay i think i'm in front of you again
not for long no no no
[Laughter]
you just placed in front of me that's
how i like it it seems that we are
yes this is the same skill level yeah
i like it i like it
[Laughter]
we're destined to be together it appears
so
the stars have aligned and placed us in
exactly the same spot
you know when we talked about having
this collab and
i asked you if you're good at this game
and if you have practice and stuff you
said
you're really bad and i didn't believe
you i thought you were being just humble
but you're actually bad and i really
like it
[Music]
ah thanks i guess
this game is this game is hard i don't
know it's not like it's
like a lot of rng but also it's it's
shortcuts and
and knowing when to do your your
drifting right
yeah i think you need to if you have
some practice and some skill
you can do much better i guess people
keep on telling me to drift but
drifting often messes up my driving i
don't want to drift
yeah it takes a lot of uh counteracting
your own drifting like if you're
drifting left you got to steer right and
you got it
also did you did your thing around how
to jump because i tried the r button but
it didn't do anything
uh it did do something for me the top
button not the uh big button on the top
but the small button they are
not the same oh you can spin
i wanna do i wear you a flip a one
180 or a 360 or something like that
this is you amusing yeah
[Music]
that was a good one
yeah the canadian there's a canadian in
front of me
do something uh
hey hey hey how about you
uh go on back to your house eh
yeah keep on dissing the canadians right
there
back to your house is that all you could
come up with
tim hortons is having a sale on donuts
don't you hey
let her go out you better go get
do canadians like donuts that much yeah
i think so i think
tim hortons is a penny is a canadian
donut place
oh really yeah i don't know are they
good
i don't know i assume so people want to
sponsor us and send them some
send us some donuts yeah collaborate
was clever
i feel like i'm number one when i'm like
probably some someone around
eight wait when did i get an 11th place
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i could have been next to you again but
master have bee or some someone else
hit me with a shell again i could have
been next to you god damn
who ruined this hidden moment again i
bet they were saving that for you too
[Music]
karma it's karma when you were saving
that shell for me
in the last race
that was a present i thought you like
shells since you're from
the ocean i love shells i love girl
oyster shells and clam shells and
mussels there you go
there you go i wanted to help you with
your collection of shells
well thank you with all your bread
shells and green shells to gouda
because she's collecting them they're
our favorite
favor and send
[Music]
uh save your your fiery items for
piada the fiery phoenix
barely anyone ever gets that item anyway
that's okay
that's a pretty rare item
oh
[Music]
how do you say turtle in japanese
how many days
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
like all the blue elements in your
design have to be green
somebody give me give me a comment give
me a turtle shell
just not in the race though it's so
perfect oh my god comment comment on it
[Music]
oh god i i
i don't want that kind of credit don't
know keep it to yourself
that's not rover what is that it's moe
robot
what is the character in the game and
marshall wow
there's a character called roving yeah
what is that
it's uh it's a cat character in the one
of the previous or a few of the previous
animal crossing games
no no no i'm not available right now i'm
busy
without you fire no right no no
[Music]
fire
nice try with your car michelle's ladies
and gentlemen
[Music]
yeah this is good now
i got lucky with uh lucky with a shell
uh not a shell with a
gold mushroom at the end that's what i
got
[Music]
i love it the next one come on i want i
wonder which one
ice skating sounds nice i like to go ice
skating
uh i do i think it'd be fun i don't know
it must have been a bit ago oh me too
but guys getting so much fun in winter
best time ever good at on skates
how how are you no i haven't done ice
skating i've done roller blading
oh i'm talking about ice skating i know
my brain went to rollerblading it's like
inline skin what is inline skinny oh
maybe that's just a
name we use for refrigerating german
even though it's english
have you seen uh people that go i call
it land skiing
have you ever seen that before yeah you
know when people see you right
yeah they do it but they do it online
they do it up like the
on the sidewalk it's so crazy what
have the long skis are you sure well
it's like
i should have stopped hiking with just
the two skip sticks on the side
i mean it looks like skiing that's
probably just hiking go down
no it's not
explaining it actually exists or is she
talking about hiking
come on guys back me up you know that's
real
cross country skiing is that a thing
actually
it's great trekking poles
right apparently it's real
i've seen people walking around with the
with those with those sticks
in the in their hands but they're not
they're not using
uh the ski skiers right
their legs are on their legs keys i
promise you
[Music]
grinnell you got three mushrooms i got
three mushrooms we're gonna start i
gotta start
with the game the game wants us to be in
the city
beautiful it's supporting our
relationship
[Music]
you sent that shell to the wrong person
my friend
should have been addressed to good
outside
[Music]
that makes me happy i like to see you in
front of me that
gives me a feeling of reassurance makes
me feel safe when you're in front of me
i'm not sure if i should be worried or
because then you're gonna you're gonna
pelt me with all your shoes
you can take that in so many ways i i
might just really
mean it in a whole some way or it might
i might mean it in a way of i want to
destroy
come on come on big money big money
yes you can be happy now because now you
get a promotion
okay i lost my crown
where's my crown goddammit okay yeah
one last game that sounds good let's do
that all right
all right which one should we go for
last game everyone last game get in
while you can
and please leave if you just we're in
the race please leave
shall we give one chance to everyone
else
kick those two how do i kick people
people telling me to kick them have they
been in there for a while
please leave thank you please
please let me politely ask you thank you
brings you
thanks to you
thank you thank you thank you new people
you're welcome to come in
come on in and and yeah
[Music]
which is random does that choose
randomly from those three or from
all of the races i don't know i assume
it'd be from the ones that are
are listed oh
oh let's see let's see
[Music]
from oh oh it's is everyone
oh there's someone someone in the chat
then all
[Laughter]
[Music]
what up you want to race with us huh are
you there challenged
us i'm making you have no chance against
us yeah okay how about guys we turn it
around this time
you guys we're challenging you to lose
uh
against us can you do it can you do it
let us see if we can take up this
challenge are you able to
lose against us huh that's gonna be a
hard one
it's actually a challenge that that is
actually a challenge
hey stop bumping me slowly like what
happened way too much in the front
oh cool why are you like doing the
second or first or something
how did you do that well it will change
soon don't worry go down
[Music]
don't get used to it i'm gonna use it
i'm so happy
kiara believes in me guys
wait
[Music]
are these people actually trying to
accept my challenge and lose against you
but you're also supposed to lose against
me
not only against buddha no no no no
ah yeah
there's a fake australian that's the
wrong flag my dude
mate that's the wrong flag oh i might
as your own flag damn night
[Music]
oh no you passed me
what
you better not mess this up right now
you better not
no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
oh gg
good job good job good job that was nice
i was downwards down
those were some good races good on you
and me were a good team that was fun i
had a lot of fun
gotta leave the race though yes yes
okay well well well
wow my how do you call this
my uh my excitement my
my there's a rush there's i have a rush
what do you call this
adrenaline called adrenaline yeah
oh it's like that
oh my god it's that race car adrenaline
now you gotta go run three miles around
around the block a few times hell yeah
i'll go do that
thank you so much for driving with me it
was a pleasure
good night
oh thank you i'm looking forward to a
future future battle with you
a future battle as in mario kart or
perhaps
yes smash i mean yeah i think we're
probably also on the both levels in
smash as well so
that depends do you lose do you lose to
the ledge too do you also fall off the
map repeatedly
of course of course i did okay
let's do smash next time
okay okay we can do that i'm down for
that let's do it
all righty uh i like to say in german to
my viewers auf wiedersehen
okay i'll see you soon
cute bye bye everyone
everybody bye bye thank you bye bye
hashtag sami told you forever
you