[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
[Applause]
a
what
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
he
ah
[Music]
no
[Applause]
oh
uh oh
hi hi
hi
KY
[Music]
no no
Purge no okay bye-bye chuny wonie I love
you so much I love you I love
you
hello k key sorry I was going to put on
um some
clothes but then I accidentally deleted
them uh inad instead of putting them on
um un
no uh where is
it no no not this one this one yes
yes did blue finish the new ones like I
see I saw she was working on something
is this good this is
okay yeah maybe a little
bit more
like yeah
okay still works okay
okay
and oh wait that's big that's too
big then it will be like like
this and
[Music]
ni let's go I'm going to beat you up I'm
going to beat you up you little [\h__\h]
yeah that's what I do I'll beat you up
with this bat are you
ready I'll skin you alive sorry that was
a bit
extreme let's
go
Alo
happy IO
happy you
see I
happy my hearts are
[Music]
pounding is that the right
word cie recently also got some but hers
are not pounding hers are not going doy
doie mine are going doy
doie oh I noticed it's like when I
blink then it goes doie doie doie doie
and it comes down and then I blink and
it goes doie doie doie do doie and it
comes
down oh oh but it's still it's still
it's still vibrating now what's the
word not
vibrating anyway anyway anyway yay
pulsating that's what I mean
pulsating oh hi oh pleas do the same
thing hi this is
me rare W top
teeth just just letting you know I have
sparkles don't forget about
them yeah yeah yeah Kitty wait let me
let me try to get chat up here now sorry
sorry sorry I had a rehearsal for the
bank that's me I had a rehearsal for the
Bangkok event and before stream and it
took a little bit longer because these
are moments where I really wish I just
had my um
goxlr because yeah the G is so much
easier to like you know play my
audio uh through my microphone you know
what I mean like normally like for
example when I want to play audio that
comes from the game or so I just turn on
desktop audio which is a separate audio
Source in
OBS but but if we're like in Zoom then
you want to have the audio go for your
microphone directly with your
mic yeah and uh yeah my new thing it can
do that but it's like a little bit like
more difficult seemingly and uh that's a
little bit
annoying but we are GNA be okay we fixed
it we figured it out um mostly I think
I wonder if I can say
this so can I can I say this I think I
can say
this
[Music]
I uh you know rehearsal starts camera on
Zoom turns on and I see the usual staff
who like uh the cover staff who is
always at the event
events there's one in particular who is
always there and then I see you know
sometimes these events they they give us
a MC
translator and yeah before they even
introduce themselves I was
like oh oh well I see the usual cover
stuff but someone else here looks very
familiar to me I say that but I get no
reactions so I get like a little bit
intimidated
so I wait I wait until they introduce
themselves and um it's a certain
kfp a certain kfp and I'm like yeah I
knew it I knew
it and I'm like what are you doing here
yeah yeah yeah yeah NeNe
diesel like what are you doing here and
she's like oh yes I I signed up for the
job and uh yeah
I'm like you little [\h__\h] can't believe
you're here doing MC work getting to
hear my rehearsal yo extra extra special
time with the
boss don't think you can get away easily
you sneaky sneaky little Nene
diesel no but it makes me also feel a
little bit relieved because the MC is
guaranteed to uh know me and cie and you
know what they they'll know like what
they're doing and all that
yeah W let's go our very
own yeah I had to had to tease her a
little
bit she's a great pick for the job our
very own yo she got a new job I wonder
how much she's getting
paid did you make a Chima subtitle video
no no I did not what do you
mean
my shoulders really hurt these
days
[Music]
really she already got paid she met you
after hours yeah yeah yeah true meeting
me after hours before hours it's my
birthday happy birthday Cardinal
crowbar cute picture was that you sure
no that's what that was not really that
was not really a
crack okay AFP getting
paid so the thing is the event is for me
it's like tomorrow I think for na it
would be today but obviously the event
is in Bangkok so it's tomorrow and for
me for my time zone it's also tomorrow
but I have to be up at like 5 a.m. is I
think the event starts at 6 my time 6:00
a.m. and I have to be there for standby
and Tech check and pre-show and
everything uh 5 a.m. so now it is
4:30
p.m. so I will not be able to stream as
long as
usual just so you know um do not let me
stream
longer than P 10 p.m. P p.m. 10 p.m.
okay please don't don't let me stream
longer than 10 p.m. cuz after that I
have to eat and this and that and
hopefully get to sleep a little bit I
mean I don't expect to get like 8 hours
that's already impossible if I stream
until
10:00 um wait is going to be so short
let's get into
it but then tomorrow so I thought I'm
probably G to sleep a little bit after
the event is over and that's why
tomorrow starts 1 hour later but then we
can go for however long I
want 10 p.m. is like 6 hours from
now uh
10 5 and a
half yeah 5 and a half hours that's so
short what the [\h__\h] we'll get nothing
done especially when
I yap yap yap yap y Yap and I want to
talk
[Music]
though let me make me small
no we're not playing Dragon's Dogma
tomorrow did you see the
schedule are you even looking at the
schedule hey hey hey hey hey would I put
you
again stud
it cuts into Yap time so far apart oh
don't cry cry me a river oh cryy
River oh cryy River oh cryy river which
one is the this
one
Jimmy
[Music]
oh oh Jimmy a Jimmy a Jimmy what a
coincidence that he's called Jimmy
because that's our funny name for our
chickens our standard
name you are the default chicken when
you're not even you don't even have me
as your
Koshi don't know if you're worthy of the
Jimmy
name should I put myself somewhere else
wait I
think maybe here
here I might cover up the map and a
little bit of the subtitles sometimes
but I'm trying to be
small okay a gym yeah for now he's just
gym Mr
Gym uh so uh yeah we are currently
looking for the Chinese
Mafia yeah because yeah and they're
probably in some casinos or something
like that
right Chinese Mafia Casino uh it's been
like a month but that's what we're doing
and I think we're we're done here in the
bar wait wait why are we not healed if
can we like sleep and heal or is that
another
thing another m t i uh where's the bed
ah ah ah a there we go perfect is a true
Jimmy I vouch for him what do you mean
vouching as in you're also not you don't
also don't have me as your Koshi but
you're still called
Jimmy huh I mean you you have been ow
what the [\h__\h] you have been here since
the beginning though so I might not be
your Koshi but that's still pretty
epic called
out no it's
okay it's okay it's okay okay I'm not
really I'm just I'm just roasting
[Music]
you
okay
now uh but yeah I don't know what to do
what are we doing where where do I go I
just follow uh the sign right there's
the pink sign right where how do I look
at the map there we go first try first
try baby do you think I'm ready
equipment wise
let's see let's learn the hard
way have you guys been enjoying
Chima you do have to it's okay CH
chicken bucket that's pretty
good no it's not about that though it's
not about the length uh of your
membership uh let's
go it's about who is your Koshi but
that's okay yeah I don't have to be a
kamhi that's fine I don't you know
that's fine I'm just saying like if
you're called
Jimmy you know how do I say hi there we
[Music]
go taking the crown now you're calling
me King
it's BK into the usual
room
Michael two weeks Michael two weeks two
weeks black
[Music]
hiis
righted dumplings let's go Cru
here hello hey how about
now wait I mean there's nothing really
to
here I made
it
louder wait how about
how about
this there's no dumplings in here
dude oh was that like a secret code like
asking
for The Dumpling stat specifically was
that a secret code where we expected to
go into the casino yeah okay that's why
he kept on repeating it I thought he
just really wanted
some I prefer the fried ones
though
always room
yeah well how does it
[Music]
work um uh 10 10
oh oh no oh [\h__\h]
good job let's
[Laughter]
go W let's go we're making it to the
casino with this
[Music]
one
oh oh oh W welcome
hello pardon the delay oh please enjoy
yourselves tonight English Jo actual
English let's go
[Music]
guys oh no it's time for
gambling what what ichan are you not
amused are you not entertained
Norm me music rotation let's
[Music]
go blackj right I can play blackj right
I know how that works right oh do I is
that the one that I
know shoot shoot lost again hey itang
come here real quick I'll teach you how
to cheat this
game get 21 or bust okay or at least
under at this we're totally going to get
cleaned that out why' you come here in
the first place uh we want to the we
wanted to the hotel we need to look the
part right sure these guys were here to
play I know oh that' be easy if we were
actually
winning okay then we got to make it so
we do win yeah no too bad luck's just
not on my side today um have you tried
winning before instead of losing oh my
God what a
loser what about K told me four of us
walked in we only need one of us to hit
their stride first St Tommy's a nog go
in fact I'd say lck's the least of his
problems what is he
doing so he's frustrated as we are what
about kidu
son what's with him t for him all damn
it you think K son would have this down
by
now this place has its fangs real deep
in US didan you don't have any ideas to
turn it around not yet but one thing's
clear what's that oh if we want to in
here we're going to have to cheat
oh I don't want to
cheat I mean not like I didn't expect
that given all we had to do just to get
in I've been keeping my eyes out for a
weak spot there's got to be something
easier easier said than done I guess we
got to find a way thing is how do we do
that
uh
I want to play fa
wi what is this what's with his brain
like two seconds ago he was saying I
know we at least one thing I know is we
have to cheat one second later I'm not
going to cheat I I'll play fair cheating
doesn't feel right I know I just said we
have to cheat and we will cheat but now
I say we will not cheat what what is
this well maybe give it a few more round
red nothing else yeah let me actually do
it
myself what I don't get to actually play
it it's F we better to talk
again I think it's loud and clear at
this point if we want to win big
cheating is our only option
great um why don't we try to have a plan
okay looks like there's no choice all
right let me think here we got to find a
way thing is how do we do that
do not live it to Tommy
Za says the way to
go think you could pull off the sweet
talking routine again huh what do you
mean oh what did you forget how you
played me true true back at aanan place
you work your magic on the dealer there
and we get him on our side from there we
cut him a piece of the action and his
money in the bag right
H okay I get it so that's what you think
of me
huh whoa what who [\h__\h] what did I
say plenty it's oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
you're going to use me like I'm so tool
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay sure
whatever you say anything else I can do
for you
H wait a tool oh hang on I didn't mean
it like
that if if you were actually willing to
do that it certainly help us
out yeah are you stupid you really think
I can seduce the guy in a crow like this
yeah just just be yourself you're
already like so Charming just like this
on top of that you're banking on him
switching sides that would never happen
whether he fell for me or not come on
quit messing around we're all busting a
butts to find your mom you mother lover
you
know uh okay sorry um now I'm kind of
scared to suggest anything
else um I guess K
you I was kind of hoping k s would show
us how it's done but I guess
not oh [\h__\h] it's worse than I thought
he's already drowning oh K what the [\h__\h]
is song of you have you not learned
anything in the past games don't get
drunk in this
situation so we can't have him stumbling
around I'll go check up on him he's what
fine I'm coming
too nice
looks like we're up a creek huh all this
way only to get stuck at the
Finish don't blame you for wanting to
knock back of
you well
cheers that's all you got to say to your
defense seems like we need to figure out
a new plan tell's not playing so hot
either I'm so fresh I'm I'm so I'm I'm
fresh out of chips um um got any more
like maybe salty maybe sour cream I
don't
know yeah uh but also maybe some real
like casino chips that as well but I
would prefer the potato chips think you
could help me with that you
chipon if you were on a roll you
wouldn't be asking for chips would
you yeah well I really thought I was
going to get to eat some G out here but
all they had was chips and now I ate
them all what am I supposed to do CH go
that's enough huh I a meaning to talk to
you guys needed you all in one place
don't worry I found our way
in hey not
allow anyway what's the plan oh the
blackjack table kasuga and choa were at
check out the
dealer don't face him just glance over
when you can whenever he deals he always
checks his own hand I got a clear shot
of his cards from where I was sitting
earlier
no peek doing a little peek a
peek no kidding so if kosan gives us a
signal we can get a read on the Dealer's
hand that's right but there's a good
chance we'll get caught if I signal you
directly we we'll pass signs through Tom
first I use hand dressers for the
dealers cards and Tomy will relay them
to
Cho oh they [\h__\h] [\h__\h] up this is like
a telephone
game Chu and press her finger into
kasuga's shoulder for whatever number
the deal is
cut this way Kasa can know the Dealer's
cards without ever looking away from on
his own yeah simply put we're about to
turn the tables on this place or table
the turns
it appears to you f well played sir ha
it already happened that was easy all
right no way I'm stopping
now don't don't lose your positions you
idiots what wrong we're on the roll
let's keep going the man you stepped out
on the
floor thank you thank you eating my tyon
has I will not make a comment about my
ass at this moment but
everybody's posting my ass and I kind of
expected that and yeah it's a it's a
pretty good
scene but I feel a bit embarrassed
because it's not like the ass is perfect
like the shape of my ass is still kind
of
[\h__\h] um but it has a lot of impact
right that is for sure and how how does
that work when you in the MV when you
have the MV open
and you press four it goes directly
there how how how how does that
work magic why is it four
guys explain to
me how does it go there it no how uh cuz
it is exactly at
40% whoa so if I press one does it go to
10% oh [\h__\h] I don't think canu did that
on purpose like having it at exactly
40% but I should prank cie I should tell
her open the
MV okay now press your favorite number
she presses four and she's
[Laughter]
like let's
go
uh anyway so he wants to show him no
doubt about it he came in from the back
after the staff called for him because
somebody won
unbelievable and that means oh it means
we got what we came for now let's go
it's up to kaso to handle the rest
me the tables are so low they're like on
their knees is that
normal awkwardly
low for for
kids
[Music]
for
for this is weirdly
intimate
what oh
four hand holding
[Music]
oh
y b she's revealing
herself she be revealing
herself
of
course run away to
C oh you're so cool you're so cool yes
let's go
[Music]
princess
we're getting into the hotel with this
one
baby I've heard this like way of saying
things a few times by
now am I saying it
right some people have been
saying this about
Kima or something I just don't
understand I'm not saying it
right
[Music]
we're making
it I said I think I said it
right what Hur getting out and getting
in both
versions
for oh
hi of course you can be
[Music]
useful
for
okay the protagonist has become a side
character talking about ich
now K wants to be on the wheel
again change of location equals
success oh sorry sorry
sorry yeah but uh well I was going to
say is I found some comments like two or
so maybe on Twitter I think where people
were saying we're making it out of or
into with this one about Kima and it was
like some some reference that I was just
not getting I was like what what what
are you talking
about have you guys seen it do you know
what I
mean I forgot what it
was I I know the the the the
the the G General meme but the location
that they were mentioning I did not
understand you don't know I'll try to
find it
again just means the song is good okay
well but I don't know why they chose the
location I forgot I forgot what it was
no
okay wait how do I get
there it's this way can I go through
no but
there's do I get there ah from the side
from
here oh we could fight a little bit so I
remember how to fight you can't measure
up to
me uh oh oh she's so cute come
on uh
or maybe no SK well
okay this is one enemy all
area one
enemy I don't know what I was always
using let's oh he's weak to
fire yeah okay we're getting uh into the
hotel with this one yeah
[Music]
breaker
maybe but this is ah I get proximity
bonus let's
go yeah this is what we want to
[Applause]
[Music]
see so
you
just some normal hits he's been poisoned
oh know poor poor
Tucker his [\h__\h] surf board is
[Music]
insane
crazy good good good good we understand
it's been really long and month since we
last played is really kind of crazy now
this is
real I didn't intend for it to take so
long nice collateral
damage it's been ages for
real but that's
okay on
me
I think we can just do normal
attack might not kill him but I want to
save my
mp yeah was really
Bey what game is this read the title of
the stream
please I forgot you have to push that so
I didn't do it much only twice now
G to me is in Goblin mode I like it
though was I supposed to change it back
and give everyone different classes
again I think this is
fine what you look at says what are we
doing yeah but before that is the title
of the
game
ala
ala okay from here we can enter but yeah
title uh I was planning on changing that
after I know what we did in the Stream
same for the thumbnail this is more like
a placeholder of a thumbnail cuz I like
to change the thumbnails afterwards for
this play
through to you know reflect what
happened hello what was your name
again
AG wonderful kasan Nana hotel is yours
for the taking we've got the clums
devices geared up so head back to Hana
when you're ready why did I come
here for you wait do we have healing
stuff in here
no oh
nice cat
food but no
cat no other healing stuff for
real yummy for my
cat pe's request I've prepared you a
little something you're looking at the
agency's latest
surveillance oh you really do work fast
enough the front thanks I could say the
same for you you think you gained access
to n hotel that quick quickly now you
can enter the heart of
gunu well really we got to thank Chan
for all that please don't more flattery
I didn't really didn't do
much now kasan
understand that you'll be on the
surveillance end this time we can take
you to the surveillance point near the
Nirvana Hotel anytime just let me know
when you
ready are you able to go now
um oh better prepare it's warning me
again recommended level 24 recommended
equipment freest Stars what level am I
do you guys know should I
check I'm 21 ooh
time for a little
grind just a little bit yeah let's see
how fast we can get to
24 thanks for the warning game oh
there's a the one with the crown what
you looking at were they really
dangerous taking the crown now you're
calling me King you're going to hear him
all
[Music]
sing
yeah they're harder red CRS are
manageable purple ones are hard
[Music]
okay why are they so far you ought to
know when to give
up oh wow good damage you're not
[Music]
so
bam [\h__\h]
yeah do he defeat it no Senpai I know
it's not
Senpai yo I saw a clip of me like
calling everybody in h x break sampler
again but I want to say the [\h__\h] one was
on purpose as a
joke uh the e h on I think was by
accident
oh let's
go increasing the battle speed no this
is fine for me I feel comfortable let's
go in here and uh although I can can I
only go in here if I go past the the
crown
dude what are you looking yeah cuz he's
like girl chickens he's like the relax
so all right let's try him I'll fling
you
wow he do be
[Music]
special does this get them they look for
K he looks like he might not
be oh
wait
the one that's chosen and everybody
who's in like their Circle right so I
would still be the best
choice yeah I know it's a
above I'm thinking of using it let's try
let's see if K gets it otherwise at
least three people get it oh okay no
k m
ah he's weak to fire good to know one
enemy light enemy area okay let's just
do fire
spinning yeah that shouldn't be too bad
this
one I already got quite a bit of damage
also he's only level
17 uh which one of these was
good
maybe grapple
one should I just attack
team
okay how does this
[Applause]
work okay I didn't do that much damage
but
okay cring
Collider m is it worth it yeah yeah he's
a boss do
it
yay that's so fun it's so fun here we go
he's PR no he
[Music]
missed
one nice so far I'm not missing at all
you like like the the the MV thank
you thank you guys I'm so happy you like
it and it's doing pretty well so far
with the
algorithm everybody's watching it it
might not just be the algorithm it might
be legit like people being interested
still uh from F and all that so I think
everybody's pretty
excited
[Music]
easy and I'm really happy to see people
like the MV this
much song but both of
the
[\h__\h] that is quite the
uh quy translation he didn't insult him
like that at all I mean it's just
Loosely in English I guess but
damn why he
[Music]
translation
I love how
he
off
I'll the transition shot to Idol out is
actually
yeah hurt it's pretty hype last course
Idol
[Music]
Wawa actually I'm going to attack nor
all
right
W that's so
cute
personally um the the black and white W
while I think they're really cute I
don't want to overuse them so hopefully
this will be the last time I'll be using
black and white wa um this is just going
to be like too much
oh
nice and it will always remind you of
duyu because the doyu impression is just
so strong you
know damn it I was hoping it would
damage the other one
too
was like do you too see that's that's
the automatic in impression that you get
that it's like do you successor I don't
even see it that way but I know the MV
with like the black and white W will
automatically make you think that
way ni nice cred guard so that's the
issue we've always using that
[Music]
now
have any choice in outfits but I'm going
to look into what is Idol
does going to look into
that flipper to the Lipper inker to the
blinker trippy flipper
Ripper the names
man
try what's
try I don't know what to
[Music]
do
nice the
gray can you use a custom 3D outfit so
yeah that's the thing I want like a 3D
outfit right but like I won't get one
from cover so I wonder if I can buy like
on boo
Japanese
site there's some like pretty outfits
that are being sold like anybody can buy
them and put them on their model but it
has to be rigged onto your
model
so I need first of all permission to do
that and then uh ideally someone
who
can rig that kind of stuff onto my model
for
cheap and then I could have some more
variety in my mvs I don't think I would
be able to use it like in
streams but we'll see about that I just
wish we had more choices for Fredy
outfits like for people like me I just
um now now you see what happens like
everybody thinks of do you with my MV
which is fine you know but that shows
you I I really need more
Choice why do you why why do you think
they might not allow it because they
also allow me using other models like
the low poy
models and if I bring up the fact that I
don't have any other way of getting a 3D
outfit then maybe they'll you know if
it's just for an MV they might consider
[Music]
it
it's just yeah that
requires it to be ried onto my bear
model yeah so no if it was like a new
model from scratch I think I can do
whatever I want with
it we'll see I have to look into it I
volunteer oh my
God I got shot because I looked at the
[Applause]
chat
yeah for recoloring that was okay as
long
as that does give me hope yeah they also
let me remove parts
so like the oh
oh yeah I don't care about
him I don't care about that whole part
of the
game um but yeah what was I saying hey
qu yeah since they're pretty lenient
with that I
have tiny hat and my oh my
God they have those anime hats
on oh my
God self-proclaimed
witch N I need to get in lot of
money this is my up
oh dear uh this one you use the one
that's furest behind right because
otherwise it ends
here yeah let's go I
remembered it's so
creepy oh yeah like uh my mom might be
watching now because she did like
Yakuza recently more than for go say hi
to
Mommy hi
Mommy playing
around what are they weak
against nothing I can really do that's
okay it's almost dead let still yeah was
hoping for that coroporation
W she was already dead
but yeah I was really happy to see
everybody so excited about Kima and all
the ass posting on Twitter is probably
helping it uh get some
reach and get people curious about it so
keep on posting my ass I guess you can
also post other parts though very
welcome cuz there's a lot of very
screenshot moments I say
maximum
mittens W I have mittens too I love my
mittens mittens for the
kittens for the Discord
kittens combat
sword my ass sto the show for real
everybody's only talking about
[Music]
the
hey
you ready for
an I was just picking some herbs can you
leave me
[Music]
alone
I want to write down and learn some
phrases in time to use
tomorrow got to do that like when I have
my stream and then I need to eat and
then I need to sleep oh this Witch is
strong oh
sh going to
hurt h
don't
you ask
Nene Nene's
busy end this before 10 probably like I
don't know we'll see we'll see if we
find a good ending
point anytime before
10 oh
[\h__\h] don't sh judge game by
this oh no K you get back up this is
going to hurt ow [\h__\h] I need you get
better at dodging [\h__\h] almost had it
almost had
[Music]
it
9999999 Watson defeated no why am I
defeating so many whole life members
what are these
names Get Wrecked
soundtrack is so
good Lance Lance I don't
know I feel good about taking down Lance
we
[Music]
level
okay I've cleared the park wait there's
more but wait there's
more
oo your face pissing me off you're going
to regret
this threatening man oh he's got a gun
he's got a freaking Gun
Guys
scared yeah well
okay
I involv the music production team in
your relase stream yeah they're so sweet
and so supportive and they always tell
me how happy they are with working with
me but I'm also so happy to work with
them like you don't
[Music]
understand Miss oh but he
died we're just vibing we're on the same
wavelength which is really great to work
with someone like
that
y they give little XP iess I should go
somewhere the stronger ones but
where where do
you at least I'm 22
[Music]
now the dungeon I don't know where the
dungeon is anymore I don't want to go
into a dungeon
now I don't feel like going into the
dungon what's up William O
[Music]
item a modified flashbang 300 damage oh
can you guys stop messing with Furniture
here going to get in trouble blue is
like really weak right blue too weak for
me
Aloha should we buy some food oh table
talk ordering ah now you're telling me
about combo
meals these special conversations can
increase your bonds with those
[Music]
involved c c combo
Ginger that I was supposed to like order
everything right and then I would figure
it
out
confirm there's there're still lock what
but am am I not unlocking them now what
why are they
locked one combo two combo hey I'm
getting combos at least I'm getting the
combo even if I don't get the
conversation the combo is what I what I
really
[Music]
want
she lost her
wallet oh really oh
no can I
help I just really like running around
in this
game
hey
blue okay how do I get to this dungeon
where is this
dungeon I forgot was it
was it
here
is was it here
no the
castle castle
icon
castle
aome near the bridge
ah there it
is
okay A little bit of grinding in my life
a little bit of leveling all the
time what the hell
huh what's going on oh you're still
was scaring around for anything valuable
and found this HK of junk Curious Thing
Ain it one bu at all what the is that is
that am in her old space suit before she
upgraded to her current
one seems like it might be worth
something if it were still moving ah
well added to the list of creepy
[\h__\h] I
suppose it's an old
masc oh no me what fairy well you dless
Travelers huh some kind of broken robot
I just be out of juice on if I take a
look you know about the stuff me I'll
bit strange it should be working now
it's almost like it's
sleeping it's probably too busted up
weird I feel like I've seen it before
somewhere whoever made it had no taste
though what did you just say to
me what it's up it was designed by the
very best in masc marketing I am
roboo
roboo oh again it that's why he looks so
familiar it's some kind of spin-off of
Ono what the what is what what I don't
know should I know wait how do you know
about Olo isn't he just the mascot for
some tiny Port Town in
Hiroshima oh yeah but still everybody
knows
onomo he's a hit with fans worldwide
most people consider him the king of
mascots the AP AP of Japanese culture
itself apic of Japanese culture a
reference to six
ah to me it's am in the space suit
yeah honestly check any shopping center
and you'll find B loads of me mer
legitimate legitimate or bootle he's
just that popular come to think of it I
heard talk of some kind of mechanized me
never knew they actually came out with
it affirmative M I am Robo
M so what's it doing out here I wonder
I'm equipped with a suit of security
functions and such I was stationed here
to W of trespassers Mei however it would
seem that I ran out of power allowing
the rare area to become infested with
criminals scum me you think they were
going to leave security to a robot
they'd give it an extension record or
something so now that you're working
again are you going to head inside and
sweep all the troublemakers out me much
too my agine I currently lack the
necessary energy to engage in combat
without full power I can only operate in
safety mode are you familiar with the
Game Gear the iconic portable
entertainment device released by S
corporation in 1991 featuring such
classic titles as Defenders of Oasis and
Sanic drift
to money is battery life and my own
abominably similar
me that's a pretty obscure
example even in recovery mode quite a
roast on that uh console
huh even in recovery mode it takes M
several days or longer to fully
charge whoa whoa is that how long that
Game Gear took to charge
too oh
[\h__\h] that's
insane oh old is
that Game Gear took six
batteries it took a villion
batteries oh she that really is crap so
what you can't do anything about delin
it's a regrettable situation my program
compels me to deal with these Mitchy Mis
grants yet my cold iron body cannot
comply wait a Mei wait a
what perhaps throwing a FL the problem
maybe may prove effective throwing flesh
okay you please if I do not complete my
m mission how will I ever face my
creator for a semi- involved primate you
seem fairly sturdy huh us semi Evol
primate your expression also suggests an
exploitable sense of justice and that
you otherwise have very little keeping
you occupied uh no I'm busy I'm
busy what if I were to offer you
recompensation Human Society I am told
functions by withholding vital resources
from the masses unless they perform
ceaseless manual labor
ma true true stupid machines got a
point oh you're fan of
onoo look at that fine we're probably
going to do back back inside anyway but
not for you thank you very mey once my
charge is complete I will be sure to
assist you which will will be when it's
least necessary at the very end F me if
you like I can offer you advice on the
many dangerous Ren LLY how shall I
address you in the future I suggest fro
me too what us let's just go with ichan
kasuga and what about Mei bun
huh yeah he did it he did it
yeah I suggested it he heard it a
pleasure M kasuga I totally came up with
that On My Own by the way no no no taka
Mii Ki help me with that I wish you the
best of your human primate
luck
interesting was this
necessary
recover no I want to look at
this concrete block blueprints will
allow you to make blocks with DIY on
blocks was I not able ble to make blocks
before okay let me
in
me
go my Island yeah my
Island another
bird she's uh
silver like this dude in a robot suit
wait can I do this one
too no okay but didn't I do this one
before I mean it's fine but
like
affir here we
go open up
FBI so I think last time I tried really
hard to find every
corner every dead end room
Etc
I don't know if I can hold myself back
from doing that this
time I did the tutorial version oh okay
okay these are also only
red oh wow
18 it works it just
works
sexy very
[Music]
sexy
resist all of my attacks are fist
though I'll just work on you
then or does he resist
everything I did a damn it Dam
it
little
sh no one can resist
friendship oh that was pretty
[Music]
weak back
attack
oh
I guess
he stronger type of
yeah
enemy I guarded perfectly let's
go I don't
know I'll try
again nice
blog she
what's
[Music]
up yeah stay on the ground where you
belong go go
go let's try this
one ooh
124 good stuff bring it you steal your
soul it's
mine speaking of stealing
Souls I finished season two of The
Witcher yes yes I am
fast oopsie and I stopped myself from
starting season I think I will not be
able to resist I I think I'll still do
it
I'll have
to no I already done with season
two what's your take
a season 1 season two together um yeah
pretty good there were some moments
where I was like that's kind of tacky or
I don't
know just something like more
unsatisfying but so it's not a perfect
show but it's pretty good
are you
scared but you guys say season 3 is like
very different from the books cuz they
went their own way I guess so that's
unfortunate but I still want to see it
because like it's
it's tickles my
fancy it does what I needed to do AKA
satisfy my
craving for a fantasy show like that
that's why yeah yeah that's why I know
cuz you guys keep on telling me about
that
off Robo
[Music]
disc if you watch some really shitty
season you will appreciate the quality
of the game
more I guess that's a good reason to
watch
it can't wait to see you play the game
yeah so we have perms for the console
version but I'm going to try to as
primms for the PC version apparently
several Holo members have uh played the
PC version before I don't know how you
guys can tell but you guys said am
played um the PC version long time ago
and a Holo star I've heard played one
Ian
holar which is more recently so I don't
know if that was just an oversight in
terms that does
happen or if it was actually okay I
think it may have been an oversight but
if it's the same publisher then it
should be
easy if it was a different publisher
then I would
understand it to be like that
sometimes why can't we also have an O
side honestly I mean even with me that
sometimes but JMA
actually noticed stuff like that
before before the stream like that that
was a Dave the diver kind of thing we
had perms for Dave the diver on the
switch not for PC then I scheduled it to
play on Steam and I was told
W but if I wouldn't have I think it's
because I I let them know that I'm
playing it on
Steam and if if I didn't have wouldn't
have said that nobody would have noticed
I
think but because I said it they were
like oh
W please play on switch and I'm like no
I can't because I played until the end
of the game on Steam no the other way
around the other way around I played
until the end of the game on switch but
we only have steam perms so I had to
apply for perms for switch Dave the
diver in
particular and I got it after like a few
weeks oh that was the end of
okay
yeah so generally it it works but it
takes a little bit but I told Callie
don't worry I'll apply for her I don't
care about the item can't be that
special can it
be I'll apply for the perms cuz I also
want to play
it this should be
possible oh hello damn on home
that's a lot of enemies five no not five
four
okayy I have found your weakness grass
snake now they move oh they all move
away wo wo wo wo wo
wo
he's so cute with his little flower
pot you chickening out on
me yeah I don't know I don't know what
to say uh I I have uh a lot of thoughts
about The Witcher but I don't know how
to vocalize
them hurry up come on ask me questions
about The Witcher if you have
any
ni oh is the is the is the oh nice is
the prequel good because after finishing
season
2 [\h__\h] uh it recommended me the prequel
there's like a spin-off prequel
nice best
character I don't know I I I generally
like jifa but then at the end where she
does the stupid thing it's like I don't
know if that was really in character and
then her sudden change of mind is also
kind of weird although out of character
maybe but then I guess she was
influenced by the witch or whatever that
was not not an animated movie no no no
no the blood moon prequel is absolute
garbage the animated movie is good
oh wow don't watch that one not blood
Origins why not what's wrong with
it also also I want to say you know at
the very end of the last episode of
season 2 when you see the the White
Flame walking in uh like a few seconds
before you could see him and all of that
happened is when I was like just about
to think about like who could the White
Flame actually be cuz we don't know who
it is huh I was thinking about and I
realized before the game revealed it to
me I realized it before so I was quite
proud of myself but maybe it was really
obvious
already maybe it was
obvious you may like
it should I take that as an insult the
way you phrased
it people say I'm such a Negative person
but then I'm I enjoy these things and
give them a chance you know and ioy
enjoy them for what what it is so in
that way am I really a negative person
huh
Checkmate first on Netflix the show
Runners wanted to write their own
version instead of respecting the book
is BAS well that happens with a lot of
shows so you know it
is wait let help them of course going to
help dance with me
come on up guys what are you
doing what a
Madman what are we talking about Witcher
The Witcher on
Netflix
y let's go go let's
[Music]
go let's
finish don't sell coin oh that's so
funny last time I I talked about The
Witcher I thought the bar is not coming
back because I thought the time skip
was I thought there was a Time skip that
was affecting
that uh right after that I go back to
watch some more and the B shows up again
I'm like okay interesting it did seem
like a character that they probably
wouldn't want to miss out
on I feel like he's a little bit too
comedic for how serious I thought the
show was going to be
h
first first I even thought it must be it
must be a uh just a a relative like
a a few Generations down the line a
relative of the B and they just made it
played by the
same actor because they liked
him they're trying to bring him back in
a way no I guess just really not that
much time has
pass he's like a side kick yeah it's so
cute I like how sarcastic he is
[Music]
sometimes at the same time he's a little
bit of
a how to say a
whmp
sometimes uh you say he's G's Robin
honestly the first time I saw him in the
show
the only thing I could think of is oh my
God he's they're like Shrek and Donkey
like 100% cuz the first time they meet
they're walking down like they're
traveling they're walking down this road
and on the countryside and suddenly the
B is like yap yap yap yap yap exciting
Yap exciting Yap and then geralt is
like shut
up it's exactly like Shrek and Donkey
like
100% yep yep
yep witches are like
onions
yeah I found I found H what I found
weird is like
um when when yenfa was like
escaping with that dude who's usually on
the horse chasing the girl uh what was
his name kahir Amir I don't
know and then the that Arc is kind of
cool cuz you think oh he's he's nice I
guess but then when he returns and he's
with that witch and that Mage and like
they're back in their Kingdom and
suddenly like yeah it's just back to
normal I guess but like it's something
something weird about that
M your latest song is a a banger thank
you I don't know it was a bit a bit
weird of a character development to me
because some in some way he changed but
in some way he didn't
like the wild Hunt isn't a part that of
that yet
what uh wild Hunt is the is the is the
people in that other dimension right
that are
hunting her the
girl right I saw them at the very end at
the in the last uh episode they showed
them they were riding on their horse
horses coming for her for
Siri just for a
moment it's overall very interesting I
want to see more I wish this the third
season was like I wish you guys liked
the third season then I would watch it
with more confidence but now I just
watch it with no confidence and will not
put too much value into it
H the game is much better I'm excited
for it but you guys say it place after
the
show and and I guess that's good in a
way cuz then I'm not just playing the
same story again but then also like how
will I
know I'm just going to say read the
books How Will I Know How will I know
what's supposed to happen in season
3 is it really that different like
a different
story or are is it just a few
things break the books oh that's it
already you don't need to know anything
read or audio book
oh the German
ones why not the Polish
ones yeah I mean I guess I'm okay with
it
to a totally different story you don't
need to know it's so different that act
I know I
know it's faster to read the books and
then start the game but I like the
visuals of these shows I like watching
something before I go to sleep and and
watching something epic in particular I
don't just want to listen I don't just
want to read I want to see something on
my TV in bed cuddling my cats you
know I want to see
beautiful
um
Landscapes I want to see cute pretty
ladies cats cats would be great too in
nice
dresses you
know my biggest pet peeve about this
show is the the color contact lenses
though that's my biggest bad
teeve
cats are nice
[Applause]
dresses the whole Arc of The Witcher um
babying and training series was kind of
get out of my
to no the story and the characters too
and as long as I don't have knowledge
about the actual story I might enjoy the
show the first season anyway
right so I'm going to go in I'm going to
watch
it I'm going to watch it and then I'll
play the game but not anytime soon
probably cuz I got to play a little bit
I'm I'm not I'm
not like forcing myself to finish
dragon's bogma we're just going to play
it and see how it is at least I got the
game for free so now I don't have to
feel bad if I don't finish it don't have
to feel bad about my money look how he's
shaking and
trembling Willow
Merlin it's actually so crazy that it
took me so long to get into The Witcher
in the first
place I don't know why it's like exactly
up my alley isn't
it I don't know
[Music]
why
expecting another elen ring scenario do
I need to
dodge do I need to dodge a
lot
what
what a
sweep oh what who who who who I don't
see
anything
ah power
coup AOE is
[Music]
strong wow
wait what what what
what but you know the the suffering will
be soon over in June is when the new
season
of uh House of the Dragon comes
out I do wonder when the
new uh Lord the Rings thing comes out
they didn't announce anything yet right
but they keep on talking about it and
and I keep on getting like news articles
recommended about their
commitment yeah rings of power hopefully
never
yeah that show is a
bit
uh but I only say that because uh
there's some visuals that bother me
that's really it but I don't know I
think besides that I had a I had a good
time with
it want to see more of the dwarfs yeah
the
dwarfes the DS let
go shun oh
[Music]
yeah I really liked it I feel like the
complaints were
weird
although
rings of power
one see you're not the only
one I think Nissa also said she L to the
right steam cleaner let's go I have that
too I think that I think it's a yeah
it's a steam cleaner it's fun I've been
using it a bit more these
days it's quite fun to use I prefer it
over over um mopping the floor
traditionally
egg sty
what yeah I mean it's not like it's not
comparable to Lord of the Rings in terms
of quality but still it's still
something better than nothing I keep on
saying that what is this room so
Random everything with steam is
useful I I have a steam uh problem this
will be a good workout steamer I guess
you just call it a steamer for
clothes for ironing so to say
clothes I I know what what the make of
it cuz maybe I'm just using it
wrong but I just can't use it so well
it's like a little
gun I think maybe I'm just using it
wrong
I'm barely getting Level
UPS this dungeon
stinks like was I was even leveling more
outside oh that's the
way oh is this the item I missed in the
first floor like the like a uh a chest
in
the elevator part oh that that might
have been
important just skip normal enemies
durian
yeah I'll bury
you yeah but what am my what about my
OCD about cleaning the whole dungeon up
I need to look at
every nook and
cranny
otherwise it feels
incom oh he's strong he's a little bit
strong that's
RI
[\h__\h] let's get some HP
back
yeah I really don't like the show but
for some reason I still plan to watch
this second season you know another
thing that should come out this year
too is another season of um what was
it what was it uh what's it
called you know that other
show that wasn't as good as the books
yeah Wheel of
Time
because didn't they say like oh next
season December or something like that
and never
came or even before December was the
original plan I
think no I never remember that name I do
like the show but I never remember the
name and there's like uh the a lot of
similarities in uh like the whole
training the
Mages and being really strict and blah
blah blah
like I saw that in The Witcher and I saw
that in Wheel of Time and it like when I
saw it in the witch I had to think about
Wheel of Time so hard it was like oh
this is like exactly the same
way also
in I I see there are some male Mages in
The Witcher but it seems to be mostly
women which is also similar to Wheel of
Time what is what is that about is that
a thing in The Witcher where most why
why do mostly women get to be mes what's
that about explain that to me Wier
Geniuses feminine mystery women and
men's train ah it's just that they train
separately and they're called something
else or so men are
[Music]
warlocks a it's a very very old fantasy
TR yeah cuz uh a Witcher they can use
magic
too but they use it differently and The
Witcher they use those po
potions to become more
powerful I
guess but then there's that the Mage I
guess that is it called a m Mage even
that had intercourse witha right he's a
mate
right or is he
not science
[Music]
potion which R is natural witchers are
made for [\h__\h] up
training okay
okay yeah I know because I already went
to the part where they
um they figure out that her blood can
make more witchers and that witchers uh
need to drink this [\h__\h] not drink it or
maybe have it in injected in their veins
and then and then they can become a
Witcher but they also need to
[Music]
train what comes first the training or
the injection in their veins
part this gives good XP okay brace
yourself the
training H but then the P the injection
can fail
quite a a lot of times right like not
everybody withstands it from what I
understand so damn a lot of failure to
be
had training to survive
[Music]
imitation
El what's
[Music]
that there's there's still a few things
I'm confused about like Elders
are like an older version of elves or so
because the elves are really excited to
hear
about an elder still being
alive so
like an old version right like from but
but when when did Elders cease to exist
and why did when did what when when did
it become
elves don't understand that
[Music]
part ah thank you for listening toim
goodbye
whoa he and Company remain unfaced
AIT of spoiler for that in the winter
okay okay
okay there's still more things that I
can't think of right now that I was
questioning
I love the reaction of the that the
other M have had to the Kim
MV I saw I saw Ana no Ana only reacted
privately I think Zeta only and CI and
Calli retweeted it with no comment
though I think and bailes went Bor Bor
Bar B B Bar
B did I miss
one I still don't have have a reaction
from
LA right she couldn't
sleepa I actually also the past two days
I haven't been sleeping well
either I don't know why though I felt I
think like really uncomfortable in terms
of pillow position no matter how many
times I repositioned it and then also
I've been feeling a little bit hot
[\h__\h] and the day before I was just too
nervous the night before I think I was a
bit nervous and stressed
out oops what did I
do guys it's it getting very hot outside
yeah today was really hot
too which is exciting
though very
exciting April weather so
far R
positive oh he's W the water too go oh
yeah cuz you know what I told you April
weather here is in Austria it's known to
be like all over the place one day it's
hot one day it's cold one day it rains
one day one day it even snows one day it
hails one day it
sunshine sometimes within one day it
will have all of
that all of
it kind of
crazy wait this way right this way yeah
no no this
way
do I got a
treasure
no
okay I'm still only level 22 what the
hell is
now was that the boss or do we get the
boss now I guess that was the boss and
then there's
more
your final boss later on
okay it was being kind of random here
too about three days ago now it's cold
and rainy yeah it's it's definitely a
thing in Austria oh what the hell not
you
again
oh is that a leaf blower or a leaf
cutter around looks
fun
yes oh he's zooming
around a
don't don't stop getting so close to me
disgusting a la trimmer oh oh yeah my
mom has one like that I
think but she um had that lawn trimmer
graduate now she has a a proper better
lawn
mower graduate La
trimmer
yeah
retired is that
better he's been
retired I hope that a plance is a better
place no my mom's still it it's just not
being used which is so sad cuz that's
like Toy Story but with
tools come on Toy Story for
adults with
tools tool story oh my God I have to
bring that to some big Hollywood movie
studio are you
scared oh Tim Allan would love
it let's
go
don't resist so much
man wow always
cooking come oning
[Music]
it God damn it
yeah Disney don't steal
him Walmart what do you mean Walmart
that makes it sound so
cheap not
[Music]
cheap
everything Great Value
toys yeah no it has to be like a shop
that sells tools
I mean Ika might be selling some
[Music]
cool I mean like focusing on
tools Home
Depo no but it's just called tool
story you don't need to bring in Home
Depot in the
[Music]
name oh my God just
die
[Music]
house yeah B
house we don't have Home Depot there's a
shop that's called Depot I
think but it's like a a small store all
over the place like it's a chain but
it's like small and it uh just sells
like all kind of decoration
for your home
like you know vases and random
[\h__\h] I like it
though oh my God I found a dead end
yay the other way
please you're getting good skills and
Equipment check them out later oh
okay Ice Ice Baby poo chips with
salt o I still have some cashew
nuts I should eat
them more
ah guys for next week I have a Holo X
break collaboration set up and then for
the week after I have girls talk set
up and I'm trying to set up uh whole
talk for the week after
that so we got some good stuff going
right
[Music]
now something nice for every week a
little
treat every week oh we need to help a
guy
[Music]
again don't you it
up yeah I told you told you I'll be you
Pandora box
P why is your boxer trying to kill
me what is up with
that oh my God Griffin I killed L's
husband
[Music]
no what should I
do Dam
it ah yeah she did her for Life yeah
yeah yeah yeah she told me about her
plan with that is it done
now
oo I bet she was
cute I need to watch it ah did she
stream it on Twitch first then is she
uploading it on YouTube got to watch
it oh what the
[\h__\h] why are they so scattered
[Music]
and let me do
this I'm happy for her that she got to
do something in
freedy I think it's really hard for
Indies to get something like that going
so good for
her yeah I remember talking with her
about it and her her her bo bo let's go
boom boom we're so
[Music]
cute boie let's
go he you are my mama my
body and you are my mama my
body n the
[\h__\h] this this dude he knows what he's
doing oh 3 free
[Music]
damage Le to the
Le sh I missed and
he we both
missed waa that's a lot of damage it's
half my
HP
she
oh are we hitting with that there we
go
coconut right to the
Noggin uh-oh yo it's I perfect guard and
she still gets pretty much half
HP taken off oh my oh my it's time to
take this bastard
down
[Music]
man do I have something
like
waterbased electric
ice maybe he's weak to ice too oh he is
but ice is water I guess in this
case take this yeah that's big damage
got to use my Addam every want to know
why right cuz I keep on ignoring them so
I think that's
good
huh he keeps on blocking kidu's
advances good fight though like that uh
I didn't look now but it should have
given good exp cuz it felt really strong
so I hope it gave good
EXP
he was buff he had uh evasion buff and
he was still very strong though even
without the
EV
water
samp
yeah
that's what I'm talking about next level
we're making it to the next level with
this
one so many Robo disc what the [\h__\h] can
I do with them rewards
okay time for some
nuts is there anyone besides me who
watches Cody Co by the way cuz he has
this one friend who's quite the
personality who's called nut
they released a song Yesterday just like
me with cimo that we both released a
song
Yesterday you
do and it's so funny cuz it's like such
a comedy song in a
way you what call Call let's go go watch
that video of him and nut their new
collaboration song it's kind of kind of
dope they're not like good singers or
anything but it's a a
pretty I mean if I were someone who goes
to parties to discos and [\h__\h] to
clubs then that song would probably go
really
hard they're just so funny in the MV
there's like so many references to all
these Jubilee and clut videos that they
keep on
watching so many references it's so
funny
who what's up all that
fruit what is that is that a is that a
um a Kaba is that um what's a cab again
no is that a is that um a squash so is
Caba right cuz squash is Kaba a type of
Kaba pumpkin pumpkin
right pumpkin squash is a pumpkin
right bit g e you there
should listen to Young no thank you wow
you look like you look like Lord
farquar the what was his name
shees king of Lings you know you you you
just look like Lord
Park this is to
[Music]
e wait there's other
guys oh he's so close actually you think
I'm stupid
Burger King yeah he does also look like
that now that you say
it oh what happened did I just I turned
Auto on
[\h__\h] oh
no wait what no now it's
it what's happening I thought it was on
because uh he did something on his own
but then I actually turned it on it was
off this ISO easy what is happening was
he just joining in SC was that a thing
that they
[Music]
did how can I there we go that's a nice
line [\h__\h] I
miss why do I need why do I
need
uhoh you think I'm stupid no
bite they're corrupt these security
guards are corrupt as
[\h__\h] your time you chickening out on
me are you wahing out on
me he's weak
o we shall take that to our
[Music]
Advantage money is a great Mage
Jobing
it you got to love
money money money
[Music]
money right in a nut
dance
oh [\h__\h] the other one was next
though
[Music]
oopsie what can I do what can I do
besides col ha kick
uh maybe we can try
this I miss again I'm so useless why am
I here what am I
doing no you're not bringing some more
minions in
no okay now I understand I have to take
you down as soon as
possible this one you take the the one
that's closest to
you and here
we woo almost dead almost got him and
king of bling excuse me I will be taking
your crown and you're calling me King
you going
to why you ruin my cool
[Music]
moment you going to
hear he's probably not worth using T te
on
huh
I
Crown now you must kneel
down oh why must you
frown do you not like my
gown trying to continue my
r
resist go oh yeah now we're going to
[Music]
[Applause]
town hurry up let's
go I guess yeah we can so far I've been
also I've always been
using some kind of Emoji for my songs
it's got to be the crown
yeah because otherwise I was thinking
about you know a Kim Chimera some people
say Chimera Chima representing Emoji
which is obviously like free animals but
that's a lot of
emojis
so the crown is fine Crown is
[Music]
good
I don't want to waste her mp on
you there we
Gove crown for Banger than
kill
yeah Japanese Bros also have beening
it everyone loves
it
yeah but my only grapple attack was 30
MP I don't I'm not going to waste it on
him it worked
anyway
okay I'm still going to
see I'm trying to finish the dungeon
anyway this room
again that's confusing I'm having a
little there a Vu
here don't waste the food if I can't eat
it it's being
wasted going to cry for
my oh dead meat why are you still alive
I thought you were dead
meat false
advertisement I'll sue
[Music]
you oh [\h__\h] I missed it but that's
okay then you wish you were actually
dead when I'm suing you
[Music]
wait I don't know if I have a hair in my
mouth or
not I guess
not it was on my
fingers oh so many
nuts
so salty
yummy
ah another hair
somewhere where's some me
[Music]
ouch why is there so much fruit here oh
my God this gives me Super Mario
Sunshine
Vibes I just want to gobble it up and
summon Yoshi
Yoshi
when I see fruit wow it's just like
Super Mario
Sunshine you're making fun of me aren't
you you're making fun of me I have this
feeling J you
addicted what the [\h__\h] directional
sense oh already already have it
huh
move on
faster have you ever played Raymond
origins there's a world that is just
trying I I played a Raymond game I don't
know which one when I was a
child it may have been Origins but even
then I wouldn't remember that world in
particular but I loved rain I'll
you I think it was fre
I'm not the nameless guy
again come
on Santa
Clauses is it that time of the year
again we're making it to North Pole with
this
one Sor right I you know how it
[Music]
is yeah
oh
yeah you playing volleyball I'm a meme
parent who talk me well just the
internet internet teaches me the
memes come
on
FAL hey
nice try to be hit with the kids no that
was not my motivation at all not at
all to the
Le yeah it was a great game just like
Spyro Raymond and Spyro oh a present for
me they don't give a rip I don't give a
rip I want it what's
inide a road strike the [\h__\h] drones are
not allowed here excuse me that's
illegal I
will report
you the Yakuza
police REM make the Spyro was fantastic
well you know I would have lik to play
it if I wasn't being constantly annoyed
about
it
is also Su I don't trust the
sui are you okay it's not safe for you
to be here thank you very much pleas
take this thank you I rescued the
missing person let's
go I think I'm comfortable saying is my
favorite song of yo like for real I've
been getting so
many like feedbacks like that people
telling me is your favorite
[Music]
now and
also like people saying normally they
don't like those people that normally
don't like cop sound also still they
really like this one which is surprising
too so damn we really hey scary
e no I'm leaving this room no no no
let's have a good let me
go I really
what oh my God I really struck a gold
mind with this song I think in terms of
everybody likes
it
and like there were certain songs that
people had as my as their favorite song
of me for a long time like do you fox or
whatever or recently W or so for
example so that's
changing when when I already have so
many like certain
favorites for you guys that seem to be
really hard
to push off its
thr I don't know I feel really happy
that I made something where you guys
feel like I I topped
myself feels like quite the
achievement oh you don't have to pick a
number one I'm just happy that people
really like this one I haven't heard
anything negative about the
song like it's crazy that even even the
fans of me that say like they don't like
K-pop which is fine on its own that
statement there's nothing wrong with
that if that's not your style of music
that's totally fine but even those
people even those people really
enjoyed Kim a lot and say like oh I'm
confused why do I like this so much it's
really
dope oh good
morning maybe I'm just
like M brainwashed you guys into liking
this kind of
music
but let's not
downplay oh Hawaiian logger it's not
downplay is an actually really Dope song
and I did sing quite well in it I did my
best can I really go did I look at
everything yeah and then turned out
great
too Mutual room really
effective it's not just a booty yeah I
think so too but the booty is helping it
reach uh meme
potential which is a good thing we like
to
meme let me check out this side first
this
time dead end
no
H nice
find equal standing for me they're both
so D fantastic oh my god oh
no well thank you take your
life you guys were also praising the
tracking and all that you guys are just
not really seeing what I'm seeing I'm
actually the surprised but relief
uh there are some parts that you can
actually clearly see there's especially
one
part um that kindo even uploaded as a
gif
today the part with the two
waas the black and white Wawa dancing in
a
miror
manner uh it's the the crotch it was
shaking while I was on my
knees look at my crotch and then you
will
know don't SP to me
that but it was it was shaking there and
I don't know if kanu didn't notice but
it was pretty pretty
obvious I just thought he couldn't fix
it but now that he made it into a gift
chft I'm like maybe he didn't see
it that one is a bit embarrassing for me
cuz that one's the most obvious I mean
the other ones we mostly just try to um
go around by
like when the legs are shaking we do a
closeup or just a different non dancing
scene you know whenever they're not
shaking we got to take advantage of
it I already found the
elevator did I go but then there's
probably another person that needs to be
rescued
somewhere nice weapon
though no it was not intentional at all
I was I was honestly all this time I was
trying my best to like dance in a very
stable
way hold on but it still comes out so
wobbly
believe don't move so
F but it was mostly fine I'm I'm happy
with the outcome
mostly I asked Kana ubu if he thinks he
can make a Youtube short for the chorus
at
least it won't be as high quality as my
others that I recorded in like am studio
for
example because of yeah extense quality
just not being as good good but it's
still good
enough I hope so we we'll get a little
short at least for people who want to
see at least the force maybe for a dance
challenge who
knows am is better am yeah am is better
but it's easier to get the X sense
running that's for
sure you to get it running and also I
don't have to fly to America for it
so finger tracking though I think is
better with
mine while still not perfect
surprisingly with
$6,000 worth of
gloves I feel like uh it's a bit better
than what I get at am am's place cuz we
still haven't had finger tracking really
figured out to be
honest we tried a few times but it just
doesn't really work that well at
all um he's kind of
dying oh there it is that's what I
wanted to
see
your body of work really is
extraordinary emphasis on the word body
joking aside you deserve to thank you I
tried really hard with what uh I
had the
class ooh all
right the power ring right now gives me
extra attack
I don't know if I want to change any of
this I want to
see ah these are new wa but then we're
not shiny anymore this is the self
upgraded one this is a new one that's
still stronger okay all right shake
those Dorian shake
them
I you're just going to be barehanded cuz
you're so
cool maybe I'll give him something else
the five HP is not
really that
[Music]
crazy I don't know what else I don't
want to think too much about this is
anything here good increase I should put
this on you for now remind me to switch
it
oh that's the one thing that stood out
to me all right let's
go resist no we're good we're
good H now I don't need any any MP
here sick look powerful he's got axes
now no more sickles oh look at those
what are
those this I think I can still some
improve the
tracking because kind of ubu doesn't
have these wobbles when he uses it so
there should be room for
improvement I'll figure it
out figure it out
guys come on
it maybe I'll try
this
wow
hope you like drowning the company I'm
trying to uh I've been trying to write
up an email before the stream actually
not just regarding the tracking but also
regarding live
streaming I have a oneyear
license that cost
$2,900 that should give me the option to
stream but I can't find the option to
stream so I'm like um excuse me
take a in
the I don't know I asked um the
G they're helping me right now look
exent we're in contact
now wo nice
TRD nice try with the
Trident and they showed me with what
icon
what icon I should be seeing in my
interface and I don't see that icon the
one for live
streaming where is
it take this holy
ouch cute diving suit though if I get my
diving line
I'm going to get myself an outfit just
like that I'm going to
be my diver outfit I'm going to put
gemstones and all kind of cute ocean
stuff all over
it fan of waa in this outfit this SW
that with the Aloha shirt I feel like I
must have seen
something
feel I
did but I'll gladly see more of
[Music]
it cuz it's really cute isn't
it it's so perfect with the swimsuit now
I can put shirts over like this and
there will not be any
weirdness with cloves underneath it's
perfect
we can do this more often in the future
like aloha
shirts think think of the things we can
do to accentuate the
tatas so versatile
yeah wait was there was there a healing
thing
here no okay
[Music]
free healing
this it seems like we have arrived at
lios here we
go
let's freaking go bring it on give me
some
exp
n I'll sue
you all right time to get lowered up the
top dog and his penalty boxers what a
cute
Trio not okay not
uh let's see if we can buff ourselves
here oh
yeah our magic is raised even though
actually why did I do that only one
person uses magic right or is any skill
magic I forgot is this considered
magic come at oh he's weak against this
nice [\h__\h] I missed it
skills with Al theist or magic okay
[Music]
okay how close are these people not
close at
all he's weak to fire okay boss is weak
to fire his minions are weak to
water oh [\h__\h] why I always get
this I pushed way too late it's okay we
still did good damage
bye-bye you have time out now go stand
in the corner think about what you've
done think about your life choices oh he
missed is the smell of the durian that
confused
him come
on M okay we have
fire wait our duam are not with fire
anymore
huh so I have no element now or
what no way saw the durian coming
uh-oh oh
okay they're neutral
no oh no
M yeah good
enough try me how about a little Clipper
to the lier for
you this time I hit it 392 let's
go huge damage do I mean huge hu huge
huge huge
damage no why do you go further
away n NE the [\h__\h] that's not how that's
not what I was hoping to do oh no
ow
huge ah [\h__\h] whoa Tommy
zawa I thought I was close enough for
that
one no wake up Tommy I need you
no need to waste another flipper to the
lier I
[Music]
think okay we're kind of low on
HP kind of need to heal right
now time for a hot
dog
yummy
oh you little [\h__\h]
die I wasn't quite enough oh no oh
no
yes Tommy come
on we need
you there fire on
[Music]
him at least I got both of
them that's something that's a
positive
ow nice T though
items to help Tommy he he he has to
learn how to get himself out of these
situations on his
own you'll figure it
out
ouch now KAS is stunned so Tommy better
get back to us
yeah he's back he's back and he's ready
to attack with
[Music]
fire oh yeah
nice and now
maybe oh [\h__\h] he still stand yeah that
was to be
expected
[Music]
M should have maybe done that
earlier pretty
strong nice will power
[Music]
debuff
we do
it what you
do it's too late for that now your AI is
not very smart is
it cing yourself in your last
turn it's been about time completed
sector one of Hawaiian hun metal shin
guards to protect with protective metal
followed into them
cool now we can play the main
story my S detect that you've wined
quite a way Z I'm impressed currently I
am approximately 30% CH sorry but I'll
have to rely on you a bit that's
honestly that's quite a lot consider
in what I've heard about you in your
batteries fairy lay a FL flower ornament
had to be inhabited by CH fa is
cute cute cute c c cute little meyy mey
oh wa it was already here
okay
so
[Music]
uh
increases item drops uhuh talk to him
again for re
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] all right here we go guys wait let
me pick up some
trash keep it
[Music]
shiny then I need it
H oh ra no I do not care about
raids a good fortune let's
go fruit
[Music]
juice I love fruit juice I love fruit I
love fruit juice I'm a simple woman I
love fruits I love fruit juice we're
doing
great and in here
let's tell them that we're ready to go
and ready to
rumble time for some nuts maybe cut
scene
wow Exile
Exile M fujia we've been expecting you
oh let's go
is that thanks wait that's someone else
no is it is oh she looks so
different I thought it was an
imposter
she she all that hair back all the
[Music]
way look at that
those
beautiful he always
wears right this way Miss fujia
thank more English please
Tommy sorry Tommy you the Third
[Music]
Wheel
cute he's the K of the group hey I'm
usually really cool even though I'm a
third wheeler I'm usually like really
popular within my
groups I'm the one I'm the cool one I'm
the glue I'm the one who calls the shots
often I'm the one that everyone is
influenced
by and may be a third wheel but I'm I'm
the heaviest wheel of all of them and
the
biggest
no he's
[Music]
dead look at her look at her
earrings
you mean Alejandro
Alejandro Al Alejandro Al Alejandro
thank you for waiting floor 7 and a half
s a
half
mysterious so cool look at those Great
Gatsby Vibes oh my
[Music]
God
wa what the [\h__\h] that's some of that is
really tacky the bike is so
tacky
M that's
[Music]
tacky he's so
cute
hey
handsome don't look there it looks like
plastic
to not because of the size but because
of the
texture looks like a
Barbie
mommy sorry
Mommy looking respectfully
for it's all for
Ichibon oh yeah ball ice
cubes
nice
do you guys like this kind of hair so I
don't really like it it looks cool a lot
of celebrities do it but I don't really
like
it this
one having your hair all oiled back
for this
length M it's okay it's all right not my
favorite
though
[Music]
for
Commander how do you
[Music]
know
well understandable that they have that
Tech
oh yeah can you really
F amongst other
super what he yapping
about
cheeks are sucked
in gold fat
removal thank you so
[Music]
much
it's not like I have
hands
prage
what was the point of this if we're
coming
anyway like in terms of script
writing was the
point just to embarrass ourselves about
the spy
stuff damn I thought I could lean
back
oh oh that was fast
hi
look you know you know how do I pause
again like this yeah you know that
that's like you know you know when
you're like late to something and you
want to show the person that's waiting
for you that you totally like you know
trying to be there as fast as possible
so when you arrive until the point where
you're arriving you just like walk
normally cuz you're going to [\h__\h] die
if you run all the way but right before
you arrive and they can see you that's
when you run that's when you run so that
you arrive a little bit out of breath
yeah just show show the act of running
and yeah that's how you do it no I oh
yeah I've been sorry I'm late I've been
running all all all the way
here sorry need to catch my
breath
is that how you guys do it
too I mean I I'll still if I'm really
late to something I don't want to be
late to I'll still try my best to like
you know run every now and then on my
way but I can't run the whole way I'm
just literally going to die my asthma is
going to kill me so run a few steps walk
walk walk walk walk run a few steps walk
walk walk walk you full Sprint the whole
way shees weird flex but
okay guess I'm too honest I run all the
time really speed walk is the Strat yeah
yeah yeah I just speed walk a
lot as fast as I can without dying
yeah good night see you tomorrow ah good
night goodbye thank
you you pull this on
us usually I'm just like at home so it
doesn't really
happen
oh you see he really
nice this
dude oh thank
you you really want
to
F it's so fat I don't want to try to
catch it but I almost could it's flying
around so
slowly froggy wa Go Get It Go Get It
froggy
waab yeah long they don't let us gamble
at all there's this whole gambling Arc
and they don't let me gamble a single
second everything fake everything's like
prescripted let me
Blackjack I'm going to hit the 21 TR
me oh it's so
empty so
empty why him don't roast
him doesn't even have a keyboard or
mous
the monitor is not even connected to
anything
anyway trying to tell me is like
aess
monitor n it doesn't look like
one
doesn't look like a mieer but yeah
that's might that might
be want us
to
I guess
so what are you
looking like
why
you want to
fight oh
[\h__\h] straight to the boss fight oh
[Music]
okay there was
no like dungeon like thing going on like
usually guess we had our own
[Music]
dungeon
oh hey let me do
something don't let me gamble don't let
me
fight where does it
end ha one [\h__\h] pen
oh a weapon
okay what do we
have maybe start with some Buffs but
they're kind of
far ah that could work that could work
that could
[Music]
work yeah I think it I think it worked
on everybody oh except for k
that's
[Applause]
okay he's raising his evasion
too yeah is okay
so Longo is weak to
fire a tire
tumbler do it we can get all the
[Music]
Minions look where are the cables now eh
I don't see any I don't see a computer I
don't see CA anything it's all fake it's
all set
up w we so close to
you wait oh it's stop is that
moving weak
200 yeah okay so it's Fire and Water
okay pretty easy and
[Music]
distinction I wonder if he's going to
call more minions cat when I killed
you well this one's
dead
fire
flying I couldn't block a single one I
was so off timing of
Rhythm what what is this
camera what was
that
[Music]
apping
weapons no need for healing yet boost
should I boost should I give
more more
Buffs actually h k doesn't even need it
right he doesn't use Magic
more Pops more
Pops listen to kimar so good can use it
for clean up study clean up study maybe
not for study for clean up I can
[Music]
imagine what wait where is he
here damages enemies in a torent oh it's
a
area let's do this one get some HP
too I
miss baby
[Music]
knock I love
you
[Music]
baby oh we have to heal
him wa the the title of the OST is
German or did you just translate from
me we
attack look at him dancing wobbling
that's how my that's how my this is
exactly how my emotion capture look
sometimes no not like that
like like
this it's actually German that's so
weird why not like Chinese if
anything can't
decide that was
good
uhoh perple
rate yeah he's
weak
we normal attack should be
fine yeah thanks
ichan you are ichan in my
heart oh yeah oh
yeah n Al okay he does have a [\h__\h] ton
of HP wow I wonder I wonder if
this if like fire spinning actually does
more damage than Soul Capture Soul
Capture just costs more MP because it
gives me HP back which is a nice little
extra and I wonder if this
also like it's just more expensive cuz
it's an AOE and on one person it might
not be so strong
you mask of
fertility
[Music]
yeah I mean why not we can do that that
sounds fun I never did that before I
think
oh oh
K okay he's got some fire
too damn
defense strong effortless
[Music]
Elegance oh raising evasion oh no isn't
that the second time he's raising his
evasion let's
go t him no can't can t Team miss or is
it guaranteed this time it didn't
miss tag team another one it's here we
go get time
oh that's that's not much but it's
okay at least it's
cute uh-oh oh
no oh [\h__\h]
poison let's
gole plus problem well plus need paddle
damages hold DS and applies your board's
attributes
yeah but maybe
unnecessary no it's [\h__\h]
evasion uh-oh oh
[\h__\h] he's enemy is next
so what the he have he has Soul Capture
his own HP is not so bad the one that's
pretty gu is our
[Music]
lady we're just got to hope that he
doesn't attack her
next I'll risk ooh
yeah nice the good thing is the tag team
always oh oh [\h__\h] gives me a b bow BFF
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] uh uh uh
buttons no I'm so late I'm so
slow we're halfway bro guys oh that was
fast I mean the the the time is little
I'm
slow oh
[Music]
Pap the blood is so
shiny
nice
[\h__\h] not
[\h__\h]
sheer no heal or what
gradually we have that too though we
have it to oh she that was a good heal
actually now uh shall we heal everybody
we could do that um with coconut
shower stand
here
[Music]
yeah why not why not there's a good good
amount of
heal
250 OU
ouch
250 while Kido disdained senseless
murder he's a cunning Marksman
nonetheless just go never misses
perfect never misses he's weak to piss
still it's made for this
[Music]
moment I pressed it too early but this
is good this is good I should use it
again and again and again and again and
again uh fire
right I too am we me
too more evasion
is your head a little bit uh
[Music]
Broken
Oh Come [\h__\h] evasion oh my God need
more skills that ignore
evasion can I de up him I hold
on I can lower his willower a little bit
I can boost my evasion
more let's try that
then I
missed so probably won't low his
willpower will it but we're going to be
fine
oh out
sh the way they fall down like rag dolls
always oh my
no my no no
no
no ah my
EMP I didn't think of that I didn't
realize I was so low
already
yeah the thing is even if I use an item
I won't get to use it for a while but
okay
[Music]
70 100 should be
okay
it be dodging a
lot
mind
agility h
H
oh or where I heal
everybody nearby Bros and Lady
Bros Anor should
hit
okay oh cute but I was I was blinded by
the cuteness and Miss for my
timing it's good
the blinding is pretty helpful I think
M oh yeah 3 53 yeah okay okay now we're
talking I steal your
soul Daran in your
face thanky bom yo easy okay okay no
need to
get his MP
up oh I didn't need to heal
his give me my item back I feel
regret the mouth guard is that a good
Island are you okay
bro
you know who we
[Music]
are was that really the fastest option
okay the one piece of furniture
fore
speee
sh me with the freaking
sword It's Kind weak
for yeah tell
us spit it
out will kill you
not doesn't kill people but let's not
tell him
that yeah really
I know when a
sweetheart I can't take these guys
seriously I can't take him
seriously they're all
dorks
except
for
lame they say owner in Japanese which is
just an English
word
[Music]
fore
for shut the [\h__\h] up no one
cares slice your
fruit Tommy slap him
not if you're
dead
you got you got what it takes Tommy no
you
don't going
die but okay I guess she's fine with
that wo look at that diving
form must have been an Olympic
diver or jumper from
the bouny
[Music]
thing
yeah
oh yeah he be loyal wow that's that's
honestly really
dumb there's nothing good about that
kind of
loyalty why you waste your life like
that they like oh no no
no
dump reinforced Windows you would hope
so
[Music]
fore
fore that's a [\h__\h] stop
signal do we need to help
you oh we're so
nice
for he SW nice like everybody's so nice
what the hell want to run to the
elevator outside the casino I should
hurry up and go after him but then again
a whole lot just went down maybe I
should go play some blackjack
is it an
option is it an option no
no come
on that would be so funny though like I
mean the game does tell you to maybe
take a moment and
prepare but it does stop you from
gambling
unbelievable invisible walls
everywhere oh she's selling stuff okay
man yeah what about the black
jack I need Blackjack to function
[Music]
properly do we need any of
this well the rest is
whatever
pepperoni the one proper food they have
is the
pepponi oh my God a the
pepponi I don't need
anything
but we're switching the ankle weights
to this was the EXP one right yeah oh it
it reduces his max MP greatly which is
one of the reasons why we had a little
MP with him decreases MP cost of skills
oh okay not for him cuz he barely uses
MP generally speaking increases items
[Music]
obtained ah
damn maybe defense I I
know
spe what uh you think that's good for
him well a lot of the time we just use
the he's good enough to be using stuff
like that you
think okay we're going to keep that on
him for for a little while then okay and
uh
the MP thingy maybe we can give to him
uh Magic nullifies oh yeah let's get rid
of that why why are we still wearing
this
um this one for him for
[Music]
example oh more money more items you use
that on
him wait I need healing do I not get
healed anywhere I have to heal myself or
is there healing behind this
door good night Teno are you saying that
because you're going to sleep or are you
saying that because you think I'm going
to die in this
battle no healing
station well then I guess I'll do it
myself yeah yes yes yes
what
[Music]
yes what the [\h__\h] look at all these
emojis um I
[Music]
what wow so
go um
going to use up all these crappy items
first
okay
and
okay looks good stock up on it I'm
fine I'm fine see I have like six 4 1
three this one I don't really
[Music]
need
no I that's healing the only thing maybe
like one of
these I don't really need any of
this bur they cheap no it's all
expensive okay I'll do you I'll do you
this okay but this is 500 dude 500 per
bottle
no we're done we're done let's
go I don't need to heal be so
fine little guy he a little guy
oh
they they all have the same hairstyle
all the same suit
intimidating
[Music]
no boy little
guye
man he's fallen from gra
quickly
F oh Kitty
kicks W the
[Music]
music
all right little
[Music]
buff Ence of
sweeping is anybody close yeah he's
close
nice
whoa look at look at their
HP is this really what I was supposed to
be so scared of or is there another
proper boss coming I guess there's a
second round over there
[Music]
but
oh
[\h__\h] F you're the
best auto
tune really strong sometimes
too not worth it not worth
it
yeah but
the sometimes autotune is a stylistic
choice nice double
guard nice baby you're
triple
[\h__\h] sometimes I can do it sometimes
I just
rock
oh man he guarded
[Music]
nice
M good night to you we have a big sleepy
sleeping party sleeping
over oh I should have switched to the
fast fighting
[Music]
style all right next group please uh as
we can see they have not been doing
anything back there they just been
staring into
nothingness the group it that looked
very different just a moment
ago cruel as
ever
for
who he did I'd hope
so
B so you trust the one you called your
enemy before
us we are indeed more
trustworthy we do be trustworthy of
these people oh
police W left the hotel with Kasa and
his crew they're heading south
where's an enemy make sure you tell the
cops they went North oh he was not an
enemy or was he over here someone just
fell out the window oh just come quick
I've never seen anything like
this over here I'm so concerned that's
why I speak like this somebody just fell
out the window even though I was
standing here this whole time I'm
telling you about it just
now
for
ooh
okay y goodbye police
good good job
police what are you come here for
police no these are not the
bar
such a
weird big nothing behind it now can't
even big talk
anymore let's
go oh sheesh those Claws and they got
some Chop Chop nice knives I got some
nice knives only too I I did buy them
thinking I want to use some really nice
sharp knives for a cooking
ASMR and I did test them out and they're
really nice wow it feels great to cut uh
through like herbs and stuff and it's
actually cutting and these ones I can
sharpen because the ceramic knives I
cannot
sharpen
even though they're so
pretty I wish I could sharpen
them yeah I don't know about good
cutting sounds because I'm I'm bad at
like chopping
properly I can't do the thing where you
protect your fingers where you tuck them
in so my chopping on hers you don't
really hear
[\h__\h] well you should be able to hear
when I chop when I cut for like I don't
know B peppers for
[Music]
example
[\h__\h]
no as long as you're not cutting your
fingers off today I cut my finger but
with a piece of paper
and it was a hell fresh recipe paper so
I think I can now sue him
I [\h__\h] what's wrong with
me no you could have died why did I mess
it
up oh man let's try this
here where are all the
enemies
not May
maybe over
there swooping in and out oh oh
no he swooped out cuz I went
fast I only got two now oh
[Music]
man use that to Blackmail
them
yeah that's what I
thought oh no the no I got some
penis they're hurting me y can't be do
something they're hurting
me
nice I'm just a
chicken I don't know what you want from
me I don't know what you want me to do
I'm just a
chicken I literally can't do [\h__\h] I'm
just a
chicken a
man no it's just ping what you guys
would
[Music]
say
wa what was
that
[Music]
the way she walks will never not be
funny to
me ah you also again almost killed him
why did you
[Music]
not
man anyway so far this was really not
worth buying items over
don't get it guys why were you so
dramatic you didn't know what was coming
did
you it was no
[Music]
B just a lot of little
minions chicken scallop
dramatic yeah I guess so cute
oh no no no no no not the ailla don't
cut the aill ca okay at least it wasn't
the a
s whoa nice kick
Tommy and
kha that's what we call a
k
fore fore
fore
h where'd she get that from when she
didn't even have a
bag and no
pockets was it padding in her
[Music]
bra
sry we're in the freaking
jungle
foree my God
[Music]
no you're not going to die from Little
stabby in the leg I mean your leg might
not be fine but you
going a little
bruise unless it was
poison I know he can bleed out from that
but he's obviously not bleeding
out
does look like heeding
[Music]
out how
conveni find his
people a
cult only cult people do this kind of
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait isn't that
the the
guy
yo I knew didn't I know he was sussy and
the whole P kind of thing was syssy like
a
cult yeah he was always kind of
suck I don't remember if I called it but
I feel like I
did the connection makes sense
everybody's looking her and he was
working with
her yo now we
know now we
[Music]
know orphanage wait a second
that that orphanage comment brings up
something I watched recently that was
funny
okay
I can't quote it I don't remember
it good
[Music]
enough
W pick
fence
nice
mom
that's the treasure the other girl is
the treasure
then why did we steal
her interesting
no he really
died oh come
on it doesn't look that small to me but
I guess she
is
enhance because
cult Oh Oh I thought he was dead now
he's still
alive welcome
fore
speee
forch for
[Music]
Fore wait
he
for for
ah
fore
for
for Fore
fore
for H
for
[Music]
C cult cult bring the C bring the cult
Bel cult
alarm
cult
[Music]
yeah that's what we want to know
you he's serving
cult
for
foree
[Music]
fore
M literally an
actor
fore
spee
ah the idol
girl
[Music]
oh
small wait kid you son also has a child
surprise just like The Witcher and he
also is also Grump always grumpy and
also has gray hair now and he also talks
in his low voice and he's also like
always monotone and he's also really
strong and he's also the
protagonist and he's also raising that
child to be strong and something special
he is The
Witcher oh my
God he's a mutation kid you of
Rivia Wier brain rot geralt of
kamoto they're both DS oh my god future
yaku a protagonist no future Witcher
actor when the next one decides to drop
his
role
with all these child
abductions oh is this Barracuda that
looks
like oh [\h__\h] they found
us is
you can put him on the thumbnail no I'll
put
oh you speak too [\h__\h]
loud
does that tree look so
comy
fore
how nice of
him
so
Dum oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh oh no he's going to burn the
forest oh [\h__\h]
oh okay that's kind of um yeah insane
and smart and
wild
um yeah yeah let's make it
bright y
fire SP light the
flame turn the night into day don't stop
don't stop
cold oh
[\h__\h] no not the nature of
Hawaii burn it that's really [\h__\h] up
man Bur the whole forest for this oh
[\h__\h] in the middle of the city
too that it's more like a park
but
rest no
no
he still got the camera glasses
on oh so
ready and that
[Music]
was
wa I thought he would be more
like when he takes
Cod I didn't think I would be able to
fight yam
again he you want me to use that I don't
know I was going to do something
[Music]
else where are we uh uh where are we
you're so close get get out of my face K
was there wait where's
Tommy am I blind is Tommy here wait
Tommy's gone
oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
uh oh that's a lot of enemies for just
us I left to get the van he's never
coming back he got the milk he's getting
the milk he never coming back uh-oh uhoh
uhoh we just need some AOE oh
[\h__\h] nice nice
evasion
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
um
uhuh that's how that works
okay like this should be
good Fight Fire with
Fire we water [\h__\h] yeah that makes sense
okay maybe I shouldn't fight fire with
fire maybe I should fight fire with
water ever thought about
that uh so can we do a little bit of
this on uh no no no no yeah yeah yeah on
you you seem fairly
close Okay a bit
disappointing they weren't overall close
enough to
fire in the water
why oh [\h__\h] no water in why
why I'm blocking it's not doing it ow
ow the new
one should I do them the favor and use
it oh he he is weak against fire but I
guess the boss is weak against
one oh I got a nice
achievement
oh
okay standing eily still
okay good for
you break it down for these spaes maybe
increase your
own should we do the AOE they're all so
close to each
[Music]
other want to move a bit more thank
you I missed I wasn't sure when it's
coming it was so slow actually but nice
big
ay so nice of him to move
fur so nice Okay can we get proximity
with him
yeah yeah we like to see
it AI
[Music]
manipulation don't really look need
healing yet I think by the looks of our
current status
[Music]
the
hippies that's good enough and we
lowered his willpower what does that do
[Music]
again
for magic defense oh okay okay
okay that one's pretty easy to dodge you
would
think well at
least it's time to
[Music]
heal
um
ooh a o e a o e a yeah I was going to
heal uh coconut out but everyone's
far ah come here here no D Dy
toy that's really sad I got to use some
items on is there something that heals
everybody 400 HP for everybody is a bit
overkill andp for the entire
[Music]
party no I don't really have what I
want ah oh yeah okay I guess I can
change uh
Target
right ah they still kind of I yeah I
guess now I could heal those
two wait do I get healed too cuz I
walked over
yes okay okay okay I walked into the
distance
[Music]
nice do I take down this small
boy do I need MP for it do you guys
think I can do it without the
skill I can do it about the
[Music]
skill
yeah
oh I I even get the the weapon from the
ground okay yeah burn burn
alive baral Lun oh no he's baral he must
have seen Chima must have pressed four
on my
MV
[Music]
oh yes jet powered
yes um I'll do another over
[Music]
he but we got him like halfway
through maybe a little gun action
[Music]
or
when did we get essence of gun I don't
know a while
[Music]
ago okay it's time for our strongest
water
attack be
[Music]
tuna you like Beast fish huh Big Tuna
isn't that what uh is that from the
[Music]
office somebody calls someone Big Tuna
somewhere I
think do do yeah Jim is Big Tuna yeah
Andy call on that a I love
Andy Andy is one of my favorites from in
the office I think speak
tun he's pretty much
dead but I'll give him another water
attack you're dead Yoo Y how many more
times will you be defeated by
me he really loves
me I feel
flattered you re watching you office
right now
I'm like always
rewatching always
constantly need a
[Music]
hug
did she just
suggest leaving him to
die oh oh my God calm
down
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah
right that's
why we learned he has canc right
now they're going to kill
[Music]
you no you little
[\h__\h]
no can
you no maybe they'll be like whatever
he's already dying I leaving
alone have some
[Music]
mercy
dude he's you recogn he's literally
dying in front of you and you oh my god
with the Crowbar while he's
down holy
[\h__\h] oh my
God [\h__\h]
y
but it's okay he has plot
armor Doom
posting
can't believe he told him to read a
room
[Music]
for pretty
sure pretty sure
for the first time you're watching
it oh my God so
special
same
go find someone else maybe the guy in
the wheelchair I'd rather stay here
because I'm going to I'm going to be out
of breath after a few stairs so you
better go with the one who's literally
in a wheelchair or something anything
anyone but me is what he's
saying y's Turf uh is in a night Square
near Anaconda Center okay
nah surf and turf how about that but
let's not be Hasty charge in head first
and Y is sure to get to jump on us I
know we don't got much time but let's do
this
[Music]
right like Tommy said we'll need a plan
if we're going after y I wonder what
everyone else is
thinking we should we talk to them last
I saw K on he was coughing a blood got
to get him out of there that's what
you're thinking wow helpful you know I
thought for sure you'd leave me behind
back there don't R too far into it it's
just how it worked out well thank you
anyhow you saved my life you ASO maybe
but poana still has your son right yeah
and I'm going to get him back and once I
do I'm going to ride ring that snake
brght his neck oh
[\h__\h] you are a little p u SS y
and the girl issues with the pic's cult
cult they really call it cult now been
using local gangs to track them down on
that note why is the DJI faction looking
for her don't tell me you're after L
too I sent a query to the high UPS about
it but I've yet to hear a reply oh you
don't
know I doubt they're going to get back
to
you okay so I didn't get very much input
K sounds regarded some as a big shot
legendary Yakuza huh the dragon of
dojima hell what son told me all about
it hard to believe things are not like
this yep
okay we need a plan what I talked to
everybody what do you mean huh did I not
talk to Tommy I guess
okay no I I feel like I
did he already told me that oh oh okay
seems like getting a
call he told me that separately he just
said the same thing
again ah yep
for
really no way I thought they didn't have
the budget to cat you
guys
properly perfect
time beach beach
for how
nostalgic she still hates
me
for let's
go
reunion it's time for a
[Music]
reunion beach beach beach let's go to
the beach beach beach oopsie it's pretty
close but I'll go like this actually can
we um guys help me where is the wasn't
it close by the place where I can
upgrade my weapons uh weapon
shop Revol no where's the place to
upgrade
again wait this gear works right
okay want to upgrade wait right wait I
can't upgrade the stuff I got right only
selfmade weapons I can upgrade right
then
actually right I can't
oh do I want to read super chats well
that will result in even less gaming
time so I don't
know let
me is this worth reading
my social stats get a new job perhaps
yeah I'm not really far behind at
all okay it goes no pushover you're
waiting into dangerous
water get out oh [\h__\h] not the
drill whoa what a threet before I drill
your head a new hole oh W wo wo
whoa
he's unbelievable don't listen to
anything he says he just likes getting a
rise out of people
H wait I'm I I want to what the [\h__\h] man
I want to upgrade
[\h__\h] but wait if I'm changing classes if
I'm changing classes then I don't need
to upgrade the weapon that they
currently
have uh am I changing though am I am I
going to be doing that this ain't a show
dip [\h__\h] no
no so that was in the shopping mall
[Music]
right maybe someone else takes the class
with that weapon
a change
job wa
so how do I know skill
inheritance I I can take one SK I don't
know how this
works ah for new jobs okay
okay
[Music]
yes yes this stuff I missed it um okay
wait so what have I done before what can
I do requirement requirement here I can
I can do this and this no this this this
I've done
done I've done
this I've done
this I don't think there's anything
new diving ah ah water a gun no I don't
have enough
style I'm not cool
enough
dumy
[Music]
because my stats are just not good
enough what's
up one day I will learn everything they
have but until
then I happy
with I have now
[Music]
yep go go to school there's a
school
school more alas I've been throwing so
many
alas so should I
should I
uh upgrade my weapons
[Music]
then nice sty
points Alo
unhappy I'm not Alo
happy what is this
fireworks what I'm
hearing huh oh who
why fire look in so sky why what you
looking at what you looking at what you
what you looking at what you looking at
what you what you looking at what you
looking at what you look looking
at I'm
feess get away you get
away hey [\h__\h] hey [\h__\h] it's not
how you greet people you stay
Aloha I'm just running around randomly
now
trying to find people to wave Al
at how's it going but okay then I'll go
upgrade some stuff might as
well
uh
mhm
[Music]
okay weapon upgrades
okay so for example pyro dancer we can
upgrade this torch light
ax
streng we have lots of iron
junks you get
to maybe let's get to plus eight again
plus eight oh maybe maybe plus 10 oh
there's no plus 10 there's just +
11 plus 9
yeah pretty
good and then the other one
was her stuff her her her Doran yeah
let's make him endure more how about
that okay we can do plus 10 for her
I don't
mind
uran
yeah okay and what's the brand stuff
down there empty I can put something on
them what was
that you can exchange weapons you don't
need for materials let's do that
k
and then I guess I don't need the
sunrise Maracas anymore or do I need
them as a base to craft something else
thank
you thank you I am
tento not kho what are you
saying not sure check if you can grab a
it such a simple
solution uh wait what would be next
wait that's the wrong thing but yeah uh
Sunrise Maracas is what I
have blooming pineapple okay no it
doesn't look like I need them
still uh okay then we can get rid of
them uh this one too I
guess 12 only 12 iron
chunks wait I didn't get rid of the
wrong one right no no
no this this
work thanks for the membership
[Music]
gifts Okay add this brand thing I wanted
to look into
that what can I do that oh oh ah boost
the
fire this and that oh we can get crit
rate and stuff too boost basic attack
damage ooh $50 this one's a bit more
expensive I might just go with this cuz
the other are you
know yeah you don't know this one helps
with
everything or healing ability oh that
possibly exists maybe maybe
maybe oh no don't see anything actually
I'll go with
this why not why
not and then yeah I'm happy with that if
I strengthen this one a bit
more we can give him a brand
too wow I'm
so so generous
today m
yeah yeah yeah oopsie
friend he uses fire a lot so we could
give him a a boost for the fire
attacks what do you
think actually that might not be the
case anymore I don't know because it
depended on the oh no it's still fire
the element is still fire
okay
mhm right what about you you're
currently using the jet plus
seven I don't know how much long I will
be using that but I guess I'll upgrade
it to
10 I hope it won't be replaced
soon what about n
and I mean they're not here yet what do
you
mean you mean what class I'll give them
or
so what do you mean oh wait I was going
to
Brand it could be water it could be
normal
attack or crit even no I give Vitality
to not the biggest issue in the world if
you don't upgrade a lot yeah I mean
generally
the forgiving enough blind is
good show di yeah we're going to pick
him up I was just upgrading before I go
there now we'll go why why am I not
walking why did I pay 10 bucks for that
it's so
close I can't believe they're
here oh my God I'm not ready
reunion play reunion Alexa play
reunion
[Music]
he's already wearing aot
shirt are they real are they
[Music]
real
he's like my new
[Music]
kids it's
complicated
[Music]
for
I look at the game a n and Tommy look
good
together oh look at aachi's
Arms whoa he must have been lifting
hard he looks more buff than
usual
[Music]
fore let's [\h__\h]
go big
party we can only have four at a time
right who am I going to kick
out ti
ti
the end of this chapter is a great
stopping point well how close is the end
you know if five party members would
only four can participate leaving one to
stand
by oh yeah we can tag in tag out during
the battle though knew the guys would
come for now we can save K on y lar is
over at oh that was gone
fast I will never
know
[\h__\h] oh my God hello
[Music]
I don't know where we're going but we're
going to go with the
[Music]
scooter
scooter can I
um Bruce oh [\h__\h] oops you looking
no no no no back back back let's go are
they all behind me with the scooters oh
my God we're like a instead of a biker
gang we're a scooter gang oh how
intimidating Dance with
Me Smackdown
[Music]
please it's so
lame it's so
lame
they look so
intimidating don't
D wait so what about their stuff should
I give them do I need to give them
equipment what are they
wearing I have some extra stuff at least
oh he's got oh okay I got good upgraded
updated equipment but no accessories no
problem how about you get some
MP and how about you get
[Music]
some
exp and then how about you get some
extra
attack and extra
defense maybe the defense should have
gone to number we know how easy to break
is they can they change drops or are
they fine as that's the
question uhi yeah I wouldn't mind having
Adai in the
party we do have magic with Tommy
already Tommy and number are kind of
overlapping
there is that a weak weapon or are we
good 60 okay I mean compared to this
upgraded Weapon It's weak
they have overlapping hair what
no n has no MP
now I mean he's got low MP
yeah well look at this cute
group
okay well we are right at the job center
uh could we could switch something
around
Brandon well the job center is here
right what am I
wrong oh I was wrong it's over
there wrong
side I'll find new weapons for them
really soon okay okay I believe I trust
die
words
a we can give that to someone
again oh wait to how am I am I getting
lost this way
yeah in that
building's go over
here
wait is autoc Cruise like he
automatically goes to a gold that I
made in the
map oh my God optimizing
everything around okay
um wait so are we going to change his
class just got
to oh you can't be anything else anyway
why did I do why did I come
here well
then let's
try why change num's equipment he's not
going to be working with us right now
unless I bring him in what what do you
want me to
change he's
fine
the ankle ah well
okay
okay that's what you mean with no
NP Carter where are we
going let me go fast with attack see
oh the gang be rolling follow me
guys we're rolling up in our
scooters like real gangsters hey my
item he walk looking like a
zombie
oh o is that that
side
how much stronger do you think is the
end of the
chap feels like are pretty long and this
start one
dungon I think it's a bit away it's the
next
dungeon about an hour one or two hours I
don't think you'll reach it there's at
least of
dungeon one
[Music]
one 2 hours well 1 hour is still within
you know
my limit
[Music]
today we'll go for a little while maybe
maybe only half an hour until half
9 he used to be F you're not fat now but
maybe but Japanese standard s even de no
you're m m and I don't actually I don't
even see a
tummy you're you're not fat you're a
little bit muscular which is good like
not even a little bit you're pretty
muscular what do you mean what are these
standards I used to be th what are you
talking
about volcano tatto let's get matching
tatto yeah he isn't he ripped without
his shirt
too
[Music]
if you put him in a
speedo no even by Japanese
I think he's fit I don't know what
they're talking
[Music]
about oh
[\h__\h] you want to talk to them good luck
ah never
for all right let's exchange some
handshakes business people that we
are here we
go you know I only want to change his
class because he just doesn't fit
in
sadly
are y'all still close enough all
[Music]
right he needs to look more tacky he
needs to get into that Speedo and have
more
confidence what the [\h__\h] is that stick
anyway what is that little
Branch
[Music]
useless anybody who wants to form a
line
now
rude maybe a little anchor to the
blinker not worth 30
[Music]
MP all
right the
blinker no flipper to the
Ripper it's a
treasure it's just a little
twig oh he's weak to that
nice no it's not how you welcome other
to the game rude do they know who he
is doesn't seem like
get no respect for the
elderly
oh it's time to
shine is this like his old skills from
back in the
day is this the first time I'm playing
with Ali in this game or did I play him
in the beginning at
all I can't remember I feel like I
didn't this feels like really
like a long time ago I did
damn damn I don't remember that at
all monkey flip
damage okay let's try
this
yeah just in the very very very
beginning for a short
time the muscles of Steel are protecting
[Music]
us you little
[\h__\h] eat my
[Music]
durian if you think it's too
stinky then that's that's going to make
me very sad cuz I prepared these Doran
for
you
I bought them just for
you I'm serving them from a golden
platter he didn't want my
Duan
[\h__\h] yeah tell
him you like
your see I actually don't so I shouldn't
be the one
talking you don't want to eat my Durant
either it's okay I don't have
any I wouldn't know where to get any in
Austria
no I'd rather have a strawberry banana
smooth thank
you
[Music]
oh it's that
[\h__\h] I want to just sped
something didn't want any any
commitment nice so many fra back here
holy
[\h__\h] who and a lot of Fortunes too
[Music]
oh
Bingo
soon
bingo are you are you a gold trainer I
thought I could say Alo to
[Music]
you oh oh wait I almost didn't see this
it's gold
let me
open let me
open free keys to
open that doesn't look so
special is that any good at my level hey
you there wait I'm going to fight you
guys because I want to get into the
trash Oh yes good oh okay wait who who's
going to use that
I expect a bit more from
[Music]
that can you
not F I
miss oh female ninja
CL
oh then I want to get that class
eventually wait I was just going to say
like what is Namba doing in my group but
no that's Tommy oh god oh my
god oh
[\h__\h]
level
this is cute
song If he go was a vocaloid song
Good makes me think of that the whole
time ever since I I saw the
Ki it's
really oh
another
I like me with my
[Music]
scoter
oh it's
so actual shave eyes place
here wow double
bond wait don't turn away from
me
shaved eyes is so good I prefer like uh
like creamy
eyes but when it's hot and summer shaped
eyes is definitely great haven't had
much in my life
though oh yeah oh
oh are we I think we're 25 yeah one is
26 I thought you came in here
prepared wait does that mean number is
also
26 I feel like we're fine like
previously we're also fine he's also
26 well we're going to get Tommy up a
level soon for
sure oh hi
SE it's always shave eyes not shaped ice
oh prefer ice cream but shaped ice SC
too yeah I mean better than nothing in
the
summer gelato yes
gelato looks good for 26 well what do
you mean it's like if anything it's the
opposite if he was
26 level up in a dungeon most likely
it's not to punish okay let's
go we'll be
fine we'll be
fine
wa why do you why do we think he's in
there I hope that's
true because it's y's uh
head
oh only got five DMS what the
[\h__\h] sent me uh one party emote one
heart hands emote and says it's so great
it's y I'm listening to it so
much
I I centered M was like I think I think
you will like this look
look got her stample
approval isn't it like free a. right
now
yeah more minion
fights little babies let's go you don't
scare me at
[Music]
all just playing My Little yuk
okay oh oh oh
oh oh you want to throw it or what
no oh you too uhoh they're going to
throw it
[Music]
soon he observes you guys are
boring
we have some fire weaknesses here and
either those or we can go for this
triple or
maybe ah I might not catch the ones in
the back let's let's go
for oh maybe that doesn't get the one on
the side
maybe I'll attempt
this yo poor
people yay H Papa's birthday coming up
oh really is it that time of the
year
nice now now we're going
to maybe just this for
now
whoa strong as
[\h__\h] you say he's only level
we
[Music]
we all
right we could charge I think I can get
all yeah maybe not maybe
this say enemy area
[Music]
but try it well now they moved even more
didn't they
wait well do I really want to try the
middle or go safe and just go for
two honestly if I do that I probably
just can hit him normally in that
direction there this this this is good
to enough let see why okay it didn't die
[\h__\h] it would have been almost
[Music]
enough he's really
far oh pretty good pretty good
that's why I love
her here comes the
botles oh he's just starting oh wa he's
just igniting still but there's one more
I think one more bottle
no maybe I killed him
[Music]
already don't stop walk
around wait I should have used the one
that's behind oh well sorry sorry but
then it would I think the line would
have been even more
off wow
w wow Chicken on
fire why are you guys on fire what
happened go go take a shower
[Music]
spee
for yeah
baby oh oh my God he's going to ignite
it oh no
come too bad you can't do it in one
turn
do I sound like a little
bit
no no I
[Music]
don't old
Asen
Castle
if you treated it better it could look
so
nice let's replace those
wallpapers and another a stupid ass
minion fight a man I guess this is what
we get for those two boss fights in a
row that we got for nothing without
going for a
dungeon now now this is the
time okay
wait it should be on
me the Banger thank you so much I'm
really happy with everybody's love and
feedback I hope it will keep on
growing
yeah oh my god oh no I needed to grow so
I get get a bigger budget
because if you want real talk I the MV
is
100% funded by me only the music was
able to be covered MV and art all funded
by me which was both pretty
[Music]
expensive
it's okay though it's worth it for a
nice epic cool ass
song Tommy you're looking really
purple are you okay oh they workn
against your KN your
axes
six
wow he really strong Tommy can be really
strong when he hits he hits
hard yeah MB will bring a lot of
eyes I sure hope
[Music]
so
I came here to clean up this beautiful
mansion then we're going to renovate it
and we're going to move in what do you
think guys what do you think if shall we
make this our new
headquarters thanks for the raid thank
you I'm I'm going to make this into our
The Great Gatsby them
headquarters make my dreams come true of
the greatest Gatsby party of all
time chicken dress
accordingly get
[Music]
down up
ah still no level up for Tommy so which
way to the
Top This
Way the that way where the camera is
staring at us there's an elevator at
least straight there we're sitting ducks
if they're waiting for us we better find
a
staircase all right let's
go we love staircases don't
we uh not here
does
no interesting
soundtrack this part gives me like wild
west Vibes small part
whatat after
all
what that's kind a
theat I felt like a cinema how do I get
there how do I jump was there a jump
button is there an opening
no this one I can get dumpster
ble later okay maybe I'll fall down
there from
above I can see it happening
[Music]
is this where I came from or am I right
I'm
right oh more little minions yeah yeah
blah blah blah oh we're on the
stage stay while and
listen we can do all this dirty work and
then tomorrow we can do the boss sounds
good sounds good oh my God call the [\h__\h]
down where's
here
just got B for my spoty so nice you
treated
yourself I'm so happy for you you
deserve
it you know I don't know maybe you guys
think about spa days and like like kind
of like a feminine thing as kind of like
a feminine thing but I think you guys
should all do it
sometime okay
sry go for it maybe even with the Bros
if you don't got no hoes I'm sorry then
do it little Bros or do it alone I did
it alone the other day remember a while
back when I brought my switch along oh
yeah I was on my break during that I
went to a spa hotel all on my own it was
a little bit awkward here and there but
it was fine mostly it was nice it was
really
nice right for the emotional damage no
it's not supposed to be my emotional
damage just if you're like oh I got no
one to go go with Bros sure you got some
[Music]
Bros oh you go that way I thought you
would go the other way so I was hoping
for some damage on them behind W nice oh
she thought I had it oh my God he's
dying uh are you die or like um
no I ra throw an item at
him your BR no I'm alone no okay then
I'm me alone going alone is fun too like
I did got to have some courage
but you will not regret it go get
yourself a massage go to a spot that has
saunas and pools and Etc I've seen not
only myself alone there too I've saw
I've seen like others like sometimes you
know couples go but they go into
different things like sometimes one
wants to go to the SAA the other one
doesn't want to go so you can find other
people alone too if that's what you're
concerned with although you might not be
concerned with
that mine has Vapor caves what's
that you mean like a steam C
yeah don't being solo stop you I know if
it's intimidating I know that
feeling basically
that nice I like those kind of like
steam rooms as
well makes me feel like I'm doing
something good for my nostrils for
[Music]
myum for my
sinuses never skip long
day yes this time I got
it a he's dying again what the
[\h__\h] how much did that even heal
it wasn't that
much hot dog
time
uhoh oh I'm getting better at that
[Music]
one I almost missed that just now
y you to do research on SP yes you
should make sure to get a a 1 hour
massage
[Music]
minimum thank you C
what 1 hour is minimum for me sometimes
I go even 2 hours if I'm really
[\h__\h]
oh you we to
[Music]
water 1 hour sounds so long no no it's
the
best with 1 hour sometimes I'm at the
end I'm like oh man I wish it was
longer but I'm just kind of addicted
to
[Music]
massages
you guys if you never had a massage
before you're probably going to fall
asleep for uh during a 1 hour
massage but I like to
[Music]
focus on the on the feeling of the
massage so I got to stay
awake oh my
[Music]
God what is this okay this fight
actually
like I'm struggling keeping him
alive maybe because I used like these
weak ass
[Music]
items miss miss miss
miss oh oh
oh oh I usually have like so much to
think about anyway so that's not really
my
issue
damn the pain where they hit a really
sore era area yeah you know it you get
it he gets
it
oh yeah I was hoping to get him while
he's still down
Yoo
oh no oh no he's igniting a
[Music]
bottle come
on
finally let's gang up on
him are they well depends on where you
live
I've heard in Bangkok the massages are
really [\h__\h]
cheap like what $10 for an hour or so
okay maybe that's exaggerated but I've
heard they're really extremely like
cheap as
[\h__\h] while here I pay like at
least at least 60
70 per hour
maybe
dripping wet umbrella wait umbrella was
that
for was that for a
n yeah so we got a good weapon for him
now let's just give it to him in case we
want
to oh bring him into the
fight nice
nice much better than
before
Madam's visor
visor for a madame then I'll give it to
you lowers the damage taken from fire
attacks I mean not saying that the
others couldn't wear
it but this would be my first
choice hope she likes hope she
appreciates
it it would look good with a little
tennis
oh no I should have healed I
[Music]
think should have healed other oh [\h__\h]
yeah I should have healed in
general next safe point should be a SP
oh that was pretty fast then
wow that I reached that
H oh well it is halfast
[Music]
9 good work good
work
[\h__\h] it works though it's
okay almost time to go to S well
first time for some so got to I think
I'm going to just have some frozen pizza
the past couple days his made I properly
made my hello fresh dishes I have one
more for this week I
think no one know
it I mixed in the weeks I still I think
I just finished the dishes from last
week but I already got the ones from the
new
week but I've been cooking yesterday I
ate my second serving of what I cooked
the the nois the day before and then you
know so 4 days in a row I've been eating
my own cooking which I would say pretty
good thank God everything's like too
serving oh but today no time for cooking
tomorrow also not
really even though the last thing I have
is pretty easy to make it's just a a
soup with with um cut
sausages and and potatoes probably some
garlic somewhere in
[Music]
there you want some mili now mili is by
far not my favorite tast
of
I don't know don't really like it that
much it's
too I know the texture
[Music]
and you have to make your own Y no no
no yeah I don't know anybody who makes
their own Yoki my mom even just buys
them usually oh they're they usually
pre-cooked nois pretty cheap in the
supermarket
ouch I think most people just buy them
free pre pre cooked they're
precooked maybe not pre-cooked but
they're like just throw heat them up in
the water and they're done or grill them
in the frying pan and you're done so
pretty easy vodka what the [\h__\h] I know
wine
sauce has the wine
sauce I know wine sauce what the [\h__\h]
is what the [\h__\h] is what
the oh that's a l
s wait did you guys say this is the last
fight before the boss or before the safe
point I guess
oh
wait okay still can't get down there
though tomato cream and but what there's
more than just tomato cream and vodka or
you mean the the H the ingredients of
the sauce tomato cream and
vodka I wonder how that tastes water sa
like wine even though I hate wine I have
to say wine based sauce is
amazing
[Music]
mm why is the word so hard for me to say
right
now Wine Not
Vine usually it's like the other way
around this feels like I've been here
before Fine Wine fine fine I'll hand you
the wine but only if First We Take a
little Vine
no that's not fine because Vine is
not fine
anymore doesn't exist anymore
so out of sadness we shall drink the
wine and then we'll be
fine Tick Tock took over
no it was better then it was better back
then was it was it not I don't know was
it nice
nice
oh yeah didn't like Tik Tok
get what was what was that recently in
USA didn't it just get
banned what am I thinking
of not yet a didn't happen yet they're
trying oh yes oh my God what will bibu
do what will bibo
do oh
no
imagine state of
tumors they'll they'll have to learn how
to use a
VPN if that helps at all I'm sure you
could do that
right
now good the door is locked up
tight okay got to find the master
[Music]
Ki I thought the safe point was
Clos oh
[\h__\h] hey guys do you um have the master
key uh sorry no no no no need to get
up not trying to trouble
you do I have the
parent bite
[Music]
dance ah let's start with a little bit
of a ukulele again although everybody's
a way to spread
out not
good
get of
them no only
two oh well
oh she never finish on top of
him let's go searching
dominance
get stepped on what a girl b
e oh that reminds me that scene in the
Wier second season with yenfa I was like
yo B and she she's so smart she had she
had alcohol in her mouth and then the
fire what did we call him the fire
fire fire fire [\h__\h] fire [\h__\h] the
fire
[\h__\h] the fir [\h__\h] wants to kill her
with fire but she has she has lost her
magic right so she has the water in the
map and she goes right when he does the
fire thing and then you know what got
fire [\h__\h] his face got fire [\h__\h]
real
heart Stu real good
stuff wow nice booty
attack
sounds crazy about content a fir [\h__\h]
is his official name excuse
[Music]
me if if Gerald and yenifer and
everybody says so then it it do be
[Music]
firer oh
no
[Music]
wow 27
already what is this Bay
room yaka be doing ballet in there what
is this
room
treasure treasure that's it that's
it that is what you
oh hi hi
[Music]
hi where are you why are you so can you
guys stay we have tactics we have
strategy can you guys never stay
together at least once wow
[Music]
girl wow okay
okay these
chairs are quite something wow wow wow
wow
wow I need to know the maker of these
chair
no more Ika never
[Music]
again they break easy but they also can
save my life I guess
so M MH
mhm okay this group was really weak this
group of
enemies why not
yapping wait was there something there
at
though
no so many rooms what the
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] that didn't sound like three people
clapping actually only two oh we're
clapping Dum Ain you ever heard of
[Music]
knocking it's his
birthday do I have to feel
bad
no I'm not feeling bad no
[Music]
more well you guys know they never die
they always show up again
anyway even if it seems like I killed
them
don't
worry cute
name
wow quick quick step on
him that's fine too okay that's the
chair we love the
chairs
what was that happy birthday scene for
HH was kind
of so Random for such a normal
fight and now they're
gone
oh is there a healing coin
soon
because then I would not heal her MP but
there's still two rooms that I didn't go
into yet I'll just give her a little bit
of an MP heal just a little
bit get her get her okay that was almost
a full one and she got drunk oopsie
this oh cut scene oh just the birthday
again
maybe
in his head it's just hallucinating
always he's guarding can I get through
that no not really
[Music]
but ooh this one could be good now all
weak to
it no why did I miss it again it gets me
so
excited oh quick go
Qui oh that feels so good W wo wo W wo
wo wo wo wo did he just spray and prey
right in front of me ow ow ow ow ow
[Music]
ow
you got to pray a little bit harder my
friend or maybe this religion isn't for
you
[Music]
she out the door with
you the exit is here let me show you let
me show you
directly
okay foreign
fore
foreign fore
spee
I'm in Rage because he skipped around
like a
[Music]
jackass
oh
y so
predictable
wow oh that's
fine as long as you're attacking
[Music]
someone
why he not dead
[Music]
yet yeah I'm going to die literally
right how do you no so dramatic wow
yeah we'll find the saving point and
then I'll
go oh what the f ow
ow it's hard to tell if the first one
was going to get me from that
angle but that's too close to
wall you're not supposed to use shot in
this kind of
[Music]
situation
ichan somehow always doing the finishing
move this just kind of works out like
that
AR this my room the key might be
here crowbar he's
crowbar look at that look at that what
the [\h__\h] is that from an elephant or
what we got a crowbar how ironic but
this crowbar is somehow hot glued to the
freaking table wait should I heal myself
I'm fine right
no that's our key not going to get
attacked right now right murder or
[Music]
boogie There we go we got
it m
okay there was one more room that I
didn't see yet which might
be is it this that looks uh
no is there fight Behind These
doors
n is there there's no safe one behind
that
oh damn it a little bit how about these
W
[Music]
yumy oh it's close oh I
examine that's what the key is
for
okay um this
[Music]
one yeah cuz I I was here before and I
went left and now I'm I've come full
circle
oh now do I really have to do this for
each door probably just these two hurry
up oh fight from behind they're coming
from behind are they not no they're not
okay thought they were going to surprise
us
sir you little shits I healed for
nothing there was no more fight I'll get
why did you not remember this from your
own play
through poetry Unbound collection of
poems and inspire you to charge and keep
hold of your freedom positive poem
book you get
that spin a minute okay I
forgive okay here we go oh my God so
many why am I making so many
sa It's Time to Say Goodbye I hope I get
some
[Music]
sleep I'll be at an event in Bangkok oh
it's over
170k right now I heard just now from
Johnny oh
Johnny let's go stream Chima Chimera
whatever you want to call it stream it
stream it guys stream it on Spotify Etc
but also on
YouTube yeah please thank
you I hope it's going to be in
everybody's brains as much as do you
used to be do you do you say do you feel
the
same we do thank you yeah press for for
if you want to try something
new
say yeah uh see you tomorrow for more
yakuda um or in Bangkok if you are there
if you happen to be there I'll see you
there uh yeah going to go grab some grub
M have a nice evening and German selfie
doesn't the YouTube version has 45 okay
the YouTube music Mission so
220k let's go true I wonder when they're
going to combine are they not going to
combine that what the [\h__\h] YouTube
You're supposed to combine
it you
idiots all right bye-bye I'll doesn't
thank you for watching today had a good
time getting back into Yakuza tomorrow
we'll go even deeper and find Bryce that
little
[\h__\h] or someone else maybe Bryce is
still too far
away
[Music]
yeah