[Music]
you
new btm this is old bdm
[Music]
the o.g
[Applause]
[Music]
hell yeah
okay wait before we go before we go into
them
into the carol karaoke room
[Music]
for the people who uh i didn't see it
yesterday
this is my new layout
there it is
i'm a bit tall today hey everyone
hello hello uh
we're doing i already have the echo on
we're doing karaoke today
it has been a while
it's been uh a while since christmas the
last time was christmas but i think a
lot of you missed it on christmas why
did you miss it on christmas i sang
a lot of nice songs and so many of you
missed it i think
real life huh what's that what's that
why is real life more important
than me just kidding
um well today the goal is
uh to read to to reach
uh 700k subscribers
i'm a bit worried that it might take me
hours and hours and hours but
i will say i will say this if i don't
reach 700k
before poruka senpai
starts her 3d stream then well
then i'm going to end it there
7k to go yeah 7k to 700k
i mean last time when we did something
like this
it went quite quickly so
i i thought we could do it but now i'm
worried
yes but yeah we will see how it goes
i'll just i mean i wanted to do a
karaoke stream anyway um
[Music]
it's been a while
this stream will be archived so the
songs that i will be singing
will only be japanese because we only
really have permission
for japanese songs so yeah
that's that and i'm gonna try to sing
new songs i didn't sing before that but
there might be songs that i have sung
before
so sorry about that
[Music]
i prepared new songs as well and before
the stream
i tried to record record myself to see
if like oh nice sticky note by the way
[Laughter]
oh thank you yeah i tried to record
myself
to see uh if everything's all right and
i don't know i feel like even though it
shouldn't be because i'm using the
goexillar i feel like there's a tiny
delay with the with my my voice and the
pgm
but i hope it's not too too much
anyway let's go to the stage
[Music]
this is the stage that i used for the
christmas carol as well i prepared
a really nice stage for you guys and a
lot of you a lot of you didn't see it
well this is your first time i also have
i have some some effects too that we can
use
also super super awesome kfb employees
cheering for me
thank you thank you thank you thank you
yay um i i don't i have a few songs
uh to put together in a playlist that i
want to sing but i don't know in which
order i will sing them
by the way i just woke up
i woke up like an hour ago
which is decent i i
when i went to bed yesterday at 6 00 am
i closed my eyes and all i could see
was sliver dot il
screen
ah i saw so many snakes
and they were moving and zooming oh all
i saw was
snacks zooming around look at that i
don't
it haunts your dreams it really does but
the thing is like after yesterday i
streamed deliver that io for like one
and a half hours but after that
i played um privately for
at least two hours i i posted about it
on twitter
i think i played two and a half hours
off off the stream
after the stream two and a half hours
and i got some people some kfp people to
join me
uh it was a bit difficult to get them to
join me but it was fun that was so much
fun
thank you to everyone who joined
yesterday so randomly to play sliver.il
with me
off stream quinoa
i closed my eyes and i can play
sliver.il with closed eyes
[Laughter]
that's fun it's just quite fun
all right should we go to the first song
i think i'll go with this song okay
i this is this is the first time it's
first time i probably sing i properly
sing this
a lot a lot of today's song will be
first timers so i'll be messing up a lot
okay
don't don't don't judge me
don't judge me please
okay uh this song starts so quickly okay
let's go uh but you guys gotta tell me
if the audio is fine
please don't say you are lazy
[Music]
okay
slightly off right what the hell man
wait i know there's a tiny delay i don't
know why though
now it's time
[Music]
very slightly
what happens if i we had this for the
christmas stream as well
one second how about okay you guys said
30 milliseconds i think my
actually no wait
it should be this shouldn't have any
delay that's
that's a weird thing
let me try let me try this
let me listen to it
please don't say you are lazy
[Music]
let me listen to that myself was that
was that better was it perfect really
well
i'll listen to it
no
no it's it's still delayed
but i guess it's better but let me let
me try instead of 20 milliseconds let me
try it
okay 40 milliseconds just one more try
one more try one more try more
wait you don't hear that
[Music]
sorry guys who was that in my chat who
was that in my chat
bonnie
is it really better
i feel like it's pretty close
yeah that might be that might be good
enough
okay i mean it's at least not
is that at least not like super super
bad
so we're gonna go with this
okay one one tip from my team
694k 6k left
everyone retweet my tweet on twitter so
that more people can join
all of the people who don't know
youtubers and you should get them
all in here
if there's a delight almost unnoticeable
it's definitely noticeable
for for me but because the rhythm is off
but oh well
let's go
please don't say
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
foreign
is
the kanji are so difficult
[Music]
you
um
[Music]
that was the first time
actually let me can i eat my banana
[Laughter]
i'm feeling hanging out yesterday i was
feeling
uh a bit sick thank you guys for the
party i was feeling a bit sick yesterday
for like
10 10 minutes
because i just woke up and now again i'm
feeling
what is this what is this why what is
this morning sickness
don't don't say what i think you're
gonna say don't say
it don't tell me why you think i have
morning sickness
[Music]
the lyrics to don't say lazy are so
difficult
oh i don't know what you guys are
talking about
oh i bunked banana against the
microphone
so kanji
oh what what's up which way let me write
the song down
why why do i feel sick
please don't please don't say
lazy
[Music]
i mean i was too lazy to write it
properly
but that's how it is blood sugar levels
really
really really could that be it
really how do i fix that what do you
what do you need for a higher blood
sugar
will my banana help
to eat something candy of course of
course you can
chocolate chocolate really really
chocolate really
i would love to eat some chocolate
okay i i don't have time for a full
banana i will eat the rest after the
next song
ah okay next song do you guys mind if i
sing
like um a beautiful slow song from a
movie like
an older movie one of my favorite anime
movies one of my first
anime movies actually i have two
i have two i have two long it's long
slow slow my brain
my brain slung slow
slow songs oh god my brain my brain
um okay let's sing this one
i this song both of these songs are kind
of
my my feelings towards a certain person
somewhat
it's not
[Music]
song
foreign
[Music]
me
it's
[Music]
and
foreign
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
the girl who lived for time
me
[Music]
m
me
[Music]
nostalgic song i'm surprised many of you
guys don't
know the song and don't know the title
[Music]
uh something that doesn't change
from the movie toki wilka de soto the
girl who lived for time
so nostalgic
i write it down
if you guys haven't seen it it's pretty
old but it's so
good it's also such amazed me really
it makes me cry
[Music]
can i sing
all right before we go for another slong
song
as i saw we are 5k away from the go
yay before we go to another slow song
listen
to um this i don't really have much
practice with this song but there we go
okay let's go
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
like
oh
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
um so i i'm not sure
if like some of you know like this is
like
from uh uh
and this is like the cute version and
then there's the the joke version which
is yada naika
um i kind of mixed the two songs but i
personally
am a hello project fan which is why i
prefer the
balance version okay i'ma say so pure
idol
but yet the yananaika version is fun too
[Music]
uh
is there are definitely people who heard
this version for the first time right
or their song at all
no no bless you for holding me on a
nikon until absolutely and actually i
mixed it in a few times did you not
notice
but the last one was a was very sexy
maybe
i know both versions never heard but
loved it
you gotta you gotta look up what what
the what the joke version means
[Laughter]
uh but i i i chose the saso version
okay
[Music]
i sang this one before but here's top
idol song
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
uh
is
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
i love this song so much
uh wait let me write down the song for
the people who don't know the song
[Music]
i sang this one before i wonder what
clippers do when i sing a song that i
already sang before hm
[Music]
i am a huge hello project fan
also i saw that super chat thanking me
uh for singing hello project songs
you are welcome best idol songs ever
yay 696 000 4k
left oh my god maybe it's not impossible
maybe i'll get down
done somewhat earl early maybe i'll get
down somewhere else
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i'm not allowed to sing that
unfortunately
i feel like i didn't i looked it up and
i didn't find any clip but i feel like i
said it before i don't know
oh no i didn't write
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait
ah maybe actually okay just for now
restart restart clippers restart one
more time let me know
i'll be quiet okay restart
[Music]
me
you'll
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
i
um
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
oh it ends kind of weird there
yay
that was fun it was so much fun the
point because that's where it goes like
do you want me to turn off the fire are
you feeling a bit hot
you know i think
there you go should be better now
i think
how much do we have left 4k more yay we
can do it we can do it we can do it
[Music]
now
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh sorry my brain my brain doesn't work
my next song is a super saiyan song
i don't think i sang this one before
correct me if i'm wrong
didn't sing this one before let's go
[Music]
me
yay
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
style
it's
[Music]
where was that
wait wait wait no oh no wait that wasn't
it wasn't there
where was that out here probably here
right
no let's sing the whole bite again
[Music]
oh
my
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
[Laughter]
this quiet part that goes like um
that's why i messed up the first time
because i looked at different
lyrics now clippers
you are welcome to cut both of these
takes together
so that they make one good take if if
you want
um
[Music]
damn
speed run 700k
or speed run like when i took the when i
when i reserved the stream
it was 9k to go and then overnight
we gained 2k and so i started i was with
7k
to go and here we are free to 3k to go
okay but thank you guys for the super
chats and the memberships by the way i
see them i see them but during the song
it's hard for me to reply i shouldn't
reply i should not
let me change my sitting position
microphone i am so sorry for hitting you
i want to try singing the song because i
love the song
but it's very difficult because there's
a lot of quick parts a lot of fast parts
this is a song that everyone knows
though uh let me see where i have it
and on it
everyone literally everyone knows the
song by now because also
every whole live member sings it in
every
what do you think it is it's a song that
everyone sings every time
in every karaoke stream
some people know which song is probably
one of the most
often sang songs in whole life karaoke
history
we often think similar songs because we
only have permissions for certain songs
unfortunately um
[Music]
i will definitely mess up the song
definitely hundred percent
definitely let's see
um
[Music]
memories
the next song is
you will know when you hear it
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is so difficult this song is so
[Music]
difficult
if the beat is off that is because of
obs
damn it the beat is so um important for
this song now
[Music]
oh
oh yeah oh yes oh yeah how many times
can i mess up
oh yeah oh yeah scuffed your slb
oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
clippers i dare you don't clip
i'll i'll i'll make and do it better at
some point
i did this better when i when i
practiced it it was better when i
practiced okay
understand don't clip it i mean okay if
you really want to clip it but
but then when i do a new version of it
that's better then no one would ever
listen to it again because there's
already a clip of me singing this online
i like this avant-garde interpretation
of the song it's high art
exactly only smart people can understand
the charm behind singing the song while
laughing
uncontrollably uncontrolled you know
what i'm not even gonna write it onto my
list of songs
[Music]
okay let's sing a song that i can
actually sing how about that
how about
no yes no let's go first for song
also first time which i probably also
can't sing well
but doesn't matter
[Music]
i missed a one two three four
foreign
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
ba
[Music]
oh my god got dizzy i got dizzy from
that
another song that i successfully messed
up
yay
i think to to calm down
in order to calm down we need another
slong
song if you know what i mean and let me
write the title of the song
this was
[Music]
from looking at it really old really old
song
this is how you write mature scale uh
oh wait what happened to you is this
is this how you write material
i hope it is and next star
next up is another
song song
what the heck boy youtube what the
you doing
boy youtube what the hell boy
it's your
what are you doing to me youtube boo boo
what the okay we're back okay okay
now
kelly nice that you're i said you're
listening
um this song is for you
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
so
my
[Music]
me
i
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
uh i messed up so many times
i messed up so many times even though
the song was for cali
as per usual but kelly stay here stay
here
kelly stay or not you can't leave yet
you can't leave here i have another song
for you
i think this is the song that you really
expected when i said the song is for you
um i am finally taking up on the
challenge
of
of messing up the following song
as much as i can
the thing is like i practiced a lot but
the problem is i just can't
breathe i just cannot breathe
we'll try okay
wait i have oh i forgot i forgot i
forgot i had to write the song
goddammit uh hey why did it why did it
do
garnet the last song was garnet
oops okay uh yep okay
yeah i'm gonna mess this up so bad
okay i realized when i was practicing it
that the key is
to stay calm but i wanna i wanna rap as
cool as as cali like
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah and the thing is also
that i have some delay
uh so
i don't know man it's probably gonna be
scuffed but
what can you do
they're used to learning in the audience
with more details to my surprise
stretching life's totally asking she's
nice try stopping the
davinci of human erase you can't stop
the taste
make sure when standing up my rhymes
safer stairs that are out there high
five i see
no one's gonna buy you i believe
you cute as all hell in the literal
sense
but it pretends for the future i'll tell
the shell of dollars and cents don't
mean not of the queen's fighting
out of sight another toy to tear her
apart at the same still the killer of
your dreams
don't take a pocket then i play the
scene it's like that if you take my
advice you'll be killed by what you
don't know
but the other thing that i like so much
more is along the lines of yuri what you
say so gotta know and it's so
could
is
[Music]
better tell you straight forward hear
all the way in hell slamming on the
keyboard go ahead and be so but i won't
run cause i'm a workaholic business lady
getting down take your souls for
the industry for success for one but
it's the mistress of god and stay in the
sun
c-a-l-i-o-p-e i really love this fake
relationship
if you take my advice you'll be killed
by what you don't know
but inside i'm kind of nervous but i
don't know what the word is for the
other side of the gap it say so
sending out do it as opposed to you i
get close to you don't mind i double
except for right for you could i
end your life commenting aside
[Music]
[Applause]
up as much as i thought it would
thank you kelly thank you
[Music]
that's how do you breathe kelly i don't
understand how
how do you breathe how how do you
breathe i don't get it
this is so hard this is so goddamn hard
but
it's so much fun you're such a genius
county you're such a genius you're so
badass when you rap
i love it i love it yay
and following that i would like to
give you a special rendition of
[Music]
wait let me first write uh the song
title that i just sang
can we shorten it because otherwise it
won't fit very well
rip okay
and now
hey where are my links still i need
[Music]
lyrics
yes
jazz version
[Music]
um
to keep on fighting
[Applause]
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray if i go
wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please
[Music]
so
luminess
[Music]
yay
[Applause]
that was my original song in jazz
version i'll
let me link really quick uh the link in
the chat right now in case you gotta
scroll really fast i'm gonna be really
fast if you want to get it but here it
is you can just uh
uh look it up on youtube though hinotori
jazz low-fi version by socks music
he made the this remix i guess it's a
i
i love this jazz version
i love it it's just so i love
it makes me realize i kind of like jazz
do you like jazz kino toy
was this song
how much 1k to go
boy you for real 1k 1k
oh my god okay what's what's your song
do you want me to mess up another song i
will gladly do so with this song
it's too low for me honestly
[Applause]
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
is
m
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
that was this this song is so low the
key is so low
and i could probably get a higher key
version but we only have permission for
the original key version so that's why i
was forced to sing it
it's actually really hard when we just
sing that little
one to go
[Music]
let's go everyone tweet on twitter we
tweet my my my stream on twitter
please and thank you kelly for hanging
out so much
oh yeah and i haven't uh drunken drank
drank for a while so let me drink some
water
white kia i can sing that yep
yep next song let's do
let's do
[Music]
can i sing another
that was pretender i love the song i
also love there's um there's a version
of pretender from
pentatonix which i love so much
pentatonic
i love pentatonix and their pretended
version is so good
so good okay let me sing a song that i
that probably a lot of you don't know
but i'm very familiar with uh because
i'm a hello project fan as you know so
let's sing it
i want to be
[Music]
is
m
[Music]
i
is
[Music]
yay
so close we're so close guys we're so
close
sky sky sky musa
[Music]
oh
myself
[Music]
what
foreign
[Music]
me
thank you
[Music]
and
um
[Music]
hey
maybe more songs get the party going
[Music]
no
um
love is so wonderful
[Music]
dancing
dancing i love the night
[Applause]
[Music]
kfb world domination
machine
[Music]
love machine love love
thank you guys
thank you so much for helping out thank
you thank you thank you
oh was there another song that i
definitely wanted to sing
[Music]
can i sing this song though
ah
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
um
yay
that's fun oh this is the first song the
first time in years that i've sang this
song
is how you're writing in english
thinking time mosaic
row oh i think
yay thank you guys so much for all the
super chats oh my god i'll be
i'll probably be reading superchats for
hours
that's not how you normally spell it um
whatever you know uh roll roll not roll
oh
no okay
is there any song that you guys still
want me to sing
uh that you think we have permission for
it must it should be something that
probably we sang before in an archive
stream
uh everyone asks for unravel but i never
i don't i don't think i can sing that
and because
i don't wait first of all do we even
have permission for that
let me see second of all i never even
yeah we have i never practiced that song
before i only heard it like a few times
i can drive but i'm gonna mess it up
[Music]
a
no i can't i can't i don't i'll pray
i know this song and i like it but i'll
have to practice it for you
uh what i can however try
is wait a second
i can try this one was it this one i
wanted to try or this one
i can try this this one i also didn't
practice i just heard it a million times
[Applause]
[Music]
my
uh
[Music]
wait i can use better
the last day we'll get there sometimes
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
no i i stopped here so you guys don't
clip it
but i'll sing this for you last song
[Music]
oh okay
how many times can you restart one song
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
oh wait i'm caught up here
foreign
[Music]
that was the last song let me write it
down
in case in case you have never heard of
this song name before
it is
no no
wait that's probably not how you're
pronouncing this that's probably not
wait that's probably not
the of a cruel angel
[Music]
yes okay
money thanks to you guys i was able to
reach 700k
subs thank you all so so much um i will
today
um release my schedule for next week
there is going to be holo talk next week
about super chat i think it might be a
smart idea
if i uh quit this stream
then rest my voice until the evening and
then then do a gorilla super chat
reading
after polka senpai's 3d stream
could that be a good idea and then i
read i read them all i re i will read
them all i promise i'll do it like after
today's
uh 3d deputy stream from poka senpai
because even if i start now i might not
even get done
and i have to rest my voice i think
probably
yay and then we can we can you know
uh take our time with the super chats
one by one i'll read them
and i'll turn off the super chat so that
you don't send more
wow 700k that's a 300k left to one
million
what what what can you guys believe it
i will um uh create my schedule now
off screen and i'll upload it probably
in the next uh
one or two hours so you look forward to
that
okay
[Music]
i don't know do i have to say something
besides that
i want to thank everyone who came here
today everyone who subscribed
in these two hours and that was 700
7k subs subs in two hours wow
thank you so much i don't know i don't
know who these people are if those are
people who already knew me but just now
decided to sub
or if there's people who who found out
about me just now for this stream
i honestly would like to know uh i
wonder
but that was quite the speed run wow
i know music
[Music]
in two hours you guys are the best thank
you everyone who
who retweeted it and stuff and and
promoted the stream thank you so much
didn't expect it to be that fast that's
quite
uh impressive thank you guys so much so
so so much
wow and i had fun singing so many songs
i think most of them were actually new
don't say lazy was new coloring
kawaranai kabalana imono was new
but i like it was new tamashii no
refrain was new
saiyan on the memories was new material
was new garnet was new
rip was kind of new you know hinotori
jazz version was
kind of new too pretend that was new
love machine was new mosaic rome was new
and that's it
and i tried some in between which i
failed miserably
which i didn't write on here oh damn it
i have to tell my manager which songs i
sang but i lost i lost track of the ones
oh unravel
and kurenge
[Music]
he wanted to write a message but he
couldn't so it's a nameless
version
everyone was so used to the normal
hinotoni version because i forced you
guys
to stream it until it reaches 1 million
views
so everyone is just so used to that
version to the normal version
that the jazz version is just so
refreshing
and so chill yeah
thank you so much damn thank you
holy macaroni holy macaroni
i know i will ever read on the super
chats
in my superchat reading stream later
today in the evening for me the evening
i hope some of you can come and hang out
with me in the usual tangent stream
what was everyone else a favorite a song
today
i feel like i could even do it better
one day i will challenge it again
rfprp jazzy not only
no sign of memories love machine i like
pretender oh
r.i.p garnet oh yeah i'm a bit pissed
because
garnet i messed up a lot even though i
wanted to sing it
nicely and beautifully our piano nailed
it really
really
[Music]
oh man i can't believe we reached 700k
the microphone is so big
featuring microphone sound
or we can turn off the little fire and
everything disco
disco disco
[Music]
is uh like recently whole live has been
putting out a lot of original songs so
next
next karaoke stream i want to do a whole
live originals only karaoke stream
i want to sing the suicide senpai songs
i want to sing
matame senpai song i wanna sing mine
senpai song fubuki senpai song
and then i wanna sing all those new
songs like blue clapper
and all that and the oh geez i wanna
sing uh kiramiki raida
and so on next color planet of course i
love next color planet so much
i have to practice the new songs blue
clapper and and
the others they came out the the the the
japanese sounding one
the content is
i'm going to sing that song oh yeah
polkas if i also put out a song recently
i want to sing that one too
i'm going to wait until all those songs
are released
and then i'll sing it for you guys
oh yes what unravels the whole life
original well i
i highly doubt that what you're
confusing me that's not a whole life
original what the hell
but i will also practice unravel okay
i'll do my best
i generally like the song unravel is an
anthem yeah kinda you guys always ask
for it what the hell
and uh
[Music]
i didn't even practice that one that
that's why i couldn't sing it but
i think if i would practice it i could
do it however i can't get that
that suicide by voice out of my out of
my throat like
uh and she goes like uh like
you know when when when she when she
sings like like
[Applause]
[Laughter]
but it sounds good sounds so good but i
don't know how to
how to get that
how to describe that anyway
what what popping rocks what's that pop
on rocks
what amelia's song
what huh
um is unofficial song you guys are
confusing me
yeah like a raspy voice anyway i'm going
to
uh take a break and eat some food
okay guys thank you so much for watching
today i will
uh leave it here and i'll see you later
and also uh everyone go watch polka
senpai's 3d
uh stream
bye bye thank you and in german we say
au vida thank you so much for your
support everyone thank you for the super
chats
on to 800k here we go 800k
800k 800k 800k
thank you so much
[Music]
ending
you