[Music]
you
uh
[Music]
hello
i'm here with my friends
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
with me in comparison to the others yes
can i have some food please give you
some steak
oh thank you oh
[Music]
thank you for the steaks i was waiting
for those
huh yeah all right put him away i don't
need him anymore i'm making a weapon
oh wait where is this girl it's in her
house
i mean okay my house
if you guys have weapons and you have
like any xp
i have some stones here you guys can use
and you go into this basement and you
can enchant your weapons
if you guys haven't done it yet hang on
a sec
i tried it earlier today let's put the
muscle
whoa wait did you enchant your uh
irons my what your iron sword or
oh yeah yeah yeah no my iron sorry i
didn't make a diamond sword i'm too
scared to lose it that's better
i can just mine more times yeah smaller
oh may i borrow some lapis lizzie
oh hey
[Music]
do you maybe first of all want to tell
the viewers what the hell we're doing oh
yeah what's happening today even i don't
know
even i have no idea we're going to the
nether
and then we're going to the never
together and all going to die
yay
[Music]
i've never been there before what's it
what's it like what kind of things
happen
it's hot with lava cali
yeah bed and then sleep in the never
because it gives you like it gives you a
buff that makes you stronger for like uh
20 minutes really okay cool yeah i'll do
that
i'm level one i can't enchant anything
now where is my bed it must be in the
house huh
i'll make one do you want to chat
something girl i can do it for you
uh yeah wait wait i have
a level down below twenty
it doesn't take away it takes away your
level though you know
it just takes a little bit oh okay
now i'm 27. yes you enchant my bow for
me
is that i have pirates speak on my game
so everything is pirate language so
um that's cool i want that okay girl
they're both
on breaking so oh wait i thought i
thought it had never ending bolts i
thought that was never
it's random i think
or maybe like me
all right i'm going to give you guys a
piece of gold armor because cara says
you want umbrella
i guess it depends on the person yeah
it's per player it changes on purple air
brought you kiara you you have to
unlimited please yeah
yeah you can't have the boots because it
has a curse of binding and i don't want
i think i should wear them because i
don't know i don't know if you could
take them off to get pants or a hat
thank you
get out golden snap bag oh wait wrong
i'm just pretending this game is all
about pretending so i'm pretending it's
a golden snapback
oh my god this is sammy milk oh my god
you know i want a gold hat it's got the
cursive
machine i don't know what
yeah i thought you were still enchanting
[Laughter]
right
does anybody want shiny pants oh i do
are they free
yeah i'll take them like shiny pants yes
i'm very behind in this game because i
don't have time to play games
so please yes i've been a wife we got
you
oh people say the hat will disappear on
death but it's okay because it is
is everyone okay what's going on i don't
think
enchanted bow he might start shooting at
us that's okay where i wanted to live oh
no where's the closet
yeah watch it yeah make a shot make a
shot
okay yeah come on yeah i dare you you're
a coward
i'll use a coward come on come on put
more
put more uh angry in your voice yeah
really get it
hey you mother f word no more cursing
guys no more cursing from me
oh yeah i haven't done it anymore
he doesn't like being called stinky no
he doesn't i'll get him oh no i'm using
the wrong weapon hang on i don't mean to
use uh oh
oh no i just drew with my pick excellent
hang on where'd it go
it's gone i lost it it's gone i got him
i killed him
i smoked it okay
[Music]
you have an arrow in your head watson oh
you have an arrow in your knee
and in your hand i hate that wait why do
we need to think about
it just kidding
it's in my hand we're mining again and
another apparently there's a lot of gold
ah okay
how do i hold things in two hands and
how do i switch between them
right there you can scroll through your
your hot bar like the stuff on the
bottom
yes yeah but i uh you guys are holding
things in two hands right
oh yeah yeah so if you if you press e
and then you see there's like a little
square on the right side next to your
feet yep
that's like a equip you can hold stuff
there callie say hand again
hand i like the way you were saying it
before you like hand
oh really i didn't notice my left hand
um oh my left hand apparently you can
just press f to switch them
between the two hands okay um i only
have one slide and it has a sword in it
and then you can you can use your hot
bar on the bottom and you can
scroll through other stuff yeah you got
it
sorry i pressed what i have no memory
you're doing it you got it
but i hang on oh the idiot idiot
you want to switch your hands you could
press f yes
yeah oh sick okay understood understood
okay let's go i was i wanted to uh say
an announcement really quick
um the hollow rail is now complete
yes well done
[Music]
it took so long
on your roof the thing on your roof
looks amazing i mean oh thank you
over there
oh i see it now i see it now that you
said it i see
[Music]
how do we build this portal i have
obsidian in my hand do i just complete
it
uh i think yeah oh yes where did you get
the obsidian
from i mined it with a diamond pickaxe
that i made mm-hmm
damn what is this how we will access the
nether
what yeah what is that is that okay if
we leave it there
well if it doesn't complete itself then
we can get rid of it
do i make it one box taller i'm making
baby cows hold on
i think okay i got i got the music
yes there's another one we're going
right in
i i'm gonna make some swords first
do you already have like a [\h__\h] ton of
weapons with you
uh i like one redstone oh
look at everybody glowing over here we
have a shining block
four what are we guessing five tall four
ones
are we breaking out one two three four
yeah
okay yeah one more what
i saw oh i need one more thing
uh this and this is this is okay okay
stop volume uh
okay now maybe oh i gotta remove that
block i think
wait so okay okay okay one two three
four four
at the time so now i just do this
yeah and then just remove that
diamond pickaxe i don't want to go get
okay
oh my mine's closed my house is right
here okay
ooh i'm off yeah bgm is off i'm playing
um i'm playing the minecraft soundtrack
from the internet
because i don't think oh yeah i totally
forgot about music
and i think we're talking so much we
don't even we don't even need music
that's guys decked out
i mean my minecraft doesn't even play
music though i guess it's the best
place yeah that's that's what i've been
doing
hey where did you guys hit your shield
what iron and wood oh okay cool i'm
gonna do that real quick
do i even have a house i guess it's over
here
i don't think i have a house you gotta
build one
yeah i guess so huh i was thinking about
i was thinking about flattening out
the area up here this this mountain
what do you guys think should i flatten
it out so we have more room to build
yes yeah sure wait one more
i'm gonna flatten this out this big
mountain
what are you doing callie i'm looking
for my chest i know i had one
i mean yeah do it like you only have
okay
okay i mean i guess it was over by the
[\h__\h] okay
that's why it's there we're open it's
okay we don't have to go right away
get to the part all right yeah i'll wait
until you guys get here
are you ready and first portal to the
nether
would you mind if i if i created a
shield first
no problem thank you yes you need a
shield
yes i will create the shield where was
my house again um
it's i think it's gone oh yes my chest
is here but i have no house because the
creeper blew it up and then i got tired
i'm gonna build you a temporary house
just live with
me i will keep you safe i'm good
i'm gonna i'm gonna throw this down i
know that i have iron
[Music]
iron
let's see can i make shields out of
anything else by chance
oh i need i need arrows for my bow oh i
got some arrows oh i have feathers you
can use too
oh wow you made like a farm
[Music]
and iron something maybe iron nugget i
don't know
i give up this is too much i can't oh
that's so cool you need assistance help
gosh back in the day i'm in i'm good
i can kill myself oh no i took it i got
a tennis court
look behind you yeah oh yeah okay ooh
thank you sorry you had to make that for
me something
you have a pickaxe in your hand and your
third and the other
okay okay and sports what do we need and
food sword pickaxe food
uh callie needs a bed i have one i have
a bed i have it i took it okay
it's wonderful
okay okay okay yeah don't don't forget
your bed okay
you want you want feather get in huh i
have 10 shots and then i'm that's not a
lot
it's fine whoa there you go
you have sticks yeah one second
where'd you get the feathers i forget
how you get feathers
chickens did you kill chickens oh
chicken
okay i need to kill chicken ah i need to
kill
chicken uh do you have um pointy rock
pointy rock yard is that an actual item
because that sounds like a pointy rock i
don't know what that is
it's a flint oh oh yeah i have a bunch
of flint here
who is mr pierce
have you seen bradley and his family
callie
no i haven't can you introduce me yes
come come this way
thank you i want to meet them
how do you mean
how do you that what hang on hello thank
you
it's interesting actually because every
every time that i call an animal or
for example a dog or a cat a default
name i always call them bubba
but because because watson has a dog
named bubba everyone will have bubba
everyone will think that i'm talking i'm
talking about that bubba
should we let's see hello bubba
they look at you like you're the mom i
want something
really get me like that
kelly
yeah he's dumb he's too tall uh he's
gonna chase you forever
oh that's unfortunate i love your dogs i
think i can kill him
uh he can't get into the three-way he
can't get in the the door so if you uh
i don't know he's gone no he's right
here he can't get
you gotta get him to stand in front of
the door because he's only he's three
blocks tall so he can't pass under a two
block
ah oh jorgen no the
enderman hey buddy
i feel like it's gonna die no no no no
no no no
i got this listen oh wait you guys are
in line aren't you
now we're at my house right now gude is
trying to kill the injured man
something sounds really odd yeah
something sounds strange
something sounds like there is water on
the wall over there
how do i harvest my my my crops
just touch this is it okay which reminds
me i need to
put the wheat again this is my home from
now on
this is my home hang
for my carrot form okay thank you
you're welcome i also have beans if you
don't have any beets or melon i have
melon i have beer roots oh wait what
beer beer roots fun
did someone claim this this is my
swimming pool this is my swimming pool
now
has someone claimed this area i think
it's mine now
okay this is a swimming pool yeah it's
it's in here already for me
nice i think he's gone i'm ready
you scared him off i think i did
my home is perfect well not yet but it
will be
sorry i'm just very excited let me know
when you guys are ready to go by the way
i don't want to hold us back oh i think
i just like you know
let me open the uh open the gate africa
uh no not yet i have the rest
okay okay oh wait it's just the one
block right yeah hold on
yeah put stuff away
get prepared probably should make a
couple pickaxes huh
oh yeah we need that maybe we should
craft some materials yeah
i will help shortly in just a moment
yeah it is dummy
yeah it is dummy oh
there's a gap in the wall what's on this
side what goes outside
evil witchery of disappearing my house
is big
well it will be big
hey do i have iron nope what do i need
flint and steel for i've never used that
for anything
um
i thought i knew that but i i don't
remember there's something
something another is there water in the
nether no
no no no there's lots of lava lots of
lava but you
[Music]
you ride um oh the phone horses
you can walk on uh lava with striders
what
in the world renovation is done for
today
yeah so if you see striders we can uh we
gotta get some stuff but then we'll be
able to ride them they're funny-looking
and then look at my pool everyone isn't
my pool wonderful
anyway this is my house congrats on the
new home thank you
whose house is this what is this is this
a farm it's not very safe cali
do you need one
[Music]
yes i just need to put him i'm just
going to drop these rocks off who has a
llama
what yeah i still somebody has a dumb
you stole it from the merchant no
i borrowed it
sounds like you stole it
yeah that's fine i i don't have a
problem with it
i want a donkey hmm yes
okay okay i will go to the gates what is
this
[Music]
[Laughter]
does anybody have a pickaxe lying around
that i can have maybe
yeah i have like uh i have two extra
um nice thank you
are you feeling breaking things anyway
oh yes now my chest is protected thank
you for whoever put
that protection around my chest that was
me tina i think i stole your llama
huh i think people are saying that i
accidentally tamed your llama so i think
you do
my llama
[Music]
do i hit it how do i make him scream let
me consistently don't hit
[Music]
here yay let's get let's fix this up
it's happening it's happening here we go
i think i know what you need you need
that little thing that makes
dip and then it's there what uh what
what zip lint and steel anybody have
flint and steel
oh i do here let me drop it
oh i will oh it's in my box what do we
what do we like right click with it and
then it like does like a chat
you gotta light it on fire yeah
i'm useful for something here hold on
there you go
okay point there out yeah yeah you got
it
whoever
are you ready
[Music]
[Applause]
what happens in here the fun
all the fun okay in one of your chests
i'll put it in one of your chests okay
okay how do you hold up a shield by the
way
uh right right you gotta do that like if
somebody's shooting arrows at you you
have to
you can't you have to block it and you
walk really slow with it up
it's not just like a passive thing you
have to be active okay
all right you don't like it don't leave
the blind pocket that says do not leave
the flint because we might need it to
get back
oh oh okay wait i get it again okay
okay should i imagine if we could never
return i'm gonna bring the rest of the
obsidian with me just in case we need to
make like another portal or something
we can do that right it'll like lead out
just somewhere else
okay someone have a shirt huh shoes
yeah shoes yeah
i noticed i'm missing shoes i can make
you shoes
yeah i have one okay perfect are we
supposed to
sleep in another really yep yeah we have
to save it just in case uh
we die oh okay i really that doesn't
sound right in my brain
yeah well what do you know about
minecraft
i don't know that much about minecraft
but that's something something's telling
me that
there might be a little bit of trickery
going on yeah i have a weird
feeling right now i don't like the way
that you guys are saying
we have some cheeky people thank you
today
are you guys trying to mess with us
why wouldn't we first time in another
together come on
we wouldn't want to work that for
everyone we just wanted to go well
just want to have fun yeah i don't like
that i don't buy it first
i'm only sleeping in the nether if you
guys are sleeping in there
i have my bed i'm totally sleeping in
the neighborhood i brought my bed
see see it's another
slumber party i'm coming
all right who wants to go first okay
you can do the honors no no no all right
all right i got this let's go okay all
right
[Laughter]
oh there's something here
it's red and square and has wings uh
and my mirror strider what the world
i've never seen that before
do you see how
what's this block
there's a monkey more importantly
there's a mushroom up there i need to
pass out like what's this
um i can i can is this soul sand
question
fine it looks so fun down there look at
all the friends
is that is that good that's all can we
use that for something
basalt coordinates
in the garden
i think like one block and another is
like eight in the world or something
like that
it's like multiplied yeah wow oh that's
not great i don't like gold
i'm go up there um i think
something to to just to keep in mind i
i'm not a minecraft
uh encyclopedia but you see these pig
people down here uh-huh yes
they uh don't touch them they won't hurt
you if you don't hurt them okay
okay oh okay yeah just like my homies
we're about seeing me and know that it's
fine
i want this gold be careful oh my god
what it's fine huh be careful
you're a piece
i think we're up pretty high there i
mean who is up there
what are you doing i want to get the
gold and the ceiling
there's gold oh that's i guess that is
gold huh guys we'll go pick it up
huh so there's pig people right that uh
won't hurt you but there are other types
of characters that will hurt you
yes
but the pig people will hurt you if you
are close to them
and mine some gold i think
really if you far away then they don't
care but if you do it like somewhere
close to them they will follow you until
you
there's more gold we should go down this
way ah okay just leave the way
okay wait i'm scared hi
hi you're making friends here
my boy he's cute and hey he is cute
i like him i want him as a pet can we
bring him back
yeah do we get down there
oh wait you need us in a mushroom
maybe build a stairway it's hard
build the stairway down it's okay we'll
figure it out that is in detail
um but the light is
[Music]
huh look at him the white the white
what is that okay maybe we should go the
other way
oh yeah i think so maybe
i knew this would be happening i knew it
when i saw him i knew it it's a guest
apparently they're called guests just
yes i want to see it
this music is nice is anybody else here
no i have a
no i had my music yeah
how about we go up here blob oh
what there's a big blob thingy
what is that lava slime
oh we're so high up
yeah should we sleep somewhere is that
what huh
what does that mean a spawn point how do
we get anywhere
everything's so long vertically okay
parkour everybody yeah that should be
easy slay
where the the red rock what
oh oh there's a guy up there with a
sword there's uh
say we can all dig down on this but is
there going to be like a gap underneath
if we go down
straight down does everybody know to
hold on
be careful yeah on the block oh no i
didn't know that thank you
yeah prevents you from falling all right
i'm gonna dig down over here you'll be
good you're digging down oh boy okay
i'm go i'm doing two blocks at that time
yeah two blocks it's good two block is
good
okay okay oh my god ghost rider please
we can we're going out here we gotta say
we can
let's take a straight line
i'll just follow you guys
well true okay
deja vu
not that you suddenly fall down that is
very possible
fellas well this music is amazing
wow hey guys how are you doing where'd
you guys go
uh we're mining going inside here
oh oh yeah
did you make it here oh yeah hello i'll
i'll put a light here so we know where
some gold lava
oh
from the group wait my water i can't put
water down i can't put water down
[Music]
nobody has already i don't have water
i have food does anybody need food water
is useless
well that makes sense how do we put out
fire if we get caught up caught on fire
drop and roll we're gonna kill these
don't get caught on fire oh no they're
friendly right they're friendly yeah
they're friendly
yes friendly old they're friendly until
they're not
exactly this gold is far enough away
from them for me to mine
no no don't take it don't take it but
they're not going that close
look for science they're coming up
no just let them leave we'll trap them
be nice to them
they don't want any trouble
oh no they're coming
[Applause]
well this this area is kind of nice if
we if we want to just
make this the the place to know
chad says no bed why i have one
yeah they said
because they want you to not get the the
buff
what happens what happens when you sleep
you get a 20
uh armor buff yes you're lying speed
boost
you're lying what happens
get out of here no no don't do it
go shoot what are we looking for in
another what do you do here
yeah well uh i think we're looking for
materials
what kind of materials i want soul
saying
oh oh [\h__\h] she's doing it yeah i do
wonder what dm oh man
wait where which one's angry oh wait
strider okay this is the way we came
from
oh there's the bed no don't don't let
them out don't let them in oh uh oh
oh sorry i didn't know i didn't know
wait
okay this is the way we came from yeah
look for the little lava but i'll put a
lantern here so that we can oh
boy here we go
so what are we gonna do i didn't even
get oh i got gold nuggets uh-huh
or me mining you want to go down here
there's stuff down here if you want
to go here no
[Music]
okay what's gonna be the uh i mean who's
gonna be the uh the tesla
i mean the who's gonna kiosk
you sleep now i mean i legit want to see
what happens
all right go to bed we'll pick you up
from home afterwards but you can take
that take my
stuff and then give it back to me
okay wait let me get a good angle ina i
only trust you with my stuff
i don't like what i'm hearing from chad
i don't like
phoenix or phoenix five piggy banks
set a spawn point okay that makes sense
they want us all to die all right i see
right and uh potatoes and
one more number two take off your 14
quarts
oh yeah take
are you guys ready to watch this he's
blocking my
kid out of the way oh god this isn't
going to be good
yeah he really is i'm ready
all right i'm doing it
it was nice knowing you all good bye
[Music]
wow fireworks
that's one way to get somewhere
you're going to try and make me do that
even even the pigs are like what is
happening
okay see we have an easy way down now
it's all
calculated now we should do a bunch more
times like
like in a yarrow you'll have to do it
again you're a phoenix so this is your
job
just blow up a path for us uh we'll need
a lot of beds tnt when you go
kiara really
deaf does not scare me so i'm
i can do it i can do it again and again
i gotta stamp out the flames oh [\h__\h] i
have no gold armor
give it to me oh wait where are you all
right
here oh it's really exciting right here
where are you
oh wait wait thank you oh
[Music]
yeah i think that was worth it right
that was totally worth it
yeah we we got an easy way down there's
a path over here
it's another course
and a bread uh
bread thank you
i think it's yours oh oh i thought that
[Music]
torches yeah follow the torches okay
there's a pathway right here
um
[Applause]
it's the big floaty thing hey this is
this is
[Music]
thank you chad what are you getting
i want this for my home that is
my new home in the cave a fortress a
biome
okay
no it sounds so cute go go can we fight
it okay
yeah i don't know
is it is it is i think it's just
randomly shooting where is it oh
i think that it knows that we're here so
it's going to try and
kill us oh my god oh yeah
well we can go this way uh maybe we can
come
close enough yeah do your worst
yeah let's go this way the stairs okay
go go go i got
like a pig hut hey guys our friends
can we kill that thing you can deflect
the fire you can attack the ball when it
shoots it and it shoots it back at the
guy
does anybody want to try that it sounds
scary
somebody make sure you have a lot of
health because you might catch on fire
let's go i'm in full health all right
okay
okay there's a lot of fun i'm on fire
now
what well oh well if i'm gonna die
anyway i might as well give it a try
okay
yeah i think we're extra intimidating
yeah yeah yeah
our dominance yeah you guys see this
oh oh are those the glowstone thingies
there's gold
here but there's a pink
oh yeah there's a forest over there
let's go that way i think we can build a
bridge
forest oh there's a yeah we can build a
bridge here
we're going to shoot it yeah
another rack wow
i'm gonna grab some rocks because i
don't have any i'll leave this to you
girls you work i don't want you guys are
good at that
team seriously wow i'm impressed
thumbs apart so easily you have to hold
shift right
yes hold shift hold still okay
so what happens can we make another
nether portal does it exit out somewhere
on the other side
yeah but it will probably be really far
away from where we came from
like super far really yeah because this
one is
in the outer world right
now what how do we get down
um if we hold
shift we can't fall right right that's
my paws that's what i thought callie
were you wrong uh i don't know
get more rock here look this is it's
possible see
no no
this far away enough from the piglets to
to get the gold
is it the music is so loud for me
there's like music in game and it's like
wow
that's like special special another
music oh my gosh
[Music]
another oh you're sick whoa what's this
red rock
is it different bush
wait what is this hell is wart
red grass oh [\h__\h] oh wait i have pirate
game hold on don't listen to what i'm
saying
i like i like can i if i take this stuff
back to the
real world i want my walls to be this
way we should probably try to go back
after we collect some of this stuff
because like uh
if we collect too much and die it'll
just be like
a big waste yeah yeah it will be plain
pickle
so collect as much stuff now and then
we'll go back for like a few minutes oh
there's another there's another floatie
what is that is that a ladder or
something
yeah where i'll shoot him down where is
he
there what's that sound yeah yeah
a shiny one well i heard something
ah i heard something explosion
that was right behind me yeah fight me
out in the open
yeah yeah don't be a coward i say as i
run away
you gotta be quicker than that buddy
tactical retreat
i want a garden with these plants
here are these ones
wait i thought they saw a fortress i'm
going to go to the fortress wait this is
wood
trees yeah oh what a cutie hello who are
you
oh are these villagers oh
is that pumbaa
it looks like there are other people
here they don't look uh nefarious or
mean
maybe they're other smarts i i have a
sneaking suspicion that the pumbaa is
not so friendly
but we shall see
ah i took my outlet and now my
oh chad says they're hostile so maybe we
shouldn't go say hi
oh
we just killed the little one dominance
all right cool i'll help i'm behind you
oh wait they're fast hold on hold on
wait
wait wait wait wait wait don't shoot
first there's so many of them
it's fine we'll be okay well it's easy
see they're all equipped with swords
so we taunt them and we get them to come
at us then we just knock out the bridge
and they fall
hey [\h__\h] boys
[Laughter]
come over and fight us and you want to
oh
we can give gold to them and maybe
they'll be friendly let's try i have a
bunch of gold
i'll go finish the bridge okay wait
what's that
girl huh i was i was ready
i was ready to shoot all right
okay yeah we're here to help i don't
have a i don't have a bow and arrow
though so i'm gonna have to
wait that's really far hold on i'm not
prepared you believe
how do i give it to them i'm no coward
uh
throw it at him maybe i tried right
click
okay throw it i think it doesn't do
anything maybe are those the ones that
won't attack you
oh yeah hold on they're not aggressive
i don't know
oh
oh he has some more gold you guys can
try everything is very strong
uh normal very strong well
i'm glad that things ended peacefully
but i'm more i'm mourning here
don't mess around with us i'm ready to
start swimming
thanks chad i'm no coward
i also want to try the katja i want to
do the kacha the gold kacha right here
here here's that
one's here
[Music]
oh thank you
yeah you better do i just throw it at
him thank you
what do we do with it give it to him
right click on him
right what's going on crying where's
kiara
oh no wait wait oh here we go
wait come back come back sir get away
from me
i tried to give it to him i hit him with
it oh
i got it he dropped his gold sword
that's kind of [\h__\h] did you kill him i
can't it's okay oh another one
[Applause]
okay all right we're good
wait i'm gonna try this guy machine i
wanna try
the best when i just got held up up here
it held up a shield instead
when i right clicked so i left clicked
and it hit him with it
i wanna
yeah the the piglet took it right away
from me
wait you're gonna kill this thing oh i
see that try to pick it up okay
so how do i hold it in your right hand
and right click on them stop okay now
give me something good
wow he gave me a meatball
i have something too it gave me [\h__\h]
maybe we should build a portal here
what am i supposed to do with a meatball
oh look at the cute little spoon
wow
[Laughter]
thank you
or what is it the crossbow okay it's a
payback water bottle
i got a water bottle okay that's time
what does it do
don't like it don't you ruin it yeah
gotcha don't you run away oh wait
you little hey what does this do wait
hold on that's right
thank you chad thank you wait do we know
how to get back
you can throw the spicy meatballs uh
oh yeah here's our bridge okay our
bridge is here i'll put oh
oh
hey so the meatballs uh it's like
throwing heart rate
when you throw the the the the the spicy
meatball they give you it makes fire
uh oh oh what was that
back it's fine i got it that's
flying squid come here let's play i'm
ready to party look at this wide open
terrain
i will fight you a hand-to-hand combat
come here
coward bring it squid well you dodged my
bullet oh
my bullet up
bring it squid i'm just
getting the way back for us really quick
security okay
oh it's coming back yeah bring it he's
afraid
hello little one hello little one
what the noises they make are so
interesting hey come back
it's so cute hello
aquarius what are you doing you're too
young to hold a weapon
hello how do i get the soul sand
maybe it's a different biome
oh you got some yeah i got it uh for
gold
i don't think that sorry i could go look
for more gold if you guys wanna
i don't think we could take the gold
from here what are these
is that good what else my side's
swinging twitter instincts were
kicking in when i saw the little one
really great apparently
i got something amazing i got
10 10 spectral arrows and the chat is
going like
you can't see the person you shot that's
all what
oh like
oh we can't we probably can't mind these
goals darn it yeah we can um
i'm a cookbook we can find gold on the
way back
i'm gonna go give me something let's
build gold yeah
or we can build those here if you guys
want yeah
if you have nothing
my house
crimson roots i like them that gives you
water like nights
this is it's like what is it worth the
world stuff
i like it yes okay
i want to save my actually i guess i
don't have to save my gold if anybody
say anybody want to go again i have
three left
i have some i wanna i'm gonna milk them
for what they got let's see what you
yeah
give me some stuff wait that job you
wanna go again
yeah okay so i'm gonna drop it here okay
okay
why are you running away from me give me
your pickaxe
oh yeah that's a bow pink axe okay
give me a crossbow yara i got another
piece of gold but you got to come over
here because
don't give me a meatball okay
thank you gold dealer did you just yeah
there you go amazed the dealer for
everything he robbed me
yes i think so yep oh okay let's not do
that what
okay what did he give me yeah enough did
you take my item that he gave me oh
yes huh you guys gotta come see us
huh you guys gotta go see this well
where are you
[Music]
where'd you go
what what does the chicken do in the
nether oh i got like um
[Applause]
he's riding her i got crying obsidian
what is that chicken doing here
[Music]
look at him riding on the chicken stop
running look at that
they said that's super rare cute very
rare
you guys want to build a portal here and
see where it goes
yeah yeah i have one obsidian good
come two three four
one two three three four
we're friends i like your gold stores
little one
oh yeah
yes i will do let's
oops
sorry my bird brain is uh not being
activated three two one go
oh all right nice okay i can drop you
off the edge of a cliff
let's go oh dear now we can spawn in the
middle of nowhere
yeah we should i mean like
we're in some sort of cave oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
outside area that we never saw before
like a nice new
biome wow really really far in oh i put
it
i put it just now
in the world
oh we are deep we are ironic
but we're not the heat we're not going
to go back
just really far in the z direction
all right uh deep in the ground see
where we're up and down right
hey guys should we sleep now
[Laughter]
oh never mind we might be underwater
everybody get ready to swim
i brought a door just in case did you
bring your floaties girls
[Laughter]
i'll
[Music]
oh sorry i took here wait where is oh
there's watson
it's gonna be the ocean sandstone's
making me feel like it's going to be
ocean
yeah maybe we should go back like that
what could possibly go wrong no i can
also be a
pyramid or something like that i died in
one before
whiskey pyramids king tuck we should
build a pyramid how cool would that be
we're not there we should be pretty
close to the surface actually right now
yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm struggling hold
on a minute
are you good i'm okay i just can't i
can't climb
just
you later okay
we're okay okay we're okay we're okay
we're okay
right yeah yeah yeah no we're fine i
definitely wasn't my fault
okay ah we did it
whoa where are we gonna get out
i need to i need to keep mining so i
might hit you oh
the desert oh hey
no wonder it took us so long it looks
like dystopia
like we came out into the store oh
oh nothing good here
is that gold block a gold can we take it
i should have brought my diamond pickaxe
fireman's stick oh gold
[Music]
yeah give me the gold i can't it's too
high up hold on i'll build away uh
oh what you know yeah but this one is
too long
i think i gotta wait one
no no it's fine it should be wait a
second no it has to be it has to be
higher yeah we just have to get rid of
these two blocks we're not gonna be able
to save it but we can remove it and then
replace it
is anybody else
[Music]
wait how much do we need in total it's
four by
what is it wait one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve thirteen
some people are saying it doesn't work
the one that i have oh
yeah no it doesn't oh the bright
obsidian doesn't work
which way did you guys go uh
i know the way the way to uh
is the way hello let's just leave this
place
yeah yeah wait okay we can come back to
it to retrieve it which way did you go
yeah where is it there's a temple over
here
hold on did you guys empty the chest yet
no i don't get to empty it what are you
doing here guys
do you know what i'm the what where are
you guys you don't need the corners
oh oh yeah but
i only have five blocks
here how many did you have three
[Music]
three oh uh but they're not the glowy
ones right it's just regular obsidian
it says obsidian okay is it trap
might be able to build it then let me
try
hold on all right we already have a
sitting here in the floor so if we do
you guys said we don't need the corners
so does anybody have tnt
then pink
[Music]
we just need to lure a creeper over here
a rabbit yeah
accurate the creeper doesn't love
obsidian i tried
oh two bottom tops
are you in the desert oh i see okay ow
come here
come here okay i don't know what you
guys mean
okay i can just do here then
okay so like this
no i have to oh okay i see i see
i'll replace this with sand like this
and then go
no yes this is right that's right
this seems like a difficult problem
it's like a puzzle huh well then it's
okay i'll
do a mock one okay this is one two three
oh
[Music]
yes okay
yeah all right now i just replaced this
side so one two three
four five six seven eight right guys
eight
yes wait this isn't this is long enough
he's fine they said chad says yes
um yeah okay that's right imagine if
this was one higher on the ground than
it would make sense
sounds good i have the coordinates don't
worry we have the right amount
all right kyra i'm waiting for you i i
think i
see it i'm coming i got lost a little
bit but
i'm i'm back almost oh it's like a real
i'm i'm there on there
i think i see it
what do you guys need to call i did not
see you
yeah i have the coordinates i have the
coordinates no we already tried to use
this one that we built but we can't mind
the obsidian so we have to try again
because it's not tall enough
mm-hmm yeah and we don't have a diamond
pickaxe with this because i didn't bring
one because i was scared i was going to
lose it
yeah see him but i don't mind i'll bring
it with us if we get back home
because like uh i have more diamonds i
it's fine yeah
same
oh wait that's just the bunny give us
your coordinates get uh
i've been trying to say i'm in a pyramid
could you hear me
i was trying to look for gouda but then
i got it
a cat yeah oh yeah there are cats yeah
oh that's a bunny it's a bunny there are
cats though in the desert i've seen cats
i am a paleontologist
that's a dinosaur person though right
oh my god the wizard is like endless
what discovers mummies what are they
called historian mummy
mummy tissues
i'm an excavator that's a truck isn't it
what
probably i mean they stole it though
um what should we do we gotta wait for
kevin
you guys we're we're still at another
portal we don't know which direction you
guys want
oh i see hold on i went up high and i
saw what i thought was a um
is here oh hi chiara
yes of course i love you
now let's try with the flint
it works
me too me too let me in okay looks good
okay we're going back in yeah or yep
unless what you want the little one is
still here
we didn't move that far
yeah we only went up i just didn't want
to go back again i mean we had another
one dude but we came back and from the
same same gate
because we put this look at these guys
jumping
oh this is the same game come on i
thought the torches here remember
you close and i ended up being how come
oh that's what callie's looking at hilo
okay
all right well i know the way back to
the home portion i'm in the case
okay what cave what oh the cave we uh we
uh we started oh okay what are these
springs
all right i know the way home okay
follow watson
what's up oh okay i think i know the way
home
yeah this is right this is right this is
right yeah that was my crafting table i
love the toys
thanks for being so chill ah they
weren't bad dudes
all right i'm ready there's another
pumbaa all right i'm ready too
no he's running away
all right i'll let you freak coward
cowards cowards
got him all right this way
out of that pig
all right there's a bridge here we'll
follow this bridge
okay i'm is so reliable honestly
it's like oh wait we go back up this way
she is the detective
i attention to detail lesson yeah
and then be careful on these stairs easy
to follow okay
wow good pair of
us bridge
like we're like following the mother
bird
wait wait wait wait wait i think so amma
is a bird too
nice i'm not the only girl
oh yeah this is where kiara blew up so
our home should be
right through this wait yeah still
burning
there you go yeah cause his name is
i think it's fun too i was going to get
more gold to give to them what i found
this hole
where better oh goodbye friend i hope
i'll see you again soon
bye you on the head but i'd probably
hurt you personally
and we did not i mean the only person
who died is me right
and i died on purpose yeah yes exactly
wow we're making like progress how many
times have we died
last time too many and there's another
man
a lot of stuff a lot of mushrooms
golden sword benjamin
it's not the one that's mad at me right
i don't think so
enemies here don't seem as big of a deal
after coming back from the netherlands
no i got so much no you leave ina alone
i'll kill you
i got it i got it do you want to sleep
or do you want to just well i'm good
forest hang out is hitting things
um well i got more gold if you guys want
to go back and i got my picture there's
another boy
i got him oh no down you go
how are you getting that sweet
experience
i did it i'm so unorganized
let
[Music]
oh did you kill them nope they're just
walking around they're chilling
yeah you should be able to ah darn it
stem oh whatever that is
this is like a door a circle door
i'm working on my house now no you can't
oh yes you can i'm dumb okay
oh i see dragons in the background
does that wasn't fantastic you sleep
yeah phantoms
what what mushroom wait
maybe we should sleep one night just
right now
good idea all right i'm in my bed
lipstick
just a moment here for now here
i'll sleep i'm
good morning good morning this morning
oh they're burning they're burning haha
okay
okay guys i'm gonna take the i'm gonna
go get us that strider i'm gonna go
bring him home
oh yeah yeah bring stuff to like uh a
good idea
saddle and the mushroom and stick
what flavor mushroom does he eat though
oh
i have a bunch of mushrooms i have got a
blue one
a brown one and a red one
and the more flavor they like red these
blue
mushrooms uh you got a blue one all
right
the warped fondant i don't got it blue
do you have one of them
i have one yeah yeah that's what he eats
apparently okay
so i don't i don't know i guess he dies
if he's outside of the lava
oh you can only use him in in there i
mean that's still pretty good can you i
wonder if you can make a little pen
hold on bring a face or something
all right i brought some fence wait well
would catch on fire in there
you put it down uh
i don't know
[Music]
oh no
oh yeah that's a good idea i'll bring
some materials
but no no beds no beds
just like furnace and crafting tables
that's so fancy yeah
ah no i didn't mean to do that i can't
oh i can't stand hang on
okay high ceiling because i am tall oh
cali's house to be yes i'm working on my
house
like hey welcome ina i'm still listening
yes my pool do you like it it was here
when i found it is this for you
organ not you
[Music]
just build a house in there and then we
can like stay pretty close
yeah it's just like a square house
cool in another yeah yeah yeah yes it
sounds fun
yeah wait i mean do you have that
mushroom wait oh yeah i got it
it's like that nice
yeah my god
three hits all right three shots
easy
[Music]
yeah here you go
hey yo you're welcome i'm going back in
to make our little base here like wait
can we put gold armor on the strider
uh is it the usual
what you call it the usual like horse
armor
it should be different armor is it uh
okay
i guess yeah right hi everybody
in the lab what are you looking at
yeah they're having a nice little bath
it's like an onsen for them
at the hospital later losers
we should make a hug
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
he's just a little anemic that's all
he's fine he needs a nap and uh
oh he's cold i don't know
[Music]
if you want to build him a little
paddock
maybe we can build him a path hey girl a
lava path
yeah look um
what does he mean can he walk on magma
rock because that might be
yes
we can perfect it later but for now yeah
thanks for your service buddy he's cute
i know right maybe we can connect over
here too
[Music]
oh the fence
that's too bad oh
something's like where'd homie go that
looks like that's how
he died
oh
[Music]
sorry my my keyboard is in japanese okay
hold on back to the game
okay he's landed the eagle has landed
he's okay okay i'll go find him i see
him here alive
okay yeah he's as long as he's alive
it's okay
wait but how are we going to get him up
here i'm going to make a real fancy
well i have all the materials
[Music]
this is tough huh i should hire um i'm
going to build me a house
i want to stay from kelly one below i
want to be the hero
yes
uh our neighbors are here our neighbors
say hi
oh i have gold i'm out of uh
oh um i have a pickaxe do you want mine
okay oh yes thank you uh yeah
is it okay thanks
i wanted
chest okay i'll bring some sun from
my house i'll be playing disappoint
thanksgiving
we'll get them we'll get them what
should i do you want to name the sign
here
oh yeah this time yeah
i think he's right below you right below
okay so as long as you make your way
down
nice and easy you'll be fine all right
i'll go save our friend
well that looks cool hang on
okay um this is gonna take some brain
power but i got it
done oh
oh i think we can only give the gold to
the villagers i guess not these random
pigs
yeah i tried
i was like oh you tried to give it to
anything and this is
this is there's probably a roundabout
way to go let's just keep moving this
way
maybe i can make some stairs wait hold
on just kidding
okay no i can't there are no stairs that
will be made here uh it's okay
i'm gonna move to i'm gonna move this
way until hang on
it's fine we got it what if i can build
actual stairs after this
is this soul sand
you could be a architect oh thank you
architect watson yeah
i could take one
no i didn't die i just came out to get
some wood
are making their way to save strider yes
is that his name that's what he's called
you can name him if you want though
i like that it's okay i keep
straightening him
you don't know right let me get it on
camera
okay um
getting getting closer i bet i can put
uh you made that jump
yeah brave it's not bad
i know i gotta save our homie
should i extend the i have two more
chests should i put it
um
wait where'd he go
is he moving is he on the move i mean
he can't be far he's not going to be far
right that far
yeah yeah he's dead no he's not he's not
dead
with
yeah you made it you made it down
hello i come in peace i wonder i wonder
if there's another village that's closer
oh i guess that one we found is the
closest one yeah
let's look at the tunnels no i found it
i'm riding on him but i'm on fire i'm on
fire
[Music]
yeah i caught on fire i found them but
then i caught on fire oh
i don't know where i am um
ah
are you okay good uh we're fine we're
fine we're fine
did you die you play calm we're calm
we're calm we're cool collected we're
comically assistants
[Applause]
[Laughter]
sounds good this area is familiar i
don't know where i am but there's a
village i'm going to go look in it
a village wait did you wait yeah are you
all that you're [\h__\h] small
i don't know where i am actually oh yeah
go to a high place and look for the h
and that's the entrance to the tunnel
and you can just take a minecart in
there from uh
the emergency exit i need to get where
you are
okay do you see the h
okay uh i'm in a village hold on a
second i need i i take it
right now hang on i'm good i'm with
strider and i got callie's stuff
oh thank you you got it you're gonna
have to move my face
where are you yeah how are you gonna get
can he jump
i see a house i i this is surrender's
house
i don't know how i'm gonna do this can
we swim up lava probably
not right all right so it is all my
fault
no no no no no no just pop down there i
think
he'll be there probably wait i should
have my pickaxe here
yes yes yes yes yes
hi friends
i require christian snow where are you
where what's going on
i want to see you all don't panic
don't panic don't panic oh get out of
here
he's scared okay um assistance is
required
in the netherlands oh i'm okay are you
okay
you want to give us your coordinates
i'm right outside i can see all your
names um i
um there's a gas do you see
oh huh oh they're on fire
oh wow you guys take out the gas which
one that's that
thing but it like went away oh i see it
hmm it
i think so it's getting closer to the
pig village because there was the path
that went
sort of in this direction over there
she's down there well i'm i'm i'm i can
see you guys names
right down here well i'm so scared i
don't like hiding
i don't know you're fine it's fine it's
all good okay i see what's in this
tennis racket
i'm going towards it like over there
i don't think our friend will leave i
think we can leave him here so i'm just
gonna
yeah just park him there it's his
parking spot
yes that's a really far far a parking
spot hello
can you guys clear my uh headspace here
why are you good oh yep oh wait it's
good
okay yeah yeah welcome back
we got a house we got a panic room and
i'll be back soon away oh wait i could
read it on the strider but he's so fast
i don't trust myself well if you guys
want to play gotcha before we go i got i
brought a bunch of gold
i brought some gold too that sounds fun
but ready
we'll wait for cali to get back and then
we can go thanks guys
then we can exit does anybody have a
chest i can put cali's stuff in there
thank you for doing that by the way i
will make it up to you
oh no worries yeah it's okay i'll put it
in uh what did you
have that um i just want my nether
stuff like uh to build my house with
cool things like uh there were some
i feel so stupid why didn't i put that
stuff in chest before i get
second time i'm silly
i'll come help in just a second
building a nice path to the gacha
welcome back
i'm here thank you everyone
for a second i felt another
let me know if i missed anything i think
you got everything thank you
write to me baked potatoes yay i'm
hungry
yeah so strider is down there where we
left him he won't really go anywhere i
don't think oh okay
oh i wonder um yeah i guess there's not
much we can do about that huh darn it
i want it to be i can come back when i
don't have anything
yeah yeah yeah i can build like
staircases for him to get him something
very slowly he doesn't die outside of
lava right
so we can just build him a really really
long long staircase
yeah yeah they have enough rocks
nobody's here but that's a project for
another time i suppose
yeah we'll save them later oh gold goes
where are you kara i'm go where are you
guys
yeah ah okay we're going to stop right
here
oh i just okay i just left let me get
some stuff away i'll come back
okay i'm right before the ah yeah i want
to go put some stuff away too
actually you should put your armor be
safe yeah oh okay that's right oh that
came off huh
um i'll continue to mine the path to the
village
sorry i lost the gold snap
[Music]
oh yeah do you need some gold armor so
they don't like that question
is
here i'm just going to put my things in
my chest no
oh yeah it's gone huh oh well
i know i used it i panicked and i used
it oh it's okay
oh that was yours oh my god i'm so sorry
it's okay you're good thanks for having
me i have a dog
you don't have to it's okay we have a
craft table at the home i'm panicking
i don't have one yeah it's not that far
okay what does it do anyway i don't know
i don't know yeah it is very beautiful
purple
do i really want to waste all my gold at
the gacha again do i have i have gold
for you
me too let's go let's go oh why don't
this railroad oh it is i thought it was
the stairs
uh make this
wait
[Music]
i have i know i don't have any rock
no i haven't just mounted them from here
is it called a rock
or rack rack yes wreck
like quack yeah
yeah that's another wreck are you guys
should i take the pig village path uh
yes yes
yeah okay i'll follow the torches
nice shiny swords you got there buddy
oops
[Music]
oh so i guess nether spawn points can be
used instead of beds i didn't know about
that
we used the crying obsidian to make
those oh
the crying one um agreed
it's okay we'll find some more killed me
oh we can mine it back with our
diamond tic tacs i brought mine wait
where is
almost died almost died all of them have
gold armor
uh you know this is where the ender
dragon is
i'm just making it so we don't actually
know okay good idea
this is not where he is where's the
ender dragon i want to see him
um maybe it's for another time
how do you summon him what do you got to
say then we have to find that
gate thing and then like complete it and
then like
you gotta go find him i'm ready to go
knock on his door
i think we have to be like all diamond
everything to do that right
and no well like for our own safety
basically uh uh i watched like
20 hours of uh and and
uh rta
and the dragon rta so i know how to do
it
but we are not we're not very friendly
why you kind of make a different kind of
portal
okay but you need a lot of ender pearls
and there's a
few ways to get the end of pearls but it
takes a long time
oh
like eventually
are you able to move sir sir you look
like you're having a hard time down
there
ready are you okay do you need help
getting back up sir see it
thank you well i hear it oh i hear lola
okay oh there he is oh he's gonna break
our bridge i think he's gone
oh he's right there yeah go there yeah
hello i'm at me hi mm-hmm
oh we taking down the the big jellyfish
in the sky
gummy uh that would be the safe choice
go do it girl i don't think i don't
think i can make that shot i can't make
this shot he's still looking a little
closer
no it's so far away i don't think i can
make that
there's our other portal too nice let me
shoot him out in the open
well here we are probably
no he's too far up where are all the
villagers there were so many here before
they died what no i don't know
there's some homies over here maybe
they're sleeping maybe it's night time
for them
yeah where's their house do you have a
crafting they're they're training the
little ones uh
no but i can make one i think
hold on
hey run away all right i have one
i'll put it
give you guys thanks amelia for the free
gold
yeah big ups three you get three how do
you
thanks oh you're thinking sorry oh oh
he doesn't he really doesn't like that
hey girl why is he a girl
it's fine i'll help all right nice
wonder why he's absolutely oh
yeah i have one heart we'll see what
happens wait do you need food
yeah who's that girl okay i'll give you
some phone i meant i'm not i'll miss
where are you kelly yeah i am sorry
bring any food i thought we were just
gonna do gotcha so i didn't bring it
that's okay that's so many steaks
thank you i have a lot of pic or cows at
home
it's okay me once who god's out with me
i do where's the gotcha dude okay
i have i actually don't have any gold
there's not what happened there's a man
on fire
boy you in the golden pen you're in the
gold helmet here
come back sorry amelia i think when you
gave me the gold you accidentally picked
it up again
i don't have it yes give me something
sorry
ah are you okay i'm okay
thank you thank you thank you big ops
thank you welcome
i don't care i have a boy that's a boy
over here
yeah it's probably just dead dudes huh
i see one he has a gold helmet come here
oh he's running away
why are you scared of me oi here
no he's hurt i died oh my god kelly
i'll grab your gold
oh my god take this oh i'll pick the
steak
yeah take the steak okay
i was just going to give him gold and
then he turned on me
i think i think if you're holding gold
they'll attack you because they're the
they're not the villagers it was the
villager though it was a regular dude he
wasn't like a zombie-like guy or
anything
not a single good thing came out of this
one i did something weird this one looks
rich
yeah this one looks rich let's see if it
gives me anything
what was that a blog what bro that's so
good
okay give me something good not a single
good thing
i did something weird with my keyboard
string i think it's the end for your boy
on this one here yeah we should we
should probably call it soon because
cali's got a stream yeah time to
wrap it up
wait did did anyone find any uh the
trader
that's out right there i thought i did
he started blasting nice i didn't drop
anything actually that's good because
then i can take the catcher home and
don't waste it
all right we can go back i'm going back
one more gotcha okay
okay
[Music]
i'm in that same village too i got lost
again
[Laughter]
somehow i doubt that you tried this one
are you still in the villa are you still
in the villagers yeah i'm trying to i'm
looking for watson's
uh tennis racket oh okay okay
terrace rocket
oh my god wait where did you thank you
because
yeah clearly this is the wrong direction
got it
okay are we gonna do operation find
kelly
sorry i will find it don't worry i'm
getting up high
what did they gain you know okay so
listen i wasn't
i wasn't wearing any gold armor and
apparently that's a thing oh
yeah yeah remember that's why i said
should we give you a gold armor
it all makes sense now yes
i'll make some i promise i'll start
minding my own stuff i don't want you
guys to have to do everything for me
no no no help we help yes we help each
other
yes team we are one
we are one thanks guys i want to be good
at video games
maybe someday
gosh where is watson's tennis racket
wow but oh i do
wow minecraft is so pretty another is so
[Music]
i see an incredibly tall building so
this must be the right way
like a ridiculously loud walk building
kiara
[Music]
oh no
wait how did you drown you drowned from
my house
i just kind of watched it
what was i supposed to do
all right gotta call the left guard
shall wait for you out here
rubber stream is going to be a sleepy
stream
it's okay it'll be fun
all right we're all here we're home yay
can do the the ending right here by the
tennis racket
i know it's a mining i'm not a mining
i'm a magnifying magnifying glass yeah
i'll put some stuff on it you guys will
see
yeah it's a beautiful magnifying glass
it looks like a splash racket
thank you hey where are we meeting no
fast track
on top here up on the stairs up top i'm
in
do you want to do a minecraft stream
with me where we build a huge
chess field uh oh my goodness
sir we can do that yeah okay
ah yes the chest feels to always
commemorate that legendary trust game
professional channel oh here callie i
have i think this is your stuff
bye oh yeah thank you
thanks guys oh i'm sorry i don't mean to
meet you
all right good here i have a present for
you too a present for me
look over here turn look at this oh
[Music]
you can because you can draw it and then
you can just have it drawn and then you
can shoot it
oh baby
do you want to know i want to give you a
present too so here you go
yay purple doors
yeah accent i just changed my door to
the purple one it matches
your purpose
sorry i'm peanut color i'm in santa
claus
cute thank you santa can i stay
on your lap okay sure absolutely come on
what do you want for christmas little
girl um
you me i have two crying
maybe she wants me to hold some way she
wants me as a friend
flowers he just got friendzoned here
i just want i just want a friendship
that's all
keep friendship friendship forever and
ever
yeah guys
gather up okay
[Laughter]
it's magnifying glass i'm sorry i know
it now i understand now
yep yep wait wait ah there we go
yay oh
we didn't yeah take a screenshot
previously i want to take one now
look yeah i'll take off my i'll take off
like oh i don't have spots in my mvp
unfortunately who was that
[Laughter]
there you go this is fine
[Music]
hey successful another trip
[Applause]
yay
[Music]
thank you for watching
well i'm gonna play uh well we're
planning on it me and gouda are planning
on playing uh minecraft together next
week so tune in
oh yeah yeah i'll be there
yeah it's gonna be fun so yeah come on
i'm having another
holo japan collaboration next week
with whom ah secret
okay cool
schedule for me will be out uh tomorrow
or the day after tomorrow yeah
new week almost saturday
all right okay thank you everybody for
[Applause]
[Music]
watching
you