[Music]
K by the time you see this this Cafe
collab isn't available anymore but I
went to Cafe asan which had a collab
with illustrator I Ami mama in Japan
especially Tokyo they have cafes like
this all over everything was cutely
decorated at the tables towards the wall
even had hammocks I went alone so sadly
I could only really order one thing the
drinks look really nice too and you get
some gacha extras for free even if you
don't buy any of this merch so here we
go this is my loot oh so cute no I Ami M
what the hell I wonder a classic
the yummy the signatures are printed by
the way it came with a salad little
hamburgers and some spaghetti which I
think is like Napoleon like a ketchup
sauce so for the drink I had some soda
float I love floats do you guys mix the
ice cream with the drink or eat it first
I do both