[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
sorry about that
[Laughter]
man it always happens i always forget
about it
need to hide that
layer in obs
oops
accidents
can happen
or show
hello hello everyone let me put on some
musical
um
okay you probably
remember this from yesterday this track
[Music]
uh then i didn't have
well there's a [\h__\h] fly in my room
because i had the
window open that's a really fat fly
my cats have to go get that fly
eat them up eat them up beat them up
but this track is so cute isn't it
so cute
probably aiming for the pizza that i
have right in front of me because um i
just warmed that up that's and i was
trying to speed eat it
because
um
right before the stream i realized
wait my stream is starting
i still haven't eaten breakfast because
i was trying to pack my
my suitcase for the past two hours
oh god fly look up go away
and i didn't have the time or i kind of
forgot about eating i don't know i was
too occupied with um
packing and packing and packing
[Music]
um breakfast yeah it's pizza pizza
breakfast at 4 p.m uh
i had pizza last night and
i have like half of it left over
so but i left it over kind of on purpose
so that i could eat it today
traveling is stressful it ironically is
stressful yeah
[Music]
um
i'm not
actually not quite done so
so we can't go on forever unfortunately
today um i'm just planning for like an
hour
maximum
[Laughter]
yeah i'm not
done i'm not done eating and i'm not
done packing
um
i still got time but not time to stream
so
that's that
um
oops no no it's okay it's okay like i i
have it all under control
i may not have the weather of the
motives under control but i do have
my
my my my packing process under control
um
yeah no no one hour stream maximum
and i i'm just gonna read some super
chats in a moment as well in between um
i guess doing some chit chat i wanna i
wanted to do more
um but you know what
we're bringing
two switches we're bringing uh a capture
card we're bringing my [\h__\h] heavy ass
gaming laptop so chances are that we'll
be streaming anyway
next week
if the internet allows it but yeah
um
we could even if the internet is not
good enough for streaming we could maybe
even like
pre-record
while we're there like us playing i
don't know mario kart or whatever
and then
recording that for an hour and then
uploading it
over the course of whatever 24 hours
however slow that internet is
and uploading it as a stream
yeah oh we could do that
[Music]
yeah well i have some other content i
have like
um
some short videos more like [\h__\h] posts
i'm glad you guys like the idea
this is not pre-recorded i have some
[\h__\h] posts prepared and
one
longer
[\h__\h] post
um
so that's four videos in total
yeah
and some of them
like after the vr collab yesterday
i was like yo yo yo yo yo yo before
before we go
before everyone leaves can we quickly
record something so that i can upload it
during my vacation so um we recorded
something in vr
um
i had like
two stupid ideas
[Music]
which were really awkward to record but
i think as a video
it's
because it's so awkward it makes it
funny
so you will see what i mean probably can
i take a bite into my pizza please i'm
sorry i wanted to finish eating before
but i kind of forgot i'm sorry
[Music]
my
pretty good
day two is still pretty good
it's not tuna
it's pineapple
i know i know
you you
pineapple pizza is great
and it it's kind of tropical you know
it's literally called pizza hawaii so
i'm just getting myself into the mood
hmm
[Music]
thanks to the people who agree with me
the border is still very crispy nice
wow
[Music]
it's actually crispier than yesterday i
like it
[Music]
dory
yeah unfortunately there's no corn on
this hawaii pizza
that is
a big disappointment i guess
um
[Music]
you know
i don't even know i'm still in my
pajamas i don't even know what i'll wear
to the airport
um
[Music]
no no
because i
i was thinking
because we have some problems with the
weight
the seaplane allows less weight than the
actual
airplane to the maldives
so
i can't even max out my suitcase
i think but
um i'm thinking i should wear my
heaviest garment
so that i don't have to put it into the
suitcase right
but the heaviest garment is i think my
prettiest garment that i'm bringing this
time
um
so if i wear it
during my travel then it's probably not
gonna be like
sweaty at the end of the whole trip
um
and then then i probably won't wear it
so what did i bring it for
i probably won't wear it during the
actual vacation just during the trip you
know what i mean wash it
i don't know if they'll have a washing
machine available
they probably if anything maybe they'll
have um a cleaning service and me and
reina yesterday were talking and we were
like both like
i don't want to spend any more money on
this trip
because like
you know we kind of we kind of were like
okay okay cool the hotel is expensive
but we that's worth it it's a nice hotel
the trip the flight to the maldives is
like okay not not that bad
but then
we would we were in our mind we were set
with okay this is how much we're
spending and then suddenly like recently
we realized that the seaplane is more
expensive than the flight to the
maldives itself
um
and we were like what the actual [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] sucks and
and because the weather is gonna be [\h__\h]
anyway i don't wanna waste any more
[\h__\h] money
and cleaning service i think is usually
pretty expensive in hotels
i mean i know that would just be like a
little dime in what we're spending in
total but still like i'm like out of
principle i'm saying no
boats uh speed boats
it's like an option
um
with combining with like a domestic
flight or something like that i read
but
speedboat only really works if this if
the island is really close
and even then the price said that it
would still be
the same
which dad
i guess is because you have to add a
domestic flight onto it
yeah
anyway um
[Music]
why don't we fly because we're bringing
luggage flying with our
own
body
is difficult when you have to bring a
[\h__\h] suitcase
fake chicken pink
[Music]
yeah
like how would we carry
one of those huge suitcases anywhere if
we need our hands for flying hmm
[Music]
we need quite the
no that doesn't work like
it doesn't work think logically
even if we carry like it on our backs or
like lifted with our legs
it's not realistic a 20 20 kilogram
suitcase
being carried by
let's just say 40 kilogram girls
[Music]
it's so heavy
it's long distance you
[Music]
know
um
i didn't weigh my suitcase i i weighed
my suitcase alone but i didn't weigh it
with the stuff inside yet because i
didn't finish packing
i hope
i helped 20 kilos enough
um
i hope so
i'm really worried about the gaming
laptop i feel like just by lifting it it
feels like 8 kilo
just a gaming laptop feels like [\h__\h]
8 kilogram
um
oh
i'm almost done
[Music]
oh i didn't quite look it up the weight
yeah
my arms are noodles yes so what
show up
[Music]
my swimsuit alone enough no
both me and dana are bringing like four
swimsuits
one is not enough no we have to
look different each day okay
yeah
i almost wanted to bring a five swim
switch
[Music]
no one i'm worried about um
since i don't know much about it
[Music]
i know
there's like it's a tropical island
right so
i wonder if there's a lot of dangerous
um
uh mosquitoes
that carry like some dangerous disease
that are gonna kill me
[Music]
if i'm just gonna be fine if i just put
some anti-mosquito spray or something on
me
because i don't think i'm like
vaccinated against
like those crazy tropical
diseases thingies
um
[Music]
yeah i don't know i looked up like like
what vaccinations are necessary there's
no vaccination that is a hundred percent
must at least not if i'm coming from
austria like if you come from some some
certain countries then you may um be
required a specific uh
vaccination against the yellow fever for
example because they just don't want to
bring it to the mothers i guess
um
but that's not the case for austria i
just saw that there's some vaccinations
that are recommended but hmm
not necessary
[Music]
well i can't get one now
do you think a repellent is enough
[Music]
yeah i would think a resort would do
their best to like also put repellents
there
[Music]
okay but
i was thinking of buying one there
because i'm guessing like maybe they
have something specific
in the motives
like i'm probably just gonna buy it at
the airport or so
hmm
[Music]
something specific for
the kind of mosquitoes that they have
there i don't know
they probably have better products
against it than we have in austria
because we don't have a problem with
that
[Music]
there's tiger mosquitoes that's that
sounds scary that sounds like a really
big [\h__\h] mosquito oh my god what does
that do is that dangerous
they have killer mosquitoes
what
like mosquitoes that actually kill when
they stay sting you
step up
[Music]
the [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
why are you killing a doctor dotting me
huh
[Music]
i'm from austria okay
i don't know what
there is out there i mean think about
australia
they have some crazy [\h__\h] in australia
killers spiders and all kinds of [\h__\h]
what do i know what they have in
tropical islands man that i've never
been to before
we have some they could have some
dangerous [\h__\h] there too
wow
and
you laugh about
mosquitoes hahaha but
there's like
tiny tiny tiny [\h__\h] jellyfish that
are tinier than your fingernail in the
ocean that can kill you when you touch
them okay
so don't laugh at me
[Music]
don't laugh at me
yeah yeah
no
but now
to scare me even more to freak me out
even more
not like i need any more stress or or
worries about this vacation let me look
up
maldives
mosquitoes
do you need mosquito repellent in the
mountains why most amount of resort
islands fumigate for mosquitoes even the
most five star luxury resorts have an
ongoing battle against the mosquito
population so be sure to bring mosquito
repellent that contains deet
d-e-e-t what the [\h__\h] is d-e-d-e-e-t
[Music]
what is that
[Laughter]
what's beat
indeed it sounds like funny
but even if they fumigate it that sounds
like it's fumigated inside but you can't
really feel me katie all the air are
outside so
[Music]
maldith
you guys are so stupid
really powerful okay you see i don't
even know if we have that kind of
repellent here
especially on a sunday
sunday shops are closed so i'm just
gonna buy it in in the maldives i think
[Music]
let me write to elena
that includes
deet
let me let me screenshot that
for
elena
also what what currency do they have in
the maldives
[Music]
what currency do they even have
what's the currency
[Music]
currency multiples
maldivian roofia that sounds cute
roofia
what can you guys look at the i don't
know how those things like how to read
those things can you guys
tell me is it smarter for me right now
to change euro to roofia or
yen to the via
because i still have
i still have some yen cash quite a lot
i don't know which one would i i i i win
more from
okay does someone know like how to look
that up
i don't have a credit card euro yen is
super weak like both whatever you mean
is that good or bad
[Music]
yeah yeah yen is low is that good
stonks euros stronger
so should i change in euro
okay when when when the thing that i
want i have is low
and then yeah i guess i'm losing money
okay then i'll change to euro
but that kind of can change in one day
anyway right
it could be different tomorrow
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
i'm supposedly very used to traveling
but with the maldives i i feel like i'm
very nervous about it like when i travel
to greece it was
you know it's close it's in europe and
and there were some worries about
um
some things like how to get to the hotel
or so but we ended up just taking a
freaking taxi so
you know
in in grace i wasn't so worried but but
with the mothers i'm kind of worried
um
it's i don't know it's just like a crazy
destination in my mind like why did i
choose them all this because it sounds
like a [\h__\h] dream vacation and now
i'm going there in the monsoon okay but
i i told reyna we're not gonna we're not
gonna think about it anymore
we're not gonna talk about it we're not
gonna think about it
just don't don't think about it it's
gonna be it's gonna be fine it's gonna
be
fine fine fine totally fine oh my god
it's already half past okay i'm so sorry
guys i want to spend more of you guys
more time with you guys but i'm like
really busy and um yeah yesterday last
night i was preparing
uh for the uh for the for the videos and
i was recording something where the
deadlines were during my vacation
um
yeah trying to get everything done
beforehand
yeah i'm not gonna be late no no no no
no that's gonna be okay
um
[Music]
um so let me read the super chat from
the members when i read i need to read
valkyrie and i need to read the kiwi
super chats i think that's where i
started kiwi
[Music]
read two switches so the title isn't
click
i mean i could still change the title if
i wanted to
[Music]
also i i looked um from my fan art
folder uh for all the fan art i saved
and i um
i sorted out everything that's like in a
swimsuit on the beach and all that and
made a folder and then uploaded it
online so i can easily reach it and
tweet like you know huh i'm i'm on the
beach
look at the great weather you know need
some stuff for tweets and thumbnails
so i sorted all of that out that i can
so that i can pick it out easily
smart ryan i'm so smart
i'm so smart in some regards but then
really stupid in other regards
don't
don't blame me please
[Music]
all right
i also have some orange juice right here
ah there's a [\h__\h] flight trying to
drown itself in there right now get out
of there get out of there i saved it but
i also killed it so [\h__\h] you
is this how it's gonna be
is this how it's gonna be mosquitoes
drowning themselves in my mocktails at
the beach
you know i'm kind of worried about
what to wear in front of reyna
i don't have
you know you know because like i'm i'm
thinking of the fact that it's going to
be [\h__\h] humid and 30 degrees
so
um i really have to wear as little as
possible
but
um
you know i have like all kinds of cute
thin
thin material short
kind of tops and all that
but they're like
they're
like you know
i i want to dress to impress but
i don't i don't have so much that
impresses you know what i mean like um
i don't really have like a designer like
[Music]
[Laughter]
my 30 degrees summer clothes are all
like
like really cheap and i think they're
cute but they're cheap they i think they
probably look cheap but they're really
cute like i love them and i think they
they are perfect for the vacation and on
being on the beach and all that but
they're they probably look a little bit
cheap
um
[Music]
i'm probably thinking about it too much
but
but but but what if what if she shows up
with i don't know gucci
what if she wears gucci and i wear i
wear h m
you know whatever
it's probably okay it's probably good
it's probably okay
[Music]
i have too many worries man
i wanted i want to i want to i don't
want to stand out that's the like
cheap cheap beach you know mm-hmm
but it's okay it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay
nobody will notice
i'll just look cute
i'll look cute with my beach fashion but
beach fashion like
beach fashion is beach fashion man
[Music]
i don't even know if there's such a
thing as gucci beach fashion
[Music]
i mean they have they probably have
swimsuits but
whatever i'm worrying too much about
[\h__\h] that's not even important
[Music]
slap the supreme little goat
gucci belt cause of that i don't have a
gucci belt
i i wouldn't even be too scared to even
enter a store like that
[Music]
i entered um
one of those stories before but you know
how much [\h__\h] courage it took me and
then i i read like online um
reviews of that store
uh that said like you get treated like
[\h__\h] if you don't already wear a
designer because they look at you
in a condescending way
um and and feel like you're not gonna
buy anything anyway
and that that made me really nervous it
makes me really nervous about going into
any of those kind of stores
apparently yeah yeah but but then see i
went in there with like
really actually cheap clothes i wore i
wore um
i wore a cute dress from like some kind
of online cheap brand uh
called um
l-e-d-i-n
but it looked really cute and i went in
there and you know what happened even
though that dress was probably like 15
or something okay it was a bit more
maybe 30 dollars you know what what what
what happened i walked in there looks
like looking absolutely fabulous and
cute
with my cheap dress and um
the
lady tenant greeting me she looks at me
and she's like looking me at me with
these excited eyes like literally hearts
in her eyes and she's like i love your
style
so cute and i'm like oh my god thank you
thank you
you don't need to wear
like
designer clothes
that cost three thousand dollars if you
know
how to choose the right clothes and how
to coordinate them the right way
into something that looks like you have
an idea and a sense for fashion and
style
hell yeah baby
[Laughter]
yes
but that's some that's that's pretty
difficult to
to get down
to nail that look to look like
somewhat sophisticated or cute or
something like that without wearing
expensive clothes it's it's a bit
difficult but it's manageable it works
it totally works
become a fashionista
anyway i wanted to read super chats yeah
yeah yeah so let me read
unknown
oh wait we're reading from kiwi right
now by the way i hope that's incorrect
with the assumption that that's the most
recent uh the oldest one that i have to
read isn't this cute the sweaters oh my
god
we look so cute
[Music]
cute
oh we have a
korean name
papa go to the rescue
[Music]
it's a
if if japanese english is is
jinglish what is korean japanese
durian
[Music]
crank
no corianas could be anything
could just be korean and english
[Music]
japan
japarian
[Music]
japan guru
sky dankest in the game of creed
dankeson
oh i hope you're
uh feeling better by now so you got a
nasty cold but that was days ago so
you're probably feeling better right now
jim tracy thank you so much kfb duncan
oh happy birthday
alex thank you soon jensen thank you
soon so thank you for the pinky hi today
is my birthday
also belated happy birthday to you i
want to thank you for always loving kfp
and keeping hard working on everything i
will never regret that i joined this one
family by the way can i have my employee
number please yes of course
wait what day was that ah it was the
13th of may but when you sent the super
chat it was probably the 14th right
feign sue are you here
so you know what your your
your um
your number your employee number will be
five one four
because that should be your birthday if
it was actually five one three then feel
free to just take one five one three but
i think it's five one four
because the stream was on the thirteen
for me but for you it was probably the
14th
okay
happy feeling his birthday
and thank you thank you so much for
being part of kfp
hope you're enjoying your time here and
enjoying the streams as always
[Music]
pepsi duncan i am the center and mr vic
thank you w korean duncan canada goose
[Music]
bananas
why is there so many banana stickers
saskatchewan is that a
human thing a mummy
viewer thing
what was up with those bananas
justin fine duncan
or just in time
[Music]
there's like 10 or 15 people who sent
banana stickers as super chats but it's
all names that i don't really recognize
so maybe it's a
it's a movie thing but miss chat likes
to give her bananas really
really
oh my god
i don't know if that's cute or weird
[Music]
nintendo
yeah i guess because supposedly it's a
berry but it's not really what you would
think is a berry
but mummy likes berries so in order to
tease her you guys give her berries but
just not quite the berries that you
would think about
if you think about berries you don't
think about bananas right so it's like
kind of like a a troll
here you have a berry enjoy it
and that's probably
the thinking process
i get it i get it
hey robin hood thank you for the pinkies
it says i always had matching halloween
costumes with my twin sister growing up
what you have a twin sister so cool
i mean i can see how
if you grow up as twins you like i'm i'm
there's like two types of twins
the ones who don't want to match with
their twin all the time and the ones who
uh want to match with their twin on
purpose because they agree and think it
looks cute
but yeah i understand both of it but i
feel like the the whole idea of
twins just always wearing the same [\h__\h]
is too much of a fantasy man your mom
made you okay yeah cause like
i don't know i think i think um media
likes to portray twins that way
um
but it's mostly
probably in reality most twins don't
want to dress the same way their their
twin does right yeah
um
it's it's just a
a nice spot but it doesn't really happen
that much probably
my mom made us do it when we were little
we don't anymore you're also a twin oh
my god
yeah as as kids
maybe as if you're like i don't know
three years old or four years old then
you as a child probably don't even quite
understand what's happening
and and your mom can still have fun with
dressing you up the same way i probably
would do the same thing
it would be so cute but if they were you
know if i had twin babies and i would
dress them up the same way that would be
honestly the cutest thing ever
yeah but at some point you have to stop
you have to stop at some point
[Music]
um
i feel like a lot of you guys were like
first um
enjoying the the low-key girl talk and
like oh this is interesting
more please i don't understand it but
interesting but then at some point it
probably reached levels
where you guys are like
what
this is i regret asking for more of this
we went too far
i feel like around the
somewhere somewhere we went a little bit
um
too deep
but if you ask for it you're getting the
whole program okay no complaints
and now you say more yeah yeah sure but
when we were talking about it about a
lot of you guys were like what the [\h__\h]
girls would what the [\h__\h]
you only want the good parts
but you'll get the full package if
anything
[Music]
i don't know i already forgot the whole
conversation
you know we talked about waxing and bras
and hair
but there was something weird that we
talked about but i think i kind of like
pushed it out of my memory
um
[Music]
you promised the wax moment yeah and i
told
the people who were coming over told
them
we're doing this feel free to join and
not let me suffer alone
they
they can't just let her suffer alone
there you know we're also entertainers
in the end so just for entertainment
sake
they have to join in
and mummy was like uh one one spot only
like please like like you know one one
one r vaccine thingy only and i'm like
no at least two
like one that's over in the second you
can't just do one you're doing at least
two mummy
the good thing is i barely have
hair left on my body so
i'm just the one waxing i'm not the one
being waxed
[Laughter]
inflecting pain on others but not
inflicting it on myself hooray hooray
[Music]
what am i waxing well it would be
probably the best to wax some leg hair i
would say
if possible some leg hair
we can also do arms i guess
worst case
but that that sounds like it will hurt
for a while nah we'll find a good spot
james walk with dynasty
[Music]
a i need like a basketball
thingy
basket
somewhere here so i can
slam dunk my
my thumbnails in there
[Music]
next up we have
um
this one i think
which is kind of mixed in with some
members super chats but that's okay
uh
this is happening by the way on the 17th
just as a reminder the collab is
starting on the 17th
pre-travel pre-travel where she going
i'm going to the maldives
said it about a million times but i'm
going to the maldives
yeah finally it's like i woke up today
and i was like
hey what the [\h__\h] i'm going to the
motives
so surreal
it feels so surreal that's that feels to
me that was always a destination that
i'm probably never gonna visit
never
but here we are
[Music]
it's a dream vacation but let's see how
much of a dream vacation it will really
be
how how dreamy it really will be
[Music]
i need to bring a
book um i have one book i'll bring that
one book
bring that one book that i've been that
i brought uh to the
to the spa
um
trip with my best friend and didn't
finish reading
yeah yeah that one was exactly the
tolkien book yeah yeah you guys remember
you guys remember everything wow
it was the smaller stories the smaller
talking stories with some hobbits yeah
there's some hobbits in there
[Music]
and then i'm gonna bring my switch to
and i wanna bring my
my ipad
but
because i feel like i don't wanna like
when i'm on the beach and wanna watch
some netflix
don't wanna bring my gaming laptop it's
[\h__\h] huge but i
i don't think my i can take that weight
like the ipad and
and uh
the
the laptop
i'm gonna first check how much it weighs
in the end and if i still have some
some
um
[Music]
what's it what's the word if i just have
some weight
to play with some room to play with then
i'll bring my ipad to bring an entire
computer live yeah i don't want to bring
that much i'm only bringing the gaming
laptop for streaming
i wouldn't bring it otherwise otherwise
i would just bring my maybe my switch
and my
and my ipad
i wouldn't break the bring the whole
laptop
[Music]
and the switch
um for i'm bringing the capture card as
well
which is so stupid
but yeah
probably probably bringing the capture
card too
[Music]
my streaming pc that's too [\h__\h] heavy
yeah the [\h__\h] adapter of the gaming
laptop alone
feels like five kilogram
or maybe more
it's like a huge [\h__\h] chunk
why is that
why is that charger adapter
so [\h__\h] huge and chalky i've never
had such a huge chunky
huge adapter before
it's like a literal brick that you can
build a house with
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is up with that the gaming
um
[Music]
how old is your laptop it's a new laptop
it's a new gaming where i bought it last
year it was the newest model
but it's just [\h__\h] huge
it needs the power yeah
i
i don't know man
it's so big
[Music]
it needs a big power
oh yeah what's the what does that what
does the
electric socket look like in the
maldives
i hope they have travel adapters man at
the hotel
[Music]
um
yeah
what are you what are you dot dot
dotting me about
i'm writing to elena
uk type
why are you doctoring
what did i say
what
now you're just doing it on purpose
[Music]
oh man okay sorry i wrote something to
elena
um
i already read the barcati pinky didn't
i
yeah i did i did and then the patsy one
i think i read as well
um
where does it start actually
here
and feel like salving your recipe
i just got up early to catch alive i'm
still lying in my oven so i hope i don't
fall asleep again it's so warm and cozy
in here
oh was it your legs that i ate uh
the day before yesterday felix
i should have left you in the oven a
little bit longer i'm not sure like you
were a little bit pinkish inside though
did you see my tweet guys
it looked delicious didn't it but i
wasn't sure like how how serious i
should take the whole
don't leave any pinkishness to it
uh how serious i should take that
and i wasn't sure like i was so
paranoid that i wasn't sure if what i
was looking at was even pink considered
pink or
or just normal flesh color
i don't know
dark meat tends to stay pink yeah some
of you guys told me that on twitter
so i was thinking maybe it was okay but
i didn't want to risk getting salmonella
right before my vacation you know
i yeah i heated i i had it in the oven
at like 220 degrees
celsius
or something i think it should be
celsius probably um
so oven heats 220 for like 40 minutes
which should be enough because
it was even a bit more than what the
what the
recipe told me
like five or ten minutes more
i think it said like leave it in the
oven for 30 to 35 minutes or so and i
left it like 40 minutes in the right
heat but
yeah but then it's still like on the
outside and even on the inside it had
some
weird colored parts and just wasn't sure
about it so i just ate some of it
that looked like the parts that looked
fine after putting it on the grill extra
like on the frying pan
i fried it for like 10 more minutes but
then i was like [\h__\h] i really don't have
any more time left i gotta prepare for
my valkyrie connect stream
no no it's not me being picky it's just
me not wanting to get [\h__\h] sick man
and me just still trying to figure out
you know all all the
cooking things
i don't have that much experience
cooking i'm just getting better recently
and trying many new things you know
[Music]
i'm not picky
um
are you saying felix style has someone
else no
i just i don't know
but i have to say a feeling see where
you were perfectly seasoned
um you originally had like um
an herb seasoning already on you that
was beautiful
and then i put some balsamico honey
um
onion
sauce on top of you felix so
really really good if that was you yummy
yummy yummy yummy on your skin was
really crispy i liked it a lot
[Music]
[Applause]
this is the first member that i
admit to have eaten
also to all the takadasis and my fellow
chimpkins i urge you to put the war
behind us at least during the collab
between our beloved attention priestess
let's make food not war i believe that
we can prove fried chicken's pair
wonderfully with takoyakis
um
not really in my books
for like if we are doing real talk
not in my books
i don't even like takoyaki to begin with
i don't like octopus eel
but maybe some other people like to
combine chicken with
no felix
that's a huge stretch
i i kind of know even if i lay aside my
personal preferences i cannot agree with
you
chicken and octopus
no that's too far felix i'm sorry but
but i i
i understand your hope for peace with
them and
we're still gonna have peace but we
don't have to eat chicken and octopus
together you know we don't have to eat
octopus at all let's just be
on good terms with them without eating
them
there doesn't necessarily have to be
a war between us
but thank you so much felix also nice to
see you here right now
hope you're doing well thank you
thank you
for two pinkies
japanese super chat but no texts
[Music]
foreign
i'm just going to finish the vacuum
super chat crispy chicken nuggets and
thank you thanks for watching good
morning to you too
[Music]
thank you always thank you so much
for
you watching are gonna be free what am i
gonna do with my gaza funds
i'm sure there will be like some
good ways of using it like real talk
uh
like even if you can't get us for free
i'm sure there's like other ways of
making good use of it
yeah
but you should be happy about it be
happy about us being
free
okay i'm so excited for the gifts
so excited
and actually until reading the script
for the stream i didn't even like know
or realize that we're even also getting
gifts from the viewers i just was aware
of the ones we're giving to each other
and the ones that we're asking for
directly from for
from valkyrie connect
i didn't know about the ones that we're
getting from you guys didn't know that
was also a thing
it's crazy i don't know why they're
giving us so much stuff
i don't understand like what
what's up with that it's crazy
[Music]
hmm oh
by the way for ina um after the stream
we talked about
uh i told her what i wished for from
valkyrie connect and she told me what
she wished for
but like you know how she said that she
thought that this was just like digital
and i thought so too originally but i i
cleared the up the misunderstanding
at some point because like after
because i thought it was digital only i
came up with some crazy ideas that
wouldn't really be possible in reality
so the management pointed out to me
several times that like sorry kiwama
this this present
it's not really manageable can you like
do something more realistic and i'm like
when at some point i realized oh
these people are actually giving us
these gifts
so i realized it eventually
and
um
uh
yeah got some
put put out some realistic ideas but
yeah apparently never realized it
never changed her wishes
and stayed with
like some
like
you know
ideas that you would implement digitally
but not in reality
um so uh i i i think i probably
shouldn't say what it was maybe she'll
say it eventually but the idea for
what she wanted from valkyrie connect
was like a really
like
relatively cheap and like
it was something that she doesn't even
need from from reality connect she could
ask someone else to get it for her
but i was like ina
you know
you should
you should ask for something bigger like
it's you should change it go go go go go
ask for a change like ask her something
proper
and she was like ah
you know a piece five would be nice and
i'm like yo get the [\h__\h] ps5 ask for
it maybe it's not too late like
no it's not about being modest it's just
about her not
like
changing it and not realizing it or like
like even when she realized she still
didn't change it
yeah um so i hope she i i told her
several times to do it and she was
considering it so i hope she did it by
now
because like i gave some crazy
ideas i gave like free ideas
um
within the budget which was a big budget
of what i would ask for
um one of them was even a flight to
freaking korea and i was like i mean i
can buy that
too because i want to go to korea anyway
but like i didn't know what else to ask
for the other two ideas were like i want
this and this and for the third one i
was like i guess i guess i'll ask for a
flight to korea
now that was not chosen but it was one
of my ideas so you can imagine um
you can imagine
what what you could have asked for
[Music]
from austria um
a two-way ticket hmm
you don't summer thank you for the red
super chat ma kiwa is so cute thank you
not as cute as you
i mean i don't know what you look like
but you're surely very cute too
um
thank you kamsa nida
and not little things with a pinky a
second one since i won't need it for the
gacha and that's right okay thank you
you thought you needed it for the gacha
but now you can just give it to me danke
soon
i think i forgot to choo choo
[Music]
is
um
monday probably no stream because we're
just settling in and all that and
yeah i think monday is gonna be the
biggest storm anyway
we will try to maybe catch up on you
guys on tuesday or so
or wednesday
um
[Music]
i don't think there will be a schedule
yeah there will be no schedule because
we don't know when we'll be streaming
every stream is probably gonna be um
um spontaneous and it will probably be
both on my channel and on and on nana's
channel so keep an eye out out for
dana's channel i will tweet out
whenever we're streaming on hers of
course as well
but yeah
[Music]
have fun enjoy the trip thank you
let us know maybe 30 minutes ahead of
course of course of course
30 minutes ahead should be possible
but um
there will be some stuff probably guys
there might be some stuff here and there
so
just keep that in mind
a twitter space yeah maybe worst case i
prefer to just do a stream but
if that doesn't work
i think
i think it should work
like we even managed to do it with
really shitty internet in in hokkaido in
that hotel
you know when i wasn't moving i was we
were both cardboard but it like still
was okay
but who knows how the weather inflicts
the internet too i don't know if it's
really stormy
um
we'll see but yeah i gotta go thank you
guys for um sending me off
i hope my trip will be safe there might
be um
[Music]
a tweet somewhere uh in the middle of my
travels it might there might be a
picture being uploaded that's just a
scheduled one
but
yeah
um
yes
i'm nervous i'm really nervous i'm so
[\h__\h] nervous
i'm nervous about going there i'm
nervous about meeting lena i'm nervous
about the weather my nerves about to fly
there was about everything
oh but but i'll make the most out of it
hopefully and um
i'm
i'll let you guys know when i arrived
safely once i have the internet
i know it's
[Music]
um i'm so nervous oh [\h__\h] i'm so nervous
it's like ah meeting someone for the
first time is already like
nerf wrecking enough but meeting them
somewhere where you have to be with them
also for like five days or so
five six days
um
in the same room in the same bed like
what if we don't get along i mean we'll
get along but you know it's still our
first time meeting
okay okay okay it's not
it's not it's not
i can't worry about it now it's
happening
[Music]
yeah
they don't have
they don't [\h__\h] have twin beds it's
honeymoon destination guys they don't
have twin beds
[Music]
they literally don't have twin beds
um
you go there for honeymoon most of the
resorts are only like honeymoon
destinations
they only have honeymoon guests
or or um anniversary or whatever
yeah it's normal
anyways
and in germany
alfie doesn't
how do you know
my bags ain't packed i'm not ready to go
i'm not standing here outside your door
yet i hate to wake you up to say
goodbye
but the dawn is breaking it's early
morning
tax is waiting he's blowing his horn
ready i'm so lonesome
i
could die
so kiss me and smile for me
tell me that you wait for me
hold me like you'll never
let me go
cause i'm
living on a seaplane
i don't know when i'll be back again
oh babe i hate to go
don't worry guys
all right guys it's gonna be all right
i'm not even gonna be gone for so long
okay there's gonna be there's gonna be
content bye-bye
[Music]
i'll miss my cats though
yo well you guys are gonna be everywhere
online anyway we can communicate but i
can't communicate with my cats and they
can't see them online
no it's a different thing
[Music]
you