[Music]
for
wow we are
live wow where are you guys have lost
the chat
hello roses are red the fire of my heart
is blue also known as The Scarlet Queen
the harbinger of order leader of Justice
I am Elizabeth Rose bloodflame
lovely to see you to see you
lovely
hello
hello how we all doing we're having a
great day great time we're playing
League again
everybody moving around with this
guy um but yeah we got we got cilia Gigi
Nissa and
kiaha yeah it's going to be fun it's
going to be
fun yay a little under the weather well
I hope you feel better
soon it's a it's that it's that time of
year it's been very chilly today very
very chilly very chilly in great
xadia I I went I went out to to I am
Santa to deliver some
presents and it was cold it was so cold
any who I'll get into the corol with the
girlies yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and
then we'll we'll play some League of
[Music]
leggings presents
yeah the tree scares you what it's my
friend he's tremendous what the
[Laughter]
frig he's my friend he's so cute
I saw this on Adobe stock I couldn't
help myself I thought it was so
cute anyway let me just unmute I shall
wow I'll even show them my DMs with you
what the fre one
dm I just my Steam and it's
redownloading all 80 gigs of Path of
Exile so I hope I lag in League of
Legends
amazing amazing this will be
great this will
be wonderful hello hello okay I'm back
okay hello
hello what are we
airing what what what what happened say
w wants to steal my cats even though she
has her own now messed up no messed up
messed up
and get yourself more then don't take
mine away steal them steal them you
should have gotten two minimum anyway
narissa I could have told you that
no why no you just want to steal are you
kleptomaniac are we ready to play some
League of Legend I'm ready I'm ready can
we do audio check can we do G yeah
everyone introduce yourselves
[Music]
oh am G moodin League of Legends Cecilia
spin leue of
Legends don't think that's the game
Elizabeth oh League of Legends
oh Nissa Raven crop spin a win leak of
less
it sound like nerve nerv if you're
nervous I am she
is uh Top Lane uh and and Heimerdinger
checking my ass out W of Legends all
right what what is he doing to find a
match thumbnail he's checking my ass out
wow I am
too CeCe you ready aren't we matching am
I ready uh yeah I think
so loud so loud is very
loud we have to switch the window anyway
H is very cute I choose a character here
yeah I gu she
by um
exciting
yeah yeah whoever you
want okay
[Music]
I'm going to start
off with uh uh uh uh rats rats rats rat
rats we the
ratat rat rats we are the rats rats rats
rats
rats ooh where that choosing seraphine I
see I see I'm your support wait I'm I
didn't pick
yet uh you got to feel click lock in I
think you have already locked in Haven
oh it says your
picking
uh uh select your runes oh
God I have no runes okay there we go get
the
ruins okay H I
think I think it's good now okay okay
sorry guys I'm I'm struggling with uh
audio balancing my biggest
weakness it's okay
okay rosarians is the audio okay oh my
God I love your Ari
skin wow hot KDA k k is fine oh great
okay
down down down
down down
down World
Atlas good luck what do I buy did your
girls not buy items uh yeah I bought the
starting starting
pack bu the little red portion K I think
for what sorry what buy the little red
portion why is the camera so weird so oh
you click the camera the click the
camera at the bottom and it will follow
you oh thank you and hit Y and it'll
follow and unfollow you you'll have to
answer a lot of beginner questions it's
okay ask as much as you want W Senpai um
thank you so well in the shop W Senai it
does give you suggestions so I mean I
buy the little starter that it pops up
with at the at the the start when you
open it
initially okay I did that too Gigi and
Nissa are the peeps like that know it
inside out so yeah careful with the
tower who did you say that kill
everyone and and and and kill the
minions
okay don't die all right I don't have a
distance attack anymore a range I like
the way you said minions you see minions
oh wait let me change my thing I'm going
to make out of them yes yes oh God
goodbye thank you goodbye oh goodbye and
I click and then oh and click and click
click the things and press the buttons
yes yes yes I'm here for you m lean nice
I have fed the enemies no it's
okay they're Bots oh what the be uh what
would be
do B is to go back to base go home like
teleportation yeah yeah oh what's yours
is M it has a Channel time and people
can cancel it by hitting
you
oh
uhoh I'm not going to lie narissa your
your your skin keeps making me think
I've accidentally got dmca music on or
something no I'm so sorry like I'm
always like did I leave a tab on no just
you're listening to League of Legends
Str the most with in the game is like
the camera just like have just hold it
down and I keep
forgetting I die again hold it
down like space
oh you don't have to if you don't want
to you can press y to keep it
fixed really the up here let's go let's
go oh
shop uhoh I'm dead it's
okay she was waiting for me even even
now here I'll
come thank you are You The Bard yes I
pressed the wrong button please avenge
me that snake lady has been bullying
me thank you that was a good
timing why did the they have a
jungler is that a jungle character okay
they have a
jungler why you leave her I thought she
was doing
fine I guess R rat rat rat uh you must
live rat I am rat watch your St hey turn
get her
okay okay are you ready getting better
CeCe what CeCe right here right here yes
okay yes she is so
confused she has no iide thank you she's
dead we did it buff
transfer
buff Chad What in in short words because
I can't look at the the text what does w
do in this case enemy kill
it's a passive it breaks armor okay wait
now I can
read AR I'm going to that I don't have
to do anything it's just always
working what's always working
my
nice we got her yeah yeah yeah yeah no
the reset
rat we are the rats we are the rats we
are the rats tell world of
atas not
good yeah I think the way VI works is
you hit something three times and then
they take more damage and then her Q
goes through terrain and walls but
charge it
up she has one more skill forgot what it
does a
something it like does AOE
stuff it's a bit much though I don't
understand anything no that's
okay yeah I
youou
iub oh the grubs how do you aim she shot
my
booty you're looking a little
too late
okay did I not sell it did I sell the
wrong
thing what' you
sell an item that that I didn't
need y so and I bought
[Music]
okay your skin
what is she up
to
I'm ow ow ow leave me alone
leaving mid laner what how where are
they yeah where are they oh
cute the Mida is here it's
Misfortune their jungle bot takes void
grubs ew
what is this an objective I just can't
believe the bots in this game take
objectives they're annoying hey what did
I step in hey what did I step in
uhoh
N so how what how many times have you
girls played this as a collab already
this is three yeah hey you in bottom
Lane mother trucker I remember you I'm
dead I'm
dead don't die don't
[Music]
die kill no no
wait oh the deer is here the deare is
here oh dear oh dear oh dear dear de oh
dear thank you she's being really mean
yeah
uhoh oh got this is a deer is a
de I wasn't saying she's a little
deer I'm almost
back kill her I'm
asleep
to what get away from
me
what I ran to link I uh iitt too much
minions they're dead that's messed up
that's mess don't worry I'm here to take
your farm why would you do that to me
I'll
leave I'm coming back narissa the spots
are kind of crazy all the things they're
doing what is
this don't be afraid go my little
minions go min
cute cute
cute oh no Cecilia is gr
now how do I buy
that this time
probably no touching watch out you see
that white thing around her it means the
next spell she hits you with you'll get
stunned yay
nice Gold Blood flame go blood
flame I'm on to you he's a queen
[Music]
Dragon idiot true what an
idiot
ID you're welcome an is
unable is there like did you set these
Bots to a high difficulty or so they're
normal could they be easier
yes I a bad match
up no you're
okay
all difficulties time don't worry about
it it's normal why is the horse on all
side horse kill the horse
I'm going to
die explain it I still don't understand
explain what what the what the
um the C Drake
that um gives us gold and gives us some
passive stuff so it's a good objective
to get wow nice is an enemy we have to
kill or yeah it's a jungle mob don't
worry okay usually in like actual games
people fight around this and then you
have to be aware but we're just playing
Bots doesn't matter too much I I got
this you sound like you totally got this
i got this to go a little
bit you going to be good down here
mhm you're looking a little
green did oh they're back
again winning evil jungler just took my
my my
Raptors your Raptors yeah I can't
believe that bot's counter
jungle I just can't believe it it's
weird it's weird right yeah it's so
strange that that will counter jungle
you should I chose someone that's far
away chat
probably after me
you an enemy has
been we
go get out of
there nice FL thank you get all these
kill that ma'am get out of here what the
freak are you doing in here there's a
little girl in the forest careful
careful careful get a B I'm
[Music]
running oh that completely missed that
was nowhere near her where did she go
wait where is she KAIT yeah maybe I want
red goodbye nice one gorp is not little
in for a while
yes yeah blue blue blue blue did you
watch Arcane did everybody watch Arcane
I haven't seen the second season yet but
I've seen the first
one I watch both finished my
Twitter I love it although the second
season was bit rushed yeah a lot of
things that they were she charm she's
charm getting down
kill copia is going back so you should
be able to get the tower pretty much
undisturbed mhm oh
charm she's Charmed she's
Charmed oops she did not run where I
wanted her to run don't
TR good
job I'm turning I'm
[Music]
turning let me kill you ow she's done
she's done
owie I'll be right under
the andk gosh DN you're having a party
there
you yeah it's a it's a it's a
party oh the snake is back that's okay
Shake oh careful back up a little
bit eny is I wanted to use my ulti yeah
right for
the oh my God leave me
alone all right let's come here
mother trucker are they going to stay
here if they stay we can kill them okay
okay okay let's just kill
her watch out she knows how to
combo oops that's that's a
minion oh you
here careful
careful careful
careful I'm
dead kill her kill her sh
yay
okayoh I'll kill her for you thank you
good job I shouldn't have gone in there
see the second
enemy rats rats she's going jungling
again and he's gone back to Jungle ah no
she's not oh okay I've got her back good
luck
Kara get this
oh
no har has Nine Kills she related to n
back off buddy no she's a goho well she
is a ninetail block so
yeah
like
uhoh thank you
yay we got her come back come back come
back you're getting toxic you're
learning the ways of League of Legends
yes it's true I'm I shouldn't should I
mean you got this
enemy you come here Lilia jungle
wonderful
bot let's go out of range
on I'm gonna try a different
character get
that
Wasing many which should I
buy sorry I didn't have
my I can't afford I need
the basic
boots you are Gucci I was being
pery oh there three why are there three
people in mid that's not this is not
fair guys this is not fair top obsessed
with you yeah they they just you just
are very
[Music]
intimidating watch your step your
step woohoo on my way Oho on my way B
never mind everyone left you yeah I she
one died
League Le
leg Le of
leg like a fine
egg now there's
a I don't know if this is like the has
it or if it's just the skin but when she
teleports home she the creat oh that's
the skin yeah it's really cool
invisible stairs and then she sits on
thr
against Throne of Leal
lean my favorite top Champion was always
Riven Voice by Christina V
yeah great
oh what's that what's that the infal
blazes what does it mean they took the
dragon so now there's things that will
pop up on this the
[Music]
map
nice nice job
yay God I'm zoning
out like mentally or yeah
my brain I wish I could zone out but I
can't even Zone
in just chilling playing league with the
ladies we
vibing you got this you got this you got
this
yay
yes iome cute look at your oh my God
good no thanks to
narissa it's all because of narissa I'm
going to die no you're not sneaky
sneaky I'm going to back got this no
you're not you got this you're so strong
Rampage oh my god let's push the tower
push the tower yeah get the
tower I guess I'll push a tower too
she's behind you
you your team destroyed AET don't worry
oh oh oh you're you're going crazy
you're going crazy you're crazy you're
crazy you're crazy you're crazy and and
because of that yes in a good way and we
have a friend and I'm going to bring you
a friend and then don't worry where am I
going why is I'm running this way that's
a cute friend he's also crazy I died oh
no oh no oh no well I sacrificed myself
for a good yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm
going to go crazy again my first
successful di why am I
turning I died
wow without my diving
license hey you're doing really good no
I'm not don't
lie got this you got
this sure first time is by this is great
I sucked this high when I first played
by c a
oh bu looks
difficult let's
go I was
hiding V is really hard yeah she's
really really difficult I thought she
was going to people were saying she's
like one of the easier ones no they Li
in the jungle she's a pretty simple
jungler yeah your team has destroyed yay
a tower is
destroyed
unfortunate oh
speed
wow I'm
here I missed it's
okay what's SC her let's get her you got
this yeah get the kill get the
kill you're so look at
you
sure you it you doing it get a get
a oh Annie's going oh you got you got
this you got this you're crazy you're
crazy she's sleeping you oh oh no oh
no I was trying to figure out to make my
how to make my ulti work but I think I
have to stand still or what I don't
think you have this stand still I was
pressing it the whole time you have to
press and then click
again on the person you want to use it
on or if you press um in the settings oh
in um there's like these little arrows
that you can if you just hover over a
person you can use them instead of
having to click on
them
okay hey if if someone can help you just
get the inhibitor bottom I Mega creeps
and we can in
Lane
hello leav everything seems to be right
click in this game is it left
click it's it's left click I don't
actually don't remember I just do it by
muscle memory I have no
clue
yay woo
feel I'm on to you let's try again an
ally
has w w w w
w to let's go
okay but it worked this
time eny has been slain
oh it's
fine it's just
me how dare you kill
narissa mother trucker dare take her
away from
us
nice spre here you're
dead Okay what are we doing team
I buy when I'm out of stuff we can just
push M what do you mean whatever
whatever makes you happy I always like
to go for a rabit On's death
cap a hat rabit on Death cap okay I
forgot to smile if your ability power
yeah I
forgot don't kill the r don't kill the
don't kill the don't kill the um no I
ran of the things on that one list that
you sent me like the three main items
you lived by this and then
I that's
amazing
hello nice strong I thought the Dare was
going to kill me she's TR she's Char
nice okay get her too get her too get
her get her get her she's so
fast don't worry we're here get her get
her aome ni nice nice nice
get the
tower
okay get the in destroyed a
turret what is that called what did you
call it inh it's an inhibitor your team
has destroyed an inhibitor have You Met
My fleas have You Met My fleas now what
now end the game behind two behind us
no you're
not thank you no you're not kill
her Kara if you attack
uhy if you attack them
over when when there's not Creeps in
front of you or if you attack someone
over a
tower like the the tower will start
attacking you so if you're in the
tower's vicinity don't attack attack one
of the enemy
Champions
okay and if there's no creep don't don't
go up by the
tower no creepe yeah what's the creep
the little guys fighting for you oh
minions
yeah
[Music]
amazing live live
it's okay I'm to end
fine team okay I'll end the game don't
worry woo
[Applause]
[Music]
yon so easy so easy easiest game easiest
game
ever winners we're winning we are
winning winner winner we are winers kfp
dinner
easy
yay first win of the day amazing our
first win of our
lives so easy T is passive is Poison the
most Stacks up to five you have the guys
want do intro box or Stacks actually K
should pick but what do you want to you
want to keep playing Bots you want to do
you want to do bots all the real people
going to be easier than the
Bots also there might be a chance that
if we go with real people we still get
bots like I'll be right back you guys
talk about what you want and then tell
me when I get back easy
Bots I mean I I I don't mind either way
I like playing against real people I'm
not sure if we can play against real
people yet since Ki is on a new account
few more b games right but we can see if
we can go into Quick Play
yeah maybe we should do bots first and
then um well right now we did M medium
Bots and we won uh so either we should
do maybe we should do hard Bots to see
if we can keep up against hard Bots
before real people
mhm maybe maybe can I do Caitlyn and top
Ling Kaitlin is fun can play yeah
whoever wherever yeah be whoever you
want to be just have just yeah just mix
it up okay I want to try her Kaitlyn
Kaitlyn Caitlyn's fun that's the that's
the she VI perfect
match all these discounted skins
purchase purchase I'm back
back welcome back you okay what do we
decide on what are we up
to and Bots okay Bots and do you just
want to do beginner Bots I'm not sure
what was the
conclusion we'll
do oh I feel like we can handle the same
level of bots you did really well yeah
we did beginner Bots we were playing
beginner Bots oh we W playing a Bots oh
we'll continue doing middle Bots okay
okay okay I I'll I'll an intermediate
I'll do
whatever yeah yeah okay continue are we
all ready mm yeah we're waiting on Kar
okay I'm pressing button okay you
already Caitlyn let's go to try someone
else our
relationship try she's like a narissa
but with a gun what if we all made a
star Guardian team who is that I have do
I need to buy a skin for that I have
Sona star Guardian there star Guardian
Ari how much cost also usually like I
think star Guardian skin would be around
$15 o 15 or 15 yes 15 what Masterpiece
shall we play
today I get to use
my if I want to invest into this game by
giving it money I will decide after this
stream okay that is
fair I do want to look pretty in a star
Guardian skin why are you Sona wait
let's talk real quick what's what's
happening here for funie
okay wor about it yeah
problem we both supports it's is one of
you you can build
AP go carry yeah you can be anyone
anything anything you
want I
can are we already
running yeah can we do the thing where
we like kill them in the in in the
bushes yeah we can we'll have to go over
here I'm so fast okay I'm fast as fud
boy I'm
speeding let's
go
hi I like your hat thank you I like your
ball or oh no not the snake again why do
we get sa there's everyone here they
killed my
War messed up we can try killing them
still I'm sure they'll
follow
running kill her kill her is it a her I
can't tell yes yes get her get her kill
her get her get her get her
first first
one uhoh I'm dead I'm dead no no no help
no you're not dead you're not dead
you're not dead I sted him I you thank
you get her get
her
very I'll take this this is mine
now the minions are here you go to
[Music]
youran
bye you're
welcome thank
you
my yes yes
oh we killed them tried
that can't believe you're here with us
yay I am
here I am running for I Am low in health
where are you running to what do you
mean you
better you sound like you're directly
out of the game like I wasn't sure if
that was a game Voice or not
yes this is the
game Let's mute the game and just have
her do it yeah can you make the noises
Bard makes I don't know what I don't
know what he sounds likees he sounds
like
Wich scream you
[Applause]
guys although it sound like I'm trying
to do crazy the start a crazy frog
[Music]
[Laughter]
so much oh
beautiful oh missed the last P
stupid no you're so good
[Music]
not bad though I don't know how to ad0
carry seraphine you don't have to ad0
carry just at carry I don't know what
that means oh just just build like
normal AP items I don't know how to AP
carry your abdons the r i just get my
rabadons yeah you can build your
rabadons
she's a coward she's a coward kill her
she's Charmed she's Charmed back be to
heal
noral I'm out
[Music]
of if we can just keep getting them to
go back even it's not too bad because
then they they don't get to level I need
healing thank
you come she's so low but I can't do it
I'm out of
no guess I shouldn't have used all the
Mana on the
Min man an ally has been
slain
serious is oh you can hide in the bushes
too like in the in the Pokmon game too
like you disappear when you're in the
bushes
Happening Here you couldn't become
stealth going on Assassin tonight
dragon
dragon dragon
be Dragon we Dragon
we where are you draging
us killing spre is happening
here do are we still on beginner Bots
[\h__\h] yeah they're very strange
[Music]
he keeps like zooming behind me it's so
frustrating what have you want what have
you want what have you want nothing
nothing nothing
nothing what do you want what do you
want though I want to get
up oh well oh
I ma'am stop it ma'am stop it ma'am stop
stop let us kill you okay thank you Yay
good
[Music]
kill so if I don't get the kill if the T
gets the kill I don't get any like work
on
leveling oh you're only level never mind
I'll stay
back out of
here oh
how does she know I'm
here I don't know oh no secret
Ward yeah I'm just trying to hit this
how does she have the knowledge that I'm
here these Bots are
cheating of course they are are always
cheating I he I heal I heal I heal y
y how could they stream snipe that's so
rude I know it's so cringe of these B
stream s IIT I have minions
now minions minions minions minions
minions I heal and then I go back into
the bushes her thank
you until changes
[Music]
go back for it
really oh I'm I mean I'm fighting your
mirror match oh mirror m a double
ganger oops didn't mean do
that nice one you're the
best you're the best music music
oo what why are they getting these and
an ally has been SL how of just watch
sow to get this a Sy of
Justice no it's not over a symphony of
Justice over somebody in the
bushes sword what sorry BF big [\h__\h]
sword
wow that oh I did get the BF sword
nothing wrong with the BF
sword
okay a moment to channel and line up
the oh
no oh
no a true
Masterpiece Cate living
no he running away I oh oh that's not
what I wanted to flash
oops
[Music]
big big large
wall big very large
wall I don't like
AER you like her she keeps like she
keeps like I'm about to charm her then
she teleports behind me and she goes
nothing I don't appreciate
that
now y I got
[Music]
her oh
my how does that
happen your stream died yeah oh my God
that's really weird what your stream
died
yeah OBS issue it's okay it's back it's
back yay
y welcome back from the
dead back
sorry well you missed me doing 20 en
yeah all of
them killed every single one of
[Music]
them don't kill me this is mine
an
enemy oopsie I forgot if you hit
someone it's okay
ah he's confused he lacks critical
knowledge oh God out played
her I went into Caitlyn I sent Caitlyn
back into her closet she was invisible
oh come on come on oh come on come on
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on no yeah you
heard me you mother trer let me kill you
let me I don't think we should do that
so I got her oh
god let's go
[Music]
minion let's eat more Snake
pleas snake for dinner snake sausage
snake sausage I already ate six sausages
today six yeah impressive
impressive impressive display I know
impressive display of it's very unlike
of K Caitlyn oops I should have done the
Alti magic is like a song uh oh what's
this it's woven into everything woven
into everything I heal I've got it
back okay
oh no we have a Like A League of Legends
voice pack from Elizabeth yeah we need
one oh oh God she going into the bushes
you're not going to escape me ha imagine
running away from a
Healer come back truck do I have to
be come here come here come here come
here come here here if you hover over it
you can see the rain no there's another
one
fre and another one you'll be fine
you're Sona another one okay okay okay I
need to
go oh no we running o Maybe
not maybe
not so many unactivated traps so sad
what do I do I just love the way that
Nissa just goes past me on her
hoverboard okay
okay oh God how low are you very oh my
God you're very low 26 HP I died to
seraphine oh they aled me oh they aled
you how could she do this you're the
seraphine though I know how could she I
have a skin
yes get hit
by y tret these BS are awesome I like
yeah I like when they run into the
turrets because it's like I would do
that mother Traer you you would do
that
yeah have today oh yeah I remember
getting confused which one which which
which colors were our
I think I think Le Riot gave me free RP
so I did buy more sarap skins I want
stuff too Ryan
please there's two of them why that two
what am I going to
do riot give me free stuff or I'm a I'm
going to Riot I'm going to Riot
yeah before we start
rioting just kidding I'm sorry riots I
have so much respect for you sorry Mr
Riot we already RI what get away from me
big I'm a dude from
Brazil TR it's a League character if I
die and I say sounds familiar the KA
nullify any negativity I've cre yeah
yeah yeah yeah it does it creates
space space for my yeah creating space
for your skills good trade good trade
good
trade oh je finally turret is
gone we can now move on with our
lives yeah we can all move on with our
lives Target the
Aurelia no come why would you come here
aelia I'm trying to get this Rift
terol my RI I work so hard
on I'm a little bit too happy when I uh
kill a champion as you should be that's
good that's your
life
here W over here I'm so
low you're little bot brain wants me so
bad I'm so
low walk over here just walk over
here I'm going look at which one the
Kaiser yeah come get
me
more come on go over here keep pressing
D nothing happens some point I don't get
it maybe a little closer oh
I got do you also have it quick
casted oh
yes walk up
here get her get her her
her she's Char charge yay that'll show
her for trying to take my Rift
heral Rift heral wonder if I can get it
now he's Brazilian like 3,000 gold okay
okay I want to hear his voice
now this one got to get a needlessly
large
Rod needlessly large yeah needless it's
so needlessly
large that's why I need it okay your
team necessary necessarily large
Rod yeah uh oh I
slow live live I live I live totally
ignored me no
respect yes come here sh yes you want me
you want to eat oh she ran away yes walk
over here you want us yes come on
over damn
Retreat tactical Retreat tactical
retreating leaving my minions
behind for a better time and I'm going
to buy boots boots boots
boots here we go
woo nice get her get her get her get her
get her get you get her you get her I'm
letting you get her yay crazy you guys
are really
pushing right into their base get the
inhibitor shall we go and help
bid destroyed an inhibitor
inhibitor an inhibitor an inhibitor
an inhibitor an inhibitor destroy an
inhibitor goodbye oh dude don't die dude
stop following me dude dude St St St
dude
them I keep forting about my
old oh hi hi hi I'm
here
hi hi everyone oh I'm standing in it
your team has
destroy what's everyone screaming
about crazy
yay
yay yipp
yipp you're on a rampage kiaha you're
crazy
crazy that's fine
I'll avenge
you I won't let them get away with
this oh I
here yes yes you're
crazy do that run away run away run
away I'll avenge you
too clicked oh my God let me out let me
out let me out am I clicking I think the
hardest part is like moving with your
mouse because like I you click because
you're trying to get away but your mouse
is completely in a different place than
you thought it
was and then you always walk into the
wrong area
g hi
G the heal
g i got
this I don't think I do
but to you and I just see like kill
them walk up this if I had more Mana I
could have done it you can do it you got
this one more one
more one
more got them G got them got them
get what
music maybe it's the star
Guardian it's so
pretty godl godl F walk back over
here yeah don't be a coward bot come on
yeah come on walk over here
beginners
bot healing
[Music]
now
Victory I'm in
the w
wow game of our lives so
easy um I think we're ready for
intermediate B yeah I need to get water
okay okay okay me too actually sorry I'm
like since I'm sick I'm drinking so much
water that's good drink more yes drink
more water girl drink I am so thirsty do
I still not have this skin oh I just
need the
icon I was about to kill myself okay
I'll be right back do it okay okay I'll
be um yeah I'll be or be
mhm K still on my stream water KDA KDA
KD know how it
is again was it me k k a what does it
mean it look within you
kitten
doggy
animals oh so they saying it's killed
def assist yeah yeah yeah yeah wow you
got that way faster than me and Cecilia
did really really I don't know if that's
fast yeah yeah yeah I didn't notice
until Cecilia brought up she was like oh
kill death like assist and I was
like oh my God why is this why is this
yellow are they telling me I did bad for
what my character could do
potentially or is it just because that's
me what's yellow my damage dealt to
Champions is just because it's me okay
okay yeah yeah yeah they were dissing
me can you get skins with the blue stuff
or
not um there's the they sometimes bring
back like a blue Essence store but it's
usually a lot of blue Essence it was
here
recently don't know where it went I
don't know if it's still here what are
these mystery
boxes oh the here oh the mystery which
one
what when would you need I want can you
explain them to me like these loot Loot
Crate Box thingies are they for skin the
ones in your
inventory
inventory there's ones in my
inventory sometimes you get these like
chest that you can use and it give you
character shards or skin shards or um
Wards and stuff but you have to unlock
it
with this other currency that you get
from breaking down what you get from
boxes
a I maybe see
uh so none of these loot boxes have
skins the loot boxes have skins if you
buy a loot box you can get a skin
they're all gold too right no well
there's these blue Miss bandle City
mystery mini icon I
icons welome back
how are we doing aers good good yeah are
we ready yes do we want to up the bot
difficulty sure by one maybe there's
only one more to go let's go nice okay
let's search we got this we got this we
got it
search yeah hope we find I am seeking
Bots what let's change the
world okay KDA skin time yay woo for me
I mean you're flexing so
hard bro I had to play to unlock this
skin I'm not
flexing still a flex no I had to play so
much to unlock her we we'll get you a
pretty skin too K don't worry next time
I yeah yeah yeah I don't know who this
guy is but he reminds me of like someone
from Myspace so I'm going to try him he
looks beautifully sad yeah yeah he looks
like a MySpace
guy oh
sorry pool party Kaitlyn p p pool party
party oops pool party pool party I want
po
sure yay no snake this time oh there's a
cow cute oh there like a little
guy you're all going the people who know
this game are like oh no he's
difficult um well I feel like I had some
bad things about Lux but did not
understand the context what do you mean
I don't know oh evil I'll just go for
that um her bot AI is really good
because she's really good at aiming
skill shots because your Bot
yeah can we kill them all in the
oh he's cute over here he has a big
thank you he has a big
paintbrush well this guy has a big paint
brush let's go 30 seconds until minion
spawn okay I'll wait for everyone to get
here you look so cute thank you we match
now are we ready sparkly yeah I'm ready
ready to press the one button I have I'm
just going to look up this guy uh
I'm in the ow he flash why did he
flash don't
flash minions have
spawned first oh thank you for the heal
yeah you're wcome thank you everyone
aners for the most burning question here
I'll just go back to my uhoh oh no look
Lux is in the middle it's over she's in
the middle she's always she's a lox and
she's in the middle I hate her she's lox
and she's the M it's okay I'm not the
same person I was two weeks
ago not lose to this spot this time be
my can yeah you are not the same person
he's like the guy
from uh from
Naruto which one sigh it was his name
Sai oh the guy he drew that's right he
he drew stuff
yes artist an
[Music]
artist if you hit him and then the
minions aggro you they'll reveal your
location in the bush yeah so if you're
agroed by something it'll show
yourself he's so
cool yeah
yeah cannot outrun your crime this is
what I want to say to wer
white are you planning on watching Sal
after yeah totally wow so awesome so
excited I'm like halfway through the
last season of Breaking B you're so
close I think I'm going to finish it
tonight
maybe
Yi also I saw I saw I was in a museum
yesterday and
um I saw painting that really looked
like Walter White I took a picture of it
I need to show it to you guys later any
understands what he looks like in the
first place it looks so much like him B
and and plases and
everything and depressed not really
depressed he pushed me in he pushed me
in now it's just like his face just says
he's got
issues he kicked into the the
thing he's rude of the ashes into the
fire
[Music]
wow I'm a cute Myspace boy that
draws yeah come
on yeah I never used
Myspace yes even though it was popular
when I was smaller death uhoh an ally
has been slain my space was too Fair me
run into our Tower no but I I should
have come home like ages ago ah and I
kept thinking I could use my Mana before
going
home a of
tea a bottle of
water bottle of water bottle of water
bottle of water here I'm ready for you
are you
bad
she all right all right I'm on her I'm
on her I'm on top of her I'm on top of
her
Okay g I feel like when it's one it BEC
a little come here little cow what
do ideally in the game you're not you
have like a better understanding or like
you you know where the jungler is and
you know when to not overextend so she
wouldn't have been in that position in
the first place if she
was watching a map or she wed or she's
not a in the middle should I and you are
close to the
middle um I think it's up to the jungler
because it's like um evaluate the kill
potential if you if like they went mid
would you guys be able to get a kill I
create the quiet that I or if there's
like other objectives even though you
might engage like oh it's not worth it
cuz I have to go to this other place
right now and it would waste too much
time here I wanted
to in a game though but since it's just
a black game I can just commit I wonder
what skins he has
[Music]
the side of me oh you're so manap Poore
good thing she's not level yet side in
the dark I'm dead no I got her don't
worry don't worry don't worry go home go
home oh he paints a portal oh my God I
really like God this is so
cool what a cool
character can you believe that airplane
why is he here and the night SK are like
shooting stars can't believe it nice
nice good job I'm going to
back I he robot yeah you sound very
roboty right now who
does intentional oh almost there is must
the is it the
ping yeah yeah yeah awesome I'll fix it
in a moment if I if it's still
happen am I w-e am I Wally can I do the
Wally
[Music]
thing oh wait I need man good thank you
EV you sound really
good is there no Mana
potions in the shop
no it's like a re aable potion but
people don't usually get it or it
depends on what chion you're playing an
enemy why is it
locked not allow I want me to fix it I
think the way I got to fix it is like
going in and out of the cool and stuff
so there's a rare occasion where this uh
happens I don't know whether it's the go
or if it's Discord been to Christmas
markets yet not
yet yeah right it's so it's all just a
lie quickly I did in a voice pack in the
last 3 days I went to like six Christmas
markets that's wow you spee running
Christmas markers I totally did
competitive Christmas Mark though and it
made it even more obvious like I never
noticed how like all the shops are so
repetitive in the Christmas markets but
it's still nice it's still nice really
nice what's your favorite Christmas
Market
snack
best get him get him get him get
him
[Music]
y what does that do
ger I'm talking about German
things those are like
[Music]
C roasted candy almond caramelized
roasted yeah
sell them at the Christmas Market I Leta
eat them and she was so fascinated she
was like oh my God this is the
[\h__\h] good it's like just the right
amount of super sweet you know M I'm
crunching uhoh uhoh oh he pushed me away
thank
goodness I'm going to heal up ooh yep go
ahead strut away
no matter where I he's painting I can't
forget where I came from he's
painting he's a
painter he's a
painter do I still sound like a robot
you Ed no oh it fixed itself
cool I didn't even touch it beautiful
Elizabeth Rose blood
flame
extermination wait is my flash and my
fire
switch oh that's why I keep flashing why
would they do why would the game do that
to me that's why would I guess it fixed
itself in the end usually I have to like
turn stuff on and off on a rare occasion
it fixed itself weird arus is not
interested in me anymore he realized I
am uh not interested in him
either good
good go somewhere else Darius
stay he go why oh CH so bad uhoh I
included him whoops no that was
the damn it missed oh oh my
God
damn my aim is so bad
stay
here no it's okay I got a B be careful
it's the
Lash the
Lash I can't give up I can't give up for
the Lash no for Flash for the
Lash they all here let's go for p over
build
over your team has
destroyed oh my
God everyone's
crunchy everyone crunchy why do I have
how about
now oh I got boots I fix
[Music]
it good now okay okay let see if I can
get this guy with this this time f f
launches a vision of pure despair that
sticks to an enemy Champion for 3
seconds
[Music]
oh like a had this weird issue recently
happened like start we my audio just BEC
really rob you but I can't hear like it
hears sounds normal in my my ears hello
jungle jungle came to the wrong
neighborhood jungle
come here come here come here you cow
nice oh let's get this mid
turret teaching me
restrain wow he's so good he's
scripting
scripting yeah kill him kill him kill
him kill him kill him he's so fast you
got died from
the I'm going home oh should I you n I'm
afraid of this killing
you just run oh
whoops Tower two
I'm here no darious oh oh let's get the
rumble Rumble come
what no
[Music]
no please there is please let me go let
me
go let me go little hi hi
hinger that's SP he does look like H her
though I F the when I was watching the
show was like is this character going to
turn into digs or what no no they're
they're their own people
oh
Unstoppable an enemy has been slain are
they
related no they're just little just the
same they're just are they yort
species changed everything oh that's
what I meant are they the same species
blood oh yeah yeah and flowers
[Music]
he crazy
cousin there's another guy down here
Rumble it's who is ready to
R wow you're Domin he back up
[Music]
let's finally get someone with this
let's go a yay
finally
yay got someone with my Al for once
everybody's like Yay I'm
like oh whoops get out of there you
silly boy are celebrating my death
they're cheating up there celebrating
your death yeah
yay W di let's go it's okay cuz she's a
phoenix he'll be back yeah he'll be back
BR I just wanted to
go get
her no you're not there's a lot people
here I'll flash for her oh I don't do
enough
damage ner okay we got him we got him we
got him we got him we got him oh he
flashed oh my
God oh God
we got him we got him got
him wow
sh you know we were ambitious yeah I
mean we have three people against us
it's yeah yeah yeah yeah we did really
well yeah what is
that it's no issue we're still beautiful
an ally has been slain I'm a beautiful
Myspace boy mhm so she came back and
then killed you that's rude kind of mean
yeah fin there was like this giant arrow
on the map and I was like what could
that be but it was on top of an enemy so
I thought the enemy was doing something
but it was her teleporting I understand
now I know what it looks like you get it
you get it I get it now I get it now
does your guy have a Santa skin I feel
like he su one a journey where you hold
sh he has a Santa skin this is his
winter one right
now he would look really cool as Santa
yeah he'd be really cute
[Music]
please have mercy
oh I'm on my way I'm on my way so okay
okay don't let her kill me Top Lane is
so
depressing who got
[Music]
this H me I you she knows it you did
your
flash your flash is crazy you you did it
you did it so
that's on the wrong butt it's not my
fault you did
it
[Music]
crazy imag yo an enemy has been SL SN no
no let me kill you please I will kill
you give me the satisfaction whoops you
scared me
you
coward
no oh
no I'm weak again who is this Rumble
where did he come from he's the jungler
can you come kill this Rumble Rumble
Rumble tumble can you come control your
jungle he's just chilling he lost his
jungle he has no idea what's going on
you know oh oh is that a
Teleport that is a Teleport okay I I see
it now I see it
now an ally has been slain there he is
there he is please let me go should have
done
anything it's a lesson I have to learn
when there's more than one en tum at
full health I should not tickle
them tickle them you outplay them S no I
died no no next time if you play them
next time okay okay I see yeah yeah see
what if you what if you for next time
that's a good Des actually maybe I
didn't think of it about that
way get away from
me oh
we got them yeah you got
this get away from me are we I
can't I'll create something beautiful in
your just one okay I can take on
one your team has destroyed a turret an
enemy has been
slain an ally has been slain
your team has she's a singer she's a
singer
singer she's a
singer listen topr out now thank
you listen to Blackbird out now on
Spotify Co sptify
your team has destroyed a
turret I'm on a roll look at you Kiara
you're slaying you're crazy all alone
baby all
alone your team has destroyed an
inhibitor all alone it's okay it's like
it's
it's character
yeah it's like the him probably what's
that why is there a red circle around me
what does that mean there's a Santa
no that's cute yeah good good good good
good okay you got red buff from
Jungle if you have a I I'll protect you
I'll protect you thank you part of me
just wants to
live oh they're all up here oh there's
so many of them yeah leave
[Music]
leave wa I was about to dodge that but
that came fast this just happened she
just got the both of us I'm glad we died
together yeah at least we're here
together she
uhoh oo thank you oh there's three of
them um get him okay okay he's he's
Charmed he's not Charmed never mind I
lied part of the
whole I flashed again Dam it you're okay
Here We
Come Oh the music
C thank
you one breath and brush she's a singer
midane she
[Music]
sing
there ch ch nice he's dead he's dead
kill him kill him I'm trying a okay it's
okay I'm
running oh come on
dude come on let me kill you let me kill
you thank
[Music]
you
why is
dead yeah destroyed a tret
yeah your team destroyed
H
yeah these guys are
crazy on means revisiting oh I'm going
to die shut down shut damn L damn it Lu
all her
fault tearing us
apart lay the cloud Drake nice want to
see when we played her against the ls
the first time I thought she would be
like super toxic character like you know
like no no the way her character is like
her characteristics she's all positivity
yeah she's like super positive in Love
Somehow that makes it worse I don't know
why someone that's like peace and love
stuns you and then like in a line H
nothing personal
yeah that's personal at all
yeah she doesn't mean it is this
joking I see I see an ally has been
slain be my wall
oh the the the same guy that voices
F who's voiced by Steven Fu voiced
um uh Chang Wu in a squid game in the
dub I really love the
dub are those the flowers from the
show those are yeah I was just looking
up I got it uh he's
voice cuz he did sound familiar I was
like I can just figure out how to this
gu sounds
familiar I'll hit there I'll hit it I'll
hit it this way I'm driving face boy
sounds familiar okay
goodbye you can drive it yeah yeah I
just looked it up and it said squid game
and I was like oh squid
game I did like voice seting
all I imagined we can end yeah you guys
can end right
now game we're wai
w
[Music]
y multitasking Queen yeah I do like to
multitask how did you like him oh I
loved him I thought he was really
cool yeah nice I'm going to see if he
has
skins oh
yeah skin timear
skin
time did I get more more gold all of a
sudden malfunction describes it
well I got more RP too yeah how do we
huh
[Music]
yay thanks RI thank you r i can get my
MySpace boy skins I can buy more
my space boy skin here we go did I also
get stuff I don't know how did they give
me stuff yeah we need to we need to
submit to them your username and stuff
but I got some stuff how do they know oh
you did like you got some RP wait how
how can I win bless okay it's time for a
new skin bye thank you
[Music]
leag ofg
uh cuz they can probably see it on my
stream
oh oh it's here thank you Riot I guess I
won't Riot then get away SC
fre has a winter
skin I'm going to get it yay how much is
that like the the how much
is 3
skin where do I buy skin go go to the
right by the RP there's like coins
stacked up you click
there uh uhuh and then you you bu stff
there
okay popo
barking does he only have one skin I
think he only has one skin W and it's
winter I love winter
oh oh require Champion I don't have
Caitlyn yet even though I'm playing her
she's she's probably free this week get
her with your your blue
stuff my blue stuff yeah yeah the
in-game iname go buy her if you like her
okay I do like
her you know sarine has a skin called
graceful Phoenix oo o is it red orange
or it's orange fiery it's nice
there's also a champion that's a cat
called
annoyed doesn't have a single green type
skin yeah can't believe
it messed
up messed up am I still in your party I
can't tell yeah uh probably maybe I'm
not in it right now I believe so I'm
buying things you're buying thing oh
you're not in here I'll invite you to
the game thanks
here something wrong hi guys okay money
is gone Riot thank you thank you Riot
thank you money is gone I spent
it I had a billion dollars but I I spent
it
all billion dollars wow very
based what is chroma what does that mean
it's different color variations so if
you go to chroma and you look up the
champion you like they might have
different variation like color
variations for this I just looked at
there's a there's a shako it's called
Arcanist shako it looks like battle
Senpai for example
yeah I was
[Laughter]
like you
know oh dud
oh this is green c yeah she has
literally an emerald K skin that's nice
yeah purchase it bye bye bye bye bye now
bye now wait I have to pick I'm going to
get the the the O Jo it's time to go to
bed
Vlad Vlad to go to bed it's time to go
to bed it's time to go to bed or Jo it's
cool cafe cend stream no what no it's
not time to go to bed yet it's time to
go to bed it's not time it's not
time oh Jo it's time to play League of
[Music]
Legends oh Joe summer it's time to play
Le I should always prioritize using the
blue ones right since those are in game
uhhuh yeah that that was something I did
wrong when I first like got got
characters and stuff okay I got a green
one
are we going to try real people now or
can we still not what do you want to do
what is this Gwen looks cool
sissors can we play against real people
sure already I feel extremely prepared
for the
challenge I
believe nothing can stop me nothing can
stop you uh I'm going to change my
thingy my character Kara you need to
select uh Top
Lane Cosmetics winter he has multiple
colors apparently everyone wants me to
tell you about
anivia I've been seeing it in my chat
too I don't care I just invested in hot
outfits for Caitlyn play Caitlyn where
do I select where do iiv a bird I don't
know uh right under your character icon
character icon there's like a little
square
you and then oh you click on the
character and okay got it he has
multiple colors is it possible to change
the skin now that's so cool I got the
red one of course yes yes red
okay red red red hot
cute hell yeah hell yeah I change the
color of my skin oh oh you hit the
little chroma button you can use the
blue
stuff W I got it I got it I got it let
me know when we're all ready flash I did
Flash oh it has
[Music]
changed
bottom the blue stuff use the blue
stuff the blue stuff the blue stuff 99%
point6
purity spash use the blue stuff female
dog you're ready everyone ready I'm
ready I'm
ready Mr White we're looking we're going
to play people we're going to play
people I'm so scared don't worry they
might be B too they think I I I'm just
the like five years we're 5 years old of
how bad I'm playing we're all you're
doing so good you're pushing top okay
because we're together with you so
you're not going to get reported oh okay
yeah that's what matters I have it's
okay even if they reported me I have
Riot on my side what can they do so the
mints a lot I got it's fine they are
it's funny they have the same name as me
so they're Elizabeth Shaw and they're
these stick ones they're called dark
chocolate mint flutes they come in a
small
packet I like them cuz the I saw them in
um
uh the range that was it the
range can they come in this little
box I'll charm them with my S I actually
initially got them for to plop in a a
gift box for someone else but then it
didn't fit so I was like oh I mean I
I'll just have
them God are these real people or are
they not real people
walk in if I walk in and I see them
maybe they are not real people check
this out everyone I'm about to face
check to see if they're real people do
it holding it they might be Bots that's
fine I'm big I hope they're
Bots thank you for reminding
me who's pinging me yeah who's pinging
us not me what's pone someone's oh the
robot I choose kindness how do you I
don't even know how to Ping is that me
oh no are the is the robot intentional
robot again how do you even do
that Rob maybe it is intentional we
don't know I don't think so Robo Liz in
the house am I back CU a robot
again
exterminate
exterminate BOS Ved terminate termined
minate them it's red now
exterminate
exterminate extermin for I can Auto
attack for a moment cuz I'm nervous
there's a
guy I'm
here show me who you are what you're
capable of
exterminate I bet oh there's a lot here
okay you you've been don't worry she's a
bot she's a bot okay maybe she will walk
into the thingy then that's good all
right all right you ready for this get
her get her get her ah okay she flashed
I'm leaving goodbye I'll take some of
this while I leave it's so nice take
this while I leave goodbye no don't eat
them I'm out of here
First Blood oh nice First Blood oh you
back thank
God y yum yum y y y i AV you don't worry
nice good
job okay CC in in about
um in about 10 seconds I will come to
you okay okay I keep down no more no
less never thought I'd
walk all right all right make her come
back make her come
back okay she will never expect this she
will never expect this she's not
expecting this one what is that has my
snowball goodbye thank you wait who are
you Noo-noo nooo and will and oh sorry
sorry and will and will okay okay oh
no I'm so scared I'm in a back don't be
scared M you're are
beautiful I am
retreating
Ming that's a jungle okay oh no how do
you know I'm guessing theit I'm again go
fter okay yeah I thought so pool of
reflection sh what you doing by the
tower I'm
reading okay I'm reading uh some bits to
do with um H didn't see this skin makes
my weapon like super super visible oh
jeez thank you invisible yeah it's it's
nice it's kind of nice actually super
super
visible Gavin bottle skin fun so
slow I am so SL I'll get
him I have a u shun oh God so I'll get
I'll get that that skin help minions
I'll get that
skin does kind of look like him good
super
visible I'm going to
oh let's see what animation okay guys
I'm going to run it down bot lanane are
you ready have fun okay well I hope
you're ready for me to run it down bot
Lane take him down wo
Y come back
huz oh thank you thank you I did how did
you know she how does she know I want
her to come back an enemy has been slain
goodbye Hi Li hello I'll help you with
this guy for a moment the sky isn't blue
the gr isn't GRE okay okay
okay oh I love playing people they're
totally people not I love to playing
against people yeah these people I love
playing against them I get it oh
oh she's
here two of them uhoh uhoh
uhoh why is there heal there
go yours o cool oh no my guy's not a
Healer I just had that on me
I might have to retweet you retweet
retweet retweet going to retweet like
and retweet get oh I just ran to the
wall never mind uhoh oh no oh no oh no I
need to run run run run run run run run
run run I'll pick their
stuff okay we going going home yeah I'm
going home we're going home I'm Going H
him I'm
done stuff it's
he's so cool don't know
why poo is freaking out a little
dance I'm a no please be someone might
be outside today is my first time you'll
be fine D it don't
worry yeah you're doing great yeah is it
easy to stream snipe in this game
uh we're probably against bot right
now is it easy to stream snipe you look
like ow shut down Nissa you look like sa
V thank you I am a magical
girl higher LS not
hession mind
oh there's a guy there's a guy
here kill him no I'm not worried about
it if anything I would have welcomed it
getting stream snip maybe they would
maybe they would be nicer to
meow go easy your feet or I'll ban you
they'll just kiss my feet my beautiful
bare
[Music]
feet please stream snipe us oh God I
died don't
I'm so sorry it's
okay down it's okay I died too in
solidarity solidarity the ashes into the
fire yeah I'm slowly but surely
overcoming greed that's good no you
should keep being greedy oh really yes
continue your greed okay okay continue
your greed be greedy okay okay oh
they're they're right here why are they
right here okay wow I'm coming top oh
you're welcome to come as long as you
don't steal my kill okay I'll let you
have it I'm going to set it up so you
can get him where is he going why is he
leaving okay
okay he's never going to expect this if
he just walks up okay okay okay snowball
get him get him get him get him get him
I'm not ready okay get get him get him
get him get him get him
TR I took it oh it's okay it feels like
I
did D we did that
together there's like four of them
what three oh that's
just okay so you're telling me if
there's two people I should still attack
them kill
them you got this
oh there's someone else teleporting in
so three people should I still yes you
should kill
them don't be a coward kill
them out of my way knockturn got a blue
buff to get an En yeah I killed her I'm
running home see greed is good who's
singing what did I say I don't know
unless not it's not us it's not me I
didn't even know how to Ping wa what the
heck I don't know how to Ping either
maybe us
ping I didn't I didn't click anywhere
there so um anything else I should bu I
create the quiet ow come back hit me
under
Tower okay okay are you
ready are you ready go in go in okay
he's trying he's trying crazy you're
crazy you're crazy
dead I will also go home I
suppose focus on completing for
biscuit I was G doesn't work I was
writing to my chat because they were
like poo box I'm like he's a
parrot he can he's a taco actually well
he's a Ty
of is
aao so like and parrots can like you
know mimic a lot of animals yeah can
mimic a dog sound if dogs really do
sound like
that I got killed I drew the line you
crossed it
thanks yes
I let out an alt and it did absolutely
nothing it was so bad the thought is
what counts yeah yeah you spooked them
my aim is so [\h__\h] man you spooked
them
what what is that why are they all doing
the
apocal US um not turn's thing ow why are
they why are they all
here they want you and they what they're
crazy Bots are crazy I want to take it I
walk up to dead
gone oh oh it reset okay I'll
leave you got this two of them
yummy no come
back where is she where is she come here
no that didn't hit
her
oo I can oh that doesn't go over there
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum
yum I'm going home
okay Queen is doing this now I'm having
fun with friends I just like multiplayer
games I like multiplayer games when I
have
time this one's fun I'm really enjoying
it
[Music]
turet walk up to me walk up to me okay
you don't need you don't don't need you
don't need to do that
Liz oh what's that got
to
ow ow well I got
dragon bloom Sol is worth it I did wrong
exeed what does
mean what does it mean what does it all
mean she where I go what the I can't
forget where I came from what was that
he does a little
dance he was teleporting uhhuh into the
minion sometimes that's just what you
have to
do
[Music]
uhoh biscuits heal you oh these I didn't
even realize I had biscuits in my
inventory
yeah
biscuits oh that's why you got
a I didn't realize I had any biscuits
nothing's as simple as black and white I
thought you guys were cuz you guys like
cookies that's
why cookie
cookie sometimes you just wait why did I
leave I can buy more stuff oh my God
killing yay oh I
miss you got her
yely y y y y y yum yum
y um if if okay so I am spending a lot
of time barely killing the the the BS
and then going home should I rather play
it safe I don't go home and push the LAN
n n you should kill them yeah kill them
okay what that that's a
nocturnal yeah are you dead no I'm alive
I came to help you oh oh no I killed him
he's gone don't worry I just did what
Chad told
me more
mins you singing I'm she sing don't sing
okay okay I'm I'm roll I'm rolling I'm
rolling I'm rolling rolling okay
okay
y
thanks There Go My
Hero level 12 is this
one death is no Muse I'm just a girl
from everything it
touches I don't know
the I'm just a
girl I don't know if I'll survive or die
you're not just a
girl toell welcome hello in my Lane
hello please assist me get away from her
oh oh oh an eny has oh oh w
what happened power down he's so
crazy can
you I mean nothing kind of work you
should morb more often almost dead she's
almost dead she's almost
dead is it the power of women that
compelled you to do this was the power
of wom that really pushed me into doing
that that's so strong I also believe in
the power of women sides it was very
powerful is she's trying I ran out of C
zero I need more C zero in between this
next match I need to go get another C
Zer wants to live it's okay you got her
you got her kill her kill her no no you
got her Qui no it's
okay it's
okay keep chasing me sarapen come on
what are you doing
yeah nice try
Lux your aim is as bad as mine all right
I'm here for you I'm here for youed I'm
rolling I'm rolling it down I'm rolling
it down I'm no I ran to the wall I ran
to the
wall oh nice nice you got it
nice
[Music]
y oh yeah oh yeah oh not
turn wo
windows I don't know what that means I
will kill you you win you win them you
know you
Windows no minion don't kill me yeah you
wi you
Windows oh God your team has destroyed
Windows Windows revenge is
sweet
mint yeah activation key oh doesn't have
the same skill as me oh oh right behind
you
oh he charm come on
me be enough for my single person
there's another one coming from Top
myself jungle I guess okay did not in in
fact come sweeter than C oh here he's
there he's there more friendly I like C
zero better # not sponsored I'm going
I'm going I'm going thanks BB yeah I
brought them over sorry about
that nice kill kill
kill nice nice nice nice nice
nice a
finally
that
O Let's get the tower K you yay nice to
Tower forgot about
him your team has
destroyed do you have your ult
kiaa yes if you use it it's like a
sniping if I can get him low enough
maybe you can can kill him get away from
her
Inhibitors
inhibitor I don't know I I I don't know
I I'm
sorryy you just walked into it
but she's she's showing me her pretty
butt get her get her get
him
Revenge
Rampage
goodbye come back come
back
yay come here Sur you charm y y y yum
yum
y an
ally walked into their
home oops you walked into their home and
died it's
okay kill
them there worse yeah yeah yeah worse
worse worse oo
heart is empty we're so good at this
game yay not bad not bad you're
slaying no right now I'm just running
because I died I have been slayed though
you're sl you slaying so good
though that is
questionable why am I here I don't know
where is
everybody you have been slain mother
trucker
no we're on our way there's two B away
away will I die to this no nice I did a
thing I got rooted I did a thing uh
guy's right behind
you our team has destroyed a
turret don't die
Kiara an ambush a stampede
hey good job yeah we were we were we
were here we were
[Applause]
here we're winners winner
[Music]
winner this was us does honor players
just never show yourself
or yeah you can't honor yourself it's
just the others oh oh this is a screen
where you choose
[Music]
why you honor yourself Kara no I thought
this was showing the the good players of
the game
already no you get to pick oh I haven't
seen that one do I skip it by accident I
don't know um I just want to go get
another drink be right back yeah okay
okay we're doing it wow so good yeah
we're we're doing a League of Legends
with the with the
professionals um quick say like some
terms only professionals would
know um I think I need to restart my
League of
Legends profal would say that is what a
professional would say to restart my
League of Legends yeah I see I see I'm
going to yeah I'm going to I'm going to
restart League I'm going to Lane Swap
and then I'll I'll mid Gap and then I'll
State and split push and then okay and
then I'll uhhuh
to tower Tower tower Tower I agree with
everything you said Soul Baron um um um
um um flash yes what what about your
micros oh all of them
yeah I I got it I understand
did you get what I meant yeah I I got it
I I understood that solo bolo jungle
uninstall un jungle iall that is what
League of Legends Pros would say proxy
proxy I am just very confused about all
the words that are being thrown around
um um they're good words jungle jungle
diff What does diff mean differ sff diff
yeah it basically if you say it to
someone it's like you're complimenting
them jungle D so if you go into a normal
game you should say that and you're
complimenting them you're lying to me I
can hear from your tone of voice don't
try gas you say don't even try you're
Gap it's a
compliment gamer oh I see I see so make
sure to use that in your next League of
Legends game me more what else should I
say so yeah just because I want to be a
good player a positive mindset what
should I say okay okay okay so next time
you go into a normal game just go just
say like pick any role and say like I
don't know mid Canyon MH yeah can
someone tell me why I got promoted to
Bronze in the game yay she's
bronze you're bronze I'll do that thanks
for the I've invited you back oh you've
invited me
y I just checked their
streams they made it for the cube
o I gave my damn how did they do that
cheat the rest of the mints what did
they cheatz
I also
enjoy so I was like here you go Queen
Mother toe a Cod harle or else I will
finish
[Laughter]
them she was like o
[Music]
she's like
oo okay I'm back minutes right it's okay
it took them it took them three hours
they waited three hours that's crazy
that is crazy hello I didn't do that
hello I'm glad I'm here guess welcome
back no regrets can play exile to or I
have partially regrets but mostly no
regrets no regrets no regrets regrets no
regrets none of
them absolutely no none
regrets no regrets allow in this
household none of that
no none of that no
Cecilia yes you jump scared me are we in
are we ready for Q
yeah oh I haven't said anything in like
a while we did something oh getting
ready for Q
sorry oh are we in oh okay okay
okay we're queuing we're queuing we're
going to queue six people queing except
queing are we doing yeah we'll we'll do
real people yes yes I like real
people yes yes I
believe oh a heart
throb Warick heart throb Warick
War
[Music]
wig real I am a hard Fric yeah you
you'll love you'll love her be on that
one yourself
remember you'll you'll love her be on
that one
k yeah yeah do she do something
special you'll see I would SP
it I'm so fast do we go into the bushes
seconds we can check we can see if
they're real people I'm big I'm little
how do we know if they're real
people
Instinct okay I think they're
Bots that's a
bot I don't have any CC I didn't start
with it myself oh thank you just a b you
won't judge me too
hard
damn why we you on my Lane hello no look
so different how could you I should have
started dou
you should have double
you for the music's cute he's inviting
me get them get them stop
it oh Nissa it's worth it I can't get
anymore man oh nice that looks cool yeah
paint mypace as cool Stu and
goodbye didn't even heal I miss you oh
they hit they hit they hit really
Warwick really really come War you
little bit they're low there's two that
are low here guys get them okay I'm
running worry
not where are they
I'm
oh okay I'm I'm here for to harass her
jungle okay okay
okay nice nice nice y good I'm going to
die from these dogs leave leave leave
run away run away
it's okay the minions are keeping
everything up I don't even have to do
anything
yay
yay you can go home you should go home
I'm going home for now I'll ref the
details
home woman who's beautiful she's a woman
wo wo I said she's a woman who's
beautiful she a woman what are you
trying to say huh oh my
God I didn't know we were like that I
didn't know we were that kind of Legends
team thank you so much make sure you
make sure you have money for for food
looking for thank you so much make sure
you have money for for your your food
and everything in the oh
gosh uh what's that what's what's his
name uh thank you so much make sure you
have money for yourselves too though
galloo Gallo I hate that guy
but he has a chicken costume and I'm
aware of it KFC I'm
aware everybody told me to look at an
enemy
has I don't feel so good I'm
back nice wow you running charm Charmed
Charmed where are you running
[Music]
to an enemy has been SL he gave me a
kill for free so y
all
right let's
go it's hard to get
out oh they are
here beautiful woman I see
her I'll switch the order now just a
trace I cuz he's hi meringa
oh my
god there was a SP in the
world wait why are the two of them
that's not that's a bot you know he just
doesn't know what's going on these seem
like BS uhoh I'm going to
die you're not going to die not
today not
today guy what is he doing keeps going
back and forth what is
they're doing their best their best is
not good enough they're trying really
hard B are going to kill you or the
minions no okay now so you're going to
Flame the
bot you saying I deserve this yes you
deserved that you deserved what was
coming for you for flaming the Bots
let's go B this yeah what is food is
that some luxury what the you get for
being toxic this is a l we should early
okay oh is that some luxury I'm too poor
to afford I guess my one cookie would be
enough for the winter oh my
God I did it right he's I'm King this
kill please please make sure you have
enough
monies for yourselves too
okay I love you all very much she Char
it's Char but thank you I do appreciate
it
okay no I did it no wait there's another
one behind I'm going to get this dragon
now H
it he could have killed me if he wanted
I think he's in love with
me oh my
God oh my
God by the
gods I'm leaving sorry wait there two
there's three I'm doing my best you're
doing great Nissa you're doing defin
you're doing great I lost my lane and
it's it's 100% because of the jungler
no way wow GG yeah my bad it's just how
it is
sometimes I'm
going I'm out of Mana I I can him okay
I'm going mid
I'm I'm eating him all I can do now I
have to leave okay I'm running away too
okay oh he's confused he's confused hit
him hit him awesome okay okay okay hold
on he's Charmed he's
Charmed go in go in go in go in y it's
it's it's easy I'll show you CH easy
okay now I'm
going killing nice yay paint
Fades
yeah we
did you use your ult already
Yes
asking oh really I'm not sure because I
know I'm alone here so no one's talking
to me no I I I'm looking I'm watching
you yeah if he's really low like that
and he's far away you can save your old
for last and you should be able to kill
him you actually talked to
me I I have my ey on you you watching me
I'm watching you charm W I'm dying thank
you thank
you uhoh I run you have my stream open
in the second screen I am no I just I
click on the map and I look at
you why I why you even have time for
that I'm my
you you should focus on your L you don't
want to you don't want to I keep foret
about these biscuits crazy with doing
that yeah I honestly thought you guys
were just making a a blood flame everywh
like Kingdom cookie comment
[Laughter]
again here's the season for cookies
here's one more for for good work
today thank you yay cookies it is the
season for cookies get get them get
them oh no make him regret
living I like um looking at all the uh
the
festive cookies with the nice tins dying
I'm going to kill that Warwick no don't
steal my kill don't die don't die kill
I'm going into my locker bye no no no
have you seen kill for you for I'm
already gone I'll get this kill I'll
I'll avenge you okay oh my God he feared
me you are you seeing what she takes out
of the
locker what does she take out of the
locker it's a picture of
VI oh really I'm rolling the ball I'm
rolling the ball he has no idea what's
going on don't
spoil yeah don't spoil please what I
don't know anything what it's the
animation in the The Bee no no no I
didn't mean that I was asking followup
questions oh
you stand no chance I killed him I see
he dead you you did that because I said
that I lost my Lane because of you
previously huh yeah I had to I had to
get rid of him I I really got it back
I thought I get
[Music]
that they don't care CH one breath
and we care no no no
no I thought I get that kill to buff
me uh-oh it's okay of course we care
about you no no no no we love you we
care I'll come back and kill him
Darkness again no
don't do that I'll make him regret he to
kill oh my
God tell him not to
okay I'll do that next time oh yeah I
need to eat the cookies eat the cookies
eat the cookies geky my Al is ready and
I'm like lowkey dying though I need to
eat my biscuits I know what he's doing
over here I stop stop fearing me I keep
forgetting to eat my
biscuits put that cookie down at least
you have
biscuit goodbye
Unstoppable double
kill your dest
Tower yay St there's some people up here
but I don't think they're coming up here
yet all not mean to flash fat finger
that right here right here it's okay
don't die to her I can do an ALT
yay okay
okay oh God oh God we can do this
sh go in go in go in go in come in come
in in in in in come
in come in come in come in come in come
in come in come in come in I'm going to
leave right here right
here look
[Music]
time yay I can have a cookie a biscuit
biscuit biscuit wait it's number two
biscuit biscuit biscuit
so didn't really heal me all that much
oh ow what the hell was that no that
sucks a lot
of he's a tanky chy apprciate it tank a
thank you
velcro wow what she doing over there
thank you for being so sweet thank you
for all being so sweet I a very lucky
queen I'm lucky cuz I have you
guys for you Warwick I'm getting kill
one way or another your
teamy legs and start walking
toward an enemy has been
SL for
you we got him
[Music]
I more I know I got I need more damage
are good it doesn't matter who gets him
as long as he dies
right oh I mean no I meant I meant I
don't know how I got him that's what I'm
saying I I don't mind who
get kill him
oh
no get
her all right all right I'm here he has
no Mana he has no
Mana keep going keep going
y oh he's behind me behind me he behind
me he's behind you oh it's a toad why is
the toad attacking a toad I mean just
kill him destroyed why are you attacking
us Mr Toad that's not very nice a toad a
toad I'm coming
jungle coming
jungle welcome what is that what was
that a
thank
you your team has D okay okay okay let's
go get him I'm
leaving moving
Onis I I thought maybe you were talking
last time so I was like oh oh down he's
trying he's
trying I'm dying it's okay run an enemy
has been slain I'll stop them
oh
whoa thank
[Music]
you
down you're really brighten my day a oh
no is so sweet HP he's running at
me okay
nice nice nice nice
nice get the turret okay awesome
[Music]
wayy what
I
bad
okay ooh
you think you walk out over here yeah
yeah he's coming your way walk over here
come
back no he's not I think he's so scared
he's too scared of you what is he scared
of he's coming
[Music]
back oh man
sucked you got two people and there
I'm not
sure play time is
nevery
monster he wants to play
league is she only she thinks I'm done
streaming cuz I'm so
quiet has destroyed an inhibitor girl
I'm still screaming let's get top Tower
oh okay guess I should talk more this
is it's okay we're all locked in we're
we're all locked in so hard
I
am your team has destroyed a turret it
was worse it was worth was worth
worth was worth
worth okay he's almost dead do you see
him yes on the right yes oh it's you
legendary nice nice nice
legendary your team has destroyed an
inhibitor just wants to live let
go going
back she going back where's my mouse I'm
[Music]
[Laughter]
coming relive the pain
not again your team died I'm fine I'm
fine I'm
fine get has destroyed a turret your
team has destroyed destroyed
[Music]
destroyed I'm coming just a
TR you got him
oh of
course crazy a triple K cookies this is
everyone a favorite one you'd
recommend I think my favorite at the
moment is Pink Panthers you can get
her you you got triple kill triple kill
yeah I think my favorite at the moment
my my favorite is Pink
Panthers what's everybody's favorite
Oreo oh that's a good one Chips a Hoy
I'm not had chips a Hoy g g they look
good though I think they're they're in
America right chips
aoy pink
Pampers oh my God I can honor more than
one person I can just honor all of them
yeah oh
oops I'm just plugging and charging my
mobile would Liz be okay going top does
w want a bot Lane oh yeah you want to
support what the hell is bot
L
Kaitlyn I is bot I didn't mind uh doing
whatever it don't bother me I mean I
love I I love you
Nissa but I I don't mind switching it up
oh bottom I thought every is bot Ling
cuz the Bots are everywhere
no what so should I go bottom yeah go
bottom you want to I'll I'll see a
different scenery for once mhm okay
okay yeah and then narissa will set up
all the kills for you
okay okay okay she will steal them all
is that what I hear from that giggle I I
nothing
intentional I believe okay one second
I'm just getting water but I'm still
like here okay you will steal them it's
okay like if I don't she can't steal
anything that doesn't exist there are no
kills in the first place with
me no she set them up and then you're
going to kill steal her it's probably
more like she's setting them up and
she's killing
them they for you I'm just there for
mental support we have to do it together
okay okay I play play again okay I'm
here okay okay let's go I'm baby I'm
baby I'm I'm
baby I'm sorry I'm a b where are you
[Music]
oh mine's still mine's still loading uh
yeah mine's still loading back into the
thing yeah now it's doing it well I've
recently met a baby so I think I'm
pretty good with you know met recently
met a babal
creature and I get I I I uh it it pulled
my hair it was pretty fascinated with me
I gave it an elephant it liked the
elephant yeah
I think it was in love with
me baby do I need to click something
different now or no okay no you can just
swap you can go
top baby whis you have to swap the
thingy you pulled my hair
yeah and I would mind I would like to go
back bottom after this game though
okay it's just a test
yeah I'm coming I'm going to go Bottom
now yeah go bottom who fairy cool I love
the this looks like Victor I know it's
so pretty yeah the
[Music]
guy are we on the oh no we on the other
side oh no oh no it's oh no
is that bad no it's
just personally it doesn't change
anything but it gets really confusing no
it is confusing yeah let's see if
they're real people so is my bottom the
top now because we're the other way
around yeah go this way no
here uh wait wait wait why is the view
always so weird in the beginning why do
I always have to change it I don't know
are we going into the into the bushes GG
we can see if they're real I'll poke my
head
over are we going into the bush seconds
SP yeah we might die I don't see that
they might be starting Legacy will I
leave Blue what'll survive of me even my
footsteps should I walk over there just
to look yeah I'm behind you I'm behind
you okay are are you guys real are you
guys B guys are you real are you B yeah
you real people oh where you going sah
where are
they're my individual own person wait
there's someone there they real are they
real get them I'm too used to
being get
hurry are they
real
yay dead it's okay oh they're here hey
what that's a real person that's really
yeah they're they're definitely real
real person okay I'm running that is a
real person back to the tower back to
the tower wow okay I'm at the tower
you're playing against a real
person who the Lux is real the Lux is
real no bot Lan is definitely real
people it's okay I got this we've
trained for this
guys no we
haven't yes we have nothing's as simple
as black and white
sorry oh hey what ELO are we playing
against What's Happening
Here what's the best thing to do now ah
life
flows
wow
um you just are supposed to kill kill
the minions last hit them you get money
so when you die go back you can um you
know things to get stronger
yeah should have meaning I meant more
like running away from me running away
from scared ah I mean there is no
retreat we just have to keep doing it if
you're struggling you can come back by
the
tower
okay I car the legs of BL full attention
blah blah she's telling us her entire
life story blah blah blah blah blah
blah this ter whoops what the
hell come here
CC where up yeah where I am I'm
coming okay charm good good kill him
kill him kill him I don't have a ward
I'm afraid of walking in I'm very
low
no
iers this questions oh my die to
this
cookie
owie to go home peaceful has oh
peaceful and
Shadow ow ow ow ow
ow I prefer playing against bots no no
it'll be okay I like I like people I
feel more fulfilled when it's a real
person than a
bot yeah it's a learning it's how you
learn it's how you actually get
better ow
all my and then I'll leave yummy yum yum
yum no I'm have confidence nope have
confidence an ally has been slain oh no
strikes oh oh no I am dead oh no oh no
no no
no oh all right I will come smack him
soon
Liz maybe let me kill all these little
tiny
[Music]
babies you me they're pretty good
they're pretty good
bot like GG you're going to have to
carry I'm I KN new okay okay I'm here L
here okay I'm going to uh oh wait I need
to get closer to be able to do what want
to
do where did he go no he healed oh I
shouldn't have Flash oh I don't know
where they are damn well nice
try watch
closely there they are
okay she has no Mana I'm running up
cookie oh okay go go go go
go nice she can I blame the Ping I have
170 ping blame the Ping thank you
okay get that goddamn ping every time
maybe I can
I ow ow he's hurting
[Music]
me I'm going to go back let's go I can
walk
bottom wow he's ice sking with himself
it's so cute I'm going for the Draven or
the Jin go
on okay well I hid them but I have to
leave they're leaving back up back up
peace of mind is a journey will you
hold so
careful b side okay
could you spell some cookies for the
tacos please m' just back up we're
really low I'm sure the the bakery and
the blood flame Kingdom will give you
give you a
cookie no justice they're very kind nice
only
Clarity oh my minion oh your minions oh
uh-oh uhoh
was that does this music come from you I
don't
know uh yeah the music comes from
nissa's
[Music]
uh
me
ouch got you bit female dog female
dog help
me still bird please save us I can't I
can't I can't fight this war no no she's
level seven okay I can't fight this
Warwick where are
you it's okay he's on
grubs can't really can't do anything
here I got you
biscuit no Lux leave leave our Tower
alone you fiend oh I'm yeah leave it
alone I take my jumper off it's
hot oh wait we can go kill Warwick if
you want I just realized I already took
my jump kill Warick two people my long
my long sleeve shirt is just too
thicker just standing there we can walk
towards him I don't think we'll make it
there in time is the only problem by
time he leaves he's very fast they're
already level six we're screwed oh he's
right there I see him they have alts we
don't oh I'm coming it's okay I'm
walking to you I'm walking to you oh no
an ally has been
slain I'm too I'm too behind to do much
it's okay it's okay sorry it's
okay let me grab this so Dragon Ball's Z
please stop piing randomly long sleeve
shirt um I've been told it's light thing
to do but it's really sick if you do it
correctly oh I think retreating was the
correct thing to do it was just too late
oh
no no she rooted me she always Roots me
no rolled at
you that's rude I hate her
goodbye do I have a cookie I don't have
any cookies oh my
God where' you go is that
the this guy stop stop stop
oh wow wow wow wow wow wow
oh he's just walking oh he's just
walking okay I'm coming from behind the
war might come back I'm I'm dead I'm
running away no I missed I missed don't
worry I scared her I scared her I scared
her I scar oh oh no oh no oh no oh no
I'm going to be more careful oo it's
good go go go go you got him an ally has
been slain ow oo okay never mind I'm
going to be I
no you got this no I I was trying to W
the bush
no wait that's messed upop only the bear
dies and the girl still lives and then
she just like lays next to him on the
floor what do you mean the bear which
bear Noo-noo and with with one I don't
know your animal
your the and she's fine and then she
just lays down on the floor she's living
that's messed up she dies of
grief
a you think about it let's go let's go
okay we can still turn this right guys
yes we can still turn this around no we
can still turn this around we can do it
duh I should have just played
team I'm a te melted
[Music]
bottom oh my God just die Str do we do
quick do this Strat number seven I think
Str number seven we do seven I think we
got this
so my first day was St number seven of
course I can tell you you didn't read
the sure everybody else knows but you
got to
explain you didn't read the manual on
the strats oh there's war coming out
behind me war's coming out behind me
he's behind me he's behind
me oh behind you okay I'll I'll him yeah
he's over here somewhere
he was behind me what it is I'm running
away again pleas okay I didn't blame you
running back to my
minions please your turet has been
destroyed
uh-oh that's not
good oh he's here oh
wait oh oh God he charm he's charm oh
I'm dead I'm going to try coming Mondo's
on his way Mundo's on his way I'm dead
want to try coming back we're both dead
okay yeah I need help I'm here for the
Gin oh he FL I mean I need help top I'm
not bottom
anymore
need yeah I need help top for a moment
watch out for this Warwick Let's Get
Him whoa what
is actually as Mr Mundo
isy what is this what is all this fire
everywhere fire fire light the
fire the
fire fire high as you desire very
collector an enemy
is no not legendary that's fine he got
executed he was greedy ni nice cool what
a loser cool just kidding he's kicking
our asses
he's a
fool let's
go where am I to
goess everything we're getting stomped
no we not no it's okay it's okay we're
fine come back yeah we're good around oh
I don't know I don't know can just has
to come up with some Strat and tell us
what to do that they have 21 kills and
we have two are you
sure uhoh uhoh uhoh I got that they're
all here the war and the freaking M got
me I will die come with no no don't die
we going to bite them okay that's a good
idea I think
that is my plan we're going to bite them
we will bite them them okay what if we
just went next you know re like a
reset
okayy like like we go to the next
game
what wait is that
surrendering what if we went to the next
that sounds like surrendering it's not
winning oh go feel like the opposite of
winning no it's winning it's winning
I can't get this ow they're all here I'm
coming I'm coming I'm coming bring them
in oh there's so oh my
god oh no the dead body and the dead
child so messed up the dead child too I
ah we can we can go next to reset and
maybe we'll get worst people uh they're
going they're going mid I think they're
all going mid poor
hoay surrender give me your full what
enemy
killing who voted no I don't
know who voted no who voted have to have
to vote it has to be animous it has to
be animous oh
[Music]
man oh it's only that was if only we
knew who that was too bad we can't
figure it out oh it's only oh it is I
suppli defeat that's the first time I
see that today it's very depressing I
know no it's okay the d stands for done
well
done e f e a
t I finished my second liter of water
give me a sec I need to grab more okay
no worries more without
me brv okay brv
[Music]
okay you are still not muted on my
screen
[Music]
okay 13 kills from that cloudy
Jester
Jin 13
oh speaking of Jester I want to try
shako shako shako
shako uh let's see do I even have him
yet we fed him too
early but I am a fast food restaurant
owner so I'm here to feed people no
that's
true I need to feed them you need to
feed I'm so
hungry I would be evil if I would let
people hunger yeah you're just so kind
and
giving I I I do like to receive too but
that's in my private life I
suppose as a professional businesswoman
I like to
give yeah
yeah what's your love
language what's my love language
uh uh
uh
H we should all take one of those
quizzes to see what it is I feel like
I'm the only person who didn't take this
like Omega quiz thing oh I haven't done
it yet do you want to do it now
everybody was taking it like is it that
short no well I don't know we can we can
still look at it afterwards after stream
after after stream you don't want to do
taking and posting the results while I
was busy with L and I don't even
understand still what a mega verse means
it's it's important it's important
apparently it's very
important
H it has 40 questions oh that shouldn't
be too long I have returned hello did
you take the Omega quiz
Cecilia no not yet oh you also didn't I
Haven
yet I should what's your EXC
I forgot about it I saw it I was I
should do this and I forgot about it
really how can you forget about it when
it's been going on for like three days K
was saying that but but her and me
haven't done it yet so yeah I see I see
but I have a good
excuse what is your excuse I was busy
the past three days with ladies in my in
my house should I pick that one yeah
ladies did you have ladies in your house
I'm a lady is my mom my mom's L amount
of ladies excessive Ladi there's too
many ladies my mom's a lady um have you
been having a nice time yeah me and the
ladies or you and the ladies Ladi me and
the ladies we had what a nice time very
nice time and magnificent marvelous time
so beautiful they love Austria so
everyone AA so two out of five of us
here have taken the Omega quiz is I will
say one thing
yes how much longer do you girls want to
play because one person in this room has
a uh thing to do that I can't even get
on don't even worry I want to apply uh
not pressure but I want to
remind who is it who has the thing to do
a someone sounds very
guilty N I
see it's it's practically done it's just
I whether I whether I want to add a
cherry on top that's all you should you
should okay you know yeah sure I'll add
the cherry on top add the cherry on top
and I will eat it should we play another
one yeah yeah we can play just one more
how long does the Cherry
take um shouldn't take too long all
right if we do one more then yeah I'll
have I'll have time all
right let's go hold on are my runes
correct okay finding match Comfort Pig
Teo oh you're doing P Teo this time okay
comt oh I want to change my
cater oh
everybody in Discord room has
participated in the Advent calendar
except for one
person I declined it you can switch your
character thank you sorry oopsie try try
Lilia
JB huh oh my God Teo with the Beast Skin
n the F we we're playing Le so cute beo
I love beo beo beo wait who are you Aus
CH ah can I go top again bottom was
stressful yeah you're going
top why would you say that like you want
changed I changed the color not a good
ad goodbye guys I changed the color and
it looks like a
battalion you'll see when I load
in it looks like a battalion
I got the um Arcanist Arcanist Shaker
and it I changed the color it looks like
a palian over the report
button okay I'm ready now I don't care
either way but you it's okay I broke up
before you broke up with me I already
said I'm going back up should she
already said a letter before good fine
then good I hope you'll have fun down
there being bottom I love bot yeah she
does love
bot who's who's joining you down there H
herb
me
[Music]
a I said off I said before the last game
I want to go back I'm ready you want to
go oh okay I wish you to happiness I see
thank you I've seen this coming in the
past weeks and months anyway the signs
were all over sign all oh my goodness
gracious well you knew that that we
would be like pairing in the in the
bottom Lane in League of Legends League
yeah honestly iing since the very
beginning I've seen the Synergy in your
colors and your designs mhm wow well
she's monitoring me you know yeah I mean
I'm monitoring yeah I mean Cecilia and
GG also monitor Thea too so yeah
I'm ready I don't see us
there are we checking if they're real
people again they're real people I'm
sure oh I hear KDA
music of
[Music]
me are we going into the bushes or not
nah that's the most way run
[Laughter]
I'm fine on my own 30 seconds until
minion spawn me and my minions guys you
want to you want to you want to see this
my goodness clown you're a little clown
my goodness oh wait who are you playing
against is okay no lucks my goodness
wait no what is
this have smolder smolder is that
a what do I need to know quick I know
nothing about him I I I think it takes
him a really long time to ramp up he
needs a lot of
farm and his hold is this big line and
he flies around and he's
like and he throws a ball at
you molder from a
caneo yes that's crazy W turn turn on
your screen question mark
someone you can't tell me is D okay okay
do whatever makes you happy that's fine
I have to I have to task manager my way
out of it why is it not Window mode what
happened wait why is he doing more
damage than
me he's going to farm
huh oh
W so nice to see you thought I was alone
did you
oh you are
wrong yes you wrong I think bot is real
people I'm pretty sure they're real
people this
still uh Warwick behaves just the way I
like it so I think he's a bot
M can the team be like half B half real
people we go sure I think that's what
happened last the first time we played
yeah I think if they don't have like a
full
team and there's like not a good amount
of people who can join with them they'll
just like supplement with Bots that
would be
evil it's okay she's
back is it like common that the Top Lane
is always played aone and the bottom is
always double yeah yeah
Bottom's not as aggressive as last time
which is
good maybe maybe they Bots may maybe
they you shouldn't have judged Me by One
game against
players I'm not judging you I would do
better now
perhaps I'm going to go back I'm not
judging you just bot bot all the lanes
and all the different areas or play
differ all Bs they're Bots for reals
mine bot B guys yeah they're all Bots
[Music]
y the jokes on you the jokes on you I'm
getting very come here come to come to
where I am you yeah yeah com oh guys
you're going to going to want to come
see this oh don't run up to him though
he's melee don't to him he's a melee
range
champ too late Sor that I wasn't looking
at me oh you got him you got him you got
him you got no
he I don't know what about this
[Music]
champion no his life
steal well nice it's okay they're Bots
my ham my ham with a little feeding
oh she's so close so close to death I'm
dead you die all I thought she was going
to die she so awkward she's so weird I
thought she was going to die
Nissa oh God now I'm going to die going
home wait wait wait yeah kill him kill
the bot kill the bot oh he just left
yeah he teleported
oh he went
bot oh what that's a skill Oh I thought
he was going home if it's purple it's
teleport I think it was
gold remember wow if it's blue it's the
back get her get her get
her
minion one more an enemy has been SL
I don't thanks so good that was very
very productive no problem uh uh uh
thanks no problem thanks Gigi just doing
my part
thanks oh
no ow
bye my go back
home I'm living my best life she says
actually I'll leave one of these here
byebye okay
[Music]
goodbye coming a little bit oh God oh
God looks funny
jungle
attacks is that what you is that what
you
need was that what was GG jungle
attacks yeah yeah is that part of
League yeah it's part of leag you know
it's normal you should get used to it
yeah it's a normal thing that everyone
does all right all right all right I
understand now
m uhoh
the oh stop
him wait there's so many of them there's
three people in the
[Music]
jungle an enemy it's okay you distracted
them I'm sure that they won't get the
last grub they're going to go to k
though okay I'm running oh my God they
killed my guy you got him kill him kill
him hey GG jungle tax jungle tax GG
jungle tax jungle tax jungle ta J jungle
taxs jungle ta come on Jungle tax I'm
I'm getting the jungler the jungle TXS a
owie he charm okay you're crazy do it
again uh give me like 5 Seconds an enemy
has Chang my mind nice okay bye goodbye
do you have like a heal or something nah
it is what it is that's fine so they do
damage to the J jungle animals don't die
can you like kill steal them and then
steal their kill yeah you can steal the
the jungle
animal that's a
strat that's why you always want to
fight objectives and take it from
them let me have your let me have this
no please
let me have your
blue
free oh where is he oh he's right there
H hit it take
it take your blue they're weak we'll
fight it together Vol
bear goodbye I'm going fight this
together okay chunky wony oh is also
here sleeping hi hi jungle TX thanks
FR oh he's he's flying he's flying oh
he's flying will be fun did you hear
that I so cute she just jumped up
chirping home oops don't press buttons
thank
you she wants me to watch the
enemy she's so cute the enemy oh all the
en
she to be my enemy she's an Arcane
hater don't be a hater from League of
Legends yeah from League of Legends
League of Legends you know they made a
game based off Arcane oh my God leg
that's how it feels to
me you're a fake fan fake League fan
they made they made a game based off of
our I'm not a league fan joining you
guys what do you
think I'm an Arcane fan sorry
Rian your Le
so
so you little get him
clone got him
aim an ally has been W he killed take
away my skin was like a oh there's a guy
oh that's his old let
[Music]
run I love taking your farm
I I was bunked might as well are you
dead no I got B
down oh they leaving oh what is he oh no
oh no you don't you don't see me I I see
you a I'm helping I'm helping I'm
helping you're helping I'm helping I'm
helping you're
crazy oh my God nice nice nice you guys
are so strong oh there two oh
no no but you just said engage yes yes
don't be afraid
do not be afraid always always greet I'm
not hitting any of my that's fine come
be here now okay okay okay
okay cleaning up yeah it's my job
perfectly
planned get him almost oh my God nice
nice nice nice nice who the heck is
that worth you worth what did you do
worth let him die that he's a bear now
what really is that still Warwick yeah
that that's still him no it's a bear why
is he a bear it's Vol Bear right yeah
Vol bear that's not war
rck they're both they're like the same
you know are are they yeah they're
basically the
same
Boozled oh okay I see Warwick and vol
time now so I think she so low you
bamboozled me no no I would not lie to
you I'll scare him away from your
lane thank you please continue doing so
an ally
SL an enemy has been
slain goodbye
ma'am stop
it I don't know why that
is are we sure they're Bots yeah we're
sure they're Bots I'm not sure if I was
a
bot an enemy has
been pretty
flowers
a did that do slating will fall soon hi
sorry about the audio
stuff maybe I should reinstall like all
my audio drivers or something
yeah every every single oneast each one
of
them what's your audio problem oh every
once in a while since like last week
every once in a while my audio just
becomes like super crunchy but I can't
hear it only chat can hear it it's like
what is you know it must be over
that's
interesting go go get him get him get
him back to
us
you
you so now G when I have like this much
health should I still what is happening
to my hold on something is going on with
my
computer something very terrible is
happening I admitted something
bad my I think what is happen I my is
flickering oh God everybody's got ISS is
loose crunchy it's it's like flick let
me take a video of this so you can see
how cursed this is be so funny
I'm going to start screen
recording what that's okay good
work okay let me send this to you uhoh
what what Just
Happening you killed her what the
this has problems con let me upload and
then send this
o speed it up can't believe he's at my
tower your team has destroyed
and there he goes the jokes on
you jokes on
you oh my my goodness what is going on y
to Broken
finally ooh I don't have boots yet I'm
okay put it here and then I'll also send
to kiaha so you can see thank you I
can't drag everybody into Val the game I
I did have a lot of flickering issues a
while ago yeah do you see that like what
is what is happening it's fine yeah
unfortunately I'm it's
fine okay ping too much
P yeah it's fine it's fine don't worry
don't worry you think it's fine think
it's okay otherwise I would it's fine
I'm pretty sure it's fine we're
winning I'm glad it's okay and nothing
is bad bad is happening no no it's
fine I don't even like what are these
circles and question marks and x's on my
screen
uh let me know if it turns into a blue
screen I had that
before I can make it through this League
of Legends game game yeah yeah we'll
we'll make it to this I bet it's Path of
Exile it's mad at me I'm going to die
you have Roblox on in this side as well
no I don't have Roblox on today don't
you know very
surprising it became dark what's going
on my greed I will die now um I mean
I'll probably ask a bunch of people
maybe someday maybe I can I deserve see
if there's some
other entertainers who are interested in
like playing some Valor EU server wise
someday but for now I'm fine just uh
casually playing accidentally flashed
I'm already in the middle I no longer
have second
monitor maybe I'll drag Cecilia someday
no it's still flickering but I I once I
have more time I don't want to drag her
into a like a
I
don't you know maybe I don't that maybe
I don't play enough you know feel it I
don't need to I feel bad if she liked it
and then I couldn't play all the time
you
know oh my
God what is where we is that Twitter
that's flickering on my page what is oh
my God takes another video so I'll
probably drag Cecilia when I know I have
time to drag her in often you know oh
what's
that looks
funny what do we want to do we're all
we're all doing pretty well don't mind
whatever you want to do beautiful
lady do we want to all go mid and push
mid do we want to push bottom what do we
want to do oh this wait they're all here
I'm here I'm
here here let's go let's go let's go
okay okay okay I'm going oh go
in Unstoppable okay I'll
get get
him Dragon scared me get this one too G
I'm dead you got this though you got it
get this
one vadra kill goodbye the panta the P
anything left over what the
Helly what's going on he run to wait
guys yeah you you got it I'm running all
running
no oh
nice I'm too far I'm too slow you still
run
goodbye my warrior team
destroyed very nice you guys are just in
their base destroying things it's
amazing that's beautiful
an ally would it makees sense like if
you just kill one lane and then ignore
the other turrets and then you go into
the base you could do that but um don't
oh the the more people that are in a
lane that you have to split XP with them
I put that on the outside so if everyone
went mid and tried to push
mid in the it sounds like a great idea
that sounds like a great
but if you're all level
one the the the single person in that
lane on their side is going to level F
and everyone else is getting lots of
freearm
wow good
job you're doing great
computer oh no I did my thing chat it's
okay almost won
oh what's this it's it's
[Music]
fine wait how
legary double
kill w she's singing oh that's you right
I was like yeah oh not walking backward
she's singer he's Charmed he's Charmed
he's Charmed she's a
single Ace s Ace she's a singer himer
Dinger
nice nice nice nice nice
nice this is so nice we're so good your
team destroyed we yay
yay come out twin let's Go's a
singer we won we y
[Music]
y my twin was here to see it
too look at my
clone good job yay
nice good keep up the good work all
right I got to dash nice
[Music]
wow okay I got to dash cuz I got to go
do do the thingy Miggy real f
if I want to add the cherry on top I
basically finished what I was finishing
but then I was like H do I add the
cherry on top I want to add you know
what I will uh but yeah thank you all
for
joining thank you all so so so so so
much you are all amazing thank you for
the support thank you for the supers
thank you for the gifted memberships
thank you for continuing memberships all
new memberships thank you for the Good
Vibes in chat that's what I I especially
um love about each and every one of you
that you uh make uh our space over here
very welcoming to everybody so thank you
it's nice that no matter what game we
play you know it's still a you know
welcoming area for everybody H yeah
anyway H potting is such sweet sorrow
but I will see you on the m
let my voice be your
strength a winky
[Laughter]
face
bye-bye see you very very soon bye bye
bye bye
[Music]