do
to the minecraft room oyshaw everyone uh
back to the game
hello hello everyone can you hear us
okay
hello hello hello ah
the twins are here i'm here with my
friends
thank you
[Music]
with with me in comparison to the others
yes hello how is it
hi
[Music]
[Laughter]
hi can i have some food i i just gave
you some steak
oh thank you oh thank you
bye thank you for the steaks
i was waiting for those huh
yeah all right put him away i don't need
him anymore
i'm making a weapon oh wait where is
this girl
i don't see him dudes in her house okay
my house
if you guys have weapons we and you have
like any xp
i have some stones here you guys can use
and you go into this basement and you
can enchant your weapons
if you guys haven't done it yet hang on
i tried it
wait did you enchant your uh iron sword
my what your iron sword or diamond oh
yeah yeah yeah oh my iron sword
oh hey is this the good one
[Music]
girl do you maybe first of all want to
tell the viewers what the hell
yeah what's happening today i don't know
and i have no idea
we're going to the nether i think yeah
yeah we're worth making another portal
and yeah something small and then we're
going to the never
together and all going to die yay
i'm trying to adjust my i've never been
there before what's it what's it like
what kind of things happen lava
everything's burning yeah break up bed
and then sleep in the never because it
gives you like a buff
it gives you a buff that makes you
stronger for like uh 20 minutes
really okay cool yeah i'll do that
i'm level one i can't enchant anything
now where is my bed it must be in the
house huh
wait i'll make one the only chat
something girl i can do for you
uh yeah yes
27 yeah it doesn't take away it takes
away your level though
it just takes a little bit between
now i'm 27. yes you enchant my bow for
me
of course
[Music]
on my game so everything is pirate
language so um
that's cool i want that okay girl
they're both fun breaking so
oh wait i thought i thought it had never
ending
i'm gonna give you guys a piece of gold
armor
depends on the person yeah it's per
player it changes on purple
i see it cool do you have the unlimited
look please
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i haven't
done that you can't have the boots
because it has a curse of binding and i
don't want
i think i should wear them because i
don't know i don't know if you could
take them off your pants
i need to go grab my hat i'll be right
back check it out golden snap bag
oh wait wrong one yeah i'm just
pretending this game is all about
pretending so i'm pretending it's a
golden snapback
oh my gosh you steal this you know want
a gold hat
oh it's got a curse of vanishing i don't
know what that is
um better than something right
yeah okay i thought you were still
enchanting where are you
oh
hello
does anybody want shiny pants ooh i do
are they clean
yes i'm very behind in this game because
i don't have time to play games
so please i mean we got you
a while i'm gonna go pick up the hat the
hat will disappear on death but it's
okay
is everyone okay what's going on i don't
think
she's having a crisis over there uh-oh
i don't know what's going on where are
you what's going on hello
i don't know i hear screaming there's a
skeleton over there he's just
oh he has an enchanted bow he might
start shooting at us that's the cave
where i wanted to oh no where's my sword
hello
yeah make a shot yeah come on yeah i
dare you hi
you're a coward he's a coward
come on come on put more uh angry in
your voice yeah really get
it hey you mother f word
no more cursing guys no more cursing
from me
he doesn't like being called stinky no
he doesn't i'll get him oh no i'm using
the wrong weapon hang on i don't mean to
use uh oh
oh no i just threw it with my pickaxe
away hang on where'd it go
it's gone i lost it it's gone forever
i got him i killed him smoke yeah you're
okay
yeah it's gone okay i'm eating hello
friends uh i need um
i need a pickaxe focus
i just you have an arrow in your head
watson
no you have an arrow in your knee and in
your hand
i hate that wait
traveler likes that it's in my hand
we're mining again in the nether
apparently there's a lot of gold
oh
how do i hold things in two hands and
how do i switch between them
right there you wanna you can scroll
through your
your hot bar like the stuff on the
bottom yeah you mean
yeah but i uh you guys are holding
things in two hands right
oh yeah yeah so if you if you press e
and then you see there's like a little
square on the right side next to your
feet
that's like a equip so you can hold the
calories again
hand i like the way you were saying it
before you like hand
oh really i didn't notice my left hand
um oh my left hand oh apparently you can
just press
f to switch them okay between the two
hands
okay um i only have one slot and it has
a sword in it
um yeah and then you can you can use
your hot bar on the bottom and you can
scroll through other stuff okay yeah you
got it
sorry i pressed what i have no memory
you you're doing it you got it
but i hang on oh the idiot idiot i got
it you want to switch your hands you
could press f
yeah yeah got it oh sick okay understood
understood
got it i okay i wanted to say an
announcement really quick
yeah the apollo rail is now complete
[Music]
it took so long
the thing on your roof looks amazing
oh i see it now i see it now
how do we build this portal i have
obsidian in my hand do i just complete
it
uh i think yeah yes where did you get
the obsidian
from i mined it with the diamond pickaxe
that i made
yeah what is this how we will access the
nether
yeah what is that is that okay if we
leave it there
well if it doesn't complete itself then
we can get rid of it
where's that i make it one block taller
i'm making baby cows hold on
okay i got i got the museu
are we going right in
look at everybody glowing over here yeah
we're shopping
wait are we guessing how do we make it
five tall four what are we breaking out
the weekend
yeah yeah one
okay now maybe oh i gotta remove that
block i think
okay wait so one two three three four
four
five so now i just do this yeah and then
just remove that
pickaxe i don't want to go get oh my my
clothes my house is right here
okay
bgm off yeah bgm is off i'm playing um
i'm playing the minecraft soundtrack
from
the internet because i don't know oh
yeah i totally forgot about music
we've been playing we don't even need to
think i think guys my minecraft doesn't
even play music so
i guess it'll be best to play whatever
yeah that's what i've been doing
oh hey where'd you guys get your shields
iron and wood oh okay cool i'm gonna do
that real quick
let
do i even have a house i guess it's over
here
i don't think you gotta have a house you
gotta build one
yeah i guess so huh i was thinking about
i was thinking about i like this area
up here this this mountain what do you
guys think should i find it out so we
have more room to build
yes right here wait woman
i'm gonna flatten this out this big
mountain what are you doing
kelly i'm looking for my chest i know i
had one i mean yeah
do it like you only have a cocktail okay
i mean
i guess it was over by the netherlands
okay that's why it's there
thank you yes you need a shield yes i
will create the shield where was my
house again um
it's i think it's gone oh yes my chest
is here but i have no house because the
creeper blew it up and then i got tired
okay
iron i know that i have iron
iron
let's see can i make shields out of
anything else
by chance oh i need i need arrows for my
bow
oh i got some arrows i have feathers you
can use
two oh i have one
you made like a farm damn yeah how do
you make
how do you make it i'll make a chicken
parmesan
and iron something maybe iron nugget i
don't know
i give up this is too much i can't sleep
you need assistance
him anymore gosh back in the day
oh no i took it again uh it's not a
tendency
look behind you yeah oh yeah
okay ooh thank you i'm sorry you had to
make that for me
you have a pickaxe in your hand and your
sword in the other
and what do we need and food sword
pickaxe food
uh kelly needs a bed i have one i have a
bed i have it i took it from my
beautiful wonderful
first okay okay okay yeah make sure
don't
don't forget your bed okay you want you
want
feather i have 10 shots and then i'm
screwed that's not a lot
that's fine whoa there you go
you have sticks yeah one second
where do you get the feathers i think
how you get feathers skeletons
chickens you kill chicken oh chicken
okay i need to kill chicken ah i need to
kill
chicken uh do you have um pointy rock
pointy rock yard is that an actual item
because that sounds like that rock i
don't know what that is
it's a flint oh oh yeah i have a bunch
of flint
here who is mr pierce
have you seen bradley and his family
callie
no i haven't can you introduce me yes
come come this way
thank you i want to meet them
happy family how do you get that
what hang on hello thank you
two babies it's interesting actually
because every
every time that i call an animal or for
example a dog or a cat a default name i
always call them bubba
but because because bubba everyone will
have a boobah
everyone will think that i'm talking i'm
talking
i love your dogs i think i can kill him
uh he can't get in the three-way he
can't get in the the door so if you uh
i don't know he's gone no he's right
here but he can't get
we gotta get him to stand in front of
the door because he's only he's three
blocks tall so he can't pass under a two
block
i feel like it is gonna die no no no no
no no no no no i got this
listen oh wait you guys are in the mind
aren't you
no we're at my house right now good uh
is trying to kill the enemy
it sounds really odd yeah something
sounds strange
something sounds like it was dying there
is water on the wall over there
why is that how do i harvest my my my
crops
yeah hit it with your hand you just
touch it just
reminds me i need to put the weed in
again
this is my home from now on this is my
home
an extra carrot i could have i have some
dirt yeah for my carrot farm
thank you put some dirt on them welcome
if you don't have any beets or melon i
have melon i have beer roots
oh wait what beer beetroot beer
it's fun someone claimed this is my
swimming pool
this is my swimming pool now has someone
cleaned this area
i think it's mine now you got a swimming
pool
yeah it's it's in here already for me
nice
i think he's gone already you scared him
off
i think i did huh my home is perfect
well not yet but it will be
sorry i'm just very excited let me know
when you guys are ready to go by the way
i don't want to hold us back oh
[Music]
open the gate i forgot uh no not yet
okay
oh wait it's just the one block right
yeah yeah okay i'm just going to
put this away get prepared
probably should make a couple pickaxes
huh
yeah yeah we need that maybe we should
craft some materials yeah
i will help in shortly just a moment
look at this dummy
dummy oh oh there's a gap in the wall
what's on this side that goes outside
evil witchery of disappearing my house
is big
oh it will be big uh let's bring it in
okay do i have iron nope
what do i need flint and steel for i've
never used that for anything
um i thought i knew that but i i don't
remember
there's something something another is
there water in the nether no
no no there's no lava lots of lava what
should i make a lava boat
see lettuce use the strata board you
guys know about the striders
no what's that
the striders are for your
um oh the bones you can't you can walk
on uh lava with strides what in the
renovation is done for today
yeah so if you see striders we can uh we
gotta get some stuff but then we'll be
able to ride them they're funny-looking
and then look at my pool everyone isn't
my pool wonderful
anyway this is my house congrats on the
new home thank you
whose house is this what is this is this
a farm it's my favorite
very safe kelly that's very cute not
very safe house
it will be i'll i will get it later when
we're not visiting the nether i don't
want to hold this all night from
visiting the netherlands
i do button yes
[Music]
yes i just need to put in my buttons i'm
just going to drop these rocks off it
has a llama
yeah i still i mean i uh adopted it it
was from the
totally from the merchant no i
borrowed it
sounds like you stole it oh listen up
hey that's fine i i don't have a problem
with it i want a donkey
yes okay okay
i will go to the gates okay what is this
top building
it's my farm it's a farm what is this
working oven
wait i need to make out does anybody
have a pickaxe lying around that i can
have
yeah i have like uh
um nice hey you
mm-hmm are you is that i feel like
breaking
things anyway oh yes now my chest is
protected thank you for whoever put
that protection around my chest i think
i stole your llama
huh i think people are saying that i
accidentally tamed your llama so i think
you need to
my i have a llama how do i how do i say
i think i'm making am i ben how do i
switch myself he's looking at me
oh i just drove it on uh
what's up now he's looking at you okay
my chest is right
why don't you spit at me
no no no that girl that girl
do i hit it how do i make him spit that
means
no a little tap on the butt a little tap
on the button
all right are we ready okay okay okay
go ghost riders ready put in the last
vlog hopefully this is where i've
en
[Applause]
[Music]
i think i know what you need you need
that little uh thing that makes sip
and then it's there what a what what zip
huh flint and steel anybody have fun and
stealing yes nice new
um here let me drop it oh i will oh it's
in my box
what do we what do we like right click
with it and then it like does like a
chat
we gotta light it on fire yeah somewhere
i'm useful for something here there you
go okay
pointing around yay all right yeah you
i shall make us our first
ever never toy pills
[Music]
what happens in here
in one of your chest i'll put it in one
of your chests okay okay
how do you hold up a shield by the way
right click right click
okay you gotta do that like if
somebody's shooting arrows at you you
have to you can't you have to block i
mean you walk really slow with it up
mm-hmm
okay it's not just like a passive thing
you have to be yeah okay okay okay
okay
let me take this right
chad says do not leave the flint because
we might need it to get back
oh okay it's in there and wait i get it
again
you're unbreaking i'm gonna bring the
rest of the obsidian with me just in
case we need to make like another portal
or something
we can do that right it'll like lead out
to somewhere else
does someone have ha shoes
yeah shoes yeah
i noticed i'm missing shoes i can make
shoes yeah i might have someone
just kidding if i have shoe stuff
did you grab your bed yeah i have one
okay okay okay perfect
are we supposed to sleep in another
really yeah we have to save it just
in case uh we die oh okay
i really that doesn't sound right in my
brain yeah
what do you know about minecraft i don't
know that much about minecraft but
that's something someone's telling me
that there might be a little bit of
tricky
[Music]
are you guys trying to mess with us
why wouldn't
yeah i don't like that i don't buy it
you guys have everybody
i'm only sleeping in the nether if you
guys are sleeping i have my bed
i have my bed i'm totally sleeping in
the never i brought my bed
see i i brought my bed see
it's another slumber party i'm coming
[Music]
all right who wants to go first you can
do the honors
no no all right i got this
let's go
don't worry about it you go there you go
oh whoa whoa
oh she's gone next it's gone
um
oh there's something here bye-bye
it's red and square and has wings
um what the hell is that
i've never seen that before
that's we can ride them if we have a we
need a saddle and then we need to
yeah i feel right at home
what's this block there's unlike
more importantly there's a mushroom up
there i need to
basalt what's this um
i can i can is this soul sand question
fun looks so fun down there look at all
the friends
waiting with weapons
oh what's this is that is that good
can we use that for something that's
salt bath
coordinates in the coordinates
are the coordinates they're the same as
the uh
other side no it's different i think
like one block and another is like eight
in the world or something like that
it's like multiplied yet oh oh that's
not great i don't like that
gold oh i'm go up there um
i think something to to just to keep in
mind i i'm not a minecraft
uh encyclopedia but you see these pig
people down here yeah
they uh don't touch them they won't hurt
you if you don't hurt them
okay okay oh no okay yeah enemies well
they'll see me and know that it's fine
i want to be careful careful
but it's fine huh be careful
last time you were
i think we're up pretty high there wait
who is up there
is that you what are you doing i want to
get the gold and the ceiling
there's gold oh that's i guess that is
gold huh we'll go pick it up
so there's pig people right that uh
won't hurt you but there are other types
of characters that will hurt you
yes
but the sick people will hurt you if you
are close to them
and uh mine some gold i think
really if you're far away then they
don't care but if you do it like
somewhere close to them they will follow
you until you
die there's more gold we should go down
this way ah okay just lead the way
okay wait i'm tired
hi you're making friends
yeah boy he's cute and hey he is cute i
want to i like him i want him his bet
can we bring him back yeah can we yeah
how do we get down there
oh wait we need to stick in a mushroom
maybe build a stairway it's hard
build the stairway down it's okay we'll
figure it out that is in
put a light and detail kind of dark here
adventure
i have someone torches okay
oh look at this guy look at him the
white
the white
[Laughter]
i knew this would be happening i knew it
when i saw him i knew it
it's a guest apparently they're called
just
yes
this music is nice is anybody else here
no i don't know
i have my music
lava slime oh ooh
oh we're still high up it should be
somewhere
is that huh should we set a scoring
point
how do we get anywhere everything's so
vertically okay parkour everybody wow
looking good where the
the red rock is what
oh oh there's a guy up there with a
sword there's uh
[Music]
say we can all dig down on this but is
there going to be like a gap underneath
if we go down
straight down
to stay on the block oh no i didn't know
that thank you
yeah yeah prevent you from falling yeah
i'm gonna i'm gonna dig it down over
here you're digging down oh boy okay
straight down two blocks at a time yeah
two block it's good okay
okay oh my god ghostwriter please
we could um
say we could let's dig in a straight
line
i'll just follow you guys oh true
that looks good
deja vu
not that you suddenly fall down that is
very possible
oh hi fellas his music is amazing
wow oh hey guys how are you doing
where'd you guys go
uh we're like inside here
oh
did you make it here oh yeah right here
hello i'll put a light here so we know
where we're going some gold uh-oh
i strayed from the group wait my water i
can't put water down i can't put water
down oh
god oh no i'm kidding
i don't have water
phoenix i have food does anybody need
food
well that makes sense doesn't it how do
we put out fire if we get
caught on fire stop drop and roll
don't get caught on fire oh no they're
friendly right yeah they're friendly
differently
yes friendly they're friendly until
they're not
exactly this gold is far enough away
from them for me to mine
no don't take it don't take it oh
they're going but they're not getting
that clothes
science oh they're coming up
let them leave them here
they don't want any traffic oh no
they're coming out excuse me
should we set a spawn point gotta
protect his dublin i want him
oh yeah uh we'll find enough gold
somewhere else don't worry
yeah we should we should set us one
point guys
well this this area is kind of nice if
we if we want to just
make make this the the police
no bed chat says no bed why i have one
oh yeah be my guest they said
oh hey
because they want you to not get the the
buff
what happens what happens when you sleep
you get a 20
uh armor buff yes you're lying speed
boost
you're lying what happens
get out of here oh don't try it
go what are we looking for in another
what do you do here
yeah well uh i think we're looking for
materials
what kind of materials i want soul sand
oh oh oh she's doing it yeah i do
wonder what bm oh man
amelia wait where which way do we come
from angry
oh wait strider okay this is the way we
came from oh there's the bed
no don't don't let them out don't let
them oh uh oh
i'm sorry i didn't know i didn't know
wait
okay this is the way we came from yeah
look for the little lava board i'll put
i'll put a lantern here so that we know
bling there we go
[Music]
so what are we gonna do i didn't even
get oh i got gold nuggets uh-huh
or me mining you want to go down here
there's stuff down here if you want
to go here no
[Music]
who's gonna be the uh i mean who's gonna
be the uh the tesla
i mean uh who's gonna kiosk
you sleep now i mean i legit want to see
what happens
go to bed we'll pick you up from home
maybe if you die
stop and give it back to me
okay wait let me get a good angle ina i
only trust you with my stuff
i don't like what i'm hearing from chad
i don't like what i'm hearing about
sleeping in the netherlands
you're phoenix i believe in your boxes
set a spawn point okay that makes sense
they want us all to die all right i see
all right and uh potatoes it's not gonna
happen
remember take off your clothes 14 quarts
but oh yeah
are you guys ready yes to watch this
he's blocking my
kid out of the way oh god this isn't
gonna be good
yeah he really is bro i'm ready
all right i'm doing it
it was nice knowing you all goodbye see
you later
[Music]
[Laughter]
alligators
[Music]
you're going to try and make me do that
see even even the pigs are like what is
happening
don't worry about okay see we have an
easy way down now it's all calculated
like in a sparrow you have to do it
again you're a phoenix so this is your
job
just blow up a path
[Music]
does not scare me so i'm i can do it i
can do it again and again
gotta stamp out the flames oh i
have no gold armor
give it to me oh wait where are you oh
um here
here oh wait the door right here where
are you
oh wait thank you attack
[Music]
uh
i think this is also yours um i think
that was worth it right that was
totally worth it yeah we we got an easy
way down
i mean there's a path over here guys
it's another course
and a bread a sun uh bread
yeah thank you this is all yours i think
it's yours
oh
torches yeah follow the torches
[Music]
it's the the big floaty thing oh hey
this is
[Music]
here's your shield thank y'all
i want this for my home
then my new home in the cave a fortress
a biome
sounds like okay
[Music]
wait it has such a cute face i know it
sounds so cute
go go go can we fight it okay yeah i
don't have a full
is it is it is i think it's just
randomly shooting or isn't it oh
i think that it knows that we're here so
it's going to try and actively uh kill
us
oh yeah yeah
well we can go this way uh maybe we can
close this i'm not close enough
yeah do your voice yeah let's go this
way with the stairs okay go go go go
i got your sticks oh it's like a pink
hut
hey guys our friends can we kill that
thing you can deflect the fire you can
attack the ball when it shoots it and it
shoots it back at the guy
does anybody want to try that that was a
battlefield
because you might catch on fire let's go
i'm in full health
all right okay there's a lot of fly here
what well oh well if i'm gonna die
anyway i might as well give it a try
oh aim
he died so easily what the heck that was
wait that was one
they're extra hit yeah yeah
are dominance yes you guys see this i
want to go
upstairs oh oh are those the glowstone
thingies
there's gold here but there's a pikmin
oh yeah there's a forest over there
let's go that way i think we can build a
bridge forest
oh there's a way yeah we can build a
bridge here a bridge
another rack
i'm gonna grab some rock cause i don't
have any i'll leave this to you girls
you work i don't wanna you guys are good
at that
team seriously wow i'm impressed
are you doing the cleanup work it comes
apart so easily
you have to hold shift right yes hold
shift and you'll be okay
so what happens can we make another
nether portal does it exit out somewhere
on the other side
i think that would probably be really
far away from where we came from
um not like super far really yeah
because this one is
in the outer world right
beautiful now what how do we get down
um
we hold shift we can't fall right right
that's my fault that's what i thought
callie
were you wrong uh i don't know let's
just go get more rock
and then here look this is it's possible
see
hold on no yeah no
the jumper thing is this far away enough
from the piglets to
to get the gold guys is the btf the
music is so loud for me there's like
music and game and it's like wow
that's like special another music oh my
gosh
i am really nice
i have now music you guys are my music
yes please minecraft
wait what is this hell's wort
red grass oh oh wait i have pirate
game hold on don't listen to what i'm
saying
i like i like i like can i if i can take
this story can i take it back to
the real world i want my walls to be we
should we should probably try to go back
after we collect some of this stuff
because like uh if we collect too much
and die it'll just be like
a waste yeah so collect as much stuff
now and then we'll go back for like
there's another there's another pump
floaty
is that is that a light starter oh yeah
it's like floating shooting down where
is he
they're they're slipping literally yeah
it's like a shiny sun
yeah yeah don't be a coward i say
[Music]
[Applause]
you're gonna be quicker than that buddy
tactical retreat i'ma help
i want a garden with these plants
here where is that plants with these
ones
wait i thought they saw a fortress i
want to go to the fortress wait this is
wood
or trees yeah yeah oh what a cutie hello
who are you
oh are these villagers oh
is that pumbaa
it looks like there are other people
here they don't look uh nefarious or
mean maybe they're other
smarts i i have a sneaking suspicion
that the pumbaa is not so friendly
but we shall see
one second ah i checked my outlet
and now my ace is friendly chad says
they are hostile so maybe we shouldn't
go say hi
oh
oh we just picked up a little one
dominant all right cool i'll help i'm
behind you
oh wait they're fast hold on hold on
wait wait wait wait wait wait
don't shoot first there's so many of
them
it's fine we'll be okay see they're all
equipped with swords
so we taunt them and we get them to come
at us then we just knock out the bridge
and they fall
hey boys
[Laughter]
come over and fight us and you want to
fight oh
we can give gold to them and maybe
they'll be friendly let's try i have a
bunch of gold
oh yeah i'll go oh
wait what's that girl huh
did you shoot him i was ready i was
ready
okay yeah we're here to help i don't
have a i don't have a bow and arrow
though so i'm gonna have to
wait that's really far hold on i'm not
prepared you believe
how
i tried right click okay throw it there
it doesn't do anything are those the
ones that won't attack you
oh oh okay okay well hold on they're not
aggressive
they give you some items back i think oh
i don't know
[Music]
does anybody want iron boots uh
yes i could use it actually um
crossbow wait can i have that who's it
talking no no try to train him what is
that
oh
oh yeah i'm going to make some more gold
you guys can try it very strong
very strong well well i'm glad that
things ended peacefully but
i'm more i'm warning you don't mess
around with us
and i'm ready to start swinging thanks
chad i'm no coward
i also want to try the gacha i want to
do the gacha the gold kacha
all right
[Music]
okay there's
it
do i just throw it at him thank you what
do we do with it trying obstruction
give it to him but right click on him
what's wrong
wait wait right click where's kiara oh
no wait wait oh okay we go wait right
wait come back come back sir he'll get
away from me
[Music]
i tried to give him to him
okay all right good
okay i'm gonna try this guide to machine
i want to try
are they the best when i did the right
one
a shield instead when i right clicked so
i left clicked and it hit him with it
i didn't give you one here yeah the the
piglet took it right away from me
wait can i kill this pig try to pick it
up okay
so how do i right here hold it now right
hand and right click on that
okay now give me something good now
oh this doesn't really hurt i'm going to
get you you give me a minute
something is chasing me
i have something too and it gave me some
maybe we should build a portal here
what am i supposed to do with a meatball
what did we give them oh look at the
cute little
[Laughter]
oh did not drop the harpoon though
or what is it the crossbow okay it's
paved up time water bottle
i gotta water that time what does it do
don't you run away don't you ruin
i want you it run away oh wait
you little hey what does this do wait
hold on that's right
thank you chad thank you wait do we know
how to get back you can throw this place
together
uh good question oh yeah here's our
bridge okay our bridge is here i'll put
a put up here
hey so the meatballs uh it's like
throwing heartburn
when you throw the the the the the spicy
meatball they give you it makes fire
oh oh
hey flying squid come here let's play
i'm ready to party look at this wide
open terrain i will fight you
easy in hand-to-hand combat get here
well you dunked my balloon that's my
bullet
i'm just getting the way back for us
really quick securing it okay it's
coming back
yeah bring it he's afraid of us
hello little one hello little one
the noises they make are so interesting
hey come back
oh look at that
it's so cute hello
what are you doing you're too young to
hold a weapon
hello where do i get the soul sand
that's
a soul sand maybe it's a different biome
i got some crap and there's something
good
oh you got some yeah i got it uh for
gold
sorry i did you go look for more gold if
you guys want to do that i don't think
we could take the gold from here
is that good my scythe swinging
twitter instincts were kicking in when i
saw them nothing really great apparently
i got something amazing
what did you get you didn't want to go
back ten ten spectral arrows and the
chat is going like oh
you can't see the person you shot that's
all it was
oh oh we can't
we probably can't mind these girls darn
it
[Music]
we can find gold on the way back yeah
i'm addicted to that give me something
it's build gold yeah
are we going to this world here you guys
want yeah
inside my house
crimson roots i like them and gives you
water
it's like what is it worth the world
stuff
i like it yeah okay
i want to save my actually i guess i
don't have to save my gold if anybody
say anybody
want to go again i have three left oh i
wanna i'm gonna
milk them for what they got let's see
yeah yeah give me some stuff
they're all here kyle you wanna go again
yeah
you don't wanna drop it here okay okay
i got another piece of gold but you
gotta come over here
thank you gold dealer did you just yeah
there you go ama is the dealer for
everything
[Music]
yes i think so yep oh okay
let's not do that what did he give me
huh you guys gotta come see this oh you
guys gotta go
see this well where are you
oh
[Music]
what what does the chicken do in the
nether oh i got
um
[Music]
i got crying obsidian
the game
you guys want to build a portal here and
see where it goes oh yeah yeah
i have one bottom good come on come on
two three four one
two three four we're friends
i like your gold sword little one oh
me nuts sweet stride
[Music]
this is nonsense all right again anybody
has who has the flint
[Music]
yes i will do let's
oops
sorry my bird brain is uh not being
activated three two one go
yeah all right drop you off the edge
let's go oh dear
[Laughter]
we're in some sort of cave oh
like an exciting outside area that we
never saw before like a nice
new bike oh wait wow we're really really
hard
oh i put it i put it just now
before oh we are deep we yeah we're live
oh we're not that good we're just really
far in the z direction
i think is that uh deep in the ground
we'll just see where
hey guys should we sleep now
we are we might be underwater oh yeah
everybody get ready to uh
swim swim i brought a door just bring it
floaty
[Music]
[Laughter]
sandstones making me feel like it's
gonna be ocean
yes okay maybe we should go back
what could possibly go wrong no it can
also be a
pyramid or something like that i died in
one before
we should build a pyramid how cool would
that be
we should be pretty close to the surface
again right now yeah yeah yeah
i'm struggling hold on a minute are you
good we're getting him i'm okay i just
can't i can't climb i can't play this
game
okay it's okay no no
no i'm sorry i was trying to mine the
stairs all right it's just a scratch
it's fine don't worry about it
all right i'll be the caboose yeah be
careful of falling sand just
i think we're close to getting out the
sand is usually
oh yeah oh right daylight
what's happening this happened to me
okay we're okay we're okay we're okay
right yeah yeah yeah okay no we're fine
it wasn't my fault
okay ah we did it
whoa where are we ah oh daylight check
it out
i need to i need to keep mining so i
might oh the desert
oh hey
whoa yeah no wonder it took us so long
it's like dystopia like we came out into
the stockings
[Music]
a gold can we take it i should have
brought my diamond pickaxe
fireman stick oh gold hey
i only have can we can we go in this
portal and they like continue in the
lava right
oh what's in the chest i have water okay
you want to get rid of the raw plants
yeah yeah yeah for water yeah give me
the gold
huh i can't it's too high up hold on
i'll build the plane
oh whoa
but this one is too long i i think we
got a oh yeah
yeah yeah we just have to get rid of
these two blocks we're not gonna be able
to save it but we can remove it and then
replace it
does anybody else have opinion
oh apparently we screwed it up oh really
all right there it is yeah yeah no we
can still we just have to get rid of
this it takes a while
[Music]
is
it works we don't have enough obsidian
to make a new one
i have three oh okay okay
three three six eleven wait how much do
we need in total it's four by
what is it wait one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirds
some people are saying it doesn't work
the one that i have
oh no oh the bright obsidian doesn't
work
which way did you guys go uh
i know that way the way tourists away
hello let's just leave this place yeah
yeah it's okay we can compile it let's
retrieve it
which way did you go yeah where did they
go there's a temple over here
hold on did you guys empty the chest yet
no i don't think i'm going to empty it
what are you doing here guys do you know
what
i'm the one where are you guys you don't
need the corners
oh oh yeah but
i only have five blocks and kiara
here how many did you have three
three oh uh but they're not the glowy
ones right it's just regular obsidian
it says obsidian okay this is it trap
we might be able to build it then let me
try
all right we already have upstairs here
in the floor so if we do
you guys said we don't need the corners
so does anybody
two bottom top
okay i can just do it here then
okay so like this
no i have to oh okay i see i see
if i replace this with sand like this
and then go on
no yes this is right it was right
this seems like a difficult problem
it's like a puzzle what are we talking
about
it is okay i'll do a mock one okay this
is one two
three oh okay we don't do the corners so
we do
not the middle minus then
and then uh
is that too short yeah one longer
one longer yeah perfect
holy yes
okay okay all right now i just replace
the sides so one two three four five six
seven eight right guys yes
should we do the work this isn't this is
long enough he's fine they said chad
says yes
yeah this looks right okay imagine if
this was one higher on the ground then
it would make sense
yeah sounds good i have the coordinates
don't worry
we have the right amount all right kyra
i'm waiting for you i
i think i see it i got lost a little bit
but
i'm i'm back almost
i'm i'm there i'm there are you
i think i see it like um
what uh yeah i have the coordinates i
have the coordinates
now we already tried to use this one
that we built but we can't mind the
obsidian so we have to try again because
it's not tall enough
yeah and we don't have a diamond pickaxe
with this because i didn't bring one
because i was scared i was gonna lose it
yeah i'll see you but i don't mind i'll
bring it with us if we get back home
because like uh i have more diamonds
it's fine yeah same
[Music]
oh wait that's just the bunny hey give
us your coordinates good uh
i've been trying to say i'm in a pyramid
could you hear me
yeah i was trying to look for gouda but
then i got like there's a pair of head
a cat yeah oh yeah there are cats yeah
but that's a bunny bunny there are cats
though in the desert
i've seen cats i am a paleontologist
that's a dinosaur person though right
what discovers mummies what are they
called historian mummy
mummy excavators
i'm an excavator that's a truck isn't it
what
probably i mean they stole it though
um what should we do we to wait for you
guys
we're we're still doing another portal
we don't know how much direction you
guys want i like the
hold on i went up high and i saw what i
thought was a um
judd is here hey oh hi kiara
okay
[Music]
yes of course i love you
now let's try with the flint hey
[Music]
me too me too let me in okay looks good
okay we're going back in yeah
hey the little one is still here we're
in the same place
oh we didn't move that far
yeah we only went up i just didn't want
to go back down i mean we had to look
forward
but we came back in from the same same
gate because we put the
look at these guys jumping oh this is
the same
yeah i put the torches here huh it's too
close and it ends up
oh that's what callie's looking at hello
okay
all right i know the way home okay
follow watson
watson oh okay
yeah this is right this is right this is
right yes yes yeah how's my crafting i
really like collection
thanks for being so chill ah they
weren't bad dudes
all right i'm ready to fight there's
another place i'm ready too
yeah yeah hi he's running away
all right i'll let you figure out
cowards cowards okay got him
got him all right this one
this is wrong burgers out of that pig
i know i was hoping all right there's a
bridge here we'll follow this bridge
attention to detail yeah
then be careful on these stairs easy to
fall
wow one at a time nice to meet you
good pair of us bridge
like we're like following the mother
bird
so i mean the birds too nice
i'm not the only one
[Laughter]
oh yeah this is where kiara blew up it's
our home shipping like right through
this
wait burning uh no not this one
it's right obviously oh yeah hey he's
just gonna make a
tail like a bit of room there there you
go
oh yeah yeah cause his name is
um i did not get any gold because like i
even go to the gata
that's okay that's okay i think it's fun
too
i was gonna get more gold to give to
them well i found this hole
we're back oh he doesn't take bread oh
goodbye friend i hope i'll see you again
soon
why you on the head but i probably hurt
you
with my sword good job
and sweet we did not i mean the only
person who died is me right
and i died on purpose yes yeah exactly
where is it making like progress how
many times did we die
last time too many and there's another
man
golden sword benjamin
it's not the one that's mad at me right
i don't think so
enemies here don't seem as big of a deal
after coming back from the nether
yeah right now i guess booty no you
leave ina alone i'll kill you
i got him oh no down you go
how are you getting the sweet experience
points
i did it okay i'm so unorganized
you take this take this
[Music]
purple purple i got purple wood
purple purple me too
yeah it's like almost like two underwear
it's purple oh did you kill
them nope they're just walking around
they're chilling
yeah you should be able to stem oh
whatever that is
i'm sorry i feel like the door purple
door
i'm working on my house now no you can
oh yes you can i'm dumb okay
oh i see dragons
those oh we should probably leave yeah
phantoms
what what mushroom wait
maybe we should sleep one night yeah
just now yeah a good idea
i'm in my bed just a moment here
here i'll
good morning good morning this morning
oh they're burning they're burning
i hear enderman near my house i'm scared
okay guys i'm gonna take the i'm gonna
go get us that strider i'm gonna go
bring him home
oh yeah yeah bring stuff yeah capture
what flavor mushroom does he eat though
i have a bunch of mushrooms i have got a
blue one
a brown one and a red one depends on
what flavor they like
i need the red these the blue mushrooms
ah you got a blue one the water i don't
know
do you have one of them i have one yeah
yeah that's what he eats apparently
okay okay so i don't i don't know who
i guess he dies if he's outside of the
lava ah
in there i mean that's still pretty good
can you i wonder if you can make a
little pen
hold on right or something
all right i brought some fence wait well
would catch on fire in there
you put it down uh i don't know
guys if it's water oh
oh yeah that's a good idea i bring some
materials
no no beds no beds
just like furnace and crafting table
i'll bring all the stones that's so
fancy
no i didn't mean to do that i can't oh i
can't stand
hang on how do i get out
there okay
high ceiling because i am tall oh cali's
house to be
yes i'm working on my house
welcome yes my pool
do you like it it was here when i found
it is it for your kid not
[Music]
well we can just build a house in there
and then we can like
just yeah it's it's just like a square
house we'll work on okie dokie
cool yeah in another yeah yes yeah
sounds fun
easy easy game
easy game
oh are you gonna tame him
[Music]
to make our little face here like right
here oh wait ina's got a crafting table
i can use this one
okay here uh i want to use these blocks
hold on
there you go okay how do i do this i
want to help
you polish fire
[Music]
can we put gold armor on this driver
uh is it the usual
what should we call it the usual like
horse armor
it should be different isn't it okay
i guess yeah hi everybody
what are you looking at what's this yeah
they're
having a nice little bath it's like an
onsen for them
yeah they're just chilling at the
hospital
later losers we should make a hot spring
[Music]
[Laughter]
no why is he purple oh i saved him
killed him already no
[Music]
he's just a little anemic that's all
he's fine he needs a nap and uh
hold on take him to the lava he's fine
he's fine
he's a champ he'll be good he'll be good
oh yeah
he's faster now i see okay i get i
understand that's like you're stabbing
there
you're good i have a fence if you want
to build him a little paddock
he goes maybe we can build him a path
there you go a lava path yeah
look what what if he's here with jamie
can you walk on magma rock because that
might he's waiting for all of us
you can try it out you can but it hurts
a bit
see easy way the easy way down now
what kiada yes
oh okay okay okay it's okay you're fine
look now we can easily sail
okay our trusty need we can perfect it
later
but for now yeah thanks for your service
buddy
he's cute i know right maybe we can
connect over here too
oh yes like the rest of the roof with it
um cool uh oh yeah
[Music]
that's too bad oh
something's on fire where'd homie go
that looks like a
he
[Music]
does those
sorry my my keyboard is in japanese okay
hold on back to the game
okay uh he's landed the eagle has landed
it's okay
wait but how are we going to get him up
here i'm going to make sure all right
fancy wow oh i have all the material
wonders this is tough huh
i should hire i'm i'm going to build me
a house
you want to save him leave one below i
want to be the hero
hang on in here anyway well then i
wanted to put it
on um hang on
uh our neighbors are here our neighbors
say hi hello
oh um i have a pickaxe do you want mine
okay oh yes thank you oh uh you guys
thought
is it okay thanks
here oh yeah you do the same yeah
[Music]
right below okay so as long as you make
your way down nice and easy you'll be
fine
all right i'll go save our friend oh
that looks cool
hang on okay
um this is gonna take some brain power
but i got it
done
oh i think we can only give the gold to
the villagers i guess not these random
things
i tried
there's probably a roundabout way to go
let's just keep moving this way
maybe i can make some stairs wait hold
on just kidding
okay no i can't there are no stairs that
will be made here uh it's okay
i'm gonna move to i'm gonna move this
way until hang on
it's fine we got it i wonder if i can
build actual stairs after this
is this soul sand
no way way way beautiful house
amy thank you beautiful you've got okay
i think
we're making progress you could be a
architect
oh thank you architect watson
no i didn't die i just came out to get
some wood
[Music]
are making their way to save strider yes
is that his name that's what he's called
you can name him if you want though
i like that it's okay we keep
straightening him out
no right after wait let me get it on
camera
okay um
okay getting closer i bet i can put uh
you made that jump
yeah brave it's not bad i know
i gotta save our homie should i extend
the
i have two more chests should i put it
uh
um just a minute one year
done wait where'd he go
is he moving is he on the move i mean
he can't be far he's not going to be far
right that far
yeah yeah he's dead no he's not he's not
done
i saw
wait what's happening okay did he open
the door
he's walking he made it down
[Laughter]
hello i come in peace fan i wonder i
wonder if there's another village that's
closer
whoa i guess that one we found is the
closest one yeah
no i found him oh i hit him the village
i'm riding on him but i'm on fire i'm on
fire
yeah i died oh no no no no well it was
the valiant effort but i found them i
found them
oh they're interested
i'm here i'm here
yeah i caught on fire i found him but
then i caught on fire
oh i don't know where i am
um uh you're probably oh is she a spot
ah
are you okay gooda we're fine we're fine
we're fine
did you die we play calm we're calm
we're calm we're cool collected we're
calm
[Laughter]
sounds good this area is familiar i
don't know where i am but there's a
village i'm going to go look in it
wait did you village are you all rocking
swans
i don't know where i am actually yeah
that must turn up somewhere random yeah
could you just be an agent
go to a high place and look for the h
and that's the entrance to the tunnel
and you can just take a mine cart in
there from uh
the emergency i need to get where you
live
do okay see the h okay uh i'm in a
village hold on a second yeah yeah yeah
right now you're alive i'm good i'm good
i'm with strider and i got cali's stuff
okay thank you you got it you're gonna
have to move my friend are you
here where are you yeah how are you
doing can he jump
i see a house i i this is a rando's
house
i don't know how i'm gonna do this can
we swim up lava probably
not right uh so it is all my fault
i'm sorry no no no no no no no no down
there
i think he'll just probably wait i
should have my pickaxe here
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
i require assistance in your house no
where are you
where what's going on
don't paint it good i don't paint any
good idea don't panic
oh i guess i can't get out of here okay
um
assistance is required in the leather
i'm okay
are you okay i'm okay with your
coordinates
i'm right outside i can see all your
names um i
um there's a gas do you see
oh huh oh they're on fire
oh wow i'm gonna take out the guests
which one i think but it looks like i
see it
[Music]
i think so it has to be is getting
closer to the pig village because there
was the path that went sort of in this
direction
over there it she's down there well
i'm i'm i'm i can see your guys's names
i'm like uh right down here
well i'm so scared i don't like it i
don't know you're fine it's fine
i see watson's tennis racket i'm going
towards it
like girl's over there i don't think our
friend will leave i think we can leave
him here so i'm just gonna
yeah just park him there it's his
parking spot
that's a really fun ferrari parking spot
hello can you guys clear my uh headspace
here why are you good yup oh wait it's
good
yeah yeah welcome back okay guys
and we got a house we got a panic room
and
i'll be back soon i'm away oh wait i
could have written it on the strider but
he's so fast i don't trust myself
well if you guys want to play gotcha
before we go i got i brought a bunch of
gold
i brought some gold too that sounds fun
but read up is a lie
well we'll we'll wait for cali to get
back thanks guys
now we can does anybody have a chest
that i can put cali's stuff in oh wait
yeah
there's a chest thank you for doing that
by the way i will make it up to you
oh no worries yeah it's okay i'll put it
in uh what did you
have um i just want my nether stuff like
uh to build my house with cool things
like uh there were some i feel so stupid
why didn't i put
that stuff in chest before i second time
i'm silly i'll come help in just a
second
maybe i just need to tell that yeah
building a nice path to the gotcha oh
welcome back
look at my hair thank you everyone
for a second i felt another it looks
let me know if i missed anything i think
you got everything thank you
can i be nice it's right to me
baked potatoes yay i'm hungry
yeah so strider is down there where we
left him he won't really go anywhere i
don't think oh okay
oh i wonder um yeah i guess there's not
much we can do about that huh darn it
i don't have anything um yeah do you
think you can build like staircases
for him to get it up
he doesn't die outside of love all right
so we can just build him a really really
long
long staircase yeah yeah
yeah we have enough rocks
yeah but that's about the project for
another time i suppose huh
yeah we'll save them later oh it goes
where are you kara i'm now you guys yeah
we're going to the palace uh right where
um
oh i just okay i just left let me put
some stuff away i'll come back
well right before the ah yeah i want to
go put some stuff away too actually
you should put your arm right on yeah oh
that's right all of it came off huh
i'll continue to mine the path to the
village
sorry i lost the gold snapback hello
oh yeah do you need some gold armor so
they don't yeah question mark
oh yes is it this way yeah yes
yeah i'm just going to put my things in
my chest no
oh yeah it's gone huh oh well
i know i used it i panicked and i used
it oh it's okay
oh that was yours oh my god i'm so sorry
it's okay you're good thanks for getting
more yeah
you don't have to it's okay we have a
craft table at the home
yeah it's not that far okay what does it
do anyway
i don't know yeah i don't think it's
pretty yeah it is
very beautiful but do i really want to
waste all my gold at the gacha again do
i have gold for you i feel like a ton
more at home
oh my god oh is it oh wait we're playing
amelia
the gold woman i want to play
me too let's go let's go oh why don't we
move this railroad oh it is the sun go
away that was the stairs
uh make this
wait no i need more room
no no no no i have
and i don't have any rack no i haven't
just mined them from here it's okay
is it called rock or wreck rack
yes rack like
yeah yeah another wreck
are you guys should i take the pig
village path uh yes yes yeah
okay i'll follow the torches
nice shiny sword you got there buddy
oops
[Music]
oh so i guess nether spawn points can be
used instead of beds i didn't know about
that
we used the crying obsidian to make
those oh
the bright the bright one mm-hmm that's
the crying one
sorry i agreed okay let's okay we'll
find some more it killed me oh we can
mine it back with our
diamond pickaxe i brought mine wait
where is it yeah
almost died almost died oh welcome have
gold armor
uh you know this is where the ender
dragon is
i'm just making it so we don't
accidentally no okay
good idea this is not where he is
where's the ender dragon i want to see
him
um maybe
for another time how do you summon him
what are you gonna say and we have to
find that gate thing and then like
complete it and then like
you gotta go find him i'm ready to go
knock on his door
yeah boy
i think we have to be like all diamond
everything to do that right
and no no no i mean like for our own
safety
yeah basically uh uh i watched like
20 hours of uh and and
uh rta
and the dragon rta so i know how to do
it
but not but we're not ready for it
oh why you kind of make a different kind
of portal
and they're pearls and there's a few
ways to get the end of pearls but it
takes a long time
oh
my
sir sir you look like you're having a
hard time down there
ready are you okay do you need help
getting back up sir
see it yeah i think i hear it
oh there he is oh i see it can it break
our bridge i think he's gone
oh there he is
that would be the safe choice go do it
girl
i don't think i don't think i can make
that shot i can't make this shot he's so
we can get a little closer no it's so
far away i don't think i can make that
there's our other portal too nice let me
shoot him out in the open
oh here we go
no he's too far up where are all the
villagers there were so many here before
they died what what
there's some homies over here maybe
they're sleeping maybe it's night time
for them where's their houses
you have a crafting they're they're
training the little one uh
no but i can make one i think
well then eat runaway
all right i have one okay
do it i have a goal to give you guys
thanks amelia for the free gold
yeah big ups three you get three thanks
and you get pickles oh he doesn't
he really doesn't like me hi girl why is
he actually good
yeah i have one heart we'll see what
happens wait do you need food
yeah who's a girl okay i'll give you
something i meant i'm there
where are you kelly oh yeah i am sorry
okay food i thought we were just going
to do gotcha so i didn't break
the food that's okay that's so many
steaks i have a loan
i have a lot of fun or cows at home it's
okay
with me i do gotcha dude oh something's
awesome
i have i'm actually not there anymore i
wonder what happened there's a man on
fire
yes give me something good sorry
are you okay i'm okay
thank you thank you thank you big ups
thank you
i have a boy
okay oh no
i'm ready to party these are the uh
netherlands where are the villagers
yeah it's probably just dead dudes huh
i see one he has a gold helmet come here
oh he's running away
why are you scared of me here
no he's hurt i died oh my god kelly
i'll grab your gold chase
oh my god take his oh i'll take the
steak
[Laughter]
yeah take the steak cali
yeah oh my god
i was just gonna give him gold and then
he turned on me
i think i think if you're holding gold
they'll attack you because they're the
they're not the villagers it was the
villager though it was a regular dude
he wasn't like a zombie like guy or
anything not a single good thing came
out of this one
looks rich this one looks rich let's see
if he gives me anything
[Laughter]
[Music]
give me something good not a single good
thing
i had something weird with my keyboard
what'd you get
[Music]
i think it's the end for your boy on
this one here
yeah we should probably call it soon
because cali's got a stream yeah
time to wrap it up
wait did did anyone find any of the
traders gotcha trader
i thought i did he started blasting
i didn't drop anything actually that's
good because then i can
take the catcher home and don't waste it
all right we can go nowhere okay okay
let's go back
[Music]
i'm in that same village too i got lost
again
where are you i doubt that somehow i
doubt that you tried this one
i'm looking for watson's uh tennis
racket oh okay okay
okay magnifying glass
tennis rack oh my god
yes oh my god wait where did you die
kiana because
[Laughter]
clearly this is the wrong direction got
it okay
are we gonna do operation find kelly
sorry i will find it don't worry i'm
getting up high
i don't know
what exactly what did they gain from you
know
okay so listen i wasn't i wasn't wearing
any gold
armor and apparently that's awesome oh
yeah yeah remember that's what i said
should we give you a coca-cola
it all makes sense now yes
you have to i'll make some i promise
i'll start minding my own stuff i don't
want you guys to have to do everything
for me
no no no help we have we help each other
we help yes team we are one
we are one thanks guys i want to be good
at video games
yeah maybe someday
um gosh where is watson's tennis racket
watson that's the real question
yeah where's the nine in gold hold on
she got this job
where's waldo where's watson where's
lots where in the world is
watson where in the world is watson
oh
oh i do okay
wow minecraft is so pretty another i'll
come back
i see an incredibly tall buildings this
must be the right way
like ridiculously yeah and walk building
[Laughter]
oh
how did you drown you drowned from my
house i just kind of watched it
[Laughter]
gotta call the lifeguard
okay hopefully our house will survive
oh i should be i'm in the basement okay
all right i shall wait for you
remember stream's going to be a sleepy
stream sleep
it's okay it'll be fun
all
[Music]
[Laughter]
magnifying glass yeah it's beautiful
on it you guys will see yeah it's a
beautiful magnifying glass
it looks like a mustache record wait
where are we going
up top here up on the stairs
what do you want to do a minecraft
stream with me where we build a huge
chess field
uh oh my god
uh we can do that it's still good
ah yes the chest feels to always
commemorate that legendary
stream professional
test oh here cali i have i think this is
your stuff okay
yeah thank you
thanks oh i'm sorry i don't mean to make
it
all right good here i have a present for
you too a present for me
look over here turn look at this oh
crossbow oh you shouldn't chant that oh
it's your inventory okay oh uh here i
have a present for you too
hey go
you can because you can draw it and then
you can just have it drawn and then you
can shoot it
oh baby nice
man the one and only now i want to give
you a present too so here you go
yay doors purple doors
yeah accent i just changed my door to
the purple one thank you
it matches it's amazing santa claus
yeah sorry i'm in santa claus
you thank you
[Music]
come on what do you want for christmas
little girl um
maybe she wants me to fall somewhere she
wants me as a friend
friends i don't care okay
i i just want i just want a friendship
that's
all i want a deep friendship
to friendship forever and ever yeah
okay guys gather up
okay yo they are sweat up everyone
brackets
[Laughter]
it's magnifying glass i'm sorry i know
it now i understand now
wait ah there we go yay
oh we didn't yeah take a screenshot
previously i want to take one now
oh no i'll take off my i'll think of
like oh i don't have spots in my
inventory
what's that
[Applause]
give
[Music]
there you go this is fine
yay another trip
[Music]
yay
nice angle
everyone who watched thanks for coming
yeah thank you for watching
i'm gonna play uh well we're planning on
it me and gouda are planning on playing
uh minecraft together next week so tune
in
with whom uh sacred
okay cool okay
uh schedule for me will be out uh
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow yeah
new week same almost
all right okay thank you everybody for
[Music]
watching
i guess i should turn off the
[Music]
you