[Music]
do
uh
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
hello
guess who just had a nap
meow me
um
hi
[Music]
hello everybody
oh how's it going
uh hello
hello
where's the game
in studio mode it was just showing me
the game
and now you're hiding it from me
shut the wait maybe it's because i
tapped out
oh
oh there it is
oh my god
hello
oh
oh the music is a little bit loud but i
like it it's pretty
fun music
oh let's lower it a little bit welcome
we're playing donut
oh county not country i always want to
say country but it's not country it's
country county county right not oh yeah
when it's that word i think it's
uh
pronounced county not con contest
oh
no yeah
[Music]
doesn't sound at all like that swear
word okay when i tap out the music stops
oh yeah hello hello oh i had a day off
how it was wonderful i uh did things
like
uh preparing halo talk and uh what else
did i do i forgot i already don't
remember anything from yesterday
um
i did some um this and that
yeah
wonderful day
of course i had lasagna and mondays are
for lasagna of course i had to
it was got the god will the will of god
do not worry about it yeah
well today
uh we shall play this game um i was
thinking about you know playing a small
game today
i was looking for games and then um
then i couldn't decide and then i asked
you guys in the members only post and
you guys gave me a lot of
recommendations
and they're all good they're all great
so
i struggled deciding once again it did
not exactly help my indecisiveness but
uh at least it gave me a lot of ideas
also for like later
uh-huh
any canada viewers real good question
where are the canadians
huh canadians my lovely canadians
oh
raise your hand with a maple leaf in
your hand come on
hello eh
you're right
hey
oh my canadians
i don't know someone specifically asked
for you guys and you know you're polite
you answer when someone asks for you
well what you calling a boot
someone asked for you well okay so yeah
this game is about um
donuts
it's a short game you won't have me um
for too long
um
i i have one question
um the marvelous mrs maisel was supposed
to come out today on amazon
and i checked and it's like not there
like what the [\h__\h] are you what what's
going on like what
where is it where is it
and it's i need to binge watch it the
new season
did it get delayed no google says 18th
of january today's the [\h__\h] vay team
already looked like like an hour past
midnight and it was not there and now i
looked again and it's still not there
where is it
[Music]
yahooza is there an insult in canadian
maybe it's midnight tonight no why would
it be if they say 18th then i expect it
to be some time doing actually like
immediately on the 18th
okay it's not netflix
but but i i was feeling cursed because i
had you know i was binge watching the
great recently which which you can watch
if you get like a subscription on amazon
for stars play some some subscription
within a service for another service
wonderful yes i don't mind having a
million subscriptions remember the good
old times when it was only netflix
remember those times when the only other
like provide the only provider of these
shows is netflix and now you need to
like what february not yet really oh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i can't wait any longer
but okay understandable
[Laughter]
but do you remember those times man i
miss those times now we gotta get a
million services i have a problem i have
a problem the
stars play
uh only has half of the second season of
the great and now i'm stuck i'm like
stuck in the middle of the season
apparently it's because i'm in austria
but i don't understand why you would
only
make half a season
public
when when when is the rest gonna come
they've been they
uploaded one half of a season sometime
in november and i'm just wondering when
the race is gonna come have you tried
hula well i
am not able to purchase a subscription
for hulu even if i wanted to see now
this is becoming a ranting stream
already because
you cannot take this away from me you
cannot take away half a season from me
from a show that i'm so into right now
can you
wait
vpn we've established before that of
using a vpn is not illegal right
but like how do i use the vpn on my tv i
don't want to want
i don't want to launch it on my laptop
going to watch it on the big screen
it's a smart tv yeah i think so
i have like a fire stick of course
because i'm phoenix so all my sticks are
on fire
but yeah i have this fire stick but uh
oh god answers go too fast
uh
a vpn on what
hook the laptop
oh
yeah you mean just okay
i guess so
i'll try that
i'll try that later tonight okay faxes
anyway let's play donut county county
county
house
okay i i already like like the the look
of it what do we do
[Music]
a dogo with a bread in his mouth and a
girl mira
when are you coming to work i'm bored
this is a tanooki speaking to all of us
yeah he i think wants to take over the
world quiet bk
i'm dead i've died you don't look very
dead
please have some respect
you're lying you did
i i was thinking about
diet just like literally yesterday i
think i was thinking about the fact that
i sometimes say
kusa out loud and remembered back into
the day where i felt that everybody who
says lol
loud
is just cringe and that i should maybe
stop saying kusa out loud because that's
just ice cream just basically the same
thing
so let's all stop saying that i love i'm
probably the only one who says kusa out
loud
it's [\h__\h] cringe man
the honking man woke me up again [\h__\h]
the honking man at the hunk of down dog
honking unbelievable don't worry
i revenge you yes
kill them all
be careful dude
this guy really honks
oh they mean [\h__\h] yeah whatever come to
the donut shop and stop feeding your dog
bread yeah because that is that uh
healthy he needs bread to live burger
king
he's a certified loaf
[Music]
oh that's funny because he looks like a
loaf my cats also look like a loaf
sometimes that that's funny
thank you chad i didn't know you could
do that
he stops
hey
there he is
when will this end oh
[Music]
the ducks dominance let me
push it it's not fair okay i don't think
he'll ever do anything
like say shut the [\h__\h] up he really
enjoys this okay
i'm leaving in five minutes bye okay
well we got some honks out oh that is
cute kawaii donuts
oh oh i thought it was going down but
it's still sad
emma
and that's fun that's fun this is not
what the game is about but this is
already fun
you know
i like the physics of that
hello what are we looking at suburb
oh
you look like you're wearing a cafe on
the farm welcome to donut county
yes
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
oh
oh we're starting okay so you kind of
suck in things does the hole get bigger
yeah i think so the hole gets bigger
with everything that you consume
and
yeah we will just uh conceal anything
what about you hey hey i'm not done here
what about you wait the screen i just
noticed the screen is off stop
stop i just realized i made a fatal
mistake with the positioning here
although this does also not like
sometimes i wonder what the hell is the
size of my layout like why does it not
fit
oh oh yeah
you can't no you can't get away oh
and tennis balls yummy we all know
tennis balls are also pretty good oh oh
the fences look everything is edible and
now you come on come on come on come
here
i trapped the
donut delivery person whatever that
person was
donut shop
yeah yeah
dude the honking stop oh did you
actually just do something to the
honking man
that that reminds me of that seinfeld
episode that i just watched like two
days ago
where where um
where there's this goggle
and and uh kramer helps elaine out to
get rid of the dogo
but she's like a little bit of cowardice
about getting rid of the doggo anyway
anyway anyway
yeah don't worry about him
i just delivered him a donut
[Music]
okay lol well i guess it distracted him
hey guess what
i'm level nine now and what what what
level nine
wow oh mine was lame [\h__\h] lame
cute cute
oh
i think i wrote it like that once before
as well
that is also pretty cringe
you don't get it mira
now level 10 i earned my quadcopter
what's that all right stick congrats
okay i guess she said at the ironically
the cue
we're gonna pass around like kings
see you soon burger king
let's go burger king
six weeks six weeks
[Music]
who cares about your stupid quadcopter
how could you destroy the entire town
priorities
999 feet below donut county
lol oh [\h__\h] i said it what did you say
i've never destroyed anything
i'm kind yeah you look like you're
[\h__\h] trash panda
oh my god what
you used that stupid app to open up
holes all over town
and now we're all stuck on the ground
everything here looks fine to me
like genius
it's obvious don't you didn't i got
swallowed by a hole right after i
ordered the donut from yusha
what does that have to do
with mirrors smashing my quadcopter
potter what happened to your son
my sweet puppy boy he must still be up
here somewhere
oh no
okay potter's rock
left click to the boil okay the blowhole
and whole
come in here we start with the small
things you gotta um
not go too big
but eventually we will go home thank you
for the ransomware
uh
what
oh [\h__\h]
wait
are you is that is that a joke is that a
joke or
if it's not a joke that i feel bad about
you know what i did in the zillow stream
uh okay swallowing get out of it get out
of there get out move it move it
i hope that's not her son
because then i have to tell her it's
already too late for her son by far
it's a joke is it are they trying to get
back at me
oh plants i need to get i was thinking
of getting a cactus uh but i'm too
scared to touch it
so i have a problem buying it can you
guys help me i need to buy a cactus can
you attach it for me chimkins it
wouldn't hurt you would it
it won't it won't hurt you guys right
with the feathers protecting you
i can't do it
[Music]
i need we need to be more aggressive
here
where's my aggressive music i mean i'm
enjoying this music but i feel like i
should turn on aggressive music
pottery huh
gloves exist
i can't just
i can't
ah what is this
come on
oh there we go
i'll make me bigger i need to i need to
swallow this come on
yeah there we go how about you know oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] well now they have something to
do down there maybe they can use it you
know as a hobby
oh [\h__\h] what
thank you for the red super chat michael
oh oh no all the beautiful pottery oh
too bad
oh but you hear that beautiful sound
it's like music in my ears
[Music]
nice gorgeous here a
thingy that goes over 900 000 million
degrees as i've heard
pretty accurate i would say i'm a genius
i know how hot that gets
yes
um not as hot as me though cause i'm
hotter than all of that
uh
again give me that wood give me that one
give me that one give me that wood give
me that look
[\h__\h] out
okay i'll start here at the chair
and this
come on go on your balance oh
physics guys this is what you call
physics
this is also physics
and this is also physics
okay oh what's going on here
is that how you start a
hot air balloon
is that how you do it
oh [\h__\h] we can swallow that oh my god
yeah bit
oh oh yeah i might set everything on
fire here oh [\h__\h] is that really how you
should handle that transportation wise
i'm i don't know man
let's let's take this first
that gives us some space
there we go
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh no we're helping you we're helping
you i guess although your butt must be
getting really hot as well oh holy [\h__\h]
yeah
i got an achievement pups odyssey oh so
you're going to uh space now
enjoy that have fun
oh my god oh my god okay we're on
[\h__\h] fire
holy [\h__\h] what did i do
yeah tanuki this is not the right way to
do it
this is uh
kind of worrying what we're doing here
okay how much longer until we can take
the house
okay it's over it's over friends
you are now homeless i'm sorry
but you can live here on the ground
great delivery
[Music]
trash of ptm
oh
barrel cactus it looks so cute you may
think there's loot inside because it
says barrel but it's full of spiders
uh some of these apparently uh funny uh
descriptions this one was not one of
them it's a free house don't let it get
wet
i guess a cardboard box could be a house
for a cat
go in here if you want to get yelled at
by coyotes oh
never seen a coyote before
donkey donkey kong let's see coffee
rules it burns your tongue and makes you
go to the bathroom
yeah i don't drink coffee what about you
guys wearing coffee drinkers protects
you from cows
do not try to wash cotton candy in the
pool this tip will save your life oh
wait
tanuki probably tried it didn't he was
it was it tanookies was it wash wash
bears uh horse bears
that's the german name for it was it the
raccoons
who tried to wash cotton candy in in in
water
or was it a different animal
it
oh was that sugar cube
who was that yeah in german it's wash
bear
maybe because they wash everything do
they actually wash everything then
they're not as as trashy as we might
think they are
raccoons so cute okay we're not gonna
look for all of this but
um
how many birds are you willing to fight
for a bag of chips
uh
i i don't have to fight any of them
because they see me as their empress and
they will willingly give it to me
without a problem have a garbage day
thank you you too
okay we're back in donut county county
county
i just wanted to surprise pop wave a
doughnut
now he's floating away alone
[Music]
no he's not if you go got swallowed
first how do you know pup is in the
balloon this star is full of holes
your brain is full of holes
and so is the entire time thanks to you
he's doing my job
wait i mean not true
i'm
[Music]
station who's the pup
which way was he handing
i don't know i got distracted i had just
ordered a donut [\h__\h] donuts
in the end it's it's their [\h__\h] fault
[Applause]
so she must have been absolutely
terrified when she was watching uh
cronies
uh kimono reveal
ranger station
one of those surprise snakes
i
i'm not i'm not scared of that this is
the effect i'm not scared of snakes it's
just the way they are
they pop like that holy [\h__\h] okay now i
know which ones are to stay stop moving
stop moving stop moving
[Music]
am i not supposed to be caught by the
light
what happens if i get caught by a light
[Music]
i don't care gosh
okay time to swallow you as well
i know
am i gonna be swallowing the chimpkins
what the [\h__\h]
snake danger
[Music]
why is there a snake a bucket sticking
out of my
oh my hole
get rid of it
[Music]
hurt the chimney
going to space soon
cute what about this we're supposed to
oh my god i just [\h__\h] broke his
eardrums
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] just happened what did i
do what did i do
oh my god let's get all the snakes holy
[\h__\h]
too many snakes
i'm gonna be honest i don't think i've
ever seen a real snake outside of the
zoo we don't have snakes here i'm not in
australia let me just repeat that for
uh importance sake i am not
from australia
the joke is over people have been taking
it too seriously
all right time to swallow everything
dominate the world
oh yummy rocks um yummy thinking yeah
you need to come too i need some friends
down there the kimkins are my only
friends
[Music]
yes i'm not from australia i know it's
unbelievable
it's one thing to own a chicken but two
chickens that's two things
oh my god do you know how many chickens
i own i have like so many
i'm i'm a rich
rich chimpkin owner
so i have
many many of things
large mug for dirt lovers
you're always on the wrong side of it
yeah [\h__\h] fences
why allows you to grab the egg and pet
the chicken
how
the wire allows you to grab the egg and
pet the chicken
i don't understand this this is supposed
to be some kind of joke but i don't get
it
gloves for your car
with jail for freaks
plastic bird that scares you a metaphor
let me tell you i know a lot about birds
but that is not a bird
a live spaghetti that is 100 accurate
yes yes yes
hippie
[Music]
because you can reach through the wires
okay put hands for the wireless okay i
guess so
it's not the the wire that's allowing me
to do that though
it's the empty space in between the
wires that's allowing me to
if we want to be really excited
says burger king
sounds like you should be thanking me
for solving your snake problem
wait
so it was you who opened up the holes
what
who what no
i'm just thinking whoever did it was
totally doing you a solid
he's probably really cool a nice guy i
love this raccoon
[Music]
did anyone else see pup
where
[Music]
10 seconds ago
he took a liking to this bird
i am
a bird made for liking
i was admiring this bird
till i was hit with hunger
so i ordered the donut but way of
count the um
then the whole game
and then the whole game it is a loafer
what the [\h__\h] are you doing what is
you are we must end you
you're stupid you're lovely but you're
also [\h__\h] stupid get rid of you quick
what are you doing
what are you doing why are you moving
like that come on down the hole down the
rabbit hole you go
oh my god that's not a real bird i got
bamboozled that movement does not look
like a real
wait no [\h__\h] no i'm filled with water
[\h__\h]
ah
i need to get rid of the water oh drink
it drink it i guess can you drink oh
big brain
[Music]
thank you
maybe you are a real bird after all the
fake bird couldn't drink water and
consume it right
right
okay oh my god you're gonna drink a lot
of water i'm sorry
yeah it's healthy though
water very healthy although i don't know
where the hell this water came from
oh tennis ball
was lost there
there you go
take it
oh there we go last one
okay uh we're done feeding you now we
can swallow you come on come on
come on
i'm not big enough yet
let me get some stuff oh wait i just i
still have some water for you
that's why i can't take you now i can
take you no
oh
nice
we have a what's it called
oh
he he jumped in there rather uh
happily in the end
great delivery
one day i once i want one of those
things that you put at the end of your
car
and then i want to travel i want to go
somewhere with a car with that car extra
thingy that dlc for your car
yes car dlc portable outhouse feeling
disgusting
half of a mouse guitar ukulele piece has
the word forever carved into it half of
a mousekit
because it's small get it get it
free sled ah
i used to
when when i didn't have a sled i used to
use sometimes even plastic bags man
press the buttons on the top to select
your flavor
extremes have a terrible way to keep
your fries safe
they're not safe from anyone because i
will eat them you can tell fish your
secrets they won't remember anything
oh so
okay so gouda is a good person to tell
my secrets to
tennis balls only grow in hard to reach
places
and the bird drinking bird tell me how
to get ate by a bird tell me
i don't um well work at kfp
easy solution
if that's really what you want
okay
wow
so are you saying you like in love of a
bird
look at all these people in the chat
they're not doing anything illegal okay
they're in love with me and it's legal
as [\h__\h]
burger king it's not about the bird
it is about a bird
it is about the bird
you hopeless dude
i'm on the road today i'm on the [\h__\h]
road
how did i
[Music]
donut shop right
out of business
moving to town [\h__\h] the raccoons i'm
gonna close the shop and move down to
the desert
oh no i'm sorry coyote
helped you this life is like a sad
country tune
country roads
as a modest living selling vengeance
[Laughter]
now me i'm the senpai can you see it oh
look at him
look at him oh yeah coyotes have funny
noses don't they
oh
you sell corn all my respect to you i'm
buying all of it give me more give me
more give me more give me more i want
the rest of it
one is not enough
serve it with some butter and some salt
and you get me
for the rest of your lifetime
there
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
the corn stand the corn stand must come
with it oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
don't eat the popcorn no no we need to
get it back we need to get it back
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] sometimes my hole is on fire i
don't know how that happens
i guess because i ate the fire oh [\h__\h] i
don't say it
mean it's
me and my dial
what's going on over there
i don't see [\h__\h]
i move the camera move it
um
[Music]
is that all i can eat i feel oh all
right yeah i still need to eat what the
hell where's it going
corn stand come on do me a favor get
into this hole
please oh my god
come in here
don't be a little [\h__\h]
you gotta hide in outside come on come
on come on yes good boy
and now we're big enough for that stupid
tent
there we go
yes kiana's hole
now
now we know it's my hole afterwards no
no no
no that's not true
the whole in minecraft is that what what
are we talking about
it's not mine it's not mine i didn't do
anything i didn't make a hole
coyote we go we got him we got him
someday everything will be made of corn
i would love that you know what's great
corn soup mmm
corn daisy
anything besides hot dogs um because
corn is also amazing hello
maybe i should try putting corn on hot
dogs
rocks were given to us by aliens this is
probably the worst place to pour milk
into um of course it is horrible what i
don't understand is
why in some countries
you put milk into the weirdest
containers ever
camping soup bowl it looks nice try
washing yourself with soup you might
feel good if it is corn soup then yes
fake house that's easy to steal from
cornett was punished
[Music]
i guess i could agree with that
an early type of television
yeah
probably also kind of true it's
it's more like mood lighting i would say
but okay
a small food fortress
not quite you can live inside this if
your house gets full
if you make a crowd crony mad it will
steal your credit card number
interesting
well i don't have a credit card so
so far i'm fine but i will i will make
sure to hide my credit card from cronie
i didn't i just got recommended a clip
with something about bails and a credit
card number
what happened there
welcome back to donut county everybody
anyway that's my sad story
okay don't you have something to say to
coyote
i mean like an apology
i'm sorry you think vegetables taste
good
[Music]
why should i apologize for delivering
this pathetic vegetable eating coyote
donut
wrecked his business twice
and stop saying you deliver donuts
what exactly do you think donuts are
good questions
[Music]
um
oh [\h__\h]
oh who can see
exactly who can sink who can't say roma
gets it
what is a donut without a hole
wow very good question
we should really stop ponder and ponder
this for as long as possible
a donut without a hole is still a donut
like jelly donuts long johns fritters
a crafting cup and apparently is that a
donut maybe maybe in this kind of a
doughnut a crab thing
and donut hole
wait donut holes don't have holes
and they don't have holes they are the
whole oh
[\h__\h] bright explosion
wow that's pretty big
don't change the subject burger king
mickey roma you two just moved to hopper
springs right
yes we moved out for retirement
to
[Music]
did you order a donut too
aroma got a new phone like the best
phone ever takes the best selfies for
instagram lovely
so we ordered donuts to celebrate but of
course sugar free and vegetarian and
with you know nothing nothing inside
that could ever hurt anybody
[Laughter]
we must
deploy pain upon them
i was at lush today
i
hello bunny what the [\h__\h] you look like
a weird bunny that's a really weird
bunny i wasn't lush today i haven't been
there in a long time and i got myself
like a [\h__\h] out of bath bombs and stuff
it was more than a pink super chat i'm
telling you that
and they saw they had like some new
stuff and one of the
was it a bath bomb
or no i think it was a
a bubble bath or something like that
and it looked like a
like a carrot but like like a carrot
what [\h__\h] it's stuck it's [\h__\h] stuck
inside oh you're gonna eat it ah
okay thank you here take it how do i how
do i bring it to help me help me help me
eat it
yo
anyway one of them looks like a like a
carrot but like you know one of those
carrots can you be faster like what the
hell
hello how do i get to you
eat this [\h__\h]
eat
it i'm trying to give it to you
what what oh maybe the other bunny's
gonna come down bonnie's please bunnies
being bunnies help me eat this shitty
carrot
go down there's the door
[Music]
i'm stuck in this game i'm stuck
unbelievable oh there's some more
bunnies up here would you maybe play his
mind coming down
eating my carrot
oh wait i think i understand i need to
bring the bunny for the door and then
above
oh man
guide the bunny you don't even look like
a bunny you look like a deer
a crafting of a deer and a bunny thank
you oh my god it took me long enough
i'm gonna swallow you for that
pain in the ass
okay thank you yeah and anyway the last
thing looks really funny oh oh no oh no
oh
oh i have a bad feeling about this i
feel like we're gonna be um
seeing a bunny revolution sometime soon
oh no
[Music]
only now weeks old
you see those hearts are still going on
how many babies are you making
stopping at once
stop it we already have enough bunnies
in this world
get them down you get them down swallow
them this is probably bad they're gonna
make even more
oh no
[Music]
uh
yeah and i'm just gonna send even more
down there i guess
[Music]
oh no
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
it's a volcano of bunnies probably
oh they're gonna eat the house baby i
don't know
no oh my god
get them back in here
get them back in you're [\h__\h] fast
wait that's not how i
it's not exactly how i wanted to say the
sentence but it has a lot of deep
meaning to it i guess
get in here
yeah okay
we're done here
[Laughter]
so what are these animals so these ones
that are like here falling down here
what are the most random vegetables
random
i like carrots wow why is it so big
wow
carrot grow underground and they are
therefore extremely untrustworthy
a green
carrot house broken imagine loving
carrots so much that you wanted to live
inside one
looks at pecora senpai
bunnies love to chew and stuff because
of their evil nature
looks sad peculiar
if i just want to destroy everything and
they don't know why
looks at pekora senpai
should but i will not be fooled
looks like that when i say but i did get
fooled i did get fooled by her cute
dance anybody anybody gets full very
cute this is too cute pick a pickle
pickle pickle dirt spoon
if you put seeds inside and water it
every day it's so boring
clearly designed by aliens does no one
else see it
you can step on this if you hate dirt
provides minimal cover
the early type of tablet from when it
used to be a piece of furniture
because it was so big okay
nice
done
garbage day is monday and thursday
apparently
what do you have to say this time holy
round of garbage people
it's really cute that you two are so in
love
uh
night and day you belong to love oh [\h__\h]
wrong voice
it's true
this is extremely close
you're gross
not gross
you'll love trash
do you love trash too everyone you love
trash
why else would you want so much of it
are everyone's homes just trash to you
don't say that about them
oh you don't
i brought my laptop also to watch a bird
surely bird videos
uh-huh oh peppa okay people let's go oh
the
crowd is some popcorn i try to feed
cronie with some popcorn next time i see
her
what's this
what's a diesel
where do we start it's not small this
broken ukulele it's not mine by the way
mine is not yet broken give me more
yes it's playing with me
one bird plays with the other
how sweet
titty
until i swallow you
then you don't think it's so funny
anymore is it i think yeah yeah
i'm gonna take this
i'll be on fire
oh
yucky yakitori tonight
it doesn't hurt you
are you a bird of hell i think
i think yes i think we have just
established that crows are birds of hell
i mean honestly i think we all knew that
since before
set it on
[Music]
[Applause]
those are some nice trees but they look
even nicer when they're on fire
burn
burn why won't you burn
take it take the laptop yes
can't watch bird videos anymore look at
real birds instead freak
[Music]
oh do i need you cold for it to make it
burn ah
now it's time for you come on don't
hesitate it's better down there it's
better in the donut hole trust me
i want you now
come with me
come with me bird of hell
eastern coined it
wait what else can i swallow
oh this is a big stone
big stone okay okay okay
here we go
yes yes beautiful beautiful
beautiful
oh now finally justice has been served
done
great delivery
old and ugly tree there's usually a
bobcat cat scrolling on top of scotland
on top of the joshua tree oh that's what
you call them laptop pour a glass of
water on this and scream
never happen to me
not with my laptop at least maybe on the
keyboard but not on the laptop
it gets really hot to protect the food
inside yes protect the food with hotness
the opposite of a refrigerator
not quite
barbecue batteries cold
that's cool
rude style of christ
bro the wild scriptures
you only get this one if you um know any
japanese comedians there's one japanese
comedian who always says
why dodo does it
he's like he says it's wild isn't it and
apparently that's really funny
i don't know
rude
kind of weird how large and purpley
shaped these boulders are
it's like the aliens are mocking us [\h__\h]
you aliens
folds up when you
when you least expect
stupid desert chairs everything sucks
you know we're all right to swallow all
of this
a dumpster you can attach no it's car
dlc i already said it why do you have to
correct my description a dumpster you
can drive
yes
yes a green
[Music]
this is like the other side of animal
crossing this is this is how
this is what uh what's his name again
what's his name what's his name again
what's that recruit's name again tanuki
what was it again i forgot
i am
uh question here i mean if you listen to
the voices that they gave the characters
in the game it's actually pretty similar
to bk what is the question
you didn't save the joshua trees because
you were too busy looking
no i i wasn't looking at the bird stuff
that time okay
then what were you doing pepper
i was
writing an email
onto a bird
no you [\h__\h] trash sniffer [\h__\h] you
and everyone that you're involved with
to my brother so
excuse me
i don't have smashed your level
oh
[Laughter]
boss is very unhinged today
i'll show you unhinged come to the usual
room later my sweet sweet chicken
darling so i'm reunited filming brother
and so the civil servants snake problems
wonderful
given the chance to give the flight
i'm a hero
you are what's it called again
what do you what do you call those
people who die uh
but then later get recognized as heroes
uh
it was a weird word what was it again
first again what's again march mercury
monitor yeah that's what you are burger
king
and you haircut
oh wow you got some cool looking air
what do you do
i sell explosives
give me
for safety
oh no i run my business completely above
board i have the most permitting donut
gun
playing with fireworks is safer than
driving your guard
i wouldn't trust him
[Laughter]
he already sounds
not dressed with me but yo look at this
beautiful beach
you sell fireworks at the beach is that
a good place to have that business
i will take this space and i will use it
to uh
make a new kfp here
okay of place
oh [\h__\h] oh
ah
how often do we do this
oh this is cute no swallow
take it oh god what oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h]
oh
i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry but at the
same time i need to swallow you um
good food substitute
people will not notice the difference
between seagulls and chimpkin will they
i wonder what they oh
wait what are we doing are we trying to
send this up to the mountain
ah it didn't surprise
how him much
how did i just turn it
oh [\h__\h]
i wait yeah i have to i have to probably
take it swallow it and then
here we go like that
[Music]
come down now come down it's time to
come down oh you want another one
we've got to help him a little bit more
here
rockets
where did the rockets go
what
oh they disappeared
oh i got something anyway
jackpot
and he got corny
i'm happy
[Music]
i think we did something beautiful today
great delivery
[Music]
everyone is weak to fire
cliffs are a type of trap created by
aliens
okay this coin has wine stuff on it and
spicy stuff it's really good the white
stuff probably mayonnaise maybe
popcorn you have to fight a seagull to
get this the texture is highly regarded
oh
hey singles like popcorn you can't make
me read i'm not gonna do it says me
99 of single secret
no no poor
singles
we gotta fix their uh we re re
reputation how do we do it we we hire
them for kfp and then we sell them as
chimken burgers and then people are
gonna eat it and love it and then i'll
be like a publicly announcing that
actually was not chimkin
and then it was seagulls and then
everyone's gonna change their mind about
seagulls and be like okay they taste
delicious from now on we shall honor
them by eating more and more of them
let's go
you can use fireworks to remove hair a
spicy candle store
pretty common type of treasure chest
picnic basket yeah yeah i got myself a
picnic basket last year
it's about time it's nice having a
picnic basket you can make a cute picnic
a little picnic basket
with all kinds of cute snacks in it and
then act cute while eating it cutely
don't drink immediately wait until the
fizz is gone
i actually i have to admit that um
i used to
nowadays maybe not so much anymore but i
used to wait
uh until my cola is uh yeah has no more
fizz and then drink it
like like on the second day or so like
after opening it on the second day that
was the best day for me to drink
coca-cola
like from a bottle though
second day or
possibly even the third day
yes oh oh they hate me oh they hate me
now
nowadays no there's not so much but i
was i was um i was very very sensitive
of against the fizziness
me too hallelujah
i think i have uh built up uh an
immunity against fizziness a bit more so
nowadays i don't i don't wait
for the fizziness to be
i'm so
you cannot accept me i will take your
hand and when i will forcefully push
your finger on your mouse to suck me
back again
seagulls love french fries because it's
the main crop of their homeland
okay
morrisville has a nicer car tonight will
[\h__\h] kill morselin
doesn't deserve a better car
whoever the [\h__\h] morsel is
oh
that
that person we just met i suppose
that's what she said
i was just cleaning up the neighborhood
who else has a gripe with me
and i i do
well my gripe is actually with mira oh
[\h__\h]
now you're
[Music]
knows the details but i figure everyone
should hear
even the bird weirdos
yes tell them
i i knew the raccoons are making the
holes
i knew the whole time
hold that
okay
oh my god lore is getting so deep
how many snakes will it take to defeat
you
[Music]
big snakes
no massage
what you gotta find in a tiny room
[Music]
okay expect a shipment soon oh
they haven't looked into the
disappearances yet
oh wait sorry the music is so loud isn't
it oh my god
i'm sorry
but it's just still too loud huh
wait has it been like this the whole
time
have you guys been able to hear me
i wish now it should be better
and no
salt hasn't answered his phone and dies
did you talk to blossom he said he has
info
a bosom told me that the earth is hollow
and flat at the same time somehow what a
[\h__\h] loser
music was five okay i'll get
tell me right you know ever since those
raccoons moved in folks have been
disappearing
isn't that sus and you work at their
donut shop
i don't know raccoons treat me really
well
because i'm trash just like them and bk
burger king is my friend
[Music]
i ordered a donut quiet
i want to see how they taste delicious
i gotta go i'll take i'll talk to you
soon
oh
back to sleep oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
let's rip up their tails
and then
put them on the sticks and then burn
them in a bonfire
i don't know why i don't know why i feel
like doing that but they're so cute
[Music]
i like i guess i enjoy um reading things
that i
think are cute
i'm sorry about that
don't run away from me
i just want to love you
no i know what yes good boy
[Music]
you look even cuter when you panic
kill inside
another one
way cuter than that crocodile
we don't need to bring that crocodile
do we
there's a lazy-ass crocodile anyone
let's take the lizards only
kawaii
flamingo
some of these some of that some radio
entertainment you know
can we get that already no
looks so difficult maybe no no
oh we need to like move some of this
there's a
there's a stool on top of it that we
could possibly
get come on
okay now this is really hard to move
maybe we do you first
give me your phone
or give me everything okay
oh that's all i wanted to the white i
need to turn it up again
the music a little bit a little bit
okay
but i'm so nice like i'm doing full
service delivery by not bringing you
down by yourself but i'm bringing on all
your belongings with you
for free
i'm taking your house even look at that
disgusting house man you live you live
in that
what's up what was in there before soup
i can't turn it around [\h__\h]
ah
and i need to flip it or something flip
it flip it come on
doesn't someone from spongebob live in
the house like that too
kfb moving service yeah you girl you
live like this
come on uh
are they doing yoga over there
maybe if i am patient yes
patient perfect fit
squidward does and there you go i knew
it i knew it squidward is one of those
people
what what trash repeating huh probably a
book with proof that aliens exist what
is it with them and aliens pulling a
book about something boring like
collectible spoons
how does he fit
inside house was perfectly me
keeps your hand warm
hand warms
ends warm
has nine thousand nine hundred ninety
nine hundred emails i i did that before
too nowadays it's not as bad
what is your clothes for getting wet
oh yes punish him punish him
the only good bird is a fake
excuse me excuse me
i'm done with this i'm done with reading
this
they don't know what they're talking
about
they will pay for that
statement i'm so sorry cocoa
coco
i just realized the name now
i took that personally yes i did
it was my fault you got put into the
hole
i should never have taken the job of the
raccoons
oh what that
i thought we were friends dude
i thought we were too
but then you ruined my town
i don't get it
i tried to help when you asked me to
i bought the catapult upgrade for you
you know what catapults are
were invented for
to catapult
one cat
to another place
yes
that's why it's called cat a
pulp yes
yes
true story man true sorry
yeah
specifically um yes specifically in
medieval times and so on you would
catapult cats
inside inside a castle or whatever
you're trying to take over
um to let the cats do its work
as we know cats uh just like plus in
boots or so and they are very good
ninjas and they can sneak in
and either get them with the cuteness
or kill them in their sleep by
scratching their eyes out
yeah they are uh
and
a weapon of mass destruction
that's what the catapult is for
yes history teacher kiwama trust me i've
been watching a lot of history shows
recently on netflix and and stars play
and uh disney plus and so on
it makes sense doesn't it that's why the
name is that of course
even though it's a waste of points
you told me that with the catapult you
could launch everyone back out of the
hole
yet here we are in the hole
a jellybean
chicken
oh you killed that chicken looks happy
i'm chunky
catastrophe pontiacho thank you
[Music]
the wikipedia entry is incorrect i need
to go modify it uh sidekiana for it
thank you please do please do please do
that's the spirit chimpkins are holy
no
it's the least you can use
after stealing one of our
didn't steal the eggs they fell for the
ground
just tell your story jelly bean
times were tough on the farm
i had to show my price rooster and make
ends meet don't love was very upset
oh and you know what happens when dollop
gets upset eggs
wait that's how
is she i thought oh she's crying i
thought it was like
uh
pooping out eggs for its head i was
confused okay now hold on why is this
why is this chimpkin in the cage we need
to free it
yo
come on i'll help you i'll help you
and then
they even put weights on top of it so it
won't escape why is the raccoon here
hear that i'll take you take you down
with everybody else
chimki no free you
afraid you trust me
oh
uh raccoon is in an idol meeting
why did you deliver a donut to coco
duh
what's the problem
burger king this is too much too
you have to buy the catapult upgrade
right now and fix things
[Music]
hey
answer me
i've shown you my duck now answer me
[\h__\h]
but i'm gonna save up for my quadcopter
do it you promised
what
[Music]
oh there she goes you see a little bit
of time and then she comes around there
and she goes come on don't think about
it do it no i know you want to
i know you want to
oh could you die
[Music]
there
come on come on show me what you got
girl
just one duck just one more duck come on
one duck it's all it takes
never gonna duck you duck never gonna
duck you duck
never gonna dock you duck duck duck
doctor come on
[\h__\h] you
fine fine
i'll fix
everything
but you owe me
bye
don't want to talk to this lady anymore
she's not fun oh
wow i
oh
i have 110 dollars
the catapult is 99.
[Music]
oh i bought these things before
apparently
ah i can buy energy drinks and the
catapult let's go
we'll we'll keep the money
we'll keep it what the [\h__\h] oh
let's go to catapult oh
back of the eggs but the chimpkin is
still not free the chicken is right now
we're free all the chips
strawberries but wait now we suck it
back in what's what's the meaning of
this
[Laughter]
young
okay
fly look guys you can fly
yo
good job jimkin and i have a chimpkin
again fly
oh wait i need to do something ah i need
to ring the bell of the chimpkin maybe
you can do it jim cannon
you can do it it's it's all counting on
you
it's all counting on you tim ken
ah
wait maybe actually um maybe here
oh
yes yes yes
i thought you were gonna land on it are
you a ghost jumping
oh wait oh
i know
oh
you can land in there can you
yes
what are we doing what are we doing the
chimpkin has infiltrated the system
am i supposed to catch the eggs oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh sh ah
this is another episode of eckhardt's
broken heart is too [\h__\h] i come with
that one
what's so young
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on come on come on come on no
we're cracking all the eggs [\h__\h]
there we go we got one so what do we do
of it
what do we do with it
it wants me to shoot it out somewhere
uh where where do you want me to shoot
it to oh [\h__\h]
got this kiara thank you
i will do my best to rescue as many eggs
as possible
save it
[Applause]
[Music]
all the time goes oh the jama goes
did you guys know tamago is egg in
japanese and now you know tamagotchi is
called something like egg
white oh my question i question it too
hallelujah
i want the big chicken statue yes yes
yes
i'm gonna put that in my apartment hell
yeah honor the chimpkins
people have underestimated chimpkins for
way too long
come on give me give me this whole thing
i want this whole thing i'm gonna make a
business out of it trust me
yes yes
the eggs did we did we know
we saved up more
yes we did yes yes we must we must
believe in our own purpose in the fact
that our purpose is always the right way
to go
this might grow up into a real barn
someday oh
i won't bow down to a chicken ever
i'm so close to quitting the game right
now
i'm
so close that is insulting
calm down kiara
kfb don't cancel this game
we will
we will be respected one day
don't worry i'm gonna make it happen for
you all
for a better world and a better life for
all of us trust me
don't worry i'm on your side i am not a
chicken but i am i say we because i'm on
your side i'm fighting for you you know
that don't you
you weren't even trying to help burger
king
i was trying it's hard to use the
catapult if you don't have a cat i think
the hole is only really good for
destroying things
it must be designed that way
designed
don't look at me i didn't design it
but you used it
well what else could i use
i don't know you could have used real
donuts
could a real doughnut have same
[Music]
you are getting hunted by bees
i'm a hero
you ordered a donut in to the middle of
the forest
hunted by
bees okay
[Laughter]
bees
my favorite bee is adam b
what's your favorite bee
hmm
okay it goes up
to the forest wiggle
let's collect honey oh wait can i like
actually collect the honey
no i don't think so okay let's start
with grass there's a frog
[Music]
same
kiana bee oh that's cute too but i don't
i don't blame you if you prefer almond
bean i mean it's just perfect recipe i'm
perfect as a frog everyone is you know
destined to be good at something
i don't think anyone can be a better
frog than i am
but when it comes to bees you know
there's just one
professional bee oh i can now throw
things
does the frog want the honey oh [\h__\h]
here take it
fat frog
where do you want to go where are you
going
where are you going where are you going
let me take you i'm faster this way
oh
are we trying to
do what i think we're trying
what a genius frog frogs are very
versatile
get it go get it go frog
why do the bees look like robots and
monsters [\h__\h]
kind of concerning but okay
yo this frog would be amazing at
basketball
huh
what
thank you thank you dubs
welcome
okay do do we now try to catch the bees
with the frog
go get him frogger
is this the new frog game let's go i
used to love to play that frog game
where you crossed the road when i was
younger
absolute genius game although i killed
too many frogs in that game that's why i
turned myself into one to make up for
all the frogs i killed
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
what's that gate froga yeah braga i
should stream it honestly
but i want to play the old one the old
one that i played myself come down here
there's no escape
come on
oh [\h__\h] we're not we're still too weak
okay
first we gotta save all the bees because
we're 100 saving them come on
oh oh frog is getting really big i
didn't notice you're actually eating
those bees oh dear
it just said
did you ever play more who
of course i did of course i did
is that a german only game
there we go we swallowed it all let's
the go and the frogs
yeah
yeah yeah
what do you say about bees bees are very
hyper and they like to kiss their moms
but
as if they knew
they like to kiss a lot of moms but they
do they do
a piece of fruit that bees love to hang
out and it's is this considered a fruit
bees are always making dessert yeah good
bees man they're hard workers we need to
hire them for kfb maybe a bee burger or
a honey burger
bees rent apartments from their mom
yeah they all live with their mom
it's a watering can but for making bees
tired
oh
i see
you can predict the weather based on the
time between the frog frogs krill
sometimes it's wrong
is that really like a thing like you
know the peeing on wheat thing
is that really a thing that's actually
interesting
i would like to look closer into that
a beef virger what
a honey burger yeah i don't know
just a patty of sticky honey
with some honey sauce
hey what about me
nobody asked about me
did bk own you with a catapult too oh no
you ruined my restaurant
oh you where's the wrong stinks
oh yeah it's crazy
how can you guys be cold salt and pepper
and not have any appreciation for soap
calm down nerds what did bk do to your
restaurant well i was dealing with a
slight bug problem
i was exhausted from rounding a bug so i
ordered a donut
we must look deeper into this story as
well cat soup oh
honestly i love the design ew
cockroaches eel i love the design of
this uh restaurant stop following me
stop following me that's absolutely
disgusting no no we don't want the we
don't want the cockroaches in the donut
hole please no yeah yeah that's it
yeah that no
no please no
yeah i guess i have
we got the cats too though the cat will
help us catch the bugs underground
hopefully oh the bird is back the bird
works here
i see oh what happens here what's that
what's oh oh you're drinking the soup
okay
what is that to this
are we actually supposed to make like
good soup
oh that's gonna be a problem
what the hell the pot and salt and
pepper
how do i put ah
it's not good yet [\h__\h] you stupid
cockroach oh
oh almost you know it's interesting
though
come on quick quick i need some pepper
pepper my soup
no no no no
no no no no no no we don't want
cockroaches i think i think we don't
want cockroaches in our soup don't drink
it yet don't drink again here
okay i think i got it drink
now you can come
oh it went it worked ew ew absolutely
infested with cockroaches that's
disgusting
well speaking of cockroaches i guess
i'll tell you a cockroach story
uh i've
in austria i've never seen a cockroach
ever before
the only cockroaches that i've ever seen
were in japan i think it's the the
climate
the fact that it's like really humid in
japan
or that it gets really hot but even in
winter i saw them i don't know we don't
have cockroaches in austria thankfully
thankfully man
yeah there was a i think i told this
story before there was one time where i
booked like an airbnb i think i think it
was an airbnb or like a cheap [\h__\h]
hotel from
booking.com some kind of apartment it
was not a hotel
and
and then uh
i wanted to go to sleep but it was it
was a really run-down place so the
shower was really old like i didn't i
didn't even know how to use it it was
ridiculous from like
100 years ago or something
and then and then i wanted to go to
sleep but i saw a cockroach uh running
around and i had like i was in this one
tatami room
and i was supposed to sleep on the
ground with um with with uh with uh with
a um
uh futon
if it was maybe like a normal bed maybe
i could have somehow sucked it up but
sleeping on the floor when there is a
cockroach running around
i
don't think so
no
no thank you
wait have unlocked the quadcopter let's
go
and that's a big nope so but i
absolutely panicked i freaked out so
much i cried and and i panicked and oh i
really didn't want to sleep there but i
was so tired it was late at night and
then
i um what did i do oh yeah after crying
for like a few hours
um and and observing while being super
tired observing if i saw the the
cockroach i eventually i didn't have a
choice i kind of like slept for like
a few hours but then i um
i the next day i left that uh
place and i i moved into a proper hotel
that was like
um
definitely not infested with cockroaches
yeah i actually made it i'm surprised
remembering the story now i'm surprised
i actually fell asleep after that
i had to like what was i supposed to do
and you really needed to sleep
[Laughter]
yeah
it's
[Music]
like fighting cockroaches i hate those
guys you like fighting them you like the
frill of it or what what do they say
about cockroaches
[Music]
candles get better the more you have at
least thousand is a good starting point
not a big deal i got like 100 of these
at home
ew
not a big deal it is a big deal you can
let a bird cook but don't let it feed
you
don't listen to them don't listen to
them guys
don't listen to them we're gonna do it
that way our way
maybe he just wanted to cuddle
i don't care what the cookie booty wants
i do not want to cuddle with them
either
i do like a lot of different types of
bugs like i i love for example i love um
uh what do you call them again kemushi
uh though the fuzzy the fuzzy ones that
are the the warm before the butterfly
uh
the the long fuzzy boy the small long
fuzzy boy
that become beautiful butterflies
caterpillars yeah i love those fluffy
caterpillars that are perhaps maybe
poisonous but i love them they're so
cute
and i also tend i used to when i saw
them in austria i used to always touch
them
but then when in japan they told me to
not touch them maybe because they have a
lot of poisonous ones
so now i'm freaked out about it now i'm
too scared to touch them anymore
but they're pretty cute
okay when she's skiing no no no no oh
you're scared of caterpillars she's such
a chicken
i've got food poisoning from good soup
more than once
yeah i used to work there it's pretty
gross
oh wow
everything i do seems to have helped
everyone yeah
he's got a board mirror maybe burger
king ain't so bad
okay everybody
we all know cat soup was a hole even
before it got home
but let's get back to the real problem
here
yeah my 100 smash quadcopter
and when did you smash the mirror
dude
i didn't want to smash it i had to
and now
the donut job
oh [\h__\h] i am the quadcopter
i can't control this right now by the
way i'm not controlling it
ah
is tanooki controlling it burger king
working i'm about to
crash
check these out
wow
oh wait that's a cute design with the
tail of the stripes that's pretty
adorable
wow
oh yeah
wow that's so useful
notice how the propellers spin really
fast
that's how it flies oh
no kidding
and it only took 12 deliveries for me to
get it
can i see
sure
break it break it break it
be careful
careful
like this
a little lower
how about this
[Music]
she's the girl she's the chosen one
she's the chosen one what are you doing
you're acting psycho
oh she's sweet on
[Music]
how can you brag about the stupid toy
when you got it by destroying your our
friends homes
they ordered the donuts
and give people what they want so they
love this [\h__\h] story like
she threw it on the ground
she took the quadcopter and she threw it
on the ground she's not part of his
system
that isn't the real donut man
[Music]
real donuts have holes and not articles
duh
i'm a [\h__\h] adult and you're a [\h__\h]
trash panda
this is pointless vk what's your
password for this thing
uh i i think it's uh it's a row four
five one
wait no i changed it to donkey kong
not burger king okay
thanks by the way uh do you know what's
at the bottom of the house
i i don't know
what are you doing
teaching you a lesson
get him get a mirror get him
where do we start we need small things
here
okay
small
small good small small is good yeah
and then become big
big big big beak
big bad
fin
oh all of this all this oh big boy
oh [\h__\h]
we can't take the house yet but we took
the trash panda we're talking
we got him good job mira but we're
taking you too
the donut hole
no more donut shops no more
do not count the achievement unlocked oh
so this is why i wasn't able to get
donuts delivered the day before
yesterday
this is why
i was wondering why they weren't
delivering
[\h__\h] it's a [\h__\h] trash panda
i had to do it dude
there was no other way to get through to
you
oh
you don't know what's it like to lose
something you care about
i mean
i guess i get what you mean you guys
love your weird trash houses and i took
them away
by doing my job
their posts proposed
which i guess in this context is an evil
job
close enough
will you help us get everyone out of the
hole now
okay fine
i love this game what the [\h__\h]
oh
god did you get donuts for today no i
didn't but i got milk
and i got some fruit and
i had some eggs um
yeah not very satisfying huh when i got
a lot of lush bath bombs i i bought like
a [\h__\h] ton of lush bath bombs
um
where do we start
hello i was hoping you would know
i'm sorry if i gave you the impression
that i know stuff but i know basically
nothing
oh god i forgot her voice uh
you you've got to find the pup oh if you
guys can find papa we can use this hot
air balloon to get back to the surface
oh yeah
bk can you look up pop on your tablet
of course devil please locate gps data
for hot air balloon containing a pup
oh [\h__\h] he did oh [\h__\h] horse or he's in
outer space
i'm kidding this ring doesn't have voice
commands
you know who might be able to find pop
possum
no no no possum is too weird
it's weird but you have to admit possum
was right
the earth is hulk
but it's not flat it's not flat
[\h__\h] all those flat earthers
[Laughter]
if you know where he lives i can get him
yeah
just deliver a donut to the abandoned
house
of course possum squats in the abandoned
house i always thought it was haunted
this is worse
let's go possum oh is that you is that
what a possum looks like
what
i've never seen a possum before
okay it goes up
let's save the world i
guess yes earth is a chicken
true you understand
you seem to understand oh do i need to
like move the
candles
in order to oh it's just a mask
in order to see stuff
oh yeah
no music right now by the way
can i
can i move uh
oh
oh okay i can only slightly see i need
to swallow all of them i guess more
light
there shall be lot
not much mud oh there we go
i use yes yes yes
way better than those stupid candles oh
he likes to use a lot of different masks
oh what a creep
come on
bones
what is that
is that
i thought it was a cat but
i guess it's so is that the blossom
wait i don't see [\h__\h] anymore there we
go
battery
open it open it
open the refrigerator whoa
the weird level
eat this
i found the blossom i found it again
thank you
oh now keep it open you may keep it open
where is the possum this time
eat eat oh [\h__\h] i see you let's see him
scary
[Laughter]
it's outlast all over again i'm
terrified coulda please help me call me
this well this is so scary why can't i
not get this stupid cage i think i'm big
enough for it yeah there we go
okay oh do we continue this until i
swallowed anything or what's going on
a bowling ball i suck at bowling by the
way i can't even carry the [\h__\h]
bowling ball
oh the light is on
it's not a possum it is a
cat what does a possum look like not
like a cat right
nickel down
suny nicholas you guys are deceived
let's just take it
it was a cat all along
noodle arms
well can can you carry a bowling ball
show me then
wait look at the
look at the wall
he's doing conspiracy theories
come on
he's into conspiracy theories
relatable me too me too
there we go
yes lies
i don't think you can carry one
don't lie to me kfb your weak
chimpanzees how would you carry it with
your chimken hands you don't even have
hands you only have wings how would you
carry it show me show me a chicken
carrying a bowling ball
gotcha
you can't
let me google
chicken
carrying
bowling
ball
there you go it's not existing
no touche right no chicken has ever
carried a bowling ball before
you can change my mind if you show me a
picture
[Laughter]
oh that's a possum
how many hours do we have to listen to
this [\h__\h]
so possum do you know how to locate pup
pup
i think i heard the cops looking for a
dog in a hot air balloon
where is he
i'm gonna be able to find out if i don't
have a cool police scanner
oh my god
burger king where can we get a recombili
scanner
the police chief probably has one look
you censor that [\h__\h]
but he's a recruit lagoon today it's his
day off let's wreck it
miranda are you serious
like raccoon lagoon is the happiest
raccoon playing summer coming up
it's got brain tunes and water balloons
raccoon lagoon is home of the fun flume
that's fun for raccoons
he really likes my cool lagoon
you have no choice burger king the flume
is doomed
fine but you have to answer the police
chief when he's down here
raccoon lego holy [\h__\h] one awesome place
how did they build that
okay
let's get
let me get the dirt first
oh oh oh yeah it's already falling apart
that's what i like to see
music is good in this game too
what do you call it the capsule capsule
thingy
oh
ah
hey
[Music]
okay oh we got a water bowl now what do
we do with the water balloon
i guess
do this
do we have to like turn it
huh now i have a fish i have a fish now
what
oh okay i did it i did it somehow
uh i still have a fish
but no
water uh
um
do i need another capsule
i have a water balloon
uh
wait
there we go we pop it we get the water
we do this
we get the raccoon up higher yeah yeah
yeah i feel like he's just having the
time i was live here though
okay no fish no thank you
take oh wait oh [\h__\h] i tapped out oh
[\h__\h] oh there we go
there we go oh where's my mouse where's
my mouse here we are whoa
uh another water balloon how did that
happen i don't know here we go
roller coaster is almost complete let's
go
oh
that looks like fun oh wait
uh
uh what do i do here
oh
do i still need to do something
oops fishy [\h__\h]
oh there we go connected it
and now we take the raccoon
i even got a photo
koi there we
go nice
oh what now i still have the fish
and i still have the water
eh
did we do
another time
i don't understand i think we're done
with this whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa i don't want
all this water
get rid of it
give me the capsule right now it'll be
so much fun
okay okay
get rid of the water oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] i'm
sorry i'm taking all of you down with me
into the hole you go
you can blame your raccoon trash panda
friend i think we might need the water
to like get them out of here
this is now a roller coaster
faster faster
[Music]
yeah
what what raccoons are stinky is that so
i want a raccoon
my my uh my old cats that i don't have
anymore
i used to call her raccoon because she
looked like a raccoon
very cute
raccoon looking thing
yeah
cute cat
get in here get in here all of this we
can rebuild it in the donut hole
donut come to you back here
continue the story
oh the police chief oh [\h__\h] what
is he alive
guys i could get in trouble for this
trash king will take away my tackle if
he finds out
oh no well are you gonna get grounded
too will he drop you and all your
friends into a weird cave
okay okay i get it
possum got anything on the scanner
uh one one sec
yes i got it
they have custom t-shirts now
[Music]
[Applause]
yes we better hurry burger king the cops
are after him let's go
the cops are after me
calm down it's okay dude i'll visit you
in jail
oh what what
i know i'm a really good friend but
first we have a delivery to make
donuts coming right to your doorstep
here we go this is what you wanted right
deploy hole get all the cars yeah but
what
damn you got a license where did you get
the license from
wait what do we need to
are we are we big enough for the car
already yes we are
what about the big cars we're gonna get
all of them too right wait wait there's
raccoons
it's only recruits driving them
what are they watching
burger
bowling ball
trash trash panda cute
cute
[Music]
remember when tvs had that shape
long long time ago
oh there we go my mom used to say if you
watch
if you watch too much tv then your eyes
become a
square size square shaped
yeah yeah my very wise mom
oh
why are you taking pictures of him you
think this is funny
what
eat a donut or something ah
he really wants a donut wait what did i
do now what's the picture
they throw it at you
oh we got a picture of him
and he's coming down oh we bamboozled
him
cheese
smile show us your best smile
we got the quadcopter i didn't have a
quadcopter
hell yeah
and now we shoot the trash pattern at
the trash panda
no he doesn't do [\h__\h]
maybe on you
and another one
oh grandma said yes yes heavy trash
banners and the photo i guess why not
no i think we need to
do it with the donut guy yeah
so he falls down
easy easy we got this in the bag
here we go are we having enough yet
already
are they
hold on to it come on
there we go
no no no no
it's like a boss fight
that was easy
i thought it would be a bit more of a
challenge oh yeah
it looks like a sheep from here
we got him now let's get the cars get
the cars
yes yes
beautiful keep on driving keep on
driving they don't know what's coming
for now oh
consume
guys nice
nice
i now own every car in the whole wide
world
[Laughter]
[Music]
we were safe
okay pop get out i need this hot air
balloon i'm going up to save us
no way dude you can't go alone you just
run away
i'm coming with you
in case i need to
[Music]
yeah don't just stay here
are you guys leaving with no plan
uh
we're going to talk the leader to the
leader of
trash king we're going to do a boss
fight oh oh we're getting a real boss
fight kick his butt
dude you always screw up the boss fight
you gotta follow my lead this time
oh maybe just try talking to him first
oh we'll try
good luck then
thanks cuckoo
here we go
we're up in the air beautiful
raccoon land
oh it's like hollywood but raccoon
wow eerie it doesn't feel that different
up here
it's like we got replaced by raccoons oh
[\h__\h] they're taking over guys we need to
take over before the raccoons take over
what
i already said i'm sorry you don't have
to rub it in
okay
you think this is all my fault i feel
bad but i cannot do what i did
bk here's a tip
you're feeling guilty
i don't blame you for everything that
raccoons do
this is getting really emotional until
you
get your tissues guys
you still want to be french
i i do and now kiss
but if you want to be friends with me
don't make your kills my problem
oh yeah and
wash my car
also give my dog a bath
and the heel titty
[Music]
it's that thing on the old observatory
hill wow kind of looks like a big
garbage can
i know cool right
i guess it makes sense trash king lives
there let's go for it
looks pretty cool yeah doesn't exactly
look like a trash can looks like some
sick architecture
oh it smells awful do you guys use like
reverse air refreshiness
oh sweet home
oh ello
you're so [\h__\h] cringe mirror
okay you should call the trash king now
try to convince him to help us fix
everything
are you kidding i can't call him it
would be extremely awkward
text him then i'm fine
[Laughter]
hey
i said quack
what
is this like beneath him or something
hey i'm talking to you
he's not fun he's not fun at all
he sucks tk
trash king hello
he's really slow
uh a new phone hold these
so slow
sorry no phone
quack
now baby no
oh man it's it's speaking
i work for you
i was wondering like uh is it possible
to
undo some of the holes and give people
their trance back
[Music]
okay never mind
no problem oh
no hey
hey hey hey what is he saying
it didn't work dude i think he's mad at
me he started typing though you didn't
need to wait until he's done typing
dang whoops you know what would be fun
boss fight boss fight
[Music]
okay
i think that is the best solution get
the hammer
get the hammer i want the hammer hey
i want that hammer
beautiful
okay got some of the good stuff
i don't know why that was outside but
okay
can we get the lights no oh
oh oh we tried oh well nothing else we
can do low
i can help
headquarters security system you can't
sneak a hole inside that way
how do we hack in
let's plug this into the security system
oh sweet usb stick we can use the
catapult
okay here goes nothing then
oh
let us in
wait where do i put it
to the like where the camera is
yeah oh
i feel like i'm playing nero tomato now
oh no didn't really want to see that but
is that that's not the king right
or is that one of his one of his
underlings one of his servants
oh
[Music]
can we go in here no okay
ooh
a trash king
golden statue
they built a whole kingdom here is this
a cult
we could learn something from them
perhaps
laboratory you do be sleeping though
yeah
nice
and now i can throw him i get all this
stuff
batteries and all that kind of stuff
nice what now
what do we do with this
do i need it in this room
coco did skydiver oh no where'd it go
did i pick it up again i think we're
leaving the room
maybe we weren't in the labs no we were
ah wait
oh not you
oh
maybe for the red room
cool this is like a dungeon guys
welcome to the biology level new
recruits the donut county was home to
many old screaming beasts nobody knows
why the animals were just outside it's
our job to figure out the purpose of
these nude creatures oh chess our top
raccoons extract the facts
oh snake
schnick yes yes and nobody knows why
snake was outside where were new ones
snake was outside i was in donut hole
get him
uh-huh
oh the snake tail again grab how do i
grab
wait oh
no what is this this is a puzzle
uh
ah it's a crane game
wait no uh i guess okay
take it i guess ah crap oh i don't know
why but i got this one this is not the
best price to be honest
i prefer something else the bird the
bird is better yes
take it
[Music]
very good frog is like the best price we
can get here froggo can hold on to stuff
quack
and frog yeah
what is this
what is it with the bunnies here
we need to free the bunnies as well
i'm gonna take that stuff grow a bit
bigger we need everything we can right
now okay
uh now with the frog we grab what
uh
i know what
we grab this thing here to free the
bunnies come on
you can do it frog yeah
[Music]
you're too weak
really then ah maybe the flies first
because frank likes flies yeah
smart
[Music]
i wouldn't really want to feast on the
fly there's much better food out there
like a kfc
wink
but
sure okay now what about now
no i know you can do one come on go get
him
do i need to help you by like sucking
you back in well didn't i do that
already
[Music]
we freed the bunnies
oh no oh no oh i should have seen that
coming
on it
zero days of other safety violence
should safety violations here no way not
a kfp
i don't panic
it's just a role call this is literally
very normal it turned on the emergency
lights because it's fun
please finish filling out your favorites
in the next five seconds
oh
over populating the planet with bunnies
and now we suck them in again
we need to become bigger again why did
we lose our bigness
we need the bunnies back
i need to become big again thank you
stop hopping around
and get into the hole
okay we need we need something
there you go you have exactly what i was
just looking for thank you
open up anthropology here i am
here i am with my
bunny clan bunny clan here we stand
i got my bunnies on the set we're gonna
take over this internet
believe it
before raccoons the people of donald
county produced a very wide variety of
trash we believe each piece of trash has
special significance our scientists
study this trash around the clock so
that we can learn to create our own
someday let's see what they're up to
setting trash on fire nice
donuts
yes
helmets safety helmets they're not
wearing the selfie safety elements take
a picture so we can uh report them
you must wear your safety helmet
god you got you got you
got you
haha
[Music]
and don't yes this will give me fire
won't it nice silent fire
oh [\h__\h]
nobody panic everything is fine
to whomever is driving this hole please
go away
no
no i will not i will not stop
until justice is done although i'm not
sure what to do
uh-huh uh-huh
oh [\h__\h] who are we shooting this again
oh we got water
oh
uh huh
[Music]
i'll drink it
okay
well this is disney it's all my brain
power man
what do we use that fire on
wait i'm not that smart wait
whoa
wait do i just do the same thing again i
feel like i'm missing something
[Music]
i don't know what do we do that what do
we do with that
what i need i need i need that
[Music]
yeah i need this i need to keep
no wait i need to keep it out there
maybe
yeah don't pick it don't pick it up and
then just wait another round to set it
on fire
okay
perhaps drink it
okay fire
wait
i need to like activate it
okay
get the water
she's watching me they could be stopping
me maybe somehow but nope they're just
watching
as i do my thing
okay and we said in the fire but where
do we where do we send it to
oh
okay
where where two though
here
home run
well
that concludes the tour attention the
whole driver meet me in my
this has kind of escalated more than i
thought it would
oh
trash king's office
donut
i think
you're not doing it this is a trap but i
want the donuts this feels like a trap
donut
why not come on
but i want it look at all the trash in
the background i see it the trash wall
[Music]
you can't drop a hole
this is very dramatic
now i'll call it
bk
oh please report to my office right now
i'm opening up direct access for you
alone bk we have urgent business
wouldn't it be funny if it's uh suddenly
from here on changes into like one of
those um
street fighter style fighting games and
then it's trash king versus bk and we
just do a fist fight
he said my name
are you sure you can handle him alone he
seems like he stinks
yeah he definitely stinks but i can
handle him
i thought about what you said earlier
this is my mess to clean up
it is but you can always call me for
backup
i appreciate it
wish me luck
you don't need it you're gonna kick butt
can't get it kick his [\h__\h] butt and i
need a fruit candy
already with all these voices
snap not good on my throat
fight to death let's go thanks dude
you can just probably go for the front
door and he like personally invited you
pickles
want the pickle
no i'm here to get you to reverse the
holes
bring everyone back
did you know you're the highest rated
whole driver in donut county
your famous bk
really
picture this dude full-time employee
status company stock
company will take care of everything for
you they'll even wipe your butt
i hate wiping my butt particularly kill
that's really um drastic but yes that's
gonna kill him
if you join me you'll get to play with
the real big boy toys
knocking quack
it has a cement cannon for tough
construction jobs
it's a pickup truck of quadcopters um
[Music]
i have one more thing to show you
follow me
he has a good argument
uh
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] do you have a
bazooka of course possum has a bazooka
or something that could blow up a bunch
of quadcopters
never mind maybe they're just here for
fun
um
they're they are um admiring our beauty
hurry up bk
oh [\h__\h]
come on bk
you're on the outside don't do anything
stupid now
that's where baby uh holds come from
sick
because those nerds in the whole damn
balloon are holding you back you gotta
learn to put yourself first
you're gonna reach in and take the
beetle
what if my hat gets stuck like yours
ah it's not stuck i could take it out
whenever
it's meant to inspire you
sign this
i'm still stuck he's still stuck though
oh wow
a branch manager
but i wanted to be dream manager not
branch manager
well
what about the health insurance
and of course a brand new god crop
all right
hand me the pen
or the pickle either even one of them is
fine
uh oh that sound
he's he's still on our side i believe it
he did it to
[\h__\h] him over with it i know it
not if we blow it up first
we're gonna use a hole
trust me
it's designed to destroy stuff
it [\h__\h] has hp oh
wait what do i like
try to okay escape it yeah
why am i supposed to take it in
and shoot it back at him maybe oh maybe
i can take that can i take that
oh [\h__\h] the small one the smaller the
small one
and then oh
forward
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
i don't even need to run and
like just do it
okay
[Music]
is
is he dead
do we kill him
thank you everybody but wait a second
think about it our friend
we we destroyed it
all without bk's help
i can't believe he abandoned us
he settled us out i'm not surprised
because it's your capitalist
well i'm gonna kick it and kick his butt
i'll fix this quadcopter and smash it
again
and frontward on the ground
it's not over yet
okay
it's back and it has a bazooka
not fair
[Music]
but your friend bk took the pickle
instead of the pen
it took the pickle instead of the pen
oh my god what the [\h__\h] idiot let
them know it's that
fun now well now we're in the pickle
sorry i'm late
i didn't take the pickles
[Music]
hold still i'm going to catapult you
right into the quadcopter
dodge the bazooka
okay
wait don't let me go don't let me get
blown down
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
we have to do it
i need to shoot something else not not
him
oh god
if i get hit again i'm gonna die
i couldn't even lose in the game like
this
he's still hacked
and now
now we take all the little pieces
oh i am whirlwind
this game really
surprised me
i'm [\h__\h] hurricane
oh oh i'm controlling it okay okay okay
destroy it all
i get it i get it oh my god
what a disaster
mix it up real nicely
achievement unlocked bus fight
beautiful
raccoon
you guys
ruined everything
i guess
raccoons just can't cut it in donut
county
i should probably go
find a
lonely island
and then
take all all the money from someone who
wants to visit and live in lonely island
and create an empire from that
and i shall call it animal crossing
because you will not cross this animal
more like you can't cut it dude
yeah well your company stinks
you ruined the neighborhood
i'll be good it's not about the company
think about all the innocent dragoons
that moved there
oh my god give me a break
the trophies we're running out of trash
we first came to donut county because
trash was plentiful
and now we have to keep opening up more
holes to get less and less trash
i was looking for out for us dude
no no you weren't
you weren't just looking out for
yourself
you didn't run out of trash you ran out
of people to steal from
what am i supposed to do
i have nothing now
bring everyone back
yeah all our stuff too
well i mean
[Music]
it's so much work though i'd have to
build a huge catapult
if you do it it will tell you how to get
your hand out of the pickle jar
really
nope
hello
[Music]
oh my god i think it's ready
okay everyone one at a time
let's get moving
oh thanks mira
and the bk stay out of trouble
ah this is like the the the thing that
uh piccolo senpai kinda pulled at me
uh and killed me with one day
before i don't know any of the voices
anymore [\h__\h]
before i go i have one request could you
please not kind of hold any stakes back
up there
i'll see what we can do
it's it's been well done
sorry again guys
it's okay wait forgive me around yeah
not you though okay
a job at our donut shop we're going to
clean i promise
[Music]
yeah i suppose i like that
but okay
[Music]
who can say if things will ever get back
to normal
things probably won't feel normal for a
while
[Music]
no matter we can sail and let the
bunnies flow
right uh well sorry for the mess
it's okay take care mira
[Music]
mira
i'm thinking
nice job blowing up that quadcopter lol
[\h__\h] broke my leg though
[Music]
you know i was thinking
i sure hope you don't mention anything
to the cops about my explosive business
they would probably be pretty shocked to
hear who destroyed the 405
and all the other stuff you guys blew up
you know
just saying as a friend
um okay
well thanks for editing us
later sucker
i got a joke for you guys
did you ever hear i don't wanna know
about the raccoon kissing the chicken
now i only ever heard the story about
the phoenix kissing the chimpkin
[Laughter]
no how does it go
dude i'm not gonna kiss your dirty
chicken
oh
that ain't no dirty chicken
well it's been real
oh yeah real waste of time
thanks for introducing me to this walk
though yeah look at him he's still so
big we raised a beautiful frog
[Music]
look
it's a cool frog it is a hella cool frog
amazing
pretty cool i guess it all worked out
don't know his voice anymore don't even
care anymore okay you can lose me now
hey guys now
stop by cat soup sometimes
sure
are you going to get rid of those bugs
i don't know
i feel like they're kind of a secret
ingredient now
that's why it's so disgusting your cat
soup
oh lol sweet you should throw some apple
cores and a fish bone in there
make a garbage still
wow good idea
oh no you
go away
i'm sorry i doubted you possum
don't worry i'll never trust him again
after all this
oh my god i'm kidding uh
[Music]
you know it's gonna take a long time for
me to forgive you guys you messed up
like every possible thing
i'm sorry coco
bk
i'm sorry too coco
you still want to go to the beach next
weekend
let's go to the beach beach
hell yeah
and last but not least
hey
mira
thanks for being
so cool to me
for showing me how to be good
and
for your patience
oh my god okay that's enough praise
i don't know maybe someday you'll make
it up to me after you do my laundry 400
years
praise me now
well okay after spending so much time
with you i decided you stinked only 75
percent as much as the trash king
you still need a bath though maybe with
lush bath bombs i bought a lot of them
today
you love my stink
i don't
i really don't
no
[\h__\h] sunday
would you do me the honor of pressing
the launch button
but then how are we gonna
if it happens immediately
oh we can now look like at the credits
oh we're we're in a quadcopter
[Applause]
yeah nice oh i got an achievement for
that let's
go cool can we go to the hot air balloon
[Music]
i saw you know when i was looking for
games i looked like uh at uh ohio
i looked at
amy's archive i can't go through that
um but i didn't like didn't see what was
gonna happen at the end
i only knew like roughly okay you you
are whole and you swallow some things
but i didn't think it would escalate so
quickly at the end
what happened i'll give the dog to the
bread come on
does some nice flips there holy [\h__\h]
i'm had a lot of fun with this too she
did didn't she
oh it's a long time ago though it was
like what 10 months ago when she played
it oh
ring the bell can i ring the bell
i want a doughnut please hello you but
not with the cockroaches
cookie buddy guy not gonna bother
i don't trust those donuts man
but that was wonderful
that was a lot of fun
yeah great game oh
i had fun that was a good short gale
thank you everybody for watching that
let me just check something really
quickly i i have to record um i have to
wake up pretty early and record whole
talk with uh jaguar
tomorrow
that's why this short this stream is
rather short
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah recording recording i'm so nervous
i have all the questions prepared and uh
i hope that
hope that you guys are gonna be happy
with what we're getting out of it i'm
just gonna
say right now that the speed quiz is uh
unfortunately canceled but that means
that we get to answer more um serious
questions instead of it
yeah yeah
i think i think jungle
jago is
too slow for the speed quiz
well that's okay i'm gonna have a lot of
questions yeah i've been i've been
denied the panzer question unfortunately
or like the whole the whole speed quiz
which is okay i have i have put in some
other questions and and i actually have
prepared clips as well
for yago to react to
so you will see the final product of
that on sunday and and and and and and
let me show you before y'all are leaving
i retweeted it on twitter but for
everyone who is not on twitter um very
important
um on friday
i will be
i wrote this on my schedule
uh what here you see
this is the stream that i couldn't
properly announce on my schedule just
yet but here it is i will be on the
official channel um on friday for this
stream this is the thumbnail um
um people think because of the tweet
that we're playing live shots no no no
that's right it's just the like the
supported by white schwarz it's like a
sponsor i guess and we're not playing
live stripes
but yeah i'm in an official stream again
on the official channel with botan
senpai and eof senpai and together with
them and aichan we're gonna
do some fun stuff and there will be
um
an announcement regarding the
it's like i think like what was it
six a.m or something
uh pst probably even shittier uh but
yeah um if you can also watch the
archive but uh i would recommend
watching the live thing it's probably
just like an hour or something i think
usually these aren't too long
yeah
i'm so happy to once again be on the
official channel to represent holy live
english uh i i
will do my best
this week is a little bit stressful um
but
good things will come out of it so
six am but i'll be there yeah i feel
like with with my streams for est and
psg if you watch my streams like all the
time then i probably
really made you live a healthy lifestyle
because i always make you guys um wake
up early
um
you must be used uh used used to it by
now no
you're probably used to it yeah yeah
take it easy take these days easy thank
you i will try as much as i can today i
was also uh
on physical therapy uh before the
before the stream uh so that's another
thing that i did today um
gunbot's potential thank you
i always missed the beginning
of my streams you gotta wake up earlier
wake up
what what do i always say kiki the key
for in the beginning of my streams it's
to wake you up
happy koreans yeah yes this stream isn't
a good time for uh s-e-a time zones
[Music]
yeah
i will wake up early okay
waiting for you guys i'll be waiting for
you let's hope it goes well last time i
was uh
on an official stream yeah the the
remember the the new year's stream i
don't know why but there were some
issues with my discord connection i
don't know why it was really weird
normally i don't have that and it's not
like it was like a golden hour a golden
time or something like that hope it
doesn't happen this time
wake me up before you go go
yes
uh
so wait tomorrow
we're i'm recording that and then i
think i'm playing zelda
am i
is that what's happening tomorrow let me
see my schedule
yeah robotory oh yes it's apparently
zelda mm-hmm i'm i feel like i'll
probably need to take a nap afterwards
if i got time holy [\h__\h]
i'm nervous
okay
the reason why we're pre-recording is
like there are a few reasons but one of
them is because i mean usually whole
talk is a japanese time 11 pm
and um
i i don't want to keep him up so long
you know i mean he might still be awake
during this time but having him
participate in a stream at 11 p.m
that usually goes on until after
midnight is a little bit rough i think
so
yeah we're we are uh uh doing it
beforehand and then i'll be broadcasting
it on sunday
yeah
okay
uh will this whole tech have stopped
this whole talk absolutely no i'll be
translating it anyway myself because
just because we decided to do it this
time this way um yeah no yeah um
i hope i hope i can do well i'm nervous
yeah
okay uh so i'll leave you guys with that
super chat reading i will do after the
zelda stream i suppose
um
yes
so
i will go now try to sleep as early as
possible and fix my sleep schedule
hopefully
impossible impossible
oh you're having your birthday today
happy birthday
unknown person
thank you
very happy birthday to you sorry for not
reading the super chats today i will
read them tomorrow okie dokie
thank you for the fun stream everybody
thank you
what am i gonna eat now
i gotta think
thank you for watching and in german we
say
bye bye
bye bye see you tomorrow at zelda
link's awakening bye-bye
[Music]
you