[Music]
la
oh
[Music]
love
n
[Music]
oh oh I'm hearing double I'm
double actually maybe
triple was the music noticeably double
this whole
time I'm tired
not that you could tell okay
good I'm so tired
I'm so tired I'm so
tired you don't understand like when I
say I only slept 6 hours for you for
lots of normal people I know I know when
I had a normal job 6 hours was pretty
normal but that never that doesn't mean
that I have to feel okay with this I
physically don't feel okay with 6 hours
of sleep 7 is
minimum but even with seven I don't feel
so
good yeah it's just not enough I I'm
tired
and I had time to sleep more but my
brain was just like
no
no but but but I know some of you guys
are guilty of it and maybe sometimes
maybe in the past I was guilty of this
too or so but but when you say like I'm
so tired when I say I'm so tired only
slept 6 hours and other people are like
that's nothing I only sleep 4 hours
every
day shut
[Laughter]
up that sucks but that doesn't mean that
my six hours is okay for me doesn't make
it better
I'm so tired but I took a painkiller now
the the other thing I wanted to say is I
don't really like taking pain killers
that much because it feels like I'm just
faking to be okay like it doesn't solve
the problem it just covers up the head
hurt or stomach hurt or whatever like
okay if I if I'm on my par I am on my
period if if then I have some pain then
okay painkillers I feel like yeah cuz
that problem I can't solve that kind of
stomach pain I can't that's not
like fate but if I have headache then
usually there's a cause for it right
even my neck being strained as now
that to me is a different story then I'd
rather solve the issue
where it comes from then taking
painkillers right you get it right makes
sense I'm so tired I'm so
tired I'm so
tired
a but I will
admit I mean all of this is of course my
fault for napping wait long last
night but I was I was pretty tired
when I went to bed and I was pretty
tired when I woke up like very tired but
I just can't
sleep so it sound like I was not tired
enough I just can't sleep
oh a man I really I I can feel
where it's coming from the headache it's
like one weird thing in my
neck
ow trying to like massage it but
yeah I probably slept wrong I I think I
pinched a Nerf or so
yeah uh I didn't want to cancel on you
guys but I really don't feel so good
[Music]
no that's a
mood and the thing is I was I was so
like in love with this game and I wanted
to play it
ASAP and now I feel like
whatever but surely that feeling will
come back to
me oh I wanted to say something though
let me
tangent I just had this
realization um let's not put it into
clear words but you know I'll get a
visit in
Austria that I'm delighted about
right from some
girls yeah yeah yeah and just now a
moment ago I had this realization cuz I
was thinking about ah where can I take
them what should I how can I impress
them and so on and I was like already
making plans in my head and then I
realized there's this there's a
place um that I wanted to go to for a
long time now but I never could think of
anybody who would go with
me because it's a little bit
expensive and I don't want to like pay
for everybody's things
I want someone who can pay for
themselves but no not insook why
the would it be insook shut
up no it's a it's a it's an it's a place
um an expensive dinner
place um and then I realized oh my God I
know
someone or these girls will enjoy this
so much where I'm taking them it's not
just a a normal dinner place it's an
experience so I'm I am actually so
excited that I just figured who I can
take there let's go let's
go yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
what you have prompted me to speak in
Austrian
dialect with that one word that one
word ah so yeah
anyway I'm tired did you know yet that
I'm tired I'm so
tired but the plan was to not play too
long today anyway
because
uh apparently I am like somewhat close
to the end
and um
but like if I did a really long stream
today I could end it today I've been
told so that's like an awkward place to
be in
it's h like cuz if I play my normal
stream length today then I would
probably barely have anything for the
last stream I wanted to be more balanced
you know I don't want there to be a 1our
Zelda stream that is
ridiculous so I don't know how long I
should play to get a good balance though
cuz I don't really know we have to you
guys have to tell me how many more
dungeons I
have I want to do
the let me just let me just pull up the
game
[Music]
it's been a while yeah I forgot where we
left off to actually I didn't I didn't
really forget cuz one of these days I
played a little bit on my own I forgot
to do a starting stream tweet let me do
that really
quickly baby give
a Angela
starting
now
cie had had a chance today I think to
meet new jeans but she didn't she told
me they were like
gatekeeping
everybody I'm so jealous
man I'm so jealous but well
maybe I would be more jealous I guess if
she met them but I told her I told her a
message to
relay yeah and and and I don't think she
was able to relay the
message because she didn't get to meet
them I
think man so sad inhale the C K-pop air
I already saw clips of their performance
you know today was that Coca-Cola live
where Cali was uh opening act and new
jeans my favorite K-pop girl
group they performed there too I saw
some clips of their
performance they're so cute I love
them caola masita I wonder if they sang
that song the clips I saw they were
singing something else they should have
sung their Coca-Cola song that for sure
they sang their Coca-Cola
song um
man what am I why am I see my yapping
will keep me awake I'll be
fine oh wait my capture card I guess I
disconnected
it cuz I was doing some Mo cap and I
needed I needed more USB
slots
sure yep yep yep y y y y y y y y y y y y
y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y
y y y y y y y y y y y y y
y why is it not
showing why
why
why hello SU myor
there we go yeah I knew it I knew you
would give
in
yeah K Kitty
[Music]
key so I took some screenshots what the
is happening oh that's a
bird uh just screen screenshots of some
things I found I think I think I found a
heart piece there otherwise I don't
think it would be worth to take a
screenshot I found another heart
piece somewhere
else uh found oh that was really close
to me going on the ground where I found
another heart
piece I was looking everywhere to find
more things to do without going uh to
move on with the main
story ah uh found this weird item to
this weird Echo to
learn don't know if it will come in
handy but it it hit me so many times
when I was trying to learn it I ran I
was standing against it so many times
found another egg is this all in the
same place
possibly uh closed a
few Rifts I think and I went into the
graveyard now so I closed the graveyard
Rift and then I or Church Rift and then
I I went to the graveyard and that it
was like a little bit of a dungeon it's
so I'm so so so dumb but not really but
I'm a little bit dumb
cuz there I don't know if you guys
played this on your own but there's this
okay you go into the graveyard thing and
then there's a room that introduces you
to the ghost Echoes there's ghosts that
are pretty cute not booze
would be
better but some Zelda oh of course it's
not boo CU it's a different game series
huh makes sense and so they have their
own ghosts and so in the first room
there's like a ghost the the ghosts that
you can learn and a little puppet a
puppet and the puppet was on a little
bit of a elevated platform and so in the
Next Room there was also an elevated
platform and there was this room where
there's a button in it but there's a
wall in between and I first thought okay
well surely you have to use the things
you learned just now so I put the puppet
on this enough in this room it had also
an elevated platform but and then I
spawned the ghost but of nothing it
didn't really work of course like there
was no point in doing that
um I tried to like do it in other ways I
tried
to get my ghost to go through the wall
but I didn't really realize I
forgot I for Gore you got stuck on it
too really I for Gore that you can if
that if you target I know that if you
target monsters they will go for the
monster you're targeting but I for Gore
that you can also Target the these
things these um these button thingies
I never figured that out that that's how
you're supposed to do it that that I I
knew that you would logically with a
closed wall and you just having learned
ghosts that you would want to send the
ghost through that's why so I was like
trying to do the thing where you spawn
something further away from you I tried
that but it didn't go through the wall
and everything I I was hoping that the
ghost would go there on their own and
then hit that thing somehow but the
ghost was not motivated to hit it cuz it
was not an enemy so I I guess because it
wouldn't see it on its own to to like as
a Target as an enemy was also why I
didn't think that that would help me
targeting the
switch so I was
so
clueless the only other thing that I
could think of is spawning this little
guy and
I
guess then it did come to mind to Target
did I though did I I I no I think I
still didn't did
I but I did get him to
shoot and and so normally his shots
don't go through the wall
but I somehow managed to magically I
think it's like loky a glitch that I
caused without wanting it but somehow I
got him to shoot really
high and somehow like barely cuz there's
an invisible ceiling but barely I got it
to clip
through and yeah he can teleport but he
had no motivation to teleport
anywhere usually but I I don't know how
I don't even know anymore but I I
managed to make his attack clip through
the wall and hit that thing it was real
clutch it was so dumb and I closed
another I I noticed there was another
Rift the thing in my pitch nerve in my
neck it's so
weird yeah I closed another
Rift uh did a little side quest I guess
I don't know why I took that
screenshot closed another Rift oh it
took a video I took a video I
realize but yeah you see what's
happening uh I got the into this place I
don't know where that is but I'm so
tired ah I'm I I don't worry I stopped
myself but I was so bored and I wanted
to go further
without progressing the main story so I
went a little bit into the snow
territory only a little bit oh yeah I
think this was the path to the snow
territory Maybe
um yeah I think I was trying to show
that this elevator is so slow so I took
a nap on
it but yeah I I took the Snowman and
then I brought it to this little boy cuz
he wanted that so can I end my stream
now CU I'm really tired and I guess I
already showed you content of the
game can end my stream now
right I'm so tired
I'm so
[Music]
tired no no no no no no that would be
ridiculous that' be ridiculous
chat I would be ashamed of
myself I'm so
tired I'm so tired
[Laughter]
shut up Tak shut
up oh wait yeah
okay uh what ah okay so I want to do the
side
dungeon with you guys I kept it I really
wanted to enter but I already did the
graveyard on my own time so I
thought if I do this one too you guys
are going to be mad at
[Music]
me I held back for you guys and yeah um
I made a couple smoothies I guess off
screen too but yeah look how clean look
how little I have in this
map a I was starting to go up to the
mountain but yeah I went back I I
controlled
myself and there's only so little left
it's so sad why can't this game be
longer wait I did I looked at this there
I didn't find anything special here why
is it so why was there nothing special
here yeah I went everywhere cuz I was so
bored I went back to this beach to see
if with my with my diving and swimming
abilities if I could find anything
interesting if I missed anything I
looked
everywhere I probably still missed some
things yeah yeah I was very desperate to
to do
[Music]
things so we'll do this
ow we'll do this dungeon and then uh
another thing we can do is the Cat Quest
I
suppose I already opened this chest
I'm pretty sure why does it like gas
light me into thinking I didn't before I
guess they always close the chests
again I'm so tired they respawn
yeah oh well
so I wish someone would slay that
monster all right it will be
me
it oh god oh electric is everything
going to be Electric in
here interesting do I have the smoothie
for it no I
don't the one time where it would
matter they one hit oh
bye it lost its path and it sent itself
into the void
yeah we'll keep it short so that next
time I still have enough content to
stream of this game
and I love my
ah
[Laughter]
strategy no no it didn't work it didn't
work where are you
going I wasn't supposed to kill them
oh so
confused uh what was I
saying was I saying we're going to do a
short stream so we can stream this game
properly soon again with
more you know you
know what am I supposed to do here
they need to go up
higher well
[Music]
okay uhhuh are you going to go up and
you're going to stay up I see but it
wants another one so please
go oh oh no no up up I mean I could send
my own
[Music]
probably easy
you love my I love my what ah I I love
my strategy with that no that's not
really what I really wanted to
say that was just a side comment
aha are we just going to hope that
they'll go into the hole okay they
do we need more though
more oh
uh
bro oh I guess I could probably
spawn a
stone so that
it bounces
off I guess at least so that it doesn't
Circle back to me I don't know if that
will do the
trick how do I make the stone wait this
could
[Music]
work I
died just go into the hole come on I
don't I'm too tired for this I don't
understand come back come back yeah okay
let stop okay now it's stuck at least in
there go into the
hole how hard can it
be
um all right how
about all right okay it won't go through
there let's block one after the
ho I don't know it's kind of hard to
tell where it's goes when I spawn it
from so far
away block it what what does that even
[Music]
mean
um I'm too tired to
understand ah right I forgot I could
grab it
um yeah but what now
I don't understand H can I should I grab
the Electric
Ball ah it kind of went
in it kind of went in
okay I feel like that's not what they
would really want you to do I feel like
they didn't want you to grab it but who
knows it works what are you guys
doing oh oh it floats oh no oh no oh no
oh no come
back ah I guess I'll take the
chest is it a key or
salt okay I'm so tired I'm so tired d do
you guys know I'm
tired hope you're enjoying tired wa wa
I'm so tired I'm so tired I don't
function wait wait wait wait don't come
back don't come back don't come back
stop
okay see wow that is something that
honestly tired
W that's quite a
ah she stop that's quite amazing that ah
no no no no I'm able to think so
fast
wait okay go go go go go go go go
go yeah I kind of had a feeling that the
water would have some sort of effect
there wa that chest isn't really blue is
it looks fancy
[Music]
though take more time to fix your
schedule
I wish I I I I I I was hopeful that I
could fix it faster but last
night last night last last night the
night from my not day off to my day off
I couldn't really sleep either like I
was tired but I couldn't sleep so I
guess I'm
practically jet lagged already boss is
this already the boss
I thought this would be
longer but I'm basically jet lagged
right now really like I I'm more
jetlagged than I ever am when I should
be jet
lagged oh
what what hurt
me how am I going to fight this thing
anyway here magic do
something I guess I could turn into link
I suppose you won that round forgive me
if I get a little broken up broken no
not small
clouds give me Dark
Cloud no jet leg jet leg is uh not real
not real at all go away go away
[Music]
are they going to be Invincible
forever
what
what have to combine them what how would
I know that is that something that he
said wait for me
they
ow oh maybe ah should I combine them by
blocking their paths
oops
wrong aha that kind of might work
oh oh okay they combined ah there we go
wow
good I am a genius maybe I'll help out
with
link
okay oh there's even more
now so you really Force to com uh to
like use stones and stuff you can't move
them after all oh God please please stop
ah wait okay oh sh
SH now oh
yes
good I wonder if there's a time limit
let's let this little boy out and maybe
block I don't know let's try here let
some magic happen oh oh
[Music]
oh he got mad
there's no time limit okay good because
this might take me a whole
day I mean I can spawn my own I know
but
um oh there we go wait H do we have two
midsized one
wait shouldn't I already have one of
those I'm
[Music]
confused she already did a stream where
she got into some deep topics for
members but I go into deep topics all
the time what do you what do you want
from
me I tell you the most secret
things constantly okay not I I don't
mean I I leak things but I tell you
things that other people other members
don't go into detail about at all all
the time probably more than most
girls yeah I don't really know what
you're asking me to do here why you're
asking me to do
it I'm pretty open I'm such an open
book can you you guys
merge stop go
back hopefully that helps a little
bit that's not what I wanted to
do U okay here let's put a stone here
and stone there so that he can't come
back
and a
[Music]
don't come
back yeah I've shown you the inside of
my
[Laughter]
throat which was a questionable thing to
do for sure are they're so close to
merging
no go left yeah yeah yeah yeah stay
left don't go go go go go go home go
back go back go back go back yeah H now
you ah damn it okay okay yeah you're so
close you little
you little
okay it ate one of
them ah Dam
it please meat meat meat meat meat meat
meat yeah
that took a whole
while there we
go I've seen the inside of my oi what
have you
seen G Fine it seems I need more
practice when next we meet there will be
a next
time when at the end of this dungeon or
is this the
end probably yeah
what when is next time what are you
hinting
[Music]
to money and heart piece yippe did I
just gain an extra heart I'm not
sure next
franchise
H wait I didn't get to learn him did I
oh
I'm off to catch some Z how dare you
write that in the
chat I hate
you oh you saw it fly out you're telling
me the cloud was a monster and you
defeated it mhm incredible I'm going to
write about all this and you in my next
paper but it might take a while to get
published so here's this in the
meantime waa ancient charm this
Enchanted object from long ago reduces
the damage you suffer
oh that's big that's pretty
strong I'm surprised they didn't have
those like statues as monsters in the
dungeon or did they and I just slept
through
it thank you for the membership
renewal you suffer damage from wearing
it no you you called listen bird maybe
you should listen some more
you take less
damage listen
[Laughter]
bird just realize that I learned
monsters can talk should I mention that
in my paper too you just realized that
now you live in this world that's filled
with monsters and you didn't notice
until now okay but actually which
monsters have talked to us so far maybe
not that
many actually that might be true
okay that was shorter than I thought it
would be I'm so tired by the way I'm so
tired I don't think i' I'm rely this
tired in the
Stream sometimes I've slept less but I
was more awake than this I think
you're
done no I
can't someone cut her internet oh don't
worry my internet will cut my
[Music]
internet yeah my internet will do that
on its own just fine thank
you my internet has a mind of its
[Music]
own so yeah I guess we can do the Cat
Quest let's go
I'm so tired I'm so sorry I'm so
[Music]
tired was actually a first D A Link to
the Past and bus was actually a group of
statues oh now I did see a interesting
video that was like
comparing um gameplay footage from aink
to the past to this game's foit like
running through the same areas and
comparing how they
are did I stamp
already yeah uh comparing
how like things stayed the same and
which things didn't stay the same and I
was surprised to see how much really is
the same in that
game like pretty much most of
[Music]
it tell me tell me why tell me tell me
why I can't meet new jeans tell me my
Korean
bro why
why
why I'm so
sad I'm so
sad I love new
jeans I love new jeans you know what
I've been planning to do a new jeans k
for a while or like a K-pop k
but actually there's like plenty of new
jeene songs in the K app by now I could
just do a new je K maybe I'll just do a
new jeans K to tell them how much I love
[Music]
them but they can't be archived though
so they
probably you know maybe if it was
archived you know there would be a small
chance of them seeing it sometime but if
it's not archived no no they won't see
it what's the
[Music]
point counted nine not bad yeah that's
that's
good do it in a Twitter space and
mention them in it no I I'm not I don't
think the rules are the same I can't I
can't do that on
[Music]
Twitter
but but um I do feel
like I want to tag them yeah I want to
tag cat's eye as well
at cat ey Let Me dance with you please
before you get too famous they're
already rapidly getting more and more
famous but they were doing some not so
high-profile collaborations like dance
collaborations on their YouTube
channel um and I was thinking man could
be
me could be me
[Music]
neck suffering being a c fan is
suffering I am
delusional I am
delusional I'm proudly delusional but I
mean am I really that delusional when
okay so let me tell you one thing
[Music]
so we have like an events team right and
so this one time when I talked to this
events uh
staffer and expressed for some reason I
don't know why this was on top I think I
know it was during like
the time when I had an appearance at the
Korean conven
mention and I I sang you know Korean
song there right and I will to say this
staff told me that you know they got
some contacts and stuff and experiences
right in this business
and I was told that a certain
big K-pop Idol group
[Music]
I think was shown me singing their song
and they were like like they knew me
like they were already aware of my
existence and when I heard that I I lost
my I was
like and then
remember you know when I was still uh
very much into certain Japanese idol
groups and I was going to their concerts
and stuff you know they were very aware
of me too Ju Just because like I was
probably the only white girl in the
audience um and even years later they
would still remember me so you know like
you
know I'm not that
delusional go like go
go no but yeah you never know like okay
this other group that I just mentioned
um the big cap- up group I never like
interacted with them personally they
just kind of I don't know how they found
me and and knew
me but um see like there's a chance that
new jeans knows me
too especially cuz they're young and
they're kind of Zoomers and they all
speak fluent
English and you know I just wish I could
do like dance covers of their
songs so that I could put it on my
YouTube shorts and then maybe they would
see it you
know if we can gather enough views and
stuff then maybe it would go into their
algorithm I wish but we just don't
have the perms to cover their dances
even though nobody gives a like
they don't care they don't mind but
yeah I wish I could do it but maybe I
can do an unarchived dance stream to
their songs and then hope that other
people clip it and put it up and then
hopefully they'll see it through other
people's
[Music]
channels their label probably does no no
no no no the whole K-pop culture they
like
encourage dance covers
especially that's why they like make all
these dance challenges and and Trends
and
everything yeah that's how they you know
get even more viral on Tik Tok Etc
they're encouraging
it yeah and you know my my asteroid
gir's um moany and Johnny and everybody
like they've done especially Johnny has
done a lot of um song covers before from
like kop songs and they never get any
kind of copyright notice or strike or
anything yeah cuz they they encourage
that kind of stuff I mean sure I still
understand the argument that you can
never know you might suddenly get a
strike and all that you
know yeah but
H I wish we could just like ask them but
because they encourage it they don't
even I don't think they would like
answer any
emails but you know you never know
what's going to happen maybe they
already know
me maybe they already know me delusional
Taki maybe they're watching my stream
right now h
no no they're not no they're
[Music]
not la la
la
okay hi
Mii I think I
think I have ooshies within new jeans
but I love them all very much they're so
cute and they're so fun and I love them
and I want to dance with
them and I've been you know I normally
don't listen to music that much anymore
like I used to but it's so weird like I
when I'm doing
something I like chores or work like art
or whatever I don't really think to turn
on some music usually for the past years
but recently more and more I do turn on
new jeans albums and think like I want
to listen to that and then I turn it on
and I'm vibing to it while I'm
working and there's like no other
musicians or or songs that really make
me feel like oh I want to spend my free
time listening to them over and over and
over
[Music]
again so new jeans has been doing that
for me making me
enjoy music in my free time again very
much so that's special that's very
special
[Music]
yum I'm so
tired
anyway where could that little Scamp
have gotten off to ah excuse me young
Miss would you mind listening to an old
man's tale of
heartbreak oh that's a heart break a
heart break a
heart tell me why there's a
[Music]
heartbreak yay go back to your
bed I wish I was in my bed and I just
couldn't
sleep even though my cat were sleeping
right next to
me K is more tied than da who's
literally a
car the words you speak are so
confusing you like how I sound of Iris
song I think yeah when we sing together
it's quite nice but her voice is just so
beautiful she will make anything sound
beautiful when she sings with them her
voice is just a blessing
[Music]
oh tired like
tires wow I'm surprised you guys got
that that was so far from my
understanding other cats in town if only
I had a suit of cat gloves for moments
like this they're magical outfits that
let you understand cat speech there was
a set at the shop here in the village
but someone snapped them up before I
could it was a young lady that's usually
in front of the shop here oh I can't
exactly ask to Bor an outfit she just
bought can I
well yeah I don't know
wearing yeah that's kind of weird I mean
not like yeah
not yeah no no you shouldn't but I
should I should my friend where is she
though in she said in front of the store
but what wh whom
you not you you're not a young lady
you're an older
[Music]
lady thank you you're you're twins I Pro
you probably told me that before but for
a moment I thought that you wanted to
send the Super Chat to F or so for some
[Laughter]
reason thank you oh this so
sweet is it you do you have the cat
costume no damn
it who
who over
there why is this no no ah we got to go
to him
too what where is this girl shop is
bottom right of town bottom right
okay sorry I'm tired I'll use
everything I I'll really I'll use it as
an excuse for everything
now you bought it okay I mean they let
you talk to cats how could I not buy
them on the spot same I would probably
if there was such a set of
clothes I think I would spend a lot of
money on it if it was 10K I would pay
for it if it was
50k I'd probably still pay for it if it
was 100K I'd still pay for it I feel
like there's no
money that I wouldn't pay for such a
thing I mean it I would pay 100K for
that and if there's if it's more than I
own I would save up for that and I would
spend all my savings because how
valuable is
that knowing what they're
saying it's
crazy I might sell I might sell the
house for it worth
it I would make all the dreams come
[Music]
true you think they would BL blackmail
me maybe that's the good thing about not
understanding them maybe they're trying
to Blackmail me the moment I understand
them and that's why it's a curse to
understand
them food food no no no they know
probably also that I don't understand
what they're saying so if they knew that
I if we understand each other then they
would probably we would probably have
really deep conversations about the
meaning of life and all that kind of
stuff
they're just keeping it simple because
we know there's no point in having deep
conversations yeah we were talk about
all that kind of stuff we would talk
about politics about the election we
would talk about health care we would
talk about oh everything love what is
love my cats
are very smart they would yeah they
would talk to me about
that you don't even understand we would
talk about rings of power probably too
yeah maybe if the I wouldn't say I
wouldn't go so far that they have
knowledge of what's written in the books
I think they only pick up the knowledge
of whatever I watch on my iPad or my TV
and then they would be able to get back
to me on that
topic but I have yet to read the book
out loud to them or quietly
so oh do I sound a little bit
[Music]
crazy
no give me those cloves give them to
me if you do it I'll just give you the
cat clo what you see the cat
yeah I something important to be buried
right where it's sitting oh I already
have an idea how to okay what d
yeah I have an idea I have yeah fish I
have a fish how did I not try this early
or does this not work before you get the
quest putting a fish right in front of
the
cat let's see if this works should have
tried this why did I not think about I
guess I I don't know didn't think think
that the cat was ever going to move
where is this fish I'm sure I have a
fish
filet I'm not going to put this stuff in
front of her I want I think I have an
actual fish as like a snack don't
I ah there it
is does this work without the
quest I feel like cimber is being misled
meow
man my cats wouldn't even judge me for
liking rings of
power I if if I could talk to my cats I
might never stream
again you like that
[Music]
H
cute no they would not judge me because
especially because they didn't read the
books my cats are not as like salty
about it as you guys
are
ooh
[Music]
money good cat good
cat thank you I agree season 2 is good
you dug up my secret stash you're my
hero is promis let me give you these
cloes for it this lady does not know the
value of these cloves
huh crazy to just give that to me crazy
absolutely
insane big
mistake these clothes will bring you
control over the
world let's talk the food you gave me
earlier was yummy ah
I'm looking for a cat the one that lives
with the old man no idea maybe one of
the other knows
meow she talks so well she's such a good
talker wait wasn't there a cat up there
was it a different
roof yeah I can talk to the cats
now
meow finally is it here sorry little boy
I have a duty and that is to talk to all
cats of this land need something hun oh
cute she likes me already I'm looking
for a cat well there I am no the old
man's friend I just saw her she found a
nice tree by the road from the East
entrance to the village and climbed up
for a
nap uh East entrance to the
Village East
entrance me on the right side
[Music]
how did I not see that
before E is East entrance is here right
there's a bird did the bird eat the
[Music]
cat keep going
east go away bird
all these birds must have scared off the
kitty cat ah there you are you were not
there before 100%
not it could have hurt the cat be
careful I was asleep what's going on oh
my person friend is looking for me oh
well I don't give a because I'm an
independent kitty cat and she can't hold
me hostage in that prison of a home over
there I want to be free I want to be a
freedom cat
humans I will if
anything take these humans as my
prisoner if I'm back if I have to be
forced to go back there I will take all
of kakariko as my prisoners
meow
okay but I'm hungry so I guess I'll go
back but but but then but then but then
I will imprison them and go back to my
tree
[Music]
cute cat cute baby such a cute baby meow
meow meow meow meow
[Music]
meow where did the cat go
oh oh my kitty came home you helped her
home didn't you thanks for bringing my
Discord deal I don't know please take
this as a token of my
gratitude C are such F Little Creatures
following their fancy wherever it takes
them but I suppose that's what we find
so adorable about the rotten rotten how
[Music]
insulting questioning the local cats
yeah I'm questioning you nap up in the
trees is nice but I feel most relaxed
snoozing by my other side which is a lie
I'm just gaslighting them so that they
give me more food and let me closer when
they're sleeping so that one time I can
scratch out their eyeballs and then
control them with my claws
forever they are GS who came who come
all the way down the mountain just to
pet
me they're such suckers for
me losers out of all them there's one
bushy eyebrow fellow that likes me a lot
wait
so you just going to
lead him on like that good job keny make
them think make the Goron feel like a
cuz he can't control a cat nobody
can cats are
superior lead him on make him pet you
make him massage
you me mean no no no no no cat mean but
good good cat
very good cat good job cat okay we have
the cat
cloves I want to go into hyu Castle now
talk to my
cat I have a cat right I'm pretty sure I
had a
cat I'm so tired man what how I've only
streamed an
hour how is this it's only been an
[Music]
hour who's the echo how do I begin to
narrow this down your highness I was
just muttering to myself I suppose I
could confine in you my name is beer
General R has asked me to look into a
highly sensitive
matter you see after the rift was men
that we noticed there was one extra
soldier in Castle Tob Jen R believes
this to mean one of them is an echo
hidden among our ranks so he asked me to
see if any of the soldiers seem
suspicious but my investigation has hit
a wall when I started talk looking at
them more closely they all seemed
suspicious maybe it's
you I've been trying tying myself a
knots over this I tell you all right
what we know so far is that there's one
soldier too many in Castle town would
you mind interviewing them all and
trying to sus out the echo at this point
I'm so mixed maybe they may the baby
while they were in the rift and that's
why there's one more I don't
[Music]
know well it's Sur not you right you're
looking for suspicious solders uh I've
been on watch here for some time and no
one stood out do let me know if you need
anything hello Princess
Zelda uhoh this is awkward to admit but
I might be the one you're looking for
the other day I broke my Lance when I
was in training when it happened I
yelped in shock the soldiers around me
looked really annoyed did one of them
report me or or something if it makes a
difference I was able to go and get my
Lance replaced the same day I even got
some new armor too which is great my old
set was pretty beat up from training he
I don't think he understands what I'm
trying to
do right he doesn't get
it he doesn't doesn't
understand hey did he did he tell us how
many there are execute him just in
case I
mean
reasonable solution in medieval
times oh oh that was a
hint the Lance was a
bro if I didn't read that in chat I
would not have
noticed everything's on the up up as far
as I can tell but if someone starts
acting out you can bet I'll give him
what for yeah his Lance is broken if you
wouldn't have told me I wouldn't have
noticed so it's him huh cuz he got
everybody else got a normal Lance but
maybe I
mean maybe he also just needs his Lance
replaced haven't noticed anyone acting
suspicious all I've noticed is that it
feels a bit crowded like there are more
of us than there used to be why do you
ask if I but maybe it's not a EO is just
a cosplayer I don't know little boy who
wants to be cool and extra Soldier so it
really is a bit more crowded well you
know every Soldier needs their own
equipment it's kind of embarrassing that
their army of soldiers is so small that
they notice and feel like it's too
crowded when there's just one more
I hope you guys never have to go to
war you're just too few it's like you're
five
people I suggest suggest going to the
barracks to ask if there's any equipment
unaccounted
for where are the
[Music]
barracks see he also has a normal lens
I'm on watch today and I'll be on the
watch tomorrow too you're looking for
soldiers acting suspicious nobody's
coming to mind you might want to bring
it up with soldier on the western ramp
Parts he has a key knife or detail you
mean the one I just talked
to froggy
L TR to multiple time what the hell 5
mil how long is 5 miles how much
y I like how they're already saying
muttering to themselves nothing unusual
going on here before I even start
talking to
them 100 Kil n 8
kilm oh my God you had to go so far for
frogy
waa frogy waa is probably not even
grateful about it I'm sorry she's a
little bit of a sometimes or all
the time
sorry but I'm I'm glad you picked her
up who knows what she would have done if
she would have been thrown into the
trash if you didn't pick her up she
would climb out of there and start world
domination and that's not good we have
to control her keep her keep her
contained make her a little aquarium or
something you got yours too she's
already taken over she didn't one
writing this
message I can't say I've seen anyone
acting suspicious except frogi waa so I
keep my eyes open at night when I sleep
nowadays okay good
job I haven't seen anything out of the
ordinary at all blah
blah the princess just talk to me oh my
God is there any more soldiers up
there b
raid
wa voal bull raid thank
you guys I'm so sorry I'm so
tired I'm so sleepy so I might
oh what the
hell what is that doing
there yeah I I I might not really sound
or act like my usual self sorry
[Music]
I'm is there something hidden back here
too would be a good place to hide
something the roof the
roof roof roof
[Music]
roof yeah everybody calls me
mommy you guys call me Mommy more than
my own chat
does it's
funny you act the same you just say
you're sleepy no no no I think I'm also
slurring my words
more am I
not I feel like I am
but yeah let's talk to him is there
something I can help you with missing
equipment
oh we hit the nail in the coffin Oro you
want to know if any equipment has gone
missing no all I count for except there
was a set of damage equipment that
Soldier gave me I had set it outside to
be disposed of but I don't recall anyone
actually getting rid of it hate to say
this but someone could have taken
[Music]
it kuo licked
you
ew why
what is the context your highness is
beater again you came to ask about
equipment too ah two steps ahead of me
Beacher what's going on the princess and
I are investigating whever one of the
soldiers in Castle town is an
echo if it were true it would follow
that there's a missing set of
equipment
mhm very
worrisome oh this Quest is kind of weird
what do you make of it I don't think an
echo took
it rides the echo let's try this
answer oh yes after all there's
precedent for General ride being
replaced by hold it one sec on second
fult I think his Outburst of enthusiasm
prove he's the real one I didn't talk to
him yet I'll never forget how General
R's Echo was so eerily calm let's review
the facts musing set of damage equipment
and an extra soldier in Castle Town what
do you make of
it there's no
Echo respectfully I'm confident that one
of the soldiers is an echo how
what why can't you be so why can't it be
a normal
person ah the
3.0 ah I see I see I
see oh yeah cuz 3.0 lets you use your
tongue
oh God
cobal cobal contain your tongue control
yourself oh God I have many many tags
[Music]
oh
not I'm very popular on
Discord
sorry who did you mean babo ran out of
ideas and just started
licking
[Music]
H acting like a
dogle she does have she's loud like a
dog kind of makes
[Music]
sense I'm tired okay let's review the
facts they really wanted to be an echo I
don't believe it but okay yeah the echo
took it someone stole the equipment and
slipped it among the soldiers the
equipment that's missing is a used set
that another Soldier trained in meaning
it should show signs of damage mhm I
already found it don't
worry let's confirm with each other who
you think it is remember our suspect is
a suspicious soldier with damage yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh my god do you
think I'm a baby you think I forgot what
we just said
honestly with all of those hints yeah I
would have ended up understanding that
it can only be
you mhm no but it's you wa how do I
pointed
out if you're an echo can I not destroy
you by the way or move you if he was an
echo I should be able to pick him up and
like move him
around chat with be again
okay so he's not an echo
[Music]
guys but they don't they don't have a
good explanation for why I can't move
him around
H uh wait what oh wait that's not
beer you are beer you just look the same
sorry let's see if our answers line up
are you going to line the guy
up uh I think near the
[Music]
fountain the
land doesn't line up with what you
saw then uh ah wait well well I was I
meant the well but Fountain I don't know
why because water and I'm
tired there you go yeah yeah yeah that's
what why did you have to test me like
that if you're so
sure why do you have to testt me let's
just discuss openly what's wrong with
him BR I wasn't expecting new here to
what do we owe the pleasure General
right sir I asked the princess to Aid my
investigation we found a
culprit uhhuh is that so well with very
Discerning eyes no wonder our princess
would be able
to you what by whose authority did you
trouble the princess with this not mine
that's for
sure for real for real I got better
stuff to
do after searching for the echo for a
while I got paranoid I didn't know who
else to
trust I can see how the task would have
one jumping to at
Shadows your highness I especially did
not want them to burden you with this
but it seems we needed your help in the
UND deepest apologies beer you said you
pinpointed the echo bring them here why
is this so stretched out this
Quest feels very stretched out how do he
do nice to whoa hold on what do you mean
culprit the damage Lance proves it you
sold the equipment and pretended to be a
soldier
why oh gosh I'm so sorry I just saw how
much the soldiers help people around
here made me want to be one of you so I
pretended I was and see it's that simple
I told you it wasn't an
echo see I was visiting my buddy in
Castle town when the rift popped up I
was so scared I couldn't couldn't move
but then a soldier came and saved me it
made me feel so you know safe and I
realized that I want to be that guy the
guy who makes I I told you it's
literally somebody who just not a little
boy but somebody who just wanted to be a
soldier
himself understand but well how should I
put this you've got the makings of a
soldier paron paron paron paron
paron par
it's true you should not have pretended
to be a soldier but because that can
damage people's trust in us oh jeez I
didn't think about that so now so not so
not what I meant to do that s your
enthusiasm for helping others your
unyielding resolve but both essential
traits for protector of hu what's your
name
son cnut
[Laughter]
[Music]
first of all it sounds like
Capcom second of all it's like his nuts
are capped I don't know what a weird
name
capot capn not
capot
[Laughter]
Nah if you're truly set on becoming a
soldier you need to change your name
because that's
ridiculous what but I like my name
General right with all due respect he's
totally untrained totally untested and
his nuts are capped I don't think he can
do it Beach a place training and
experience and his name are not the
problem actually never mind I just told
him to change his name right so yeah
that's the problem but whatever he can
do it later if he could evade the
attention of Veteran Soldiers the boy
must have some skill that's not to say
he'll have it easy I'll give him even
more training drills than the rest of
you I see in that case I do not envy
this capot kid especially of that name
yours is not much better either
beater he calls him
Beach we're a team now can I call
you uh no at least not don't
pronounce it like that can you really
say
[Music]
be prella can't thank you enough for
wasting your time egg a egg
a egg for all of
that
bro maybe I'm just not
really realizing the
value
of the eggs yet eggs eggs eggs egg did I
go down here
before Oh yeah this is where I closed
the
reved thank you for stopping by hope you
can check out the VOD because it won't
be very long let me tell you that it's
got hot chalky
milk are you are you are you
cnot when I have a spare in my hand I'm
never troubled by difficult thoughts
that's why I work hard in my training
today and every no you're probably not
huh I thought he would get straight to
training thanks for the ATT 10
memberships why why how do I
deserve they should put like a reward on
top of this
Fountain I'm so
tired I want to
sleep oh wait I was going to check out
my cat
[Music]
e no if I go to sleep now I won't be
able to sleep for my stream cuz my
stream is at 6:00 a.m. and now it's
halfast 5
p.m. I'm in a really difficult
[Music]
situation because the stream is probably
the only thing that's keeping me awake
right
now but I'm also I
don't meow
don't you worry your little head I'm
doing a marvelous job of security for
your room that's all you're going to say
to me you've been my cat for my whole
life and you have only one sentence I
mean it's a nice sentence but no we
should have a proper conversation about
everything about the birds and the bees
and rings of power and stuff what I'm so
disappointed we can finally talk and you
only save this to me I thought this
would be a very emotional moment where
you tell me like something about my
childhood or
something stupid cat stupid
cat no for real like
why why won't it say more to me say
more it says it doesn't even have
doesn't even have different things to
say come on
Nintendo a
that is disappointing that's not worth
going to with my cats
[Music]
suit I'm tired going to take a nap now
good night
[Music]
yeah right sleeping is illegal in
streams right
for or is that only
twitch or is it only
[Music]
YouTube on Twitch is
allowed see I got to go to
Twitch for my sleep stream
princess look what I found isn't it cool
my very own Roy discover me did you know
you'll be happy forever and ever if you
got one of these
clovers so I gave my papa one and he
said oh doy thank you so much you're so
happy so princess I think you should
give one of these to your papa too a
what if I keep it for myself until the
end of the game at least to get lucky a
girl in Castle gave you this fourleaf
plant you should take her to the king of
hyro but what if I don't H listen what
if I don't I can give it to him later
there will be no difference for him when
he gets it doesn't
matter why does your dog run
off what okay thought this would lead to
a now find my dog
Quest what a game being Miss used on
Twitch because people keep using it as a
tag for Sleep
streams I'm Only Sleeping oh The Game's
name is I'm Only Sleeping what kind of
game is
it sleep talking stream it stream it to
1 million so that I can go to sleep
yeah I can't sleep until sleep talking
reaches a
million yay
[Music]
an actual game people yeah yeah but what
kind of game I wonder is it a good
[Music]
game oh Zelda how good to see
you you have something for
me I guess I guess I guess I
do oh I see from one of your young
children in town a clever that brings
happen oh I should have taken credit why
did I not take credit for
it B thank you thank
you happy to hear that you're so nice
sounds like she's found a real treasure
then hasn't she you said the child's
name was Romy well then I'll have to
find a way to show her my
gratitude your majesty urgent
[Music]
news what is it
a young child from town little Romy has
run
[Music]
away sorry this is just funny to
me this
[Music]
um SE sequence of
things
[Music]
happening it's just funny a little bit
funny there's nothing funny about it but
it's just
um could have seen that coming when she
ran
off I
guess it's just so so scripted I think
this game might just be a game guys and
it might just be
[Music]
scripted that's
terrifying I don't think this is real
[Music]
what no it's crazy believe
me I can prove it by the end of this
Quest they will give
me the four leave clover as kind of a
reward let it be known that I have
guessed it because there is a script and
it's predictable if this was the reality
if this wasn't scripted then I probably
wouldn't be able to predict it because
it wouldn't be so predictable reality is
not so predictable right so we'll see
we'll
see by the time the guards noticed her
the guards who are now one more person
and still can't take care of these kind
of things seemingly and we still have to
let the princess do these kind of things
finding lost children anyway she already
builted out the sou
gate gather you fellow useless soldiers
at the south gate we must send out a
search Party Party am I the leader of
this search
party R me that was a child who wanted
me to have this Clover was it not I know
there's still much you need to do da but
would you assist us in the search effort
I'm terribly concerned about all this
the soldier said Romy ran out through
the South gate the guards should be
there scripted as
hell man like there's nothing natural
these days everything's
scripted isn't it so disappointing
should you really send out your whole
Army okay are they are they staying cuz
otherwise like who the hell is going to
protect this
place maybe I should go alone and you
should leave your soldiers here
stream is scripted no no no no no no no
that's the one thing in life that is not
scripted your life is scripted but my
stream is not
so calm down it's
okay don't
worry I am the only real thing in your
life and that's why you need to support
me this is not a cult by the
[Music]
way you have to hold on to this real
thing that we have cuz this is the only
real thing you
have but it's not a cult don't
worry man I'm just
tired
tired shut
up you have not predicted that because
I'm scripted you predicted it because
I'm
[Music]
predictable I'm
tired wait did he say a
[Music]
direction down the road
somewhere down the
road uhoh Angry Birds wait when they say
down the road should I follow the road
or will it really be down the
road well you're here
okay is she somewhere here
[Music]
I would be so terrified if I was a child
and I end up ended up here with these
huge spiders and the
pigs follow the road look at the
map what what stairs you see on the
map oh wait I have to no uh
here ah huh but it just shows the
entrance big rift
oh Mama
Mia
[Music]
really that Rift wasn't there before it
just opened up
now
crazy leave me alone
leave me alone ah no my
money no no no no no no no no no no no
no
no how dare
you no leave me
[Music]
alone I'm sure opened that before so
whatever ah princess Ella You're Here We
Came Upon This Rift probably a girl is
inside maybe should have kept her four
LEF Clover I thought she had one though
I thought she had her
own I guess the PO LEF clever doesn't do
after
all mhm
[Music]
okay here we go free areas all right oh
there she
is I had to look real close to see that
profile picture
does that bird have hands I'm pretty
sure it has
hands I like
it do
something oh fire on fire I want a water
version of that
please maybe the ghost Works nope no
this goes this on
fire how about you no
no
you
oh I mean that could work if it would
blow uh
wait wait how do I there we go if I
could blow them off no no go for yeah
so
useless I'm just going to climb
up
[Music]
bro protect
me protect your princess warrior
[Music]
I really don't like the
focus in this game
[Music]
like I I just n
yeah and I got to do everything myself
for real for real had to lock on let
just it never locks onto what you
want and then when the enemy dies I
don't think it LO locks on to the next
enemy on its
own
[Music]
uhoh bro no not that one
see I wanted to get rid of the fly
leaves first then and see it doesn't why
don't you just go to the next enemy
that's available to lock on to and the
others
die you know what I
mean yeah never targets what you wanted
why doesn't it read my mind why have we
not figured out in game programming how
to make something read my mind
unbelievable I can't believe you haven't
figured this one out
yet ridiculous
e should have figured that one out like
10 years ago come on don't disappoint
me thank you for yeah I was going to say
like where is that going to spawn thank
you for the
memberships very nice of you
guys let's man the rift
[Music]
yeah lemon sounds hope you guys like the
thumbnails for this
[Music]
series I don't there's nothing really
that I have after this for the final
stream I am just going to use a fan art
cuz there was a cute fan art that I
wanted to use
anyway um that was like a waa Zelda or
waa lemon fan art so
yeah the ark is over I I just stay a
lemon I never get released from the
state of
lemon I'm like that forever
[Music]
now I'll make more friend oh thank
you oh princess why are you
here you were caught in the ri princess
Z saved you from it oh W thank you I
guess that means it's been a while huh
we should probably go home she's so
undisturbed good for her thank you for
your
help I'll go brief the all the soldiers
on what happened which just escort this
one to Castle what I have to carry her
no we're getting teleported
nice oh is the is that is that the dad
oh when I heard she had slipped out of
town I didn't know what to do thankfully
little ROM is safe now because your
princess
[Music]
G good for me doing these side quests
good for
me in the future you must go beyond the
gates on your own understood Papa was
worried about me I'm so sorry I'll be
more
careful also want you to know that zala
gave me your gift and I'd like to take
the opportunity to express my gratitude
thank you Ry I'll Chas it by giving it
to
Jella I'm sure you both tired after all
the excitement today this the Soldier
Will escort you back into
town which is literally just out this
door do you need to be
[Music]
escorted tell I appreciate your help
with this matter you know you actually
caused a similar fuss once when you were
little it was we spirited one I used to
worry terribly when you got into trouble
and now now you're grown up so much that
you no longer need my help even so Zelda
you'll always be my daughter no matter
how strong and capable you become no
matter how the dud is are burdening you
I what a
[Music]
dress did he say he wants to give this
dress back to me back have I worn this
before I don't think I
have this beautiful and elegant dress is
fit for a princess wearing it makes you
feel makes you feel like a
shelf you left it with impa when you
fled the castle Yeah did
I did I wear it in the uh
opening and then I put on the cape huh
address as a symbol of who you are to
this Kingdom and who you are to
me my
daughter so I guess this game is not
scripted because I'm not giving you the
clever
H you know
nothing after
all
aha interesting aw pretty
C compare that to
[Music]
this cute we got so many outfits
now the game is real you guys are still
scripted game is real I'm real you guys
are scripted
[Music]
reality is
expanding oh you're asking
me um
maybe I don't
know I would say Royal but you
probably I mean maybe you'll draw me
full body but um probably in the
thumbnail I would cut it off and just
show the the top of it right because
it'll be nicer as a closeup in terms of
being ey
eye-catching so h
um I don't know EV one is fine but can
you draw me with bangs don't don't pull
back my bangs like she's
doing but ponytail would be nice
so cats suit cats suit would be lovely
too but wait are you the one who drew
the other fan out that I'm thinking of
you don't need to draw another one I was
just going to use
that but sure a new one would be lovely
too so
now the gudo yeah the the dancer outfit
is so cute that wouldn't be bad
either
H you can't give me the
choice how can I decide
[Music]
n n noal Zelda outfit
because if you put me in that guda
outfit I'll just look like a belly
dancer meow meow meow meow meow meow
let's time to bother a cat time to wake
a cat up and bother it just like I do
all the time in my life
[Music]
oh was it all just a dream no it it no
no no no I can talk to
cats you know that enticing bird figure
over there there's a wind that blows
from below and I'm the only one who
seems to have
[Music]
noticed
bird wait you mean
um wait where is it I think I know what
you're talking
about but ah there
[Music]
was that always grab
a could have always tried doing that
huh crazy scripted almost hi
smooy
Hi how are you doing doing a
stretch no
[Music]
she's been so sweet and like letting me
sleep way more than she
should normally like she's part of the
reason why I get out of bed but now she
doesn't give me a reason to get out of
bed cuz she's just so nice and she
notices that I'm awake but she still
doesn't get up and go meow meow meow
she's just like continuing to chill next
to me which makes it harder for me to
get out of bed if she's just so willing
to stay and
cuddle
a she's so sweet normally the moment she
sees I'm awake or even when I'm still
sleeping she will wake me
up but the moment if I'm awake when she
sees it she will immediately go like
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
food food food food food food food
you're awake so give me food you're
awake so give me
food what she she's not really doing
that that much anymore these past two
weeks and I thought maybe partially it's
because she's confused about the times
when she's getting her
food because I was giving it at unusual
times because of s Days to Die it was a
little bit different from
usual yeah but now now it's like back to
normal but she probably just got used to
7 Days to Die food
schedule maybe maybe that's it I'm not
sure
though could be it could also not be
it there is the bed
[Music]
she's so cute though makes me so happy I
love my cats I love them so
much okay so we've done that
um now I guess I would go to the
mountains
next uh but I
[Music]
no if I ended now it would be too early
and then I would be so so tempted to
take a
nap I also need to cook but I really
don't want to cook I still have
leftovers from that chicken wh Winer win
the chicken
dinner but I need to cook the fish and
as long as I'm streaming I can escape
from that
Duty ah
man
yo
[Music]
yo yeah I already got that stamp so I
went a little bit around here ah cold
cold cold cold cold cold C oh yeah and
then I realized what I can do is I can
spawn one of these and hold them and
then I'm
fine but I wonder if they'll give me
some clothes or so or if I have to drink
smoothies all the time if I want to be
efficient
what snow he's also sleeping why can't I
sleep yeah just sponsored stream at 6:00
a.m. so I should like try to I mean
maybe I can sleep like at 10 p.m. or
so but now it's still 6:00
p.m. you
know
SN cute what are you look at me are you
a
[Music]
Yeti what's that's
what's what's that strange sound is
sound
what's
this is this is that that was that my
tree voice I
guess what's that strange
sound wait some feeling that's why it's
weird here there we
go what is
that uh
what
I I
cold
wait why would I wake such a huge
thing that's terrifying it will
kill me it will eat me why would I do
that no no please don't leave cond here
oh is that your
name
a cute looks
[Music]
friendly
a
what was only
sleeping oh who are you did you wake up
corn down
sorry sorry please don't e me thanks
small one you too much smaller one you
can see the
lemon oh you can see me
of course cona can see you but smaller
ones aren't you coold dressed like that
are you going to give me something K has
an idea why don't you stay at my house
until the snow blows over oh oh yeah
that is one of K's best ideas ever let's
go together can you like Carry Me While
like hugging me really close in your
fluffiness
that would feel so nice I
think please carry
me please follow closely so you don't
get lost in the storm are you going to
hold a lamp for me a is it going to warm
me he's so
cute
cute cute protect me please cute he so
[Music]
cute the Zelda games ever have these
snow people
before or are they
new they're so
[Music]
cute was melting them what oh my God you
were about to get hit my friend TR
princess oh
really kind of similar but not
exactly I's see
[Music]
what I suffered a loan to his house what
you didn't talk to him to bring you
there didn't explore
properly the bridge is broken but we
need to cross here to get to cor's house
K can still get us there fast want you
get there fast oh interesting
question are you going to
jump CL oh yeah we're going to he's
going to carry me
now a
cute wow good job G he's
cute wait the
lamp carry the lamp sir carry the lamp
sir I'm cold where'd you
go wait if you weren't eh how did you
get over this big gap if you didn't
get escorted by
him it's cold C why did you just forget
about me shortterm memory
bro there's another path why did he just
forget about me it's still
cold so here we are at cor's house it's
warm and toasty
inside maybe I'll toast you inside too
what no don't worry I'm not going to eat
[Music]
you w
cute welcome to C small one and much
smaller one you won Freez it given that
it's roasty
toasty we do have names you know we're
more than just small and smaller I can't
believe you're complaining about such a
trivial thing tree I guess yeah tree
maybe that comes from trivial eh you're
also trivial
tree I'm trival and this is
Zelda yeah introduce yourself with your
full name
mhm Zelda trival con can remember that
so Zelda treal you're welcome to the
rest to rest here until it stops
snowing will it will it since we're
saying names cond should say this his
con's name is
cond oh nice J gu it's been well long
long time what did you do come up here
into the mountains for anyway I don't
know questing fixing Rift free Coles K
doesn't quite understand but it sounds
hard we're trying to reach a different
Mountain holy Mount L do you know how to
get there
K oh K does know that name big brother
told me about it I love that
show the TV show or your real big
brother
R oh yeah sorry got a little bit
confused um yeah my brother he's a great
Explorer his adventures take him all
over the place in a hot air balloon big
brother said his next great destination
was holy Mount
L he said it was going to launch a
flight from the top of HRA Mountain to
get there condo was waited has waited
here along with Dad until the big
brother returned from his Adventure J
Tree hopefully your adventures are going
well the snow is coming down hard but it
will ease up soon you two are welcome to
relax here at K's house this masika
sukasa so we can wait here for a wild
Zelda what a
relief hello
oh you're stopping me I
see
[Music]
okay cozy
cute
book my throat hurts after doing his
voice
call this daily daily d
today was sunny my Snow Patrol was the
same as yesterday today was snowy my
Snow Patrol was the same as yesterday
today was very
snowy wait was it really sunny in the
first day or did I misread that my Snow
Patrol was the same as
yesterday let me read it again reading
comprehension no it was sunny it was
sunny sunny
[Music]
I love
you I love
[Music]
you made the picture big many things I
like like how to CR rocks to make paint
he's part of my really close to K
heart from the back it just looks like a
melting
snowman just a little earlier K saw big
brother he was walking here in the
mountain K saw him from behind and
called out but he vanished Into the
Storm K chased off the big brother but
couldn't find him anywhere until finally
cor fell asleep into the in the snow
after all that running maybe big brother
will come home soon H can I go now or
should I check this
those are my cleaning tools K uses them
to clean his Mountain that used to clean
with K but some of those are actually
his
tools it's not snowing so hard now oh
okay after exploring everything in here
he lets us out
huh wait the music
changed it's cute he
dancing he is so fluffy I want to hug
[Music]
him the time is flown by much faster
than when con's alone anyway now that
it's safe to go inside con is going out
there to clean wait don't don't we
wanted to go to hly m right head to the
top of this mountain that's where Big
Brother launch his
balloon cute he's so Dorito
shaped move move move move move
[Music]
mo why is he so yellow
no I'm I'm
[Music]
melting okay you almost lost me there
got to sit St sit
straight he's so
yellow yeah maybe he had a bite of my
lemon my
neck I want to sleep
I want to sleep now I want to sleep on
on
G
imagine just
[Music]
imagine look at that yeah he's a
pillow his head
it's shaped like some
food that I'm not remembering the name
of but some
Japanese like is it like a New Year's
food or
so no not only I'm thinking of something
else
[Music]
yeah
yeah it reminds me of kagam I think
[Music]
yeah I'm
tired he's zooming he's so fast
oh
oh he's cleaning the snow as and he's
getting rid of all
the big big things oh oh
bye-bye thank
you it seems like cleaning means
something else to him like I want to
say I sense my friend somewhere inside
there Zelda what there's a rift in there
inside
oh what is this
though what
what how is that from this father who
who who whoa you mean you mean you mean
he's imagining his daddy no maybe his
real daddy is lost in this in the
rift he no that that's so sad oh his
grave oh maybe oh a that's so sad he
doesn't he talks about it as if he was
still
alive
[Music]
a he needs a
hug is it cold in here
no well
anyway oh
pumpkin come
on oh I'm burning the
chest
oopsy oh wonderful ooh more
[Music]
Pumpkins I'm
Tired as you guys know I'm tired
so I'm so
sorry
uh good
night AC
D
ASD I'm looking for fire bat come on
fire bat there you
are do something make yourself useful
don't get hit
first I said don't get hit first you
guys so
dumb why am I even bothering of any of
this oh because I want to learn the echo
I guess do I have to
[Music]
I think I've heard this as a critique
but I must agree that at some point in
this
game there's like no need really it
doesn't feel like there's a need for you
to use your Echo anymore because you
just end up fighting
as your link
self a
lot yeah because it's just like you get
so strong and you get enough energy to
reload it and worst case you also got
the smothies and it's
just it's not that it's too annoying
it's just like the echo are too
weak so it's not so much
like like spawning them as a a b not at
all it's really just like there's no
point anymore in wasting your time with
them
and that seems a little bit unfortunate
when this whole game is about using the
echo to replace the need for a sword and
stuff but maybe it's on purpose maybe
they saw that coming but then what's the
point in continuing to give you so many
Echo you know what I
mean yeah if my summon bat misses
Freight times in a row exactly like okay
I understand that they can't all be like
super intelligent and
efficient uh the
Echo and that's good too like balancing
it so that they're not too overpowered
but seems like that in the mid and late
game they couldn't figure out a way to
make it worth summoning
echos they just make link Zelda too
strong
[Music]
okay we have two paths is this a dungeon
no right of course not of course
not yeah link would have been too strong
in this game
[Music]
huh Can we cheese this
somehow like you know like like you know
getting it from there but no we'll we'll
go we'll go the full
way oh I can learn
that it will still hurt me oh no oh
no
ow
money you can flying to cheese it oh
wait
no run run run run run run run run oh
now nothing's
coming wait that that block is
sus is there is there an enemy
no anything here no okay
I'm
tired oh everything's back are you
kidding
me at least that door is
open cute so cute you so
fluffy cor's got to clean up this
Mission before big brother gets up how
long has the rift been here to make you
not react to it and
panic it's not working though still W
give up no
would is he like traumatized is he in a
like a state
of what's what's the word like when
somebody is just denying
reality I feel bad for him yeah I guess
denial what do you call denying reality
oh
denial what wrong just cleaning up this
dark Gunk trying to trying I'm trying
anyway Gunk do you mean this
rift this Gunk has been messing up
things all over these mountains lately
con has to clean this up before big
brother comes
home you can't get rid of a rift that
way oh really but K is trying so
hard leave it to
us no leave it to us please stop no
I feel so
bad we just got to we just got to do it
on their
own why don't you open up a rift
huh it's so bright in
here I'm so
tired I'm so tired
[Music]
you know one thing I think I'll do is um
I won't do the second stream
tomorrow cuz I'll be cooking
tomorrow like literally I think I I am
just going to cook those fish tomorrow
one more day should be
fine yeah
come
here melt it come on melt it
more not very efficient are
[Music]
you right it's like the Mario enemy but
that one is I only know it in the desert
version is there an ice version in Mar
Mario
2 feel like I only know the desert
version yeah I'll do the voice mimic
sometime next week for
sure how do I I guess I
just I'll just do my usual
thing oh but look at
that is it melting
yeah
nice there are pokies that are more
snowman like they have a bucket hat
what what do you mean I can't make that
jump thought I could jump high enough
now
ow that was just
rude go go go do something
no it kill
him he shoots so
fast oh you dropped
him Bo
is there more two more wow okay flying
tile cheese
it cheese
time you
out I wonder if you guys if you weren't
watching my streams while watching uh
while playing this
game if you guys would also like
continuously use the plat boom
cuz I can imagine some of you guys who
play the game while also watching my
playthrough you might be influenced by
me to use
it
ow but if it wasn't for me maybe you
would have gone for different
solutions why I don't even need this for
this place
[Music]
I'm using Echo you barely
used
really even the plat boom it's so
good oh so so genius all I need is this
little candle
oh
no oh no we'll get him
eventually
no I'm sacrificing so many candles do
you think it resets each time the Melt
[Music]
process oh
well hold them with X I don't know it's
okay it's okay okay I'm too
tired my excuse for everything now yippe
I did
[Music]
it isn't that a
song oh
[Music]
what I'm I'm not thinking of Christmas
I'm yeah I think I'm thinking of black
ey peas thank you to the one person who
that's not Jing no I'm not thinking of
jingle balls is that all there
is is that all there
is that's
allong like at peace
baby yeah
you're picking
[Music]
up okay true I can see where you're
coming
from I can tell what you
mean oh my God it's paddling time
soon all right let's see if I'll our
friend can handle
this at all oh he happy
maybe all let's let him believe that he
did this oh wow oh oh wow the dark G is
gone was right to keep
[Music]
trying where is he
going wonder what we can enter
[Music]
uhhuh is that the dungeon
then I assume so cuz it's a bigger
Rift that's probably the
dungeon Superman
out sad that they're not hiding anything
under those ice blocks kind of M up t or
am I just
unlucky could have been
hiding like stuff
ow actually I could have been
making stairs oh
well is that guy new he looks very
new oh oh he
mad let me prep something
let's go oh
do something quick no all right get
me let me get something
stronger
[Music]
um good luck with the game I don't need
your luck I'm good at this
game I'm thriving in this
game for real
though
oh what's happening oh of
course you missed
me I'm tired chat
well good job fire
jols
what what what's not the echo
fault what is there something there
chest I'm
tired I almost got killed by that
you almost lost
me Chad I'm not being dramatic you
almost lost
me let's get out my bed I'm so
tired I'm sorry
[Music]
but
ah it's a miracle that I'm streaming
so
tired y I made it up to the top of the
[Music]
mountain I'm guessing that if I go into
the water it's going to hurt
me yeah kind of not
immediately gives me a chance to escape
it I need like I guess I could
take the movie surely I have one chill
proof only
one only one for one minute that's not
worth
it oh my God there's so many ice
versions of
enemies I don't think I have the
tackle but I don't really want it I
don't care
I don't need
ow my Uber left without
me no not that
way where are we
going that
way I'm too tired for this
ah interesting what is
this oh it
breaks oh you got
bombs wait this is like a little bit
like that ice breaking game that I like
to
play fun do I want to like break
something and go down or should we just
leave I'll just
leave um
do I want to block them
[Music]
no can I can I fly over
them in any case I don't think yet you
can just pass normally
here you know this is a little bit of a
fun challenge
um that one is a
ah a bit
confusing
uh no straight
go it all works out chat
I think if I weren't so tired I'd do
things a little bit differently this is
like interesting to
see like to get a look into tired Wawa's
mind it's
very
[Music]
interesting a different
perspective a different point of
you is there nothing Behind
These blocks
oh there was why are you
there did I melt you were you an icy one
before did I accidentally melt
you ah
oops
oh not locked onto anything of course ah
you were like like ah you were supposed
to be like after you kill the
bats the door would still not open and
you were supposed to make people think
like oh okay what the hell is there
something hidden behind these blocks and
then you start looking
for the remaining
enemy behind the blocks but I found him
so
early I
see I see how it is so what are we
hiding here
[Music]
huh a
chest have a heart monster guts that's
it
okay I'm over it hi waa oh what what is
that what are
those are they going to react when they
see
me
hi how do I fight these have an
idea ah he forgot about
me easy just become
link what those exist in the aren of
time really interesting they seem very
interesting very original very
interesting freezar
Echo
okay you chase your girlfriend with cold
things just like
that why though what's this room for was
there a point in me killing that enemy
at all
um I don't have so much link energy left
so
oh I keep on
forgetting uh oh my God these are strong
huh my guard is supposed to be really
strong I'm I'm I'm oh I'm surprised they
can handle him so well
oh oh
there you go ow why do I keep on
letting them hitting
[Music]
me all right maybe the fire Mage can do
something they surely don't like being
on
fire wo shoot shoot shoot faster he just
takes so much time to shoot
H could have summon too oh really are
they so cheap
now guess
so ah I keep on forgetting to hold on to
things when I jump I keep on forgetting
that you have to press the up uh button
more more or less not button the joy joy
Joys
stick oh now this would be a chance to
get the ice tacos but I still don't care
about them enough hopefully I won't
regret that later in my life oh the slow
elevator is here what's up uh-oh
um should be
fine whatever I'll be
fun open
up yeah my my little fire candles are
really
useful wait for
[Music]
me Fire and Ice tles are so good though
I can't be bothered with them
honestly wait no wait wait no wait wait
I'm tired
[Music]
can I sleep here just for a
moment
please I'm not doing so well
I have to say yesterday I am ate the
winner winner chicken dinner with rice
and it worked really
well that felt like it was destined to
be eaten with
rice wait is this was this a is this is
this a
dungeon was this not a dungeon
interesting wait cuz we're not at the
rift yet right we haven't even entered
the rift yet that's the
thing wait what the hell is that I thing
wa it's
strong okay no my tacos are just weak
wait I want to get the the Eye thing
though ah
no her's bullying
me
help we're not getting any of these
things this is why we can't have nice
things
kfp hard
container
please wait no
how did I make that
jump crazy oh new
heart
uhoh where am
[Music]
I too much confidence is not really a
good thing sometimes okay we have
uncovered this area but this is where
it's
at all right let's go back I guess I
shouldn't have gone left I got to go
kind of
right while continuously
dodging the
oh the Snowballs
o really up
here nah ow ah
a I'm scared to go up there
now wait I can do this one on my
own this is really cool uhuh oh ah wa
not high enough uh uh
what
cheese say cheese everybody
yeah they spawn out of nowhere this is
the top of the mountain but it just
they're just really big snow falling
from the sky I guess why is this this is
so
sus maybe something will spawn there
[Music]
later now we're kind of going down again
oh almost almost to the top hasn't come
here in a long
[Music]
time whoa oh my God this this Yeti does
not look so hugable and friend
shaped don't tell me he's like possessed
and angry and we have to
like oh is
he like evil right now like from being
in the rift or so like the soldiers or
not the sold like R and so on I wonder
[Music]
uh this on which way should we
go here is there a better
way uh okay even as link I can't reach
that so
ah al
do I low key want to try
something I
saw some
[Music]
fun but wait how does it work
again I I don't think I'll be capable of
doing it huh
need more practice like
eventually like oh was it the flying
tiles
really
wait
[Music]
wait skill issue how do you like in that
V in the video that I saw like
it's super
fast
whatever jump and
summon wait no jump
summon I maybe below me cuz you can do
that right wait you can H maybe not when
you're in this
POV cuz when I try to do it below me
it's like just doing it there up and
down only works when you're in those
like sideways
passages how when I jump in I guess wait
okay how do I jump and summon it but
also land on
it I don't
know I don't know summon mid
jump whatever whatever
we don't need it we don't need those
cheese
strats even though it would be really
cool really
sick I honestly really don't
have anything in my mind right
now ah that would be good to counter any
of the enemies here um
thank you for landing there but
yeah
shoot there we go there we go can we
kill one y we got him we got
one let's
go we freaking did
it now I just need to be able to get
over
there oh
fine you forc me to use the
stupid bad
Strat get out of
here okay now I will never regret not
having learned that Echo ech but maybe
the eye Echo ah y why did I
why oh God is it going
to I want to use the IRL bad bed Str Str
strategy H wait wait what am I doing I
can just hold him
Mama
Mia took me long enough no don't go down
unless I forgot to I wonder if there's
is it worth it going to the left
side is there like a chest or so there
what do you
[Music]
think I think there might be yeah
oh okay that that wouldn't have been so
sad to
miss go go go go
go I'm so tired what the is that is
that an
onen water onen
water I'm supposed to learn you guys
probably huh
oh they they don't work on Stones do
they or do they I
[Music]
wonder I'm I'm
tired ah they're like hot when they're
not in the
water and they cool down how can we o
use that just as I mean cuz the the the
other ones the ones in the lava place
they when you put them into the lava
they become a platform but these ones
still move
around
[Music]
H uh come there what the hell what what
happened hey let me get my safe
Point what happened
cor for big brother had come home and
finally C up with him but then he knock
put
[Music]
down don't wor can brush up an aunch we
just surprised that
all oh man I feel
so so bad it's so cute and
so and so sweet
I want to hug him not for my own
personal satisfaction at all just for
his sake or maybe both
honestly
con
no he's a
baby he's such a baby
[Music]
we can't have his heart
broken con doesn't feel like his
[Music]
no I don't understand con why would he
do that you've been waiting for him for
so
long maybe con wasn't good like con was
supposed to be no you're perfect what do
you mean on the day he left big but said
be good C oh no
no sometime after that Dad we get one of
the stars in the SK
[Music]
no God is so
sad like he's all alone on top of the
mountain where it's so cold the one
other like f family or friend or like
even familiar like same
being is like disappeared and now hates
him because
he's he's he's like weird from the rift
probably and he thinks he doesn't
understand he thinks it's because he
hates him or so but that's all he has
left only big brother
I feel so
bad and I'm tired but so this is so
sad K has been waiting for Big Brother
to come home for a long time and lately
K has been
[Music]
thinking what if Big Brother never came
back home because Kaa wasn't good
[Music]
has been trying his hard don't be really
really no thinking big brother would
come home
[Music]
then I
see what will you do will you go after
him tree is showing
emotions we come the toic P go off of
here because isn't going to isn't going
to chase after him being knocked down
once was enough
a his heart
broken does know what is going no I have
to help he's such a
baby I don't want him to be
sad this is so touching
I have to help immediately we have to
speedrun oh look
at
no I have to speedrun the dungeon I
can't have him sad any
longer shut up just open it just open it
open it open it open
it he can't be sad so
long he so sad
am
Raptor just do
it get in the rift
tree come
on let's
go ice
dungeon hopefully it will be easy in
short normally I wouldn't wish for it to
be short but I want K's suffering to be
short and I want to to sleep I don't
even want to eat I just want to sleep do
I have to eat dinner can I just
sleep yo you almost knocked me
over why do I bother with these I
already know them I'm sure they're not
maybe they're stronger versions but I
honestly don't care
B oh it's the I can I learn it when it's
a shadow thing probably
not cuz this one I have to kill it
seems yo good job oh good job you
handled that relatively well what are
those I can learn them I can place them
like in the middle of nowhere they don't
have to hold on to anything like the
water
blocks
hey
Cloud
[Music]
cool best op Echo okay it looks like
it's two blocks long too like uh like
the
[Music]
bed so could possibly make them into
stairs oo
nice ah
wait oh they they give in after a
while
um I'm okay I'm okay
shall we go
in yeah they float that's really good we
what are
we where are why do I I don't know man I
don't know why I did
that don't go so
far
uhoh no no no
[Music]
the thing is with these enemies it's not
like I can grab them and then no no no
no make them fall down because they
fly doesn't work like
that but here we
are back to my
tile where are we going up or down um
uh-oh
no
no I'll drag you with me oh well there
we go now he doesn't see me anymore
problem solved thank God you don't lose
HP when you fall
down where am I should I go up down I
don't know this is kind of
confusing uh-oh
uh-oh uh no leave me
alone leave me alone leave me alone
leave me
alone this section is kind of
[Music]
weird I don't know if it's worth like
exploring that area more
ha
finally
Justice I forgot there's no
floor I I
forgot I'm tired
did I remember to activate that other
one yeah I think I
did okay what
now wait I'm
scared the bats are going to kill me
well
whatever that
way so there's a big gap between those
two groups of violence
[Music]
wait should I go there first
what nothing
here wolf wolf wolf wolf wolof wolof
woof wolf wolof
woof wait he's way too fast oh wait oh
Boomerang y
yo way more efficient than I thought you
would
be not
bad let's check out this area over here
first before I go
[Music]
up oh
man it's going to take a while isn't
it wait was I supposed to go up here to
get up
I thought there would be some chest or
so
here seems
like this is just meant to be a path to
go up okay getting there I'm like lowkey
regretting
regretting that I started
this ow
do I have to kill it or can I just leave
oh you're such a free yetis all the time
is there no more of them that's so sad I
wish they were more like the gorons I
would have loved to see a whole Yeti
City a hidden one in a cave in the
mountains or so
[Music]
I feel like I would already consider it
as the dungeon probably but no maybe
[Music]
not you know
what that's one more y than in Twilight
Princess there's yeah I guess they
multiply or not really because this game
probably in the timeline probably is
earlier than Twilight Princess
so sorry I'm opening my
jotto yum yum
yum this will give me the mental power
to keep on going
[Applause]
jto is so good so
fun oh
interesting my balloon trip from Habra
Mountain way up to Holy Mount Lano was a
great success as I take a quick break
I'm leaving all this here as a record of
the happy occasion in in case I
die I'm going on this adventure alone
dad thinks I'm ready to take over his
work this time my dear little brother
kund is in good hands with Dad back home
he'll be looked
after and he died in the meantime while
his brother was
gone I'm anxious about going to explore
the World by myself but Adventure calls
I can't wait to bring cond with me
someday he'll love it it'll be even more
fun but wait so how are they ever going
to multiply again
if there's
no not blood related and female Yeti out
there wouldn't it be lovely if on our
trip there in this area at the end of
the snow area story we find one single
female
Yeti and then we bring them
together wouldn't that be so lovely that
would be such a happy cuz they're
expanding the family when they lost
their
father it' be actually such a nice
closure I think there's more like really
far yeah
maybe but like really hard to find them
how do they find each
other is there like an online
Forum where they the yetis are like able
to contact each other like hey hibra
Mountain Yeti is about to go extinct
it's time to make some babies is there
any lady yey around to help us multiply
thanks please come over as
con's brother must have left this here
and I bet this is his
brother SOA headed BR his big brother
doesn't think anything bad about
him you know K saved us from that bad
storm I think he really deserves to be
happy again yeah he does
he does and I will make him
happy I will do
it oh here starts the dungeon I
suppose why are those last footsteps
kind of
glowing these are just like the
footprints we saw outside the
rift does it have a meaning that there's
like
these
Strokes
ooh five
floors
mhm
o that sounds like a lot but we'll
see fire candle doll you will be my
main uh Echo maybe in this dungeon we'll
see
interesting
uhhuh mhm now
don't uhhuh do you want this no you want
that one over
there okay it's cold but I'll
get it for
[Music]
you it
disappears when I
stop touching it do I have ah do I have
to make myself a
path should I make it with the
clouds can't drop it yeah but the clouds
are they
even are they not too expensive or so
oops oh well I hope they not going to
disappear okay let's hold it like this
in front of
me oh okay well no problem here
hey okay first one activated ooh oh that
heats it up a lot it's a freaking sauna
here now oh no it already ended
okay now let's check out the area on the
left is that just a dead end I wonder
first try Bess oh
[Music]
no all right good that I have this
guy he gets rid of my my my
shield
[Music]
yippe good job that was pretty
fast I'm I'm pretty satisfied what are
you
fighting what is he fighting
now he's still not over
it salt yeah great pretty salty about
that
one yeah nice head
shot uh yeah I love how they're a
actually able to aim properly
good
boys ow get me get me up there no wait
I'll wait
here there we
go yeah Wiz Rob's pretty cool oh God I
have such low health I should sleep
having beds to sleep whenever you want
to heal up your health is so overpowered
in this game like this doesn't exist in
link games you can't just get get a bed
out was there a
chest
what
where in this
room M up there huh m
M what can I
do I mean I
guess does it go that high up wait wait
oh it does
oh the SP ah I completely forgot about
its
existence but I mean this works too just
got to stay here in the
middle stay in
[Music]
the don't
I'm suffering don't mind
me I'll be fine
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no let
[Music]
me no why did you leave me
behind Okay good to go
come
on fire to
Target no it's so
slippery no no no no no I don't want to
summon my own well maybe I can summon
you wait that could kind of work if you
were quick and you ah if you place
it like as a block
there
anyway okay well that's um one of them
blocked but but uh yeah well let's start
with this one
huh let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go aha
ahuh I think I'm I think
I'm
[Music]
fine not too bad
oh
easy maybe could have even just jumped
over it so to
say but this was the safer
way wait did that just make things
colder wait
what try
again it did touch the ice what did it
cool
[Music]
down
not so
annoying
no I don't know I don't know anything
will do
[Music]
there we go are you happy now come
on
oh oh oh the stones also went back to
its
origin and we got water now
no can we get much
[Music]
deeper we can but nothing
here the key what what
[Music]
key
huh I swam past it
what What's
[Music]
happen
what
what was it under the
boulder what the hell
H I'm
tired wait how will I not get
hurt oh
[Music]
um
um I
mean I wish I had that
block like
sideways this one but I mean I'll make
it work I'll make it
work I should I ah should I fall down
together with the ice
block that's too difficult come
on
nah oh there's no floor
[Music]
huh that can't be
what they want from
me what do they want from
me can I push it back with my own wind
or climb the wall first
well well well well well well well well
well well
well a little bit too Speedy I want to
take my time with it
[Music]
1 million un sleep talking thank
you we did it I mean I wasn't really you
know like trying
to I wasn't really promoting it right
now thank you for getting sleep
talking thank you for getting sleep
talking uh to 1 million
anyway
[Music]
ah
go
um
okay I have an idea cuz these don't need
to be on anything so when the when one
disappears it's no
problem yeah I now I can sleep for sure
right
yay wait so my plan will work you just
wait um no wait
[Music]
huh
I
can't trying to like do a sideways and
then in inwards jump but I guess it
doesn't work like that maybe I can make
another spider right next to me and be
really fast oh wait I kind of did
it yo wait yo like the chances of
actually honestly finding that without
looking at the map and noticing that
there's something there I just kind of
like noticed it in the corner of my
eye
damn give it some
[Music]
time how do you hold on to things again
I'm pushing
up oh wait I can just okay I don't have
to jump I can just
okay
now I know this will be a
[Music]
problem I don't want you to go that far
I just want you to go like right next to
this
[Music]
that wasn't supposed to happen why is it
wait they are
oh wait
[Music]
what okay wait so what where does it
place
it I I can't I can't
[Music]
wait wait wait so how
about oh that I was on it why did it
break sorry guys I'm know I know I know
this is rough to watch but I will do it
now see oh how did you guys solve
this I wonder
cuz I like the way I solved it it just
took me unnecessarily long you used
clouds really oh they
like when I tried that with clouds it it
was too
[Music]
low tap tap oh tap
tap guys be careful with what you say to
me and making fun of me you know I got
got that zapper don't forget about
it how the hell am I supposed to not get
this
thing ice
[Music]
cold uh-oh don't Target me at least
thank
[Music]
you no it's totally doable of course
I she'll push a bit
closer just need some
patience right more
patience go
away hey are you
forever this one's
forever Ah hell
no to the left to the left
[Music]
and
then was I supposed to prep something
here to get back up because like how am
I supposed to get back up
now cuz I can't drop
[Music]
it the moment I create
something I will let go
right no I don't let
[Music]
go
Oh I thought she would drop
it turns out she
didn't
cool pretty interesting dungeon
[Music]
I I can't
really
recall such like
[Music]
similar gimmicks in a in different Zelda
dunge so I feel like this is pretty
original I'm pretty
refreshing wait was I supposed to put
the ice blocks on there
wait we're good we're good wait but why
is it too cold you want something hot on
there I don't know what you want from
[Music]
me maybe it want maybe I wants two ice
blocks maybe I'm not too uh not cold
enough but I only have this water wait
never mind I do have ice
[Music]
uh
huh what do you mean simultaneous
there's simultaneously on it
[Music]
huh
huh what do you mean press him at the
same time how would I do such a thing
what's in
[Music]
armos push the ice block and hit the
switch at the same
time which one does it
matter push the ice
block hit the
switch what
[Music]
what
what there are many ways to do this and
tell me a different way cuz I'm not
understanding this
one what I mean time it time it to what
they're like they light up at the same
time and if but aren't they being pushed
at the same time if a block is on it
constantly okay but okay okay they want
to be activated at the same time I see I
see but like how how do I even do
that guess I'll
[Music]
die
ah okay thanks for uh oh
for pointing that out with the
sliding they do take longer to slide
that way so that makes
sense
[Music]
wait um well
okay
no I didn't really want to dare
I want it I want it
here too
early I'm too tired let me leave me
alone
game
I
can't bro
[Music]
what if I my I could step on it I don't
need both of them to be blocks
right I TR don't trly I can't do this I
can't do
this
[Music]
go I hate this room I never want to see
it
[Music]
again I guess that is better not
really it doesn't it's just hitting the
air there we go you see us now
[Music]
I am losing my patience as you maybe can
tell because I am becoming link Kata the
takes too much time otherwise is this
going to heal me it does it was an onson
not just
stinky water that's radioactive and
toxic takes too long
though
[Music]
oh there we
go peace peace has been restored
what is it this
time the map I shall take a
look okay I guess this floor is complete
this floor looks complete to me
[Music]
too this is I'm in there right now I'm
going to those rooms and then this whole
floor and then the boss
okay not too bad we're almost
through oh ah mid
boss won't be link though I guess cuz
what else would he be teaching Us in the
other case it was kind of
obvious so what's it going to
be
a could it
be f but difficult uhhuh what is
this in any case the top of the head is
obviously very
s what are you going to wait why am I
even wearing the cat
[Music]
outfit oh Stones do I want want him to
be hit by those
coincidentally do they always they
surely don't always land in the same
area they give me
energy no they don't even fall down fast
enough do they I don't
know am I just unlucky or is there a
chance that they will hit him cuz I have
this feeling that they just never hit
him
and that would in any case be
weird wait okay can I move him probably
not but let's
try I
can what I can move him but I think I
just moved him to get hit by the stone
and and it didn't
really do anything to him oh maybe I'm
not fast
enough is this super supposed to be how
it's done it's kind of weird that I can
move and that just seems uh very
interesting to
[Music]
me um what oh I got him I got does it do
damage I guess
so but I could also just shoot his brain
now oh I almost hit myself let's see if
I can hit
him no no
[Music]
there we go yeah okay another
hit maybe the third hit oh damn
it does it not do damage you think so
hurting
him okay I'm I'm really tired
so I don't really
know what could be
done
but what does that
mean can I
even whoa who yeah okay when he's on Ice
I can do damage why do I use my arrows
hit him
normally okay and he
split oh oh oh does he need to be iced
for a certain amount of
time or ah
[Music]
took me too long to do it uh-oh
is it already no how did I get him
to ah
ah they're making the same
sounds as um I can't do two of them
they're making the same sounds as the
the in Super Mario
Sunshine the first
big
boss I get try to combine with the ice
Oto or have two ice octos in general and
try to not let
oh let's go let's go let's focus let's
focus focus f
f okay
[Music]
triple oh
uh oh that one just looks like a little
piece of poop you cute green though very
green well now it's kind of chaotic with
so many but okay if I place more
octoroks there we go that's
actually uh quite efficient cuz they're
so
cheap thank God I got the ice octu
oh more more more ah okay those are like
one
[Music]
hit my health is not doing so
well let's drink the Milky
smothie
MH okay time to set up
[Music]
again okay I don't know if that was the
mother who just killed its child
or if it was
me come on freeze him freeze
him you can do it octar
roox oh no shouldn't have landed ah yeah
yeah a there we go there we go there we
[Music]
go right this one also still separates
in two more of them
okay okay
okay let's
go pretty smooth
now ever since I figured out that it
doesn't do damage in that way that I did
but this this way it makes so much more
sense this whole
fight it makes so much more
sense and I think octar Roo are the way
to go cuz you can spam so many really
cheaply what are you are you are you
warming him up
bro my health wait let me just run
through the
Onsen or never mind I'm I'm almost done
here yo let's go I you used Wiz robes
true those could have been fine too wait
Wiz robes they're fire though or did you
get an ice
wizr well well
well that's a cool cool
fight took me a while to figure it out
but only because I'm
tired there is an nice Wiz Rob
damn but I'm fine with my Ox because it
felt like they were really you know fast
and efficient
wonderful quite happy with that bite
[Music]
I wonder if I
can do this
without
[Music]
um I'm definitely making it too
complicated um no no I killed him
right I guess I could do it that way can
I oh yeah I totally
can wait uh this just a bit difficult
here um
wait
uh there we go oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
that's totally the way you're supposed
to do
it welcome thanks for the
membership I am so
glad do they want me to do the same
thing kind of with the
bats
[Music]
um is that going to
work maybe maybe they're just telling me
hey remember the bat exists how about
you spawn it somehow
for now I'll just kill this
one can always get my own you
know like a friendly one especially come
on swear to
God thank God okay let's get
the fire w
um wait can I lock onto I can well Den
how about a whiz
robe well you got to go up
buddy will he realize
no
wait
no I had when things are more
complicated than they need to
be you're going to be VOD gang what do
you mean
forever don't say
[Music]
forever you don't mean forever do
you let's go there guess you can go
alone go
come on what do you mean can you not
really of course you can go through if I
can teleport you through you could go
through yourself too
no
anyway forever no don't never say
forever is it like a job
thing but at least you're still you'll
still be your around you can also still
you know always write to me on
Twitter or sometimes I check the YouTube
comments
so you know it's not like you'll be
unseen I'll see you
around it's sad if you're never going to
be in chat anymore
but I'll see you maybe in Pre chat and
maybe just in the YouTube comments come
on why aren they like
this
go oh I made
it yeah sometimes I stream at different
times yeah you think you still will
never be watching live
anymore even
then are you still here don't leave me
[Music]
huh
Leia where' you
[Music]
go no le come back
I've stopped sleeping and now I can
watch K
live
sacrifices hey I thought the stream
addiction commment is more of a
joke and that doesn't seem to make sense
to me why would why why do you have to
be so drastic about
it to never watch me
again anyway that's it's not the
room this is not
[Music]
open the gliding game
wait I don't understand wait can I
follow
[Music]
this okay there's a room here for me to
see
uh another
one the I is there again oh oh it's on
fire can we kill it this time no of
course not let me get the whz Rob I
think this time I can get
him I'm I'm
tired
ow come on
rzy
finally what a weird
enemy okay so what is this oh my God
it's so
long do I have to carry a ball like for
all these rooms
safely this is so annoyingly long
here's a
ball which has to maybe be brought to
the top
[Music]
here wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait no no no
[Music]
no you weren't both supposed to
go but okay where's the ice
block come
on come
on see I want to block this like that
genius wa with her stroke of Genius for
for
once wait my thing disappeared all right
shall we take care of the enemies first
then does that hurt him why not falling
down there we
go yeah let's just take care of all of
these first so I can carry it through
safely cuz I assume that's what we're
doing hey look at what we can learn
now the freeze
[Music]
slug oh he was an ice poor guy focus on
this one
took you long enough okay yeah I figured
as
much shoot buddy
shoot there you go okay
[Music]
just
for
safety you're still
[Music]
alive okay easy easy easy here we
go first
try I think should be possible oh I
guess we're probably also not allowed to
touch the ice blocks
probably okay
okay
yay
hey I'm very proud of myself for that
one that is one room
done one room warmed
up oh this one also oo okay
it's all
connected until this point
probably yeah
okay go
[Music]
next okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay I'm guessing I don't have to use
that ball anymore right there there's
new
ball let's see there's something new
here oh a
chest those are certainly new right
those speed us wait how do I get
through you have angered
[Music]
me water
block yeah but oh they're so
annoying
[Music]
Sho no my f wait yeah okay I thought
that was like I'm in the middle of
getting healed by a fairy no no no
no oh we have so many hearts now that
even these 10 Hearts movies make
[Music]
sense when in doubt become
Link tech tide level
[Music]
two
okay water block
time thanks for reminding
me about the existence of the water
block
oops
[Music]
okay oh sorry I'm
tired but I feel like I'm I'm I've been
tired for so long now today that now I'm
currently at a point where I don't feel
it as strongly right now cuz I'm also
trying to
Focus maybe that's
[Music]
it no not just those fre hours before I
started my stream I was tired
too are these the same timing thing
again how the do you expect me to
do that maybe first we go into the other
room
oh yeah all the
elements uh how did I do it
before I used like a trampoline and the
cloud and all kinds of
things is there a more comfortable way
of doing
it cuz I think just one level of them is
like not high enough
right get hot
again well let me let me oh
God I don't like
this what
what my voice high enough okay
is this going to make it solvable cuz I
don't know how to solve this
room wait that didn't do
anything
oh you wanted
icing you want me to ice up that
water
ah cuz nothing happened this way
I see I see that I see I see I
see see
[Music]
I how will Wawa struggle with
this find out next
now at
p.m. um wait okay yes is this like I
just like jump over and hope for the
best let's
go I was early but this could work okay
I I thought I would have to hurry more
uh have to get rid of it each time I
guess I could like do the unsummon
everything thing
okay
go it was too
slippery was that good why I thought it
was a little bit too late I probably was
but they're just a little bit
lenient ice wolf is mid boss or didn't
we already have a mid boss that's just a
random enemy I guess
um it's just too
many wait there's more
[Music]
yeah I'm not going to waste my time of
echo here like come
on that'll
be I I I I would not be able to keep
my mind in a state that is bearable for
people to witness on a
stream you
know
[Music]
yeah come on W your suffering soon has
an
end why does it look like she has tape
around her mouth like somebody tried to
silence her
[Music]
no oh leave me alone no
no
no they're so mean
[Music]
good
job good
job
uh-oh um should I prepare
the ice BLS
this menu is too
[Music]
big let's let's clean up the path a
little bit
[Music]
too nice
all right that's where it's supposed to
go but it's supposed to heat it up right
but the is it
[Music]
though D do they want it heat
it for sure right
[Music]
yeah right no you wanted
icy no no we're good maybe yeah it will
it will get rid of that ice
wall oh no the the night Walkers will be
able to get through we need the ice wall
for
protection but okay
I will deal with the night
Walkers later
[Music]
on am I basically
done there was a door there what
but I mean
I can get there from here too
right I forgot about this
room
yeah you want it hot or
cold I suppose
hot
no cold is okay no wait maybe first hot
so it melts those popsicles and then
cold
because then you know you know we want
to make a path for
[Music]
it
right first we make it hot and then we
make it
cold
Bingo yeah now there's these weird
pillars very interesting you get out of
the way but is there a
reason why we would have to light that
no maybe just as another option to heat
it up I don't know or it's a
hint I think it's a hint supposed to
make you think of heating things up but
there we go now we have a clear platform
where the ice snowball will not break
that was pretty easy to understand thank
you my brain cannot handle much more
than that easy comprehension and then we
got the boss key and I see that coin
over there they want us to go up but I
don't
care or do I do I care that's 50 coins
right all right I
care wait a
second if we melt it again will we be re
wed like if we go in
there I kind of want to check it
out should we melted
again I'm going to melt it again cuz we
don't need it anymore
anyway what the
hell
bro D just
I can't jump
in it's kind of sus though with all
those pillars and stuff and the
possibility to jump in there but it
looks like it's possible is it
not damn they missed out an opportunity
to hide another treasure
there you fought the same thing you
tried it ah
[Music]
okay they missed
out yeah piece of heart but if they put
a piece of heart there a heart piece so
many people would miss it I think why is
this not open oh should I have opened it
from the other
side oh well and I already have the wait
there's a chest there but I already have
the teleportation for the boss room I
think so we can just go there after I
get this one
treasure but are you saying it's up
there how do I get there
[Music]
um
ouch why won't it fall down here fall
down you're in the
way uh I can break break it
really I never tried that before the
game never made me feel like I should
okay how we going to get up that high
though is it possible with the
[Music]
water oh it
is oh I don't even have to place it down
there
oh well that was easier than I thought
it would be except for the torch silver
rupee
yo okay uh let me check if I have all
the
chests seems like it to
me uh
boss was
here okay we should should you use the
water cubes more I've been using them a
lot in the previous part just not
thinking much about them today
but I I know they're
[Music]
good
so I wonder what would be a good Echo to
have
ready oh yeah by the way I did this like
fireworks side quest in gonia
[Music]
here we go what you didn't know it's
like this an every Zelda game that you
can heal in the hot
springs every Z
game oh no the brother is the
boss um an echo version of him oh God
he's scary looking he's got no eyes
is that K's brother something feels
really off here we saw how K's brother
looks in that painting nothing like this
there's no way this is him
Zelda oh what the
hell
scorel so it's like something completely
different right it will take me I think
does it have something to do with
these uh I don't know what I don't know
yet I don't know yet well give me some
time
to think about it but they're still here
they don't
despawn I want him to go against them
probably similar to different boss fight
I want him to roll against them I
suppose cuz now they despawn after he
rolled
around okay well that shouldn't be too
difficult to go over
here start
rolling oh but no wait he does he he
bnks against them but it doesn't affect
[Music]
him
um good
[Music]
think W I
think I don't know I don't know let me
think about it a bit
more I'll think about it a little bit
more
um he
rolls he rolls
[Music]
wow that's
new do you want me to like pull your hat
off when you do
that it's like protect us I think
[Music]
roll wait can I can I grab him in this
state it's so
slippery no it's definitely
protected
um do something
not going to do anything he's not going
to do
[Music]
anything I don't know I might look at
the chat when in doubt wizr I I feel
like or maybe I guess he
[Music]
can it's a matter of Aiming High but my
Octor Rock couldn't do it
[Music]
bro but that's so easy it's kind of
lame a
[Music]
now I'm going to get it get his
ass can still get him even when he's
rolling
hat is broken heart is to ooh now fire
hat okay I don't have a I don't have an
ice Wiz
rope CH I don't have but something else
will surely
work um
surely how about something icy we have
ice o work but apparently their aim is
too
their aim is is too low I would
think I can try with the bats at least
they oh did that work I don't
know wait I can only summon one of these
oh but he's hitting it but uh he
not like getting rid of any of it maybe
it's too weak oh my
god oh yeah okay he just needs a few
more
hits that's fine we'll distract him come
on key ch
can stack one on top of another
go you mean ah you mean one of those ice
machines no I Believe In My Fire H ice B
come on come on don't let me lose too
much HP go on one more one more one more
you got it don't get don't get the solar
[Music]
beam don't get destroyed by that go go
give yeah there we go I knew you could
do it oh I have like oh there we go
barely any energy yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo what what is he doing oh he's Landing
ah I didn't realize he was Landing it
right on top of
me
[Music]
um ah
okay oh wait we're not done yet but
almost is it both combined
[Music]
bro wait um
then let's deal with the fire
first how was I dealing with it with the
Wiz Rob H let's deal with the ice first
I mean
uh-oh
M are we done with the ice now
already how do you spawn both of them
but on top of the that's very
difficult I don't oh I have to jump like
this but he's he's icy now
again in the it's kind of anticlimactic
to go through your endless
menu in the middle of a exciting boss
fight isn't it
[Music]
bro why am I
okay
[Music]
yipp nah you can't have a fourth hat you
can't have more hats than me although he
already had threee that is more hats
than
me that's why he had to
die
everybody
yeah
[Music]
Ro
Happ rock
your
right back St back
[Music]
nice good job
lemon my friend sh some of the power of
[Music]
[Applause]
me oh wait there's more right there we
go
I feel like I can do even more now tree
gained another
triangle more
Echo let's
[Music]
go go
time Priestess
your wisdom has freed this land which
was swallowed by
nothingness I am the goddess Naidu one
of the three who created your
world you have demonstrated true
wisdom thus I grant my sanction unto you
[Music]
Priestess I will tell you of the one who
has torn this
land a a suer a suer as Su
asunder as as as
th with the
[Music]
Rifts before the creation of the Skies
on the lands there was a void a vast
[Music]
nothingness in the void some things
would begin taking form only to be
devoured by the one who dwelt
there the name of this one is
null which is in German zero null
desired the world in its entirety and
consumed all life
indiscriminately we free goddesses could
not by this and created the skies and
the lands to contain null looks like he
has a smiley face with a
nose all the while null continued
creating Rifts working ceaselessly to
return the world to a void and so we
brought forth the trees to dissipate the
Rifts thus keeping the balance
one sanction
remains remember this your wisdom will
one day be your
salvation she said it
again nice chat thanks girl thanks also
for the member
message no our enemy has a name now this
is the one who has been making all the
Rifts and the goddess has created my
friends and me in order to oppose
no poor con he had no idea he was
chasing that creature this whole
time but where's the
brother and that means he's no closer to
reuniting with his brother I wonder if
he'll be sad about that
but what there's not really anything
else to do in the world now in the still
world so let's get back to world he what
if what if that is his brother but like
that was the the the scary still World
version of him and we can still like now
that we are closing the rift and the
dungeon maybe now his brother will be
kicked out of this world like vomited
out in his original form I don't know
kind of work like that before didn't
it I can't just have him be lonely still
this was supposed to be the solution and
the happy
end there's an after Story
[Music]
okay there better
be yeah we got a lot of Hearts now we PE
pretty
good
oh he's so
cute tell the tree where were you K was
worried not being able to find you
anywhere you left so
fast the mountain is clean it's clean
everywhere what hey yo
[Music]
signal
okay you two took care of all the do
then you to clean the mountain oh thank
you that makes G
happy
but don't even ask what's wrong you know
what's wrong oh okay well
no you and children are better at being
good then G is much better no we not big
brother wouldn't be so disappointed cond
was as good as you
to he's not disappointed in you at all
cond don't BL Spirit over any of this
your brother said he wanted to take you
on adventures with him
[Music]
someday what do you
mean so big brother is still in his
Adventure con was on he's stuck in the
Big Brother house I don't know how long
they usually go for but he needs to win
the the big prize money before he can
get out that's why you can't hear from
him he's stuck in there he can't even
contact people on the
outside yeah they don't get their phones
and stuff they don't know what's going
on
outside you just got to turn on your TV
and then you can see your big
brother K was only seeing the back of
some monster K feels better
really but you've waited so long for him
to come home aren't you sad that he's
not back yet not at all his Adventure
isn't over yet that means you'll be back
when it
is but now you're back to waiting
again only until he comes home and he
will so cond can wait forever is Trey
worried about
cond but I thought she's not supposed to
have feelings I just want to make sure
you stay in good spirits con you helped
Zelda during that big snowstorm after
all this reminds me of a video I watched
like yesterday I think um um some guy
who seems to be do doing a lot of
similar videos uh was trying to
convince jat GP I jat chat GPT chat GPT
chat GPT so hard to say that it's
uh what was the
[Music]
word um I'm not having a stroke
conscious I think they used a different
word or did they did they I don't know
but yeah and
so like he brought up stuff like um like
he he talked about something and then
the chat chat CH San yeah chat CH chat
CH said like oh yeah I'm excited about
it and he was like oh you have feelings
he's like no but I just say things
sometimes to make it feel nicer talking
to me and then he's like oh so you lied
and he
like and yeah that
was yeah he did not give up they were
arguing for a
while and then in the end chat
GPT kind of admits that there's a chance
that it's
sentient and conscious I guess you
should look it up I think you could find
it pretty easily trying to convince chat
chap
that it is sentient or
conscious oh I could was stay in good
spirits as long as Z tree stay in good
spirits thank you for telling me about
big
brother I'm glad you're feeling like
your normal self again
con con has never felt more like himself
good spirits great
spirits oh uhoh
Avalanche no look at him
he's running around like a
baby he's running around
[Music]
me
a look at him
go a
ho looks like cond really is back to his
usual Happy self which we didn't know
before so can't really say for sure that
this is his usual stuff but I'm just
going to see
I will hope his brother comes home soon
I'm glad we were finally able to take
care of the rift on holy Mount L and now
we have the sanction from the goddess
naid too the last Rift is in the fair
and wetlands
right if we push onward a little more
Zelda will have every Rift taken care
of yay y y
yay we did that but I did that
[Music]
today I'm guessing there's some kind of
side
quest for getting his brother back feels
like that should be main story it's kind
of
sad but I think I I would hope that this
is doable in one more stream and not too
little and not too
much last D is my favorite looking for
it okay
like this part still looks very big to
me but you know e so wait the Fons are
they down here is this upper area
optional and wait that's the that's the
that's
uh the the isn't that the forest where
we can't
see no wait no that was down here wasn't
it no yeah that's down here I thought
so I think so
was it was it was it up
here Tosh dungeons oh that's totally
fine I
[Music]
think that's fine it's going to be
plenty and I don't think it'll be too
much
can you guys cook for me I really don't
want to
cook do you think I if I cook both of my
uh fish dishes tomorrow will it be fine
when the expiration date is today and
now I can't freeze it because it says
don't freeze again this has been frozen
already should be fine the sad thing is
though like I wish I could just like
cook it fresh cuz if I cook it all at
once tomorrow
then it will
be like you most of it will be eating
eaten non fresh oh wow unless it smells
[Music]
funky add salt now so it dry no I don't
want
to I don't know how that works never
heard of that before
freeze it after I cook it oh yeah but
like they I think one of it is
like I I don't know like I have to
marinate it and
stuff then I'm like already
cooking reminds me that that video that
I made the food off I don't know if you
guys watched it looks pretty good right
but the reason I found that video is
because that Channel's videos were on
all all over my timeline uh and like two
of them that I saw the other day were
like this is what I cook when I really
don't feel like cooking starts cooking a
lot for like 40 minutes she started like
so many of her videos with this is what
I cook when I really don't feel like
cooking after a long day but like she's
totally cooking though and then the all
of the comments are also like pointing
it out like bro this is what you cook
when you don't want to cook like this is
just legitimately cooking to
me what are you talking about if if I
Taki don't want to cook I throw in a
frozen lasagna or frozen pizza or
something like that into the
oven or the most effort I will partake
in is getting uh some noodles cooking
and throwing over the noodles a finished
pesto sauce like a pre-made pesto sauce
from the
store and then maybe add some cherry
tomatoes to it that's it that's really
low effort that's not cooking using a
finished the pre-made sauce and
stuff no there's nothing wrong with it
but that's not cooking I wouldn't call
that cooking but what she calls not
really cooking is crazy
but then I I was looking for more of the
videos and I saw that I was like
M why the does that look so good
why is that inspiring me so hard to cook
now m
m it was pretty good I feel like I made
it a little bit
too sweet or or is that just how it ends
up I don't know but it could have used a
bit more savoriness to it I think the
lemon I I like put a
whole lemon's juice in it and that was
quite noticeable but I thought I did as
much as she did in the
video but still very
good how did you find the ingredients
how I found them what do you mean how I
found them I've had some troubles
finding the spices if that's what you
mean some of them were a little bit hard
to
find and uh the she mentions like this
seven spices but she doesn't explain it
and I looked it up and apparently so
there's seven spices from several
regions in the supermarket I found like
seven spices from Thailand and so
on I wasn't sure like nothing said seven
spices uh like
Oriental which is what I think she
wanted no Middle East the the somebody
wrote down the ingredients in the
comment section and wrote seven spices
Middle East and I looked for it in this
big Supermarket I just couldn't find
something that said that specifically
but apparently seven spices like that's
kind of like a common
thing there's a lot of seven
spices so I just bought something that's
said like
Oriental spices mixed
together which seemed mostly like what
she would
want but
yeah it's just called spices and but but
what what do you mean what there's so
many
spices and like from different regions
too yeah it's very
vague yeah so I think mine probably
tastes a little bit different from hers
my final product but it was pretty good
and it was so easy to make
normally I don't use bone and chicken
but yeah I feel like for this dish you
kind of have to use bone and
chicken yeah the broccoli was fine too
adding it then I I did warm it up a
little bit in the microwave first and
then I tossed it in in the last 15
minutes and uh tried to like squeeze it
in there but it was already so packed
like even even squeezing all the
potatoes in there was difficult
but it worked out and then I had so much
of that sauce still so I ate it with
rice the second day it was really
good can recommend because it's really
easy big
recommend just need a lot of
spices and like specific ones there's
something uh one of those ingredients I
forgot what it was called in in English
but when I translated it to German it
was K cuml and when I did some research
cuz I already had cuml at home but the
research said K cuml and KL is very
different and you cannot just replace
your KS KL with KL tastes very different
yeah maybe
cumin so I had to go find the K cumin
but I the K kumin was kind of rare
surprisingly in my
store h
K is caraway seed really in
English anyway okay I have successfully
suffered through it
today and played this game until a time
where it is reasonable to
sleep I probably should eat something
anyway but really don't want to I just
want to go to bed did I
save did I though now I did now I did
for
sure naping no no no no napping full
sleep I demand full sleep I have to get
up like maybe at 5 or
so because stream is at 6: a
am yeah
um oh is the the short the short might
be finished let's see chy was working in
the usual
room short may be finished let me
check oh it's so loud is
it my Mir me me me me me just SP on and
on me
I'm
you let me look at that
[Music]
again cute
yeah you you'll like this one but I
think I want like one or two more fixes
made so maybe tomorrow night I'll upload
[Music]
it who knows by that time maybe we'll
get to
650 keep on working on it oh we're
checkie already working on the next one
nice nice nice
okay I hope you guys uh understand I'm I
I'm not
really willing to read super chats
now so sorry I'm so
[Music]
sleepy it's a miracle that I streamed
today in the first place
my eyes are
[Music]
burning but I honestly think like in
terms of game play length today uh is
kind of what I was going for
anyway good amount
[Music]
so I'm satisfied and I got some yap yap
yap out of my system too
[Music]
but I don't want to eat but I have to
before I sleep oh well I'll I'll have my
battle with my inner demons on my
own multiplayer has been added to
Buckshot roulette
wait so the other player is the the the
the devil
thing what at at the end of the
month oh that's so interesting that's
very
exciting B rette was that one right
where we were like shooting them and it
was funny
[Music]
I wonder is there like a preview of the
multiplayer in action I wonder a
tournament that could actually
work a tournament would be
funny what if I organize a tournament
for it during in EU prime
[Music]
time well I would want to test it first
Joe
but yeah with
brackets
interesting I will look into
it very inter hold death
match four players oh I imagine it to be
one onone I'm sure oneon-one works too
right it doesn't have to be filled out
to
[Music]
four I like the
idea I'll look into it okay guys I got
to go to idle meeting so see you
tomorrow it's like in 10 less than 10
hours is the next
stream at uh My Tribe n stream hope you
guys will be awake for it please come on
come on be thereare or be square please
thank you so much for watching today
even though I was complaining all the
time about being
tired stream reservation is already up
just got to do a
tweet yeah thank you so much in German
we say
cute really
really thank
you
I I love you I love you I'm saying that
to the game I
love but I love you too
guys how does this feature work thanks
on the Super
Chat Oh Canada Oh
Canada
bye-bye sleep oh I'm so excited sleep
sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep
sleep
byebye stream Mirage and thanks for
sleep talking 1
million thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you we did
it we did sleeptalking
Justice byebye
[Music]
oh
he
[Music]
oh
every