[Music]
Hmm,
me, I
don't
[Music]
Hmm
yeah
[Music]
Me
with Mushu
[Music]
Hmm
me
ha
[Music]
Hmm,
yeah yeah
[Music]
Hmm
today
me
[Music]
Hmm
me
can you
DO
[Music]
Yeah
Huh,
Morny 2x,
and it's a Chocolate Chocolate.
Horo Live Marika is great. I'll
be participating in Small Fish High again this year. Hello, I'm Yuuko Melancholy.
Thank you very much.
So, let's do it again today. Shall I be
miserable? Yes, I
want to do my best to win the small fish range for the third time in a row.  No,
Sasaraenhakan
[Music]
Thank you for your support
Cheeks, oil soufflé
Axa Hmm, a little bit, I got it in town The
crown of the small fry range that I received last year or a year ago
Where has it gone?  I
thought about it, but I can't find it.Hmm, I can't find it.I don't know
what will happen this year, but I'm going to keep going.I'm
going to try my best to become a small fry in the tour.Thank
you in advance.My
goal is
not to come in last place.
Well, I
think the signs are the most important thing, so I'm going to
do my best.
Well, well, what's with
this face?
Dentists are gathered here. With 5 losses,
well, I'm looking forward to seeing what will happen this year.
Hey,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
Puck is kudokimky,
chocolate is too, but I made him eat coke, that's
good, isn't it? Well, what's that? Well, let's just say chocolate. I
took the bow. Watch everyone run.
Yeah, I watched everyone run.
That's it.
I was like, ``I'm so cool.'' I
thought, ``Why is the person who threw it so hot?'' and I want to see that cool guy's
fan 8 flight.2
Hmm, I
want to do an Eccho-kun.  I thought chocolate,
and every time I smelled it, the
items that came out were killer umbrellas.
Now, come on, the
only thing that came out was mushrooms. Yeah, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa,
hold it!  It looks
like it's going to start soon
Hey, I'm looking forward to it Hey, I'm looking forward to it I'm
looking forward to it
Hiraa is 2char weird  Besides killers, why don't you
try using Chocho? His past
beliefs are pretty
cool. It's like the
first time, isn't it?
[Music]
Thank you for the song Sedan Mai. Let's
aim for Soraman. I think we can aim for it and be in the middle.
Maybe,
maybe, maybe, that's what you're aiming for. It
's fine. If you
can do it left and right, you'll see the cherry blossoms too. That's
not the world of Amachuri. Do you
understand?
This small fry is
n't like that. There's no such thing.
[Music]
Ah,
then.  Shall we start? Ah,
whoa,
let's go
[Music]
Well, I'm going to show you my good side here in Nature May's four-leaf style.
Emma Why is chocolate the best?
Why is it that the small fry are the ones in the back?
Hey
[Music] That's
great!
It's a hotbed of delicious food. Come
here. Mess here.
Metty. I
took one.
Don't look at everyone. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute. Everybody's fast. Everybody's quick.
Wait a minute. I
love you. Shave it and
take it.
Take it air
[Music] I
got it from a problem that wasn't there. It's a
difficult space now that I've stopped it. Ahahaha, it's
valid. I took the coin totter. I
irradiated my feet with
oj. It's
information that I come in and stand up
[Music]  It has
become
[Music] The
feature is the fight that the remedy person wants to create. If you
go, you will go.
Isogo will go. It
was a winning course. Go for the
cup.
Ana, if the
big bone bone starts running, let it fall.
Typhoon. There are
a lot of scary things like parfait.  It's
not a biter, but it's full of opinions.
It's a hot scrapped car. It's
Hashimi. [Music] Unlike, I got off the car and this didn't make me fall. Hey, I'm a champion. Let's catch up with the song here. Isk Royal Castle Listed Designer Korokko  I
want you to come home with a heartbeat. I'm going to give you
five pairs of chocolates. I'm going to give you some flour. I
said kneaded sweets. Once I saw it, the direction changed
and the big reason was blood deficiency.
Use it quickly. Killer. Use killer.
1st arrival,
2nd time,
ku, you can get the weapons you want there.
Leafa Ido-machi release is near, so it's good. It's getting closer, it's
getting closer.
What do you mean?
[Music]
Ah, well,
well,
well, well,
still.  Yes,
there are more, so let's use ``if''. This
is the fourth case in the mom, so
what are you talking about?
[Music]
Alfin Pitch I
wonder what you're talking about. It's really
just something you say with your fingers.  Of course
[Music] I
wonder if Air Maamamo Miya is shy about that chocolate
[Music]
Everyone looks like chocolate Hey, I wonder if it's
weird that they look so thin
[Music]
The director should make them, but I can't go.
Pyoko Nee minutes,
but how about this? Koi is No. 2 Tokyo
Daddy. Even after your company rained on Iran on the 3rd, the opponent
is also a strong defense team. Please look at me. I'm horny. I'm
a little bit rude. 1st place tt tt dk I can do it, I can
do it, I can do it.  It's a
victory day that ends with Bankai Star, and I'm
saying the 5 zones, and I want to say about everyone today too.  It
would be nice if you could open something for me. Location: te te 4 e 4 I'm not at the bottom. I'm going to
use this.
Ha ha ha, I can
go. It's going to
boil over here and go.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Isn't this your first time? Next time,
why are you singing about the prefecture? 6. I'm a little tired.
Wait,
wait,
wait, why? Wait a minute, why
? I must have been the governor
for 22 seconds.  What happened
to Wait for the song that just hatched and what happened to 11th place?  I want to wake up
when I'm doing
music.If I
take just one photo of Koremasa, I
'll have a party where I'll reveal it.I'll leave it to you for
50,000 yen.Let's do our best.Hoshi
Oshio Kowase.The
notebook is opening an archive, so take a look.I
wasn't at the bottom, so it's
the end.  2nd from
the beginning,
press ``Awesome'', and this time, Totsuka is a little girl, but when I
used it with my older sister, I'm sorry, ``than''
and ``1'' are a little bit, but
I'm the only one who did a nail character.
goo My
mother is a navy blue girl and she looks at my older sister right
under her photo book. Do
n't act like a child like that. Someone said
that if you take a bath, you'll taste faster. You
can see the pure sound of your heart right in front of your eyes.  There are still a few people who don't have it. It
's still a reunion, but I'm not at the bottom. I
can still go on. I still
have to do it here and there.
Or should I go to the sea? I
don't understand this enzyme at all, but it's
falling. It
cuts through the snow.  I wish I didn't fall,
but I'm still alive. I'm
hiking here. I don't know
what Abadi's eyes are, but it's
strange. It
looks like a house, divided into parts. I feel
like I can't stand it
now.  Let's
all do
this and shave off the six hairs that we have now.Here, the
other person will smile as well.It's a Taisetsu-type
agreement.Here, let's
use it here, and let's go to Union Wai.Sasa, my
husband is having trouble here.  So Iida's career in the experiment is
gone, so
where are you going? Wait a minute,
don't hit it, give me a little chocolate, this week's certificate,
here, here, here, star.  It's
big, it's built, it
feels good, it feels good, it's good, it's abandoned here, the
tunnel, tunnel, oh, it's a
rocket, oh, here's the voice saying,
good a stop,
this isn't a road, it's a bad road, it's an umbrella road,
but I want you to think of it.  At the corner
Lighter Cola Wow
okay! [Music] Let's meet again. Mixed. That's weird. That's weird. They're
already calling it ex-joe rice. I do
n't think it's with Papa and Papa.
What's with the Ron Correction Department?  Are you saying that?
Choco is good,
right? It's not going to be a 3rd grade Nezugusa 5 loss championship here.
Choco will do
well, Cho will do well here, and he will take first place here.
Even if it's low, he
can still make a comeback.
Maybe it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay to be male, why don't you say it, check the several places where you have an opinion.That's the difference between today's women.
This is the love champion.The
audio is sure, but I'll think about it on the second day, so it's
no good.The walls and the sound aren't the same.If I
play Touhou, the song I want to be friends with is
Nekomi Pochirin.I'm
already
late.  I can do it, Hiroboko
Nee, it's a good example of instant escape, a
strong car,
here's the killer, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good,
it's good, it
's
ana
dj ko,
so it's accomplished, here, here, here, I'll show you the third generation,
Toki the third generation, please give me a [ __ ]  Hmm,
Onsho-te, there's someone in front of me.
Yes, here,
here, it's okay to do this here and there. It's fine now. The
retreat drum. Everyone
agrees that it's not the best record.
This is good, but it's okay.
It's Arthur. It's a problem.  If I can do it, I can do it.
re answer. It's
okay. I'll use it. Who's going to record this?
[Music] I ca
n't see it. I can't see it. I can't see it. I can't see it. I can't see
it. I can't see it. I ca
n't see it. I can't see it.  Like,
squid ink has made it easier to see.If you want to
stop for a while, straight tea is also good.Pancho
's cola and the first part are good.AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaTOTOTO  Do
n't leave me behind, I'll
give you some chocolate gum and go!
Wait a minute for the store to open. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Jaxa
Lander. Please surpass me. I
can't think of anything, so I say, ``
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!''  That's a relief, but it's
town.
Mac was in 5th place for a moment, so why don't you
just stand there and let everyone go ahead?
Hey, wait, wait,
wait,
that
's funny. Everyone's going too fast. Hey, he's kind to beginners.  Good
[Music] There's
still a lot more to it than if we win first place.
Eh, this is still a chocolate life.
This is a chocolate life.
Well, it's not the final. It's
not the final. It's fine if we win all at once. I
can't get excited about it. It's my first time
here.
Hey.  kyoko If you go to the public today,
why are you dismounting 3-Wait a minute, the
pot is going to fall.Eh,
say something about chocolate and change it.Baby, if it's
my rally, I'm going to go to the man.
Okay, cad! It's
not a good idea to be at the bottom. I
think Hiller should come out. I
think we can still go. You can finish me. Yes, I'm going to do this.
Everything will be different. Hey,
no,
that's the chassis.  If I were immortal, I
would have been able to carry it around with me. Hino isn't a sly kid.
He's got those sly abs. He's got
a list of corns
on his side. Let's put ena on the side
.
Now, move left.
Nice, nice.
Here, here, move.  I
feel like the people who received it said that it's still a bad gel because it hasn't fallen off in a long
time.I feel like I'm telling everyone that I got hit by lightning so I'm going to cut it off.I feel like I'm getting into a swamp here and there.  Wait, I
drew a killer, so I solved the chocolate power
and got ready. Now, there's a drop. Land
is the current situation. Hahaha,
it's
coming blue, wow. I'm
in the third week of high.
This drop is still going strong. I
can still use the window chocolate.
Ohshosho.
Even if I didn't take it, if I didn't
say it correctly, I'd be in the suburbs after the chocolates, and I wouldn't be able to get to the bank.Camco.I can take the items from the other party, and it's okay.I made it, and then I went back and talked to the robot.
After that, please at
least bring it back.
[Music]
Hey, it's all
over the place. There were two of them right now.
ua
arthur and day moon.
Ah, that's
it
. Yuru, oh, the chocolate is amazing. Even though it was Thunder.
What a good thing!
Choco,
chocolate, I won't give up.
In the end, it's like this. We'll
reach the goal. There's no demons. There's a
wall of people who agree with the support. The final raise is finally over.  It's
terrible
5th goal tie place 5
[Applause]
takanome
ran 4 horror eggs AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAa
There's still a long term for both chocolate and chocolate.It's
not because there's no one here yet.I'm going to buy it.Gay,
gay,
hanano, melon.I've
been chased since the melon came in.Wait a minute, I
can wait.I
say it's now.Let's
take on the sticky bottom.It's finally
here.  So I passed here and remember Hiroko
a It's now, I can still go, I can go, I
can go Inkao Your company is a girl, before the practice day I was a child of sunlight filtering through the foliage 4th I'm still here No, everyone is saying dah, I'm going on a trip I haven't done it
er 6th place  6th place, 6th generation, here, this,
green tea for humans,
version there is no path, I haven't heard a No,
no, 0
I'm here
[Music]
Bunsei Koko I'm
pissed Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
Tanaka Doko
Say it, say it, March  Aren't we still at the bottom?
Let's
go! Hey, now's a good time. I'm heading towards Iyo. It's finally hotbed girl. I do
n't want to restart the caster instead of reuniting with them
.
This
is it. I mean, this is still one of the eras. I do
n't like it, Choco.  Please leave the
washer scrivener is delicious. It's
okay here, and yesterday, the US version is also the US version.
Yeah Yeah Yeah Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
By the way, I'm going to go to ice
cream
this year as well.This
year I'm going to
go to chocolate garter.Thank you very much to everyone for visiting the small fry.Ah,
I also
thank you for coming out for the third consecutive year this year.See you
all
at the awards ceremony.Yes,
next year.  I
hope Hatai Oto is not a small fry. I want to do it.
Wow, I tried my best. I won't be able to win the
seat of Dumber One. Ah,
Kuroo.
Everyone, Takko didn't win.
To my mother,
please give me your best wishes.
Thank you for your hard work. Weather Forty. Thank you for spreading the Shogokyo bridge.