foreign
[Music]
thank you
no it's okay hello
hello oh hi
oh goodness I'm sorry I think I've
sneezed like 30 times today and my nose
is really stuffy getting that out of the
way but Hi how are you guys doing
welcome to the stream oh glitter's what
we got here ah
hi hi hi oh
there's background music oh that's nice
sorry sorry I've been I've been plagued
by allergies
allergies yes indeed but it's okay I
feel fine I just sound really weird
um I'm gonna be playing among us today
with Ian and ID members
we have a big collaboration happening
with Among Us here
um as you can see we I can I see it can
you guys see I can see all right here we
go
um yes yes so we got
um
collaboration merch
um we've known for a while that we've
been we have had some assets within the
game itself stuff you can unlock with
the Cosmic Cube but we also have this
merchandise that's on sale
um but the orders are going to be
stopping soon so be sure to check that
if you want any in case you didn't know
what's available
there are acrylic diorama stands of the
members to your left here your your left
our left cut to the left is me from your
perspective
we got those we also have a hollow crew
made plushie set oh gosh you can't see
there's a keychain in the way oh gosh
wait hold on let's give her that real
quick we'll come back
welcome back to that
um emergency meeting DJ which I just
turned on from the screen I'll give you
a better look in a second and
collaboration stickers and play tag I
don't play tag keychain that's that's
what I remember
that's what I removed there you go
um because they have no pictures for you
guys
wow
yeah yeah here's a bunch of other
merchandise we have median Senpai
um
[Music]
we have merchandise for all of them here
and in game assets that they have inside
I can't see girls hoodies there you go
very cute very cute
and then here we are these are the
stickers sorry
we're we're all we're all learning
things today these are stickers of Ian
an ID that are available
um yeah I just don't want to say no more
merch I'm not gonna buy well here's your
movie merch hear some of it we have
sticker you can't read everything but
it's a bit of it cut off I don't know so
I look so cute Anderson like I never
ever ever kill anybody I'd be really bad
at killing people actually and you're
here he's the best best look you get oh
there we go is
Mr President sneezed ugh
you got a keychain a Mia looking so pure
and uh and uh like I just I Could Do no
harm onto anybody
I'm just a little owl a little owl
little brown ow ow ow ow like that's
howling owls don't do that
um oh it's so interesting that Hal and
Al there's Al in the word Hal I'm sorry
um
[Music]
and there you go
that's the merchandise that's available
but it's going to be
gone real soon so be sure to click on
the links below if you're interested at
all and ordering any of these you want a
keychain where
um clearly not the Imposter you want a
sticker where I look so cute
I'm sorry
I'm really excited to play today
um who we got here you can see right
actually you can see who we got like
[Music]
that that is indeed Muna
me and myself Kiara
she's a fish or his husband
um
well yeah I also apologize I have the
sniffles like I said I have a case of
allergies I thought it was I thought I
was getting sick well first I thought I
strained my voice from doing karaoke
um but then I got a really stuffy nose
so yesterday I took allergy medicine and
I was super drowsy knocked out but it
helped a lot today I did not take any
allergy medicine because I didn't want
to be super drowsy
and here we are I'm still kind of out of
it
I think we're all a bit out of it it's
very very early for
um ID members
um and forever
it's a bit early so oh sorry I'm gonna
be sniffling a lot I'm very sorry I have
I don't own tissues
but I have toilet paper so
we will make do with what we have
um expect sneezes
I hope they don't uh oh you know what
I'm going to take advantage of this me
sounding sick because it makes it easier
for me to sound sad
and like I'm about to cry and I'm
sniffling
[Music]
so I think it'll work out okay
um unless people think
I'm capable of killing people for some
reason
um
who knows who knows I need to be a
little careful in the past I've acted
like an imposter when I'm not the
Imposter and then I feel like when I am
the Imposter I get really quiet I just
have to work on that a little bit I just
to always be really scary
I have to always be intimidating I think
so what
anyways that was the merchandise
and um there's a game here
behind that wait how do I
wait what
I'm silly I'm a silly I'm a silly Billy
here we go okay I'm gonna join the call
now oh
okay
basic it is
already had a Omega stream like this red
like four hours ago or so yeah yeah yeah
yeah we had it yesterday
no we were kind of promoting and
chatting at the same time just now
wow
for the other girls why are you guys so
fast
oh
[Music]
yeah so okay if I made a new one one
second I don't trust streamer mode
on all right
[Music]
hello hello
wow everybody's really tired huh
the third hellos
[Music]
it looks like a morning voice do we want
to do like uh you know a classic
introduction of everyone yeah there used
to be a soundtrack community me yeah
sound check let's start by the top
button yeah
hello everyone hello it's Anya Melissa
from polarvidi second generation how
how's my voice
thank you
God I I really love that it's still
fancy
okay fails next what what's up it's me
the rat I'm tired
um
the red I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best sauce rat that I can
hello
carefully
[Music]
oh no you silly
it's bails in the room yet I don't see
her in the room no I'm not isn't it yeah
[Music]
exactly
I think it compared to everyone else oh
yeah beauty beauty is is you're just
beautiful Florida you know yeah
you were born naked the natural beauty
why was that dog
I'll join you've convinced me
you're turning to Nature
clothes
hello it's me Oro crony from Halloween
I'm going to kill everyone
yeah
sound effect the sound effect is sending
me
they say crony's low but I have her on
Max I can't do anything else
it's just your voice just talk louder or
something
yeah
speak from the stomach crony be higher
let the world die around desire they
said you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed a bottoms but
then nothing happened
[Laughter]
oh say again crony this is this loud
enough now
yeah
um
okay yeah
thank you
you should be fine
me too
foreign
bye next
time
[Laughter]
[Music]
we did not only
[Applause]
is adapting The Voice amazing incredible
wow amazing
[Music]
now
the monkey
thank you for waking up so early
[Music]
hello oh hi I'm nasty movie from Whole
Life English I have a stuffy nose little
man
you didn't register to me that you're
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then you just cut it halfway
because you could be bothered today
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
I mean it would take too long the room
is gonna dispense
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
we need
what is that I can't see
all right
no I'm not ready
I need a warm up or something at least I
kind of know this
I kind of know this map right
no I'm going to eventually
I'm going to fail
if you don't play this game regularly
you're gonna you are at such a
disadvantage because you don't know what
task is what people can easily say what
task were you doing and you can maybe
kind of remember it but you can't
remember where it was
with crony okay okay
and there's no like um
foreign
no okay no I I just have to have the
mind of a crewmate right now
and my my mind is if wanna we have to
keep each other warm because we don't
have clothes
that's where my mind is right now where
do I want to go okay wait no where's the
one I think it was this one this is the
one where like you throw stuff out right
oh gosh oh wait there's background I
don't want you guys to have music we
both are in awkward silence all right
can I sabotage
hi Anya
I'm so bad at this
you know to the earlier today I was
thinking I'm gonna play
not play I'm gonna watch gameplay
of imposters but
I'm so unlucky I'm so unlucky girl I am
so unlucky crony
I was like I hope no one saw me
oh gosh sorry you couldn't hear the game
all right well everybody
yeah there's yeah Ollie and Lona died
where was everyone I
was doing that I was around
today I think I just arrived on the
shield
made several times when Bales you're
muted in case you're trying to speak
your muted
oh sorry oh yeah
should be muted
and only should be muted because
the body I need to look at the map okay
um
there was a hallway to the left you know
the hallway that leads to electrical and
then yeah yeah yeah
and I
I go in that direction right before I
discovered the body
oh
[Music]
would you like to explain
wait uh but like I've been traveling
like everywhere else like I've been
traveling the right side of the section
so I didn't really notice anything like
I was checking samples
three seconds before that I when I found
the body why did you not report the body
if you were there
I'm so tired
that doesn't make sense because there
was something there I didn't even go to
the right the whole time
you've already lost two crew members
[Music]
yeah we were on the right side
um yeah
laughs
let's do wait sorry I have to figure
some stuff out okay there you go
there we go okay
do you think how many people do how many
people do we have to kill
for us to uh win maybe we can go on a
rampage real quick
or something
oh
[Laughter]
I saw Anya and Greta being in the same
okay
where are you guys
why is it so fast is it because you're
still near to the body because you just
killed her
it was something I mean what happened
that was so fun
I didn't see it did you all see it I
didn't see it no because it was like it
was like yeah
in front of my eyes oh okay I we were
all there together so cronies kind of
sauce yeah yeah she has an obvious
um reason to do it
thank you
Anya and Zetta wow
me and Anna were together though
well goodbye
well you know okay fine I'm just gonna
like yes I am the Imposter but guess
what
the other one you know
who's the other one
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
all right
really
do we believe her
no this is too much pressure for me
foreign I don't know what I'm doing I
didn't know I have to go there sorry
didn't know about that my bad
to their is that electrical
[Music]
um
there's a vent in there
no
please I go in here
wait what
wait wait what
wait
oh wow
again the oxygen
calculated it's so embarrassing
for the oxygen in case someone doesn't
know
like I just want to say if someone is
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
[Music]
were in the room which means that
they're going to be innocent the only
two people remaining were Kiara I had to
choose between the two
okay
we both did so much work for us to win
that round Right
double he had no hesitation to kill
anybody I totally lost track of any
examples
yeah but thank you for not voting me out
appreciation there's one person missing
I think you killed Ollie like when I was
about to walk over and Anya was there
and I was like crony you just got me in
so much trouble because I thought
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
man I was like when when you guys were
in the discussion and Courtney was like
no it was like people were there and
then everyone else seemed not convinced
and I'm like she killed him front of you
guys
yes
that was so funny
yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
and then like I was like okay
were the ones in the room yeah and like
I was like I was hoping I was hoping
that Zeta would say something so that I
didn't understand me I didn't see it but
I was making task yeah it was very lucky
that ran the funny thing is that I was
like I was about to go out from that
room so if only you had waited for like
a few more seconds I probably wouldn't
have thought that
yeah
crony learned her lesson for next round
right yeah
I wonder if he can get imposter twice
[Music]
I can't believe
what
oh goodness okay now I'm scared I want
to access now that I'm not imposter I'm
gonna follow wanna
I think this gives away that it's not me
because why would I do this if I was
like if I was crazy I do this if I was a
crew in my ooh One swipe
what I have to go there's a lot of
people here oh gosh what's this
oh okay oh oh
I knew I had a feeling on what happened
twice in a row
it's very dangerous
there were a bunch of people I was crazy
and I was trying my best trying to turn
it on but people kept turning it off
but if you wouldn't have just admitted
immediately that it was you then I
wouldn't have known because there was so
much going on
you don't you shouldn't run away
I was in there I was in there because
electrical was out and everyone else was
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah how
could we know it was her we don't know
if it was her
there were so many people there
yeah
the animation of chronic killing it okay
I don't know because like I saw it
that's what I was like the way I saw a
movie like I don't know I just arrived
no no no it's not mummy I suck running
in front of my eyes killing it really
they're unfortunate
that is oh no oh no what Luna said crony
just incriminated herself by the way I
mean you can try
[Music]
who knows
oh thank goodness it's an honor
we already see
wouldn't it be funny if honor turned out
to be the Imposter
foreign
wait what I didn't I didn't see what it
did
Bob fauna
no I should do this she's looking at me
um
foreign
[Music]
sorry that required a lot of focusing
all right don't make the same mistake
gotta take care of the oxygen where is
it I think I have to go this way anyway
hello everybody
hello hello oh someone's over there this
is not oxygen but I'll do it
I trust the others will do it
problem for somebody else look at all he
seems to be doing tasks or is she
I need to go up here too
okay I don't need to go that way oh wait
no
let's see let's see I just need to carry
this energy
in every round I should have been I
shouldn't have been so scared the first
one
I just need to be
[Music]
mommy
chasing me and then she went off to the
right side of the map
running around yeah
he was the Imposter because she was
chasing me but
sorry it sounds so suspicious right now
I know I do but
I'm chasing me around the table but I
almost called a meeting because I was
like that's kind of susp and I was like
oh it's movie so it's just normal yeah
it's probably mumably yeah
just a check
actually I wanted to do a little
promotions
tomorrow yeah sure today
um why did you go to the electrical for
like one second and then she went out
immediately wow I was just checking to
see what's inside
why would you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there I don't know man that
was kind of sauce yeah yeah if you don't
have any tasks like inside the
electrical then why won't you go inside
because I just want to see who's inside
and see if I could stick to anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead where is I'm sorry where
is this intense
and like we only were like going out but
like you you like you were like going
inside for like one second and then you
came out immediately
yeah because if you talk I don't want to
get like fine someone then why didn't
you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
[Music]
um
okay somebody stick with me then
pick two people for that
I wonder if crony really was the other
imposter again
um
is that a somebody stick with me
oh that's not what I meant to do where's
this thing I have to do oh here it is
wait what I don't
what am I anything here what
okay they have to do something there at
least I can go through walls for
security again
over here
are you
um
I have one more task Anya
oh did this other so we can't see people
do the mid Bay thing
this one yeah
oh wait the dang it I thought it was the
poopy one what's crony doing is she
I'm done right
you can make a different color wait wait
stay still
we can make a different color you and I
foreign
oh my goodness wait this is danger stay
that's dangerous
oh goodness gracious
ifanna
I wonder if
oh maybe she's not imposter Elmo
animals
[Music]
I shouldn't do that
why am I following Luna
whoa wait
they want to do a dance together is
everybody busy but me
I want to do a dance
I'm bored dance with me babe
dancing yes she's kind of getting it
dance with me
you're getting it dance with me
damn
she didn't get it I was hoping she was
um
what'd she say what up hello
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
you know what what's interesting is that
Zeta came after that
today yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't
I was like walking I was walking I don't
know I didn't see anyone teleporting
though but that uh Zeta was like yeah I
said I came to admin constantly because
I saw you guys I was in security we were
doing stuff
interesting
I'm I'm suspicious interesting
so can you describe the the how many and
it took to arrive at your destination
but
um I'm just gonna say I finished my
tasks
there's only a bit left
yeah okay
for those who finishes
[Music]
I can't
are we voting Anya we need Anya to vote
oh yeah
you're just skipping I I have voted
no I hope you like space accidents
laughs
oh
my God
we want game over
yeah
[Applause]
because that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
[Music]
might have been the pain
can I just mention that
in the ghost chat babe is trying to sing
a Taylor Swift song to crony and Coney
just was not getting
it okay
Courtney did you not actually get it I
thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song
goes I didn't even know that was a song
until later on
[Laughter]
I'm standing there and you're my job
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
that imposter because I don't know these
men yeah
okay
all right
um
anything but mirror it's cute it's like
the winter one the snowy one oh yeah
okay let's try let's try paulus I guess
I don't like it that much but sure might
be fun okay
[Music]
uh standing cold there you go
thank you thank you
y'all see nothing one second one second
[Music]
we'll use the excuse that they don't
know the map well so they didn't know
where to go oh exactly
I never know where to go
um
yeah
[Music]
okay bye everyone did I sound sick
I don't know where anything is
I'm lost
I'm lost what is this oh can I touch
this no I can't touch it
how do we get fast food up here
well hopefully somebody else is lost
all right
and yeah is anyone else around here yes
okay
um wait oh yeah
I already look really suspicious
I'm gonna follow that as just a creeper
wait where she goes
pause pause
I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
outfit I think so I was in the office
and then I go after you
you seemed a bit sus
me you know I was right behind her oh
she was like acting a bit sus in that
hallway right before she entered the
right office so
yeah but I was behind you
side of the of the office I saw her I
was in the office I was in the office
and then I saw something going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office though yeah and I was inside the
office
I saw you and you go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think
yeah I think mommy is near
Communications or something yeah
as well
yeah they and Anya are kind of teaming
up against Muna
um
are we folding well I don't I don't know
I don't know if there's enough
information or anything
[Music]
interesting
[Laughter]
said no
all right I have two set up
here
and here
oh yeah
um maybe this isn't the game to talk
about stuff while I do stuff because I
don't know what to do I'm just
walking around aimlessly
um I was thinking you know what I'm
gonna do I'm gonna find Zetta I'm just
gonna follow her
I've decided yes okay where's Zetta
um where is that a
maybe I chose the wrong person I'm just
okay wait was last night
this is what I would do if I was
a crewmate
uh-huh
I wonder if she likes it or not okay
I'll let her be now
when I see her again I might kill her
she's not here wait
this is where is she
where'd she go now
ah
wait I'm not there oh shoot
where is she
is
[Music]
should I creep her out more
I think if honestly oh good I can follow
both of them
is watching
can they see the animation of somebody
killing
where should I go well that's not a spot
I think it is oh here we go oh I can do
a task here
all right wait can I
I don't know what anything is oh gosh
let me see oh hello Miss Muna hello this
is trying to telepathically tell me
something
okay what do I do
I don't know this works
no one find them
maybe if I see somebody do I see anybody
near base body
wait who's that it might have been
was that is that a near the body
oh I got stuck
do a double
I saw nothing
okay I wanna go see if someone's
nearby's body
okay
okay we're not really bad imposter
please don't have too much faith in me
let's see no no one's here
if someone's nearby I don't survival
that's why I don't want to report it
until I know there's someone around here
unless it could have been enough time do
you think enough time has passed
um
what do you guys think
okay I'm gonna report I'm gonna report
it
um
oops
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
security
yeah I didn't go there
oh
yeah and Ollie yeah
yeah we were from the specimen oh wait
he was there and we met up with Zetta
yeah yep on the way to the Bay was
suspicious of Muna and I didn't see her
the whole round no I was with Mommy
before but I go with Mommy before yeah I
didn't see nothing but I know not at all
I was in the boiler room still doing my
task
yeah
but
um
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait
what side are you guys on I have no idea
right
and we just like stand in there yeah
in the emergency room yeah yeah
the oh yeah the office
went to the specimen room and then we
met up with Anya and then we went yeah
yeah I was mostly on the right side of
the map the whole time yeah me too so I
can't be on the left side of the map
wait you said right side right wait who
voted out yet right that's kind of bad
yeah yeah this is kind of bad I mean
there's two people left right I don't
know man I'm gonna go with left Luna
Senpai cause yeah
you know and barely sussing her
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win okay
I'm already done with my test so I'll
just follow people around oh I have like
one more I have one more I have like one
more
[Music]
I got one guide I got one guy somebody
told me to do it dang it
I got one guide I don't I can't tell
what's going on in this I just said
I don't think I could blame it on Zeta
but then they said that Zeta met up with
her because that was over here why
didn't
I meant oh yeah yeah yeah
I I oh you are you leave me alone what
are you doing
what are you doing huh huh it'll creep
you out
[Music]
to play more
it was moomy she was chasing me at the
end
anyway
s
I'm a really good opinion posture guys
no I'm not either
I was thinking wait can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill again
explain Friendly Fire excuse me
yeah it's a new mode haven't you I was
there to explain why did you miss it you
should have prepared and you wouldn't
have you wouldn't have missed it uh-huh
was following me and I was like where's
Muna trying to tell him
good huge big brain idea that I can't
catch up on I'm missing one person
mom
[Music]
um
all right well I think we can at least
squeeze in one more round yeah maybe we
can do one more thing okay let's yeah
no no no
okay what what on Earth this game this
game is giving me too many chances what
on Earth this is
wait where are we
drop ship how does this work can we go
it's not fair
[Music]
ly I do want to follow the chroni
[Laughter]
foreign
too much pressure for me it's too much
pressure I'm gonna follow crony for one
minute
I just I wanna
spread myself
killer though
she would have been pretty hidden there
untouched
oh that's funny
I'm gonna keep finding out
okay
I'm gonna get blamed for that if I want
to find I'm gonna get blame for that
oh I found it
[Music]
no I was on the security cameras I saw
it what and who was it what what who was
it could you what what
happened
I didn't see your body
from me
I saw her on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
and also running away
earlier to creep her house
right there when she died why didn't you
report her right then and there what
yeah
what wait where but that was her natural
state
[Laughter]
um
he will report it I didn't see her body
I didn't leave the lights out in the
first part of the game but there's the
report
a little bit yeah I didn't see so I
don't know I have no idea
um
because she was running she was like
there and then she went the opposite
direction so I don't know if she really
didn't see it or she said
another double M I think another double
M
imposter I didn't see crony die so I I
didn't say honestly but okay
it'll be all okay wait I'll show you
exactly
um oh
[Music]
punish me for that
I I
I I I
[Music]
I thought I'd get my chance at
Redemption I didn't even do anything
do anything
[Music]
what the heck is that can I do anything
else I don't understand how sabotage
Works can I do this
did I sabotage it
I truly don't understand how this works
huh wait that's so unfair there's a
security camera that can see people's
names
how does this work can I do this oh did
I do that
did I do that
look at that chat
foreign
there's a bit of a miscommunication
[Music]
do you think that was a calculator moved
by Among Us
yeah you don't even need these
is there anything else I can do to help
um
what is this oh this is close access
[Music]
she said that
wait who is it
again again
different people
don't kill anybody
you did walk over my bed
after moving uh get out it was like it's
so hard to kill everyone yeah everyone
was together
[Music]
and I was like bro this can't be real
you can see people's names when they're
watching somebody that's no I just saw
your your character your colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah I think you
should be able to like see the colors
[Music]
um
why are you looking on a camera babe
that's creepy
I was like
in the snack what I was like about to
kill you guys when you guys inside but
but you guys instead not in like one
step but have like a different style so
I just like oh this is hard even though
I do it
it is hard I think everybody should be
off on their own and isolated at all
times honestly
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
yeah
I'm going to kill all of you
okay so someone who gets it again
okay yeah if someone gets it like
um
you want to play one more round it
doesn't matter who imposter is if I get
it again
let's do that well like if we get
imposter again either Muno or me we
could just do the emergency meeting and
cast okay yeah I found an imposter I'll
be throwing it
foreign
faster I wasn't gonna throw it okay
so he's doing here in a circle do you go
Kumbaya
[Music]
oh it's so dark fine no that's that's
deep
oh dang
Muna
oh
but what I I saw someone but I don't
know who it was because I wasn't looking
at the screen but there was someone
running
man
spider Rockets right oh yeah yeah by the
Rockets
me I I was stalking fauna and then it
got dark and I lost sight of her but
then I saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I don't think yes
the rocket oh it's nearby the laboratory
all I'm saying is that I'm like on the
left side of the map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see them they were
running to the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know I I don't know I just wanted to
keep playing this crony then she might
have
um
so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what but like
should you cast me out now
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
give me the hats of imposter and we'll
just continue like that give me a hint
oh imaginary kill people I will just act
as if I did it
so like if I'm in pause for a good
should I just out myself and just too
many people are doing like it narrows it
down too much so I'm not sure we can
really do that I mean we could just keep
crony around
I'll just not kill anyone else's new
sabotage
sabotaging
oh oh that was close
oh man oh close
well at least she's honest she's very
honest yeah
all right
I have tasks I have to do
I should do those you have to go over
here
I just hope I don't die
huh
okay
let's see if I can figure this out okay
this way lavatory
[Music]
what's this still
it needs to read three
oh no I need to look
is it oh whoever that is don't hurt me
oh
yeah
oh I'll keep you up
wait Connie's still alive I told me what
happened
what am I supposed to do up to where
wait where to where oh all the way I see
I see
myself
we have to go she was like in the
hallway on the left side of the map like
which was like a like a tree yeah
she's in like the middle left oh okay in
a hallway who was with someone was with
me at stabilizer so they're also safe
um
I I was walking up with you but then I
went to the left and I met crony and she
was coming from that area but I guess
she didn't she didn't touch it yeah
okay
what a little bit scared was it every
time I see crony I won't lie
it's okay yeah anything can happen it
must be the other imposter
Fisher friends not food God I I have no
idea skipping
I kind of really does anyone have any
leaves I don't know who to choose
[Music]
honestly at this point what woman
let me know stuffy
I'm very out of it
don't call me no don't okay good
oh goodness oh I want to say it is my
Pokemon off stream what do I have to do
I have to go this way
this way well you can't see it very well
okay I wasn't supposed to go this way
how do I get out of here go this way
this way
[Music]
and playing Pokemon off stream fully
evolved my little questly fellow
it's turned into quite the character
who did that
I mean oh
oh I see I have to take a shower don't
look
let's see let's see and what do I have
to do in here
wait what
wait is there something I can't see
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
it was so simple am I stuck in here oh
you could go through here let's just
take another shower
all right see I see
what the heck is that I don't know
I have to fix no fix I have to do our
task but anyways I think I have two gems
left
I can battle the Elite Four then I can
see my Pokemon's IVs but I still have to
complete the poker decks
I think Kyla and I are gonna Exchange
Pokemon that are exclusive
to Violet and Scarlet she has Scarlet
so we can get the shiny charm
okay
um
but what else
ah I'm not I don't know I'm kind of
close I'm probably like
halfway there to get everything I want
before breeding Chinese
so that's nice then I can breed them
although it appears it'd be really easy
to get shinies from the outbreaks or
whatever they're called
right in the back
[Music]
oh wait my task oh thank you baby that a
lot easier for me thank you
thank you
that's right it's my body on the floor
there's a girl on the floor if she what
romantic
I have I have a very big Theory so I was
assessing uh Zeta
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that then came
out after meeting Anya
um and it isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get anyone's dress if she's an imposter
so it couldn't be heard it couldn't be
me it's inside a car Senpai or bae
but that's just the zombie Theory
why was impulsory I could have killed
you right
oh baby your cooldown was not done yet
okay
I don't know I feel like I I really okay
because we're kind of dwindling to the
final people so if you waste a if you
waste the thing we're gonna we're gonna
lose by the way the body is that
um the karate has a name and you better
choose someone
why is cardi still here
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
but like really big props to like the
other imposter doing a very nice job
Let's Stay Together and finish us I'm
done by the way yeah
yeah I'm done with my macaroni so I can
go
doing their task do your task goes sorry
I'm one of the people who hasn't done
their tasks but I'm Just a Nobody wait
what's this oh all the way right oh
[Music]
is this
I don't even do it again yes okay
the Pokemon game has been pretty fun
actually
and a lot of people have their opinions
about it I have some opinions about
stuff but I've been enjoying it the game
itself it was just me like two tasks I
see
it
stay with me hey I'm sorry
in the Back Bay
stop me where in the back
yeah I felt it in my spine when you did
it
respect to the ones who stayed alive and
finished the tasks oh honestly I was
dead and had to finish the tasks I think
it was me I'm sorry but I did it
one more if that's possible since it was
hard for the other imposter
on red
the on my screen I was like what
are they someone in bed
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
[Music]
and the killing time is like 10 like the
lowest 10 seconds and pretty much they
have to try and kill every everyone
before they finish the talk
[Music]
yeah yeah so you have to tell you have
to say that you're the Imposter when you
get it okay um and you've set the the
running speed to the fastest whoever's
making the room and then okay you just
count to ten if you're the Imposter and
then yeah okay I have the player speed
on Max oh my God that is so fast whoa
10 seconds
10 seconds yeah no it doesn't get any
lower do we have okay do we have to do
task yeah yeah yeah yeah so the point is
to finish all the tasks before you get
killed
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah there's the task was too
little yeah
so wait so how many should I do
another
which oil do you want to do you want to
do the normal one for now
let's go
lower imposter Vision as well oh we're
not gonna mean ourselves by the way
right yeah until yeah
go wild
okay oh you can hear each other
screaming
let's go
who is it
again
[Music]
yeah we should be hiding oh wait oh wait
I'm sorry I think I'm not sure
okay
[Music]
uh it's impossible I'm meant to die
I have no idea
I'm good
if we if we die should we do a test
um
let's just say yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was me
everywhere
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
play the elevator music oh my God oh my
God
you don't need to wait what do you mean
I haven't killed anyone in a while
this is
everybody
yes dangerous place
where's everybody
[Music]
wait is it only is it only me and Bana
oh
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
go grab a coffee no dude
go grab a coffee
and who um
oh
sabotage
[Music]
I thought
Oh No Maybe This Time five seconds I
don't know and we're gonna hide it ten
seconds give them five seconds five
seconds I think it's good I think it's
well balanced but oh challenge
again four three
bye
one more one more one okay possible
[Music]
wow wow amazing I'm saying that would
work so that we would win what what good
job
[Music]
okay
should I change something any
Improvement advice was actually okay
if I hadn't messed up I would have won
so it's okay
okay
play well if you want to win it's
possible
who is it I don't actually don't I don't
actually want to be it so please no
thank you wait we should restart it
again
kick her out
okay
all right
goodbye
goodbye and we have to wait
while we're waiting why don't we just
you know doing the marketing
[Applause]
[Music]
let's do it
do it
the
contrasting do it is incredible
it just fault me me
[Music]
all right will it be fun again
we learn easy
Cube
yes
oh
it's me it's not me it's me yeah
[Applause]
stop counting okay
wait what
we were doing past you guys are
confusing me oh yeah
wait okay
oh man I think it started
I have no idea what should I do
yeah
what is happening
the Keystone that is broken
now
well this is peaceful
I'm definitely he's not in the cafeteria
right now you don't need to go looking
for me
I can't do the card
s
no
um
you're so small
no not in the cafeteria at all
every time I was doing a white kinky
moment
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wow
you are scary
[Music]
I'm so sorry
[Laughter]
that was fun I never got it did anyone
mm-hmm
yeah I know right it's not fair oh
that's cute I'm going to sue someone I
don't know who but I'm going to school
probably maybe Susie
or hello
actually means milk in Indonesia wow oh
[Music]
how do I say please give me uh
it depends that you can at least give
you can always just say
uh something dong
oh
my God
only I'm surprised
I will marry you or something like that
[Laughter]
oh
my shoulders like
anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon
yeah yeah in like 12 hours I think so
make sure to grab the merch guys
[Music]
are really cool t-shirt
mm-hmm
[Music]
you got the moon yeah
yeah very nice
guys
thank you for joining so spontaneously
especially to the IG members who already
did their homework
thank you
so much I hope it was fun for you guys
too thank you yeah it was really fun
thank you
thank you thank you everyone else
but not for me I have to show you guys
stuff first
thing you remember this wait did I get
coins can I use them
oh you know I don't have anything just
kidding I don't have anything but I was
gonna wait I can't tell
can I buy stuff I want it
just kidding I don't have currency
I thought I
I thought I had some
anyways this is the tree this is how the
Cosmic Cube the hollow life Cosmic Cube
it's how you
get stuff I already I have three
thousand wait no
huh
it seems that
oh it's in the customized
how I see okay I can't do it right now
but this is I this is how you do it hi
animal
is here now hello
itchy
spot
thank you guys for watching
um I don't think I'm gonna have another
stream today yeah
well but I'll be around tomorrow I'm
gonna try to make a schedule for this
week actually but I'm not sure if it'll
be released tonight or tomorrow I have
to figure some stuff out first uh but
thank you guys for watching thank you
thank you thank you I'll see you
tomorrow
I feel very nasally oh my goodness do
you guys hear it thank you okay sorry I
forgot to show you guys in the beginning
now I remembered that's okay
see you later
telling people
's me kill responsibly bye bye
[Music]
kill responsibly in the game among us
bye
[Music]
foreign