[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I got kicked out of my room as well oh
no I'll be waiting for you
hello everybody
hello hi
hello hello welcome to Monopoly with
these girls oh
um I have been waiting to play this game
for forever I always wanted to play this
eventually
um with the girls uh you know I love
English and today is the day and the
chosen competitors slash investors in
the stonks are right next to me you know
my Inon is what what what is what is
your motivation for today
um my motivation today is my lovely
penguin piece and my fantasy outfit
today I want to match up to the fastness
of the fanciest the fancy and I shall
live
oh that's that's a cat thing to do so
you want to leave the fancy cat live
this is true speaking of a fauna what is
your motivation for today's Monopoly
game
hello well when I was a kid I thought I
was amazing and Monopoly but these days
I realized that my grandparents just
always let me win so
today is the real thing hmm
[Music]
that is uh let's see I want we we will
not let you win we're not your
grandparents so be careful
okay and then we have Gua who's also
dressed very fancily
are you motivated
[Music]
was that Spanish
yeah I think so oh I'm pretty sure
go to jail
okay and uh then there's me my my
motivation is
um
to not be last place because according
to the poll not even my own uh
subscribers believe in me because
um I have been asking the audience what
they think who will be winning today the
bets are following uh fourth place
takanasi Kiana with 15 not even my own
people will live with me
and it's not really
this game it's about look well then
fourth place is good out of 17 hey
what the heck KFC yeah why
it's not only KFC in here but the bottom
three but there's the clear winner
yeah then there's fun that was 21
uh kind of uh I'm not sure why uh you do
you think you have such high chances but
still you know much much higher
you know the 47 guy guys do you think
you know can live up to the expectations
I think so she scares me
yeah
I love mommy when are you lucky yeah
it's about planning your your Monopoly
your housing Empire right that's
Monopoly right yeah yeah
how well you
extort money from your fellow players
yes yes
oh I'm excited
okay oh just a heads up guys there's a
chance that the game might just for fun
crash at some point but yeah we're just
gonna if it crashes early on we're just
gonna do a new one it might just happen
but that's okay so I'll close the polls
the polls are closed
[Music]
and we shall start this game of Monopoly
wow
we're in guys here we go this Monopoly
game looks so fancy music strategy of
Monopoly I don't know there's bloody
houses everywhere yeah yeah first let's
just spend all your money buying and
then later regret
okay if you have any other suggestions
chat let me know
if someone is too quiet or too loud for
you let me know
um I can't think we have a roller
coaster in the middle of the city
and that's amazing okay I love this part
of town
okay
pretty good in a little quiet okay
let's go
what's six not bad not bad okay
double or first okay
well we're starting off with Hannah
all right it's time I'm gonna buy
everything before anyone else has a
chance to
oh no yeah
we'll see about that oh look at that
fancy board
pretty cool
oh cute look at that we like we wear
pieces around maybe not what the heck
I'm zooming I love it oh yeah
oh
what oh okay I was only visiting anyway
11. okay
wow yes
it is cheap
is somewhere actually way more expensive
though some are cheaper some are more
expensive yeah and the rents that you
pay is also more expensive
um oh and turn I guess
yes yes in the beginning there's not
much to do
besides buying
yeah
I had when I played privately today I
had a million doubles like 80 percent of
my rolls were doubles it was great wow
wow but sometimes it's not that good
because like you don't want to spend any
more money but they like keep on letting
you go and go and go
wait wait wait
you bought it yay your first property
okay
does everyone remember the basic rules
of Monopoly
yeah
you land on other people's squares you
pay money
like this oh never mind
wow wow do you want lights on in your
house give me money
oh no I guess it can't be helped
not the electric shocks
everybody money comes to me oh no you
want Wi-Fi give it to me this is an
intern okay now
let me land on your squares
.com
because penguin is fancy and where's the
tuxedo but I feel like you're just
trying to get closer to me by choosing a
bird
Penguins can't fly oh it's still a bird
is bird I feel I feel closer to you
yeah honestly it's like it's like pretty
pretty quick
[Applause]
put it pretty close yeah
I also penguin eat these fish
what about the painting
that they have I can't remember the word
but they have like
webbing
no it's the way that they keep their
feet warm
oh come on I'm the only one who can't
buy something in the first
hands
look at the penguin knees their knees
are like bent up inside their bodies
penguins are pretty cute though
they're cute oh man they are owls have
you seen their legs owl legs
you like lift their body up and the leg
just stays there are you guys laughing
at Muma in her absence wow that's rude
no we're just saying that mummy has
really long legs
[Music]
Pennsylvania let me buy two
Pennsylvania
that cat is looking dangerous getting a
double turn
at these games
literally just begun we know nothing yet
my gut feeling the ancient ones are
Whispering watch out foreign
people like land on your square or like
you have like utilities and cards and
stuff I guess your time has come oh wait
am I using this with the game of life
because I was like oh when do we pick
our jobs
[Laughter]
I swear Oh
I thought it was
you lost the Kentucky Kiara
Kentucky Avenue
[Applause]
but that means that bana is now not able
to get a full red uh thingy unless screw
that sells it to her or the other way
around yeah
somehow oh YouTube was there for a
moment welcome back sorry
oh
uh could I if you missed it could I just
bought a red property
yes I would like to buy
I'm a little bit worried I feel like I'm
gonna run out of money
no no no no don't worry you know you got
our best to collect
um but I haven't done any collecting so
far you want me buying no no Sheena has
done some collecting she collected from
me
already
[Laughter]
let me buy now please I'm skipping so
it's faster oh orange orange
already has orange too yeah oh well I'll
buy any line of course
you know you can sell me yours later
please
lucky
oh now we're going into the into the
expenses you're in the corner wait I'm
going to jail
no what have you done what was her
crying
oh my God I did nothing wrong I only
knocked things off the tables
I repeat cats in jail
that's why she belongs to uh how will
she ever no stay dead I did nothing you
bought too many properties
yellow oh
what is Atlantic Avenue oh how fitting
okay
[Music]
this is good okay what happens in jail
you stay down for free turns unless you
pay 50 bucks to get out early
um
or you can get a free ticket to get out
of a jail beforehand in one of those
ticket squares
Illinois
yes
taking away all the properties that I
can take
[Music]
bye bye bye give me a color that no one
has yet please
I love it that's feeling like jail
go fast
yellow oh
oh it's right next I'm taking it
this is a doggy dog world
[Applause]
I guess I'll roll
if I roll doubles do I get out
I think if you roll a three
yeah if you would get a double then you
would have like uh one another less
rounds to spend in jail but you went
from three to two now yeah
right
oh
no oh that's the good one the blue ones
are expensive so you get more money from
it later
I wish I wasn't in jail
Bad Kitty nice
wait how big is this board I thought
we'd already gone all the way around
squares that's the most expensive ones
from
[Music]
okay
I'll give me something good
Jail jail
yes bye bye bye
but these are expensive yeah this is so
expensively in the luxury part of town
[Music]
a smart though
where am I going
where am I going is this great yes okay
the bank is
expensive oh wait never mind
I think it's like once you land on them
again you can like okay yeah oh you can
only put houses on it extra houses if
you already have the full Lane the full
color
so right now I think everyone's sharing
so that would be a problem
have to do some trains to bully them out
of it or make them go away
I'm gonna pay get me out of here it's
about time
I should have paid last turn but how was
jail
it was
almost the food the food was horrible
um
one that's a win
you can go to jail again then
no thanks you can play again to get out
of it please no
roll roll those dice ow okay okay
oh
now you did wonderful turn one full turn
thank you thank you for the money six
bucks
all right take to roll nice chocolate
where do I go
eight
oh you can count yes
um I wanted one of the blue ones
she's part of the system
what happened when I was in jail
you gotta kick her out of there go down
otherwise she's gonna make all the money
never share it with you
a property
a little bit of pocket money
songs
next round
I hope Chad has snacks because this is
gonna be a long long game
nine
I remember as a kid having Monopoly
games that would last multiple days
yeah
no it would be like leave the board like
that no one touch it
at some expensive parking over there so
damn
I'm just busy I like how I actually like
yeah yeah we're just visiting part
the frame rate on this game is weird
though is there any color that's not
taken at all again yellow
yellow is
yellow nine
oh you can see what cards people have I
see at the bottom um
yeah I think no one has no one owns a
railroad yet
oh
damn it I made like a full loop success
yes the Reading Rainbow
by the trail
the railroad
oh man okay that was also double oh
this is great
this is awful we need to cause Financial
pain and you know as soon as possible
yeah double he's buying up all the
properties
eleven with these huge rolls yes oh I
think I'm stopping but is that my place
oh yeah then you can't do it in a hotel
hello I own this property
thank you
okay I'm in a safe spot it's all good
um
[Music]
lucky salad
can't even go
okay
wait does someone have this color
already
I don't think so yes
[Music]
you call this much money this is nothing
this is nothing
Lucky Seven
what is this no I don't want community
hey does anybody
have green we're sharing
[Music]
with anyone no
can you trade oh you can you can where's
a man
um do I have anything worth training why
do you already want to trade
why would you like it I want to trade I
wanted Monopoly
um well I don't know maybe maybe it's
not time yet I don't think it's time yet
they're still empty uh empty spots
behind
a six
where does it leave us alone
what does bno stand for
piano
welcome to the body odor railroad you
know I I thought of it I didn't want to
say it ah
oh
six buy an order
you're not going in here
a chance
ring rigged
easy game this is an octopus in the
background I love the octopus
you see I used up all my luck playing
before the Stream
oh you're playing I don't know come on
and all the properties I could land on
why does it have to be this one why not
the one next to it honey that's good
yeah
I see
[Music]
no oh no
I'm gonna owe a million dollars here
away
[Applause]
right yeah
this is the worst
thank you so much oh
thank you
this is the worst it's got a paste
holds for you I'm running out of money
oh I'm so close
I think you're at the stars Jail jail
[Applause]
we got her
what was her crime
all right
laughs
a three oh no oh you're not going very
far that is uh
wraps you've been collecting money in
jail I never got money to get out of
jail
[Music]
okay I'll pay for it
yeah so sweet
toothachian mates
we don't care for each other
I have no properties I'm the odd one out
I guess I have more than you do maybe
maybe maybe
smell that 20.
I wish
okay
the awesome bunny owns this one
oh no
oh yeah
maybe fauna maybe that's why I invited
you so that we we myths can come again
nah just kidding there's only one with
like more than a thousand right now you
know you never know you can win big with
the Stars yeah
yeah and sometimes things
away a lot of money from you too so it's
really random no hello
popular place
Well everybody's on my channel now so
this is how it's supposed to be
interesting
thank you
this is the case
I didn't realize it was Tennessee
five
oh yeah I think the names are different
for Kiara
Jail jail
oh my goodness already oh yeah all right
well jayla's always occupied
there's only one one person next
I am I am straight edge say so bird I
don't go to jail
I'm keeping my seat warm for you if my
crime is being killed then arrest me
officer
God damn it why doesn't happen again oh
you're not arrested it's so boring let
me go somewhere else
oh
foreign
no wait does someone own this one you do
oh I do okay well that's fine I guess
all good
wait what if we all just keep landing on
stuff we already own oh nothing really
yeah
if you at least own the whole color
thingy the whole Avenue then you can
build houses but otherwise you can't do
anything
he's landing on their own [\h__\h]
and I'm getting out of here oh really I
let you roll when you're in jail though
you just pay it and then you roll anyway
that's so Mario Party no I don't think
so
I'm getting out of here
what ah okay I'm Gonna Miss You Ina hope
your visit again
oh no kfp tax itadakimasu
at least I'm making money oh no
let's open it
okay not going far one two three who's
who's that
oh it's nothing
[Music]
get some 300 wow okay wow I buy cutting
cutting cream
I would need more properties no okay so
now I have two green ones and Ena has
one green
can I buy this Waterworks yes natural
[Applause]
on it
will not be using the water surfaces oh
no not the water you don't trust my
natural spring water
which spring does it come from oh wow
I'll have to uh
inspect the cleanliness of the wander
hygiene instructions foreign
if you need some pocket money I'll
happily buy
red products
or the blue one the blue one is good
well a chance card why do you keep
getting it
oh 50 not bad not bad
to go to the hospital
yeah Hospital why no internet that's so
loud
having a rough go of it oh
who am I visiting
oh no
at least none of you are getting this so
you think the dice and see what the
future okay my taxes like a good citizen
that I am
oh is this another Community chest
oh yeah oh yeah please be good
unboxing of the gacha oh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
camera excuse me
oh wow all right back in the game yeah
this is how it happens
a nine
okay
[Music]
I'm boring
penguin territory
the Pacific Ocean
okay
too loud you can't roll a one yeah the
double dice is not fair yeah I never get
double dices in this game why I want
double guys too
out of all this game is not fair
what is happening
your turn starts give me something good
please
we'll take it
and it's a 10. I just want more
properties please
oh I think it's new is it open I think
it's open
um
brown brown
more than you know yeah I think Brown is
new that's new yeah
eight
it's four dollars what do you expect
that's enough for taco
so close so close my own place
all right
home sweet home Monopoly all right let's
roll Monopoly
nine
[Music]
yeah
oh ten dollars
[Music]
a pajama party
I like the tropical music
looks like it's like the evening time
now oh yeah oh golden hour do you get a
bonus if you land on here ah yeah that's
just the beginning of the board you
always get 200 here
I thought it was jail too
awesome I'm landing on a cat
no dinosaurs
[Music]
yeah popping your lights on thank you
man please chase a few pennies I don't
care
take it you say that now mm-hmm until I
have my Monopoly and then I'll cry
[Applause]
what the [\h__\h] I'm making moves
another Community Test please be good
they brought the disco party to you
thank you
roll again my doubles
nope sorry
oh no
okay then
to land to Tennessee oh my God no I land
on my own space and
all right
or later on you'll be happy about
landing on your own space but now it's
like give me something else oh another
10.
where do I go is it jail come visit me
thank you enough
he was visiting you I brought you some
cookies oh thank you it's way better
than the phone oh they serve here oh
train station
thank you
last time when everyone played Monopoly
battling
I don't even remember I really knew I
was a kid the last time
okay seems about the same for everyone
can't even remember when it was
long long long ago what is it unowned
oh Ben oh I'm Katina I think you own two
of three properly
oh you're so close
[Music]
otherwise she's gonna build houses on it
I wanna I'm gonna build all the hotels
oh maybe not me this time
oh
this time right yeah
hello thank you have a nice day
honestly
high speed prices
[Music]
somewhere good please
I love what you've done at the place I
don't know like nothing
done nothing yet
please
[Music]
oh man I wanted to buy one
she's not falling asleep
[Applause]
the most I think
well I'm just like corrupt businessman
maybe you know Nature's God deal of
Nature's gotta do oh nice no not nice
oh you could have won at least one more
Square you know
just kind of pay taxes what a city you
don't pay it to anyone about taxes
you get your nails done
oh I see a dinosaur oh body odor
[Music]
yes
wait does it actually say that on your
Maps because for me it has a different
name yeah I think we have different
names because I chose I chose the
language British English probably yes
it's called fan Church Street Station
double final
a double for the bird
um
at least we move on we're moving on
moving on
yes roll it again another double oh no
no no
[Music]
not that lucky right now
the most expensive Square for ish
British British Monopoly how do you say
Monopoly very britishly Monopoly
be a lucky you know realist playing with
my eyes closed I'm just like
oh she's nerfing herself by clothes
closing her eyes I see yeah
I'm telling you there's some squares
that just attract people
mm-hmm
oh sorry fun
oh
it's my own property
come on
do you own the other green places Kiara
uh oh yeah yeah and I want yours
um
offering you know didn't you want to get
on on my good terms again
I don't like to say anything and you
placed me right beside you so I thought
you know maybe it's already worked
foreign
oh no
it's more in free Dallas we're training
oh my God
oh he's paying some extra as an apology
for all the Cockroaches thank you
in my own place because I have a fear of
bugs oh
there's some cute bugs though you don't
do this like all the books no no not
everybody
I'll take the pink who said that Daddy
oh
wait that was good that was good I don't
care about the pink one no you want to
make a trade girl then you can find them
fight fight
collateral damage to the cat
oh no no no no no no no no
35 dollars
[Music]
my turn
thank you
what Nina what do I get for those six
bucks huh
well and I offer a train
oh how do I offer a trade
not sure about that one
I will trade you
oh a red for your pink
oh
[Music]
wait do I even own any room you do you
have one red
one red who owns the other one no Ena I
don't know if they actually get it from
though
wait I've been away for too long my turn
will be bypassed
maybe there's no time to drink
that's my stuff
maybe there's a setting like maybe a
feet of oh you're buying a lot perhaps
I'll Trail you trade you a railroad you
want to train a railroad
I'll trade you are real no no no
it seems like like a Mario party thing
to do
hmm
you're 11.
oh uh-huh okay manage your portfolio
Railroad
where does it lead
you only pay taxes if you pass it or
only if you land on your land on it yeah
that's it oh it's my real room
oh yeah you also own one
where did we go I go
I'm like the biggest investor I feel
like
take it take it
time has come yeah how many properties
are left
I see one light no no the light blue
ones are gone pink ones are gone orange
is gone red is born
oh yeah yellow has one left over I think
uh
uh it's so hard to keep track one yellow
one Brown
yeah two spots are left yellow and brown
each one
gotta try to land on those
um
but Brown is cheap as hell can't make
much money from that
am I going to jail
so the jail
Bush too
kfp jail which is nice
the usual room today we don't serve
chicken we serve duck meat please enjoy
Kiara fried duck
oh I've never heard of that before oh
really
oh it's all right look
duck is like fancy sounds yummy
I get it all the time try anything if
you want to
watch this
you could also fry a penguin if you
wanted to oh no we need to be careful
did they just threaten me yeah I didn't
quite understand why they say that but
probably because later on if you move
too much you just end up spending too
much money sometimes maybe wait I think
if you roll three doubles you go to jail
right oh wait is that right
okay that makes a lot of sense then
that makes more sense because you're
you're too good you know
if you can take it
it's like eating
oh good I need to turn off the eurobeat
music
what you need to turn down the eurobeat
music stop speeding
you're the scary videos
she's feeling guilty oh and who else is
feeling guilty oh you're just visiting
because you miss it yeah
oh four that's my space
your own space
maybe it's time to manage your portfolio
got no time for that
not in stock portfolio nine
one instance
expensive
the bills are rising
who will be the first one to get over a
thousand bucks again
tomorrow
hey
I feel like I shouldn't actually
maybe we could sweeten the deal though
if we'd love me
I just give me two properties Chad would
probably know but are these streets real
like do they exist for real like is this
London streets because I have it in
British English
safe spot
they're real but is there really free
parking in London I don't believe that
wait you didn't get anything no when you
land on free parking you get like a
billion dollars no no no not your
grandparents that's
that's one
that's true after five hours you get a
million bucks on the free parking my
dear Father John oh you're so lucky I
realizing my childhood was a lie
wow
she had nice grandparents can I meet
them can I adopt your grandparents I
have none left
said wow so sad you can meet them oh
did I also have a cat we can play
Monopoly oh yeah they're awesome real
life Monopoly but then they'll probably
still let you win and not me
[Laughter]
oh it's okay chat don't worry it's not
so dark
this is okay Chad don't worry at all
not the community
it's okay you have to get out of jail
free card this [\h__\h] possibly go wrong
you're still going to school back to
school back to school time being in
business classes because I really need
them
well if your childhood was alive then
school was probably also a lie
I got a scam degree on accident I've
been paid so much money it's time to go
to jail for that fauna
time to pay the rent if that was if that
was fake then you're gonna go to jail I
don't think that's legal to fake a
degree no no no no I I'm the one being
scammed yeah yeah that's not an excuse
yeah you're looking at my property
I am
sorry I will settle for a dark blue no
less oh no
thank you
damn well oh wait she's gotta have her
standards good business no less
understandable have a nice day
ah some point we're gonna run out of
money yeah when oh it's the bno oh no
not the piano
for your money
it's just gonna repeat itself endlessly
I'll trade the red for your being a real
real girls
no compromise no no how extreme foreign
territory
what a deal everybody uh drink water
okay maybe not this one of water but
just drink some clean water instead it's
clean I don't believe I tasted it was
but
whoa whoa taste felt like
tasted her water
um it tasted like old old cookies
it's not that bad yeah
that's the natural taste what do you
have against meal cookies
I only like my fresh cookies you know
um
um how about to training some fun water
for a pink
how do you feel about that one oh what
do I get if I get your water you get the
fun and water
is that all yeah the house is on it
but it's on the water you have both the
utilities there guys up there no yeah oh
it's here oh I see
that's probably not worth it because you
can't even build houses on it can you
nope you can't oh no my mine it's not
worth it not worth it
foreign
[Music]
was gonna pass
but think about it think about it
still stands
[Music]
oh it's so slow uh if one utility is own
wind is four times amount if both
utilities are owned rendez ten times
zero ten times
put a pink wait I have two pink you have
one piano I have one pink I can't read
it's okay
oh
yeah oh no
oh yes
you gotta think logically because I
don't think you can ever convince
spawner to sell you two pinks so no one
will ever have the Monopoly on the pink
one unless you trade yours
that's true
unless unless you run out of money
[Laughter]
well by the way
you give me green I give you Orange
hmm the last orange is a girl though
you gotta trade with food or something
that maybe she has
she has
if you get her orange you can you can
give her your blue she'll take that for
sure
yeah
I'll roll for now see where I go
hmm
please let me know if you want to ever
trade your green
okay never mind oh well I see yeah Green
Chihuahua Street
give me
give me give me give me
[Music]
I'll think about it I'll think about it
if I didn't land on the green just now I
will understand yes but you know it's
like nothing in night so it's an upfront
payment
double finally something good good card
please advances
[Applause]
business discussions all right I'll give
you the green yeah
okay I'll try to figure out how to do it
after this turn
trained
[Music]
Taco uh Taco Bell and kfp making
business again no more just business
okay manage properties trade
oh wait no no wait wrong wrong wrong
manage properties
let me quickly uh I'm giving you the
orange right
yes let me quickly uh this is the one it
goes up to
950 and the one quick quick quick
for uh
oh
oh it shows you the total value
wait ah did I ah and then I put the
orange one in
foreign
I don't know how to move this
uh does care I have to do it if you push
r r
or I don't know if it's the bone yeah
okay okay
like green
just move to my green oh oh sorry slow
brain
[Laughter]
money
[Music]
oh
you were ready
120. I will not match a full uh 300 but
oh no stop it stop stop stop stop
I mean the value of the property for
cutting all green is honestly us pretty
hot
100 match maximum 100 my lady no one
twenty one ten
110 110.
Bill oh dear
do you have another
one one fifteen one fifteen one nine
with disrespect wait how does it still
go up to 300.
I don't know
it went wrong oh well okay oh I'm scared
from the hotels that are about to happen
we're fit word for this is so worth it
this is actually so worth it thank you
very much enough for your business
is on hold now
it's a good good business where are we
going
business no
oh
[Music]
I want to be in jail I don't know can I
trade from jail
Hello
friends there
I'm gonna make some jail trains grew up
I might how are you thinking about it
how are you feeling about that the
utility for a pink
you know I'll even throw in an extra for
you oh a freebie if you will
I want your
I don't know if you actually own it
though wait can I see the map
well I can't tell what these little
colored pictures are what are these what
do you what are you looking what are you
looking for
um
pale lilac no idea
get out of here I don't want you
okay so you don't want the roaches but
how about
utility in a red whoa a red
you can't say notes I don't know how
many Reds do I have the one you have one
that's something
not a value look at the value wants that
place extreme value that's pretty good
that's a pretty good author
look at that look at that I'm looking
it's so it's such a good deal for you
how do you feel how do you feel about a
deal
wow
um well
who owns the other red though
and is never gonna give you that no no
no actually I'm gonna give you an orange
beautiful game forward gotta think ahead
yeah yeah we're moving the game forward
that's what we're doing it's not about
when you're losing okay
about Advanced no it's time yeah
um
can I
wait how do I
I think r
yeah oh yeah oh oh
we can only do one per turn oh no I
can't oh yeah and you can only um
you have to keep them all at the same
amount of houses okay
okay
um bam
okay I shouldn't spend all my money
that's good I think
okay
[Music]
let's make trade deals from jail that's
where all them all the deals are made
you never know what's happening but
you're behind that plastic uh wall the
plastic screen on the phone you know
oh yeah you're calling your um
yeah
you want to give me your uh whatever
this is lilac
my lab now
yeah because like money to work I have
only that light blue one and the yellow
one I need to work on one of those
no no don't trade with her give me the
yellow one and I'll give you those no
don't listen to her
foreign
[Music]
next time maybe you can't continue
talking
tricky
[Music]
snake eyes
you narrowly avoided my pink she's a
changed woman jail happened
mortgage I don't know what that means
I'm too young for knowing that means
a new mortgage what does that mean I
think it means you you like make your
property inactive and you get the amount
of money but when people land on it they
don't have to pay you anything else
you can do that to get money
hello Tennessee
huh
oh oh you bought the oh
um
there's still one yellow one left over
and one brown one no one landed on them
yet huh yeah yeah that's me
need big need
are hotels cheaper for the cheaper
properties
or are they always the same price a
seven I don't know
what oh she's going to stonk's territory
oh yes goodbye oh she got the
and the copper the Cockroach one whoa
[Applause]
whoa okay oh I forgot to wait during my
land uh
oh double nice
are you gonna visit me in jail oh no
he's visiting me
wow
hi
I'm in jail
there's one more for today
the orange one
oh wait I can uh I can roll one more
time right
um
for
real good okay okay okay
I wanna buy houses once I'm done moving
oh wow
shark water a hundred okay so how do we
do this again I have all the greens okay
Water Works excuse me I'm a game
wow
[Applause]
okay I'm scared
I'll keep that one the world is becoming
a scary place yeah
okay I am done so I built two houses
I'll keep some money because this is
getting scary
I don't actually want to leave
stay in jail
why you have enough money to pay
yourself out no no no I'm gonna stay
here
the world is scary
she's scared she made friends in jail
yeah yeah this is where my people are
huh
who was the council member who was in
Twitter jail when they debuted uh
[Applause]
[Music]
so those are your friends in jail nice
unless you have to give me their purple
lilac I do I'll change for your orange
you can have a yellow orange how do I do
this
uh you can push y to start it and then
you'll get more time
say where wait why um yeah you can push
it anywhere I think
it's not working I think you got a first
one oh
select the one that you ah we're not
working what the heck it's a bit
confusing
maybe uh maybe Ina can do the to start
the trade because she's next anyway
okay
ah roll first and then trade apparently
oh yeah I'm good good uh
good point
oh there's white to trade here
okay
uh yeah why what am I doing Orange
for one of your down here Vermont Avenue
or Connecticut Avenue
Mall
sure
wait which one are you penguin yeah
the right one is the Penguin
uh
oh God how do I yes orange select your
orange no no no no wait wait wait
oh B oh yeah that's what you're offering
yeah ah select me no the duck is still
penguin what's the orange
I'll try again it didn't work and then
press r r
yes and it's like yeah blue lilac
yeah this one don't you want red so you
can complete the set I also give you
some money 100 the money well that's
only one time the money is only one time
a hundred
you get only 100 one time but so much
more every time someone lands on never
mind I'm just gonna
hold up this one and then what if I gave
you money oh now you want to give the
money oh
you know that's dangerous though she
would have too much Monopoly
true oh [\h__\h] yeah true ghost get a
monopoly out of this you both do yes
people still
[Music]
ah and then she wants one more light
blue one for me probably which I'll
might give you for the yellow one
I'm looking at around 140 in about my
friends
one 140 dollars
and I shall give him
still go faster
how much how much you want how much
money you want 200 even all right sounds
like a deal no wait
business
wow
yeah I'll just last sneak of your life
is just perfect
[Music]
thank you
everybody's making moves
oh wait how do I do this wait what have
I just done it's your turn
wait what because then it just comes
down the probability of landing on
Spaces yeah you've done incorrectly
what I done did I no it's fine
I think it was right wasn't it I I put
in the money she says uh maybe it was on
the wrong side the money wasn't made was
the money I think money didn't count
from Guru that's fine I don't mind
oh there was no money if there's ever
another trade between you two she can
make up for it no no no no no hello
hello third party not part of the deal
no
hahaha
oh no oh no
110. you'll change your mind if I'm part
of the deal once you want that light
blue one from me
and one bad comment I'll have to refink
it
unless
we want the yellow though I don't think
so I'm gonna look at the value though
look at the value mule is pretty good
volume it's like the middle
[Music]
just moving to another property of mine
sweet home
ah whatever
I might just end up
100 bucks left oh
yeah otherwise I'll just sell another
sell another house again another couple
I'll just chill
it's not so bad to be honest you only
have a hundred and you won't like yeah
exactly I don't want to land anywhere
with the plane what was that okay what's
happening
it's Father's turn right oh yeah it's my
turn Okay Okay
card as well
yeah
wait can you not trade from jail do you
have to roll first time right you have
to roll first I think
no never mind managed property not only
I don't know
um I thought you could oh yes
[Music]
oh yeah I don't know I don't really have
anything to trade
um
pretty off here
how about there foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I'll think about it once you have maybe
something I would want more you know
anything yeah she has nothing to work
with I know I never know what's gonna
happen
unless you get rid of your your own
until utilities hmm
[Music]
oh yeah do you place houses
uh um you go to the yeah and then plus r
the r uh-huh yeah you can do it from the
map too I think you don't have not bad
railroads and cruise houses daddy are
Arya
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
one half each
Stokes right
Monopoly
getting there
oh
do you like a yellow
yes
yes yes
um however there's still one empty
yellow left I hope no one else gets it
[Music]
we might want to wait a little bit and
see if someone lands on that yellow one
anytime soon
it's the best Zone
this is just the way the world is going
soon every space will cost you 500 bucks
exactly
how do you win monopoly
can't win everyone else goes broken even
if you win you lost yourself
and turn
well interesting yeah
I don't know how to know how would you
consider selling your brown card enough
no for money no
all right all right
keep in mind
I could throw in and get out of jail
okay
wait are they kicking me out
this ain't a hotel lady
am I getting kicked out you are I just
can't stay no okay
for free
smart
thank you thank you for your red how
come you have to pay to get out of jail
still
a stability let's
that's what I want to say no no no
I never heard of someone before wanting
to stay in jail forever
well you can't collect the paycheck the
200 paycheck if you stay in jail all the
time that's true but I already lost 80
bucks
I've been out one day
it's dangerous out there fauna it is
dangerous world
it's not like playing with your
grandparents
wow two dollar bills wow
the damage
can't fix it anymore oh entering hurts
too much
man you're gonna get that last yellow
You're Gonna Roll it right now where the
hell is that why no one lands on it
it's the legendary yellow
no oh yeah
this is Dino Road baby
I only paid 80 88 dollars
two
[Music]
oh yeah
oh Amy
jumping jump
oh
wow
[Music]
donkey sins for the Super Chat Ina
hello oh
[Music]
aggressive I see I'm going out now
okay
um I hope I don't land on Enos thingy
um
wow fifty dollars
I don't want to go
[Music]
let me go back to jail no it's the dino
we know it's not Dino room
maybe you get the yellow
did I no
no please
finally you have something that yeah
do I have something that you want yeah
[Music]
it's been rough man
[Applause]
I'll train you
um I'm Brown for your yellow
it makes no sense no no no
oh
my yellow Tiara holy [\h__\h] oh my gosh I'm
so scared but it scares me too
oh my God I'm running low oh my God my
yellow fifty dollar rent now all that
orange to Red transition is deadly
girl you give me Connecticut Avenue and
then I'll give you
you can have a taste of Dino Road
oh maybe you just gotta convince Lana
you'll get like you give me yellow I
give you light blue
is that what you're saying yeah
how much how much do you make from light
blue
not much but it's a strategy
I'll take it
wait but I will still need bonus yellow
it's an offer I'll leave it and I I well
maybe gura could give you a railroad and
then oh I'll give you
he doesn't have anything uh trade
because I don't want to get rid of my oh
my green one
okay I will only trade that one that
light blue one for that one black uh
utility or white world or whatever that
is why do you order you're not getting
body of the room
foreign
damn
oh no
it's not like this if the blues get
reunited that's devastating yeah
for fifteen hundred dollar rent
oh
I'm pretty
much
I'm scared the fights are happening I
don't have much
um
excuse me
oh my god oh camera
so generous yeah go eat some ice cream
with that or whatever some hug and Ducks
your favorite ice cream
oh no I think I'm giving it right back
to you does anyone have a favorite ice
cream
and chocolate chip oh no I mean like a
specific brand actually
I don't know
for me it's the Adidas is all right for
me yeah it's nice for me it's one that I
can't even get in my country but I like
the Baskin-Robbins 51 ice cream
labi one that's only in Japan
we're like
oh
[\h__\h]
in Austria please open up and get in
Japan in the summer
I love Baskin Robbins what kind of was a
burger
at what cost where am I ending up
I bet Baskin Robbins has this like
really messed up flavors like cotton
candy
I mean love potion is not only in Japan
I guess the one that I like Love Potion
31. but one time that one single time
when I was in America I checked out the
the Baskin Robbins there and they did
not have the lava potion 31.
what is what is the Love Potion it's um
like kind of uh kind of berry tasting
with chocolate Hearts solid chocolate
hearts
I'm going out
oh what you doing oh my God
[Music]
never should have given up my image
color
oh man
I have a feeling this game yeah
okay you know what
oh good yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I'll wait until the world outside is not
so scary anymore
which leads me to how much does it cost
to put another house on my green ones
200.
I need to make a bit more money
out in here get me out of here meet me
out Mia can you tell me out I don't want
them yeah
you're like a two dollar rent please
it could be more it could be more if you
want to make some trains
railroad for a brown you could have your
end all the way up to like what if three
hundred dollars
[Music]
two two dollar rent what is it a box no
it's a cardboard box I told you I'm not
letting go of my cardboard box
everyone always lands on Bo Railroad I
mean it's better than landing on the
house before Oh my God
oh my God
yes
it's a threat
I can only take the yellow if I can get
a deal with Moana
oh no do you have do I have anything you
want
oh I don't I don't forgive me
by what
All Your Greens well no that's no
it's not happening I guess
unless
do you like ma'am hello
put those on the table let's see let's
look at the value
260. uh-huh
and then the blue one
oh whatever I think and then
oh hmm yeah but the problem is that I
don't know if I'll ever get the other
yellow one from fauna and I think about
that
so I would like you to add something
to make up for that because otherwise it
no Moana I can't turn the phone
otherwise I have nothing to trade if I
give you my last piece
[Music]
um
think two steps ahead yeah
uh I might be stupid generally but when
it when it comes to this I I would not
make this mistake 700
.
hello wow
this is where everything starts falling
apart
I don't like this
all right
[Music]
I'll buy your brown piece you know
I'm Brown for how much running out of
time for 150.
150. that's not enough
better than mortgaging it you only get
30 if you mortgage it
what happens if they put out bankrupt
I think you lose yeah because you need
to sell before they bypass you know
though
just get rid of some of your houses yeah
you are now well by the railroad too if
you want
all right
um how much are we talking three three
hundo the desperation
[Music]
oh whoops sorry oh wait
oh God oh my God
you want my brown and my railroad for
three hundred wow
like that
okay
I wish there was a way to toggle like
hundreds rather than pressing right
oh my God
I'm scared of the future what if I get
out of jail
spot exactly exactly
I'm like
oh man I'll put like I can't
oh no let me give you my yellow
what give me your blue
I give people and you give me yellow
yeah yeah yeah
unless I can paint portal yellow one
that fauna has with money only if she
takes that cashier
[Music]
um
it's real scary you know
laughs
oh
I think yeah I think
this game is scary
do you scare yourself yes
none of us can afford shark Road
alone
once I have some more money would you
let me buy your yellow one just um okay
if I'm bankrupt yes okay okay I'll wait
for that that will happen soon
I'm sure
oh God
alone
uh that's your new title yeah
oh no oh buy that yellow from you hello
okay
wait what no oh yeah fauna no what was
our brothers
hey
those three times call for desperate
measures
100 or no less
yeah I want
I want
um
wow
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
It's 260 that's ma'am
ma'am that's understandable though
because gouda is gonna make so much
money with her houses oh yeah exactly
this is nothing it's more compared to
how much
thank you for well-being she has a roof
over her head
over my head
Instagram don't you want all the
properties on the board
I will never trust your word ever again
because you first promised that yellow
one to me
he said if I'm bankrupt and you're
paying then I'm buying well now I have
to last two pieces that Buddha ones both
in both the blue one and the yellow one
yeah why not mean it's good I would give
gura maybe the yellow one or the blue
one if she gives me the two others
then we both have one Monopoly
wait what you can uh instead of
me giving you both the last pieces that
you need how about I give you yellow you
give me blue or the other way around
both of you Blues in that case
or the both of the yellows I love this
one
attention because I mean otherwise
you're never you're never gonna get them
from anyone else because I have them
that's true
okay
this city is really nice it's really
expensive when we say blue you mean part
of town the icy blue right
yeah yeah yeah yeah because that's the
only one I have
like to make a trade man
would you like to get your first
Monopoly Second Monopoly Second Monopoly
yeah
oh no hello ma'am but I will take the
one that uh where the rent is higher
so you want the icy blue one I'm not
sure which one it is but yeah if that
one is actually blue
wait how do I
wait isn't yellow higher
the yellow I need to check that
was definitely hot yeah
yellow's high so now you want yellow yes
I want the two yellows so I give you the
light blue
well let's just
oh
Road
[Music]
get me out of here
God damn
I'm fine
thank you take me to jail I live here
now I don't want to go to jail
the birds are in jail Birds once again
like Twitter well I'm staying
laughs
I'm staying
I live here now I'm gonna
oh
you think what do you think
give me your yellows but shark Road
become a reality
area for potential really high return oh
no no I'm only taking the yellow
um I will take the two if you are okay
with that I will start the trade
unfortunately no ma'am
then shark Road will never go never come
true keep on dreaming
the 99 is all right I'll take it what
[Music]
99 completion it's only one color off
she's scary I called you I told you
girls what do you want to do
I want
no ID you can no no I want
this and this
is
[Music]
well you never get those two those two
monopolies will forever be refused to
you you'll never get those two
never never I think she'll be fine
without it I'll be honest
[Laughter]
laughs oh I don't want to be I would be
so bad if the game suddenly crashed
because of the internet connection oh no
no no
I switched recently when I was playing
Pokemon
crushed okay yes yes Pokemon correct
many times many times
right right that game notorious for
crashing especially when you don't get
the Pokemon you want
when you run out of pokeballs it's a
great timing to be honest so I'm not
even mad
oh I guess so
[Music]
um
between me fauna and Ina who's like the
worst off right now I feel like we're
all like that's definitely
[Applause]
um I guess sometimes you have to pay the
price
but you have a lot of expensive houses
I'm doing okay
I think I'm the worst it was the red
house
oh red house
whoever lands on the next shark space is
the worst yeah
yep
[Music]
because none of us can afford it no
the loan shark is coming for you
three I never want to land any nail
clothes it's gonna happen
happening you know let's stay jail
forever hello Ina I see you are in some
uh she wants the blue now deep water
would you like to trade that blue that
shiny blue for some money you turns
thank you very much
[Music]
yeah I like it here it's safe
um
oh no I need to get out
I have to get out now
bye Kiara I don't want to go I have to
make you okay to get out even okay
number on that real space themselves now
oh really oh there's still the people
are landing on it oh
it's okay
okay
oh my gosh I landed I threaded the
needle we're saying for one more turn
oh
that was pretty good maybe something
good
okay I'll take it 25. who are you
Consulting
um I don't know probably my jail friends
[Music]
so one stopper I am like that good dice
good dice
where is she going go to jail oh you're
visiting me oh hi did they give me that
blue hello
do you have a moment to sell me that
beautiful piece
stay strong stay strong
oh
foreign
people are underestimating gouda because
she's really into board games and yeah
I understand it now Laura are going to
be strong
yeah
underestimated
I like the shark strange oh
go back for free okay free words for you
where is Dad where's Dad where's Dad
where's that you know
oh oh that's also not very good
enough
[Music]
uh I'll give you some money for that
yellow
I only take another property for that
um
oh that's okay I'll just um
what I'm not inactive I'm doing it right
now stop stressing me out game
okay how smart I didn't know you could
do that yeah
yeah all good all good all good in the
neighborhood whatever is this is correct
do I still have
I'm confused I'm back
okay
there's someone Wanna Give me two bucks
two pennies
can you trade something for nothing
oh well I'll give you two bucks for
nothing oh oh never mind never mind
thanks though thank you uh back to make
up from my past betrayal a little bit
you know it's so expensive
you know I'm suffering
I'm sorry oh God oh God I don't want to
roll
same too
please let that be high enough to get
out
oh oh you're passing shark Street
are you still in shark Street okay well
at least it doesn't have the houses okay
I hear her breathing I'll keep you all
safe she'll never get that yellow one
unless she gives me the blue one oh no
the other way around or so
at this point I might just even take the
blue room
it's a dangerous okay
oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
spices are just stuck in there
between my props for days
it's so free
but jail is so good it was safety
harsh world
why do I never win in these kind of
games man
it's always just about luck and I still
always fail where's the Phoenix
I don't want to get out yet
at least you can afford it now
it's fun
oh it is
oh no but the next row
uh a big roll okay Five Points five
I want to go around straight but the
yellow one I think no no
oh yeah
um
I will uh I will actually
um I will be okay to give you the uh
sorry the other way around the one that
that the cheaper I'll give you
um uh the yellow one if you give me the
two uh um uh blue ones you just have to
match me enough to pay the rent here
okay so otherwise I'll die you don't
think it doesn't matter yeah
wait let's let's try it look oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] uh uh wait I I will also give away
here then then it should somehow work uh
what you owe money I'm not an active
shut up now uh so when we're doing uh
we're doing uh this
um no no uh oh God oh God oh God I'm
under pressure
enough money in the game
can I get this in writing oh the economy
uh uh let's wait how much do I even
I still probably won't be able to um
yeah
[Music]
uh 750 oh my God
well they do indeed not really make much
money now anyway
um
how do you mortgage
this okay so I'm not losing it right I
can always reactivate it
what wait is that not so that's that's
still not enough though is it
you might have to do more possible
where's the other one
[Music]
sorry sorry it all comes tumbling down
foreign
are you kidding me
oh I don't want to
people you have to mortgage all
everything how do I make money then
it don't hurt but that's not oh dear
I want to trade please
foreign
can someone do the math here how much or
um
what what I give you um I give you wait
how much more do I need uh I need I need
I think like 400 oh damn you might get
out of jail card I don't really have
much to give
oh
well I I okay I mortgage this one too
and then okay okay if we do this and you
give me 200 then I think it's enough
um I you give me 200 and I gave you the
yellow one that you want
uh and you also please give me um
the blue one
no wait uh yeah yeah no yes yes
how about that how about that
so I'm giving you the yellow and enough
to not be bankrupt no no you're giving
wait wait wait what am I no but you're
also getting the 600 or the 700 from me
anyway because I'm paying rent to you
yeah so yeah what do you want from me uh
the the blue ones that make less money
than than yellow anyway I just give you
the yellow one and give me can you give
me a property that you mortgage bill
s oh let's test it out uh
oh God this requires a lot of brain
power right now from me I uh I I gave
this and then no no the other way around
right oh I give it seems like I can do
it confusing I give this
uh and then I take this and this
but also I will need
the money
uh to survive to pay you because this is
in the end just going back into your own
pocket right
yeah
is taking this money in order to pay the
700 bucks for your red sponge
it's not how it is
wait what how do you what happens when
you sell a mortgage property though wait
I would need 500. are you giving to me
uh no you will receive it on mortgage
diving I don't know
it's okay does anyone know if I give her
a mortgaged one just to get mortgage
stays
says one person it says two people okay
um well but it's not so expensive to to
rent it it was cheap originally
oh I don't know I don't know
[Music]
okay what happens when you bankrupt all
you don't leave the game you can come
back I don't know if I bankrupt then um
the game is over at least for me you
guys can continue playing I'll just
watch
I don't know I don't know I'm pretty
comfy right now also I don't have that
much money maybe when I have more money
more money funny
it's Monopoly what do you want for me
[Laughter]
okay do I have enough now
you have enough but no no property
yeah okay this is enough well I didn't
get it back yes
okay
just stand to do many laps around the
next turn it might be the end of me oh
my goodness
what I'm scared of me
I guess I'll have dinner so once you
guys continue to play
don't worry I'll be doing it
I believe
I think this might be the reason why why
we stop stop playing Monopoly yeah
Monopoly at some point because we get so
adults uh we get out of the childhood
and then we lose the ability to not get
salty we get so old that Monopoly always
makes us salty and feel pain I feel like
as a child you don't feel that pain just
quite that much yet
I always feel pain yeah
yeah no matter what age and now that I
brought it back I I forgot the feelings
I forgot the feelings that it could
awake inside of me
that's right he just wanted to have
grandparents who let you win that's the
only way to enjoy Monopoly I adopt them
oh how nice to land on your own field
how nice
[Music]
houses but I'm too scared look she has
so much money now that she can now get
even more houses on her own fields
I'm done you can buy that yellow off you
know
essentially isn't that just
it will be mortgage though
yeah what happens I need what happens
you just have to buy it back which is
not no problem with your money
um
well but now I
but that will probably not even help me
much well
let's I
only for some extra money though
some pocket money so if I buy the yellow
one for you yes
that means that you get to survive
hmm you better give her like 800 for it
though
survive for how long
think think
wait how do I do this
it's happening you just click on one of
the ones you own
which one are you ducky um
the duck out of La girl once we don't
want
oh no no you just first have to um
[Music]
I think you first pressed the light blue
ones now because you're on your side
no I'm just gonna give you money are you
yellow
no no no no I'm taking blue tiles and
money only
we're back
now it's blue tiles and money yeah
before I wanted the yellow ones I
already actually went down with my
requirements because first I wanted the
yellow ones to have a more out of it but
now I'm taking now I'm settling for a
one-time payment and the blue ones
you gotta appreciate the dedication
I'd rather leave this game than give the
shark Street any more power turn Starts
Now why all right because micro world
you can be a part of something great
yellow tile
I'll eventually pass
[Music]
for now
I love to see another day
okay if I give you that just for money
then I would be part of your foundation
but it would be my skeleton buried in
the foundation we'll build a park bench
and we'll put your name on it
it'll be great it's not enough to honor
me
no no I have a watering fountain as well
a bench and a waterfront the fountain
made out of Heroes tears
I just want my salary
oh thank God please something good
[Music]
life insurance matures though does it
happen you died
must get money
I'm a little bit safe for a moment
a moment
let me pass go
oh yeah cockroach alley it's time to
manage your portfolio
on mortgage next time
on the mortgage
I think I'm going to jail not fair yeah
keep her there you have to stay out of
jail money
money I'm not sure which one is better
oh man no oh man yummy
[Music]
seems hard
purple you know what it's okay at least
I have the Monopoly over Europe Europe
as a live streamer
I have the European time zones all for
myself
okay
come on let me get my salary and that's
worth more actually than this stupid
game
I'm I'm smelling cockroach Avenue
real life saver
honestly four dollars I'll make it I'll
take it this is all it costs
I'll take it
I'm sorry to have invited all of you to
such a suffering game I didn't think it
would be like this
where am I Landing
please be kind to me
oh it's enough
not the blue one on it yeah
50 bucks doesn't seem so bad
700. actually it's more expensive it's
like 900 now
did someone just roll a dice really
no no
Monopoly in real life
think I'll get this one back at least
for now
okay
oh is that candy okay
[Music]
well she's recreating this whole scene
on a real Monopoly field
of course of course feels even better
that's why she's looking down all the
time utilities no not utilities
let's go on the strike 90 is better than
900. yeah I think I'm gonna play
like these pinks are not enough
I'm gonna play a risky game
do it like it ah
the best thing bankruptcy let's go
he's investing she's starting to believe
but I'm gonna be in trouble if I land on
shark's face are you getting real close
to Taco laying in shark Street yeah the
Ocean Ocean Avenue
oh
you're going oh you don't even want to
pay for getting out of jail in there get
out of there
it's my turn to sit in the gym
I mean you do for all the crimes you've
committed but
what I'll help you break out
I'll commit my own friends
[Music]
eh
um you just buy it's a hotel room it's
just a little more expensive
how do you do that
wait can you not get it all right it's
too expensive you need to pay one files
wait no no 150 but yeah
I try R again
oh oh I see
um
my god well well
well
oh
cool serious
serious
oh no amounts of super chats is gonna
save me from this
I cook PG
is that tears oil and I don't want to go
to shark alley why it's got really nice
um
one red house is filled with blood
outside and inside
um
let's roll the dice yes
yes
come on Duck
oh hello
[Music]
thank you
I'm gonna choose one I don't know oh God
cannot afford
can I put these
okay welcome back I'll sell it again
when I need money again
okay
no I don't want to go oh by the way to
lift the hood a little bit
um have you guys always played the
normal Monopoly or like a special kind
because there's like so many different
ones which would you like I used to
adore the credit cards oh no you lucky
credit card
I am oh man
gaming I used to play and this was my
favorite uh Lord of the Rings themed
Monopoly all the streets and everything
the figures it was all under the Rings
it was really cool lots of references
you know
oh fun I was starting to buy up
I have to
gotta stay in the game wait is there
Pokemon with no Queen
there's a lot of weird monopolies out
there yeah there should be Hollow live
Monopoly
is this not real life I thought this was
no we don't actually have to play it if
we're just on the board
just put our names on the board and
don't make us play
when I was so confused I Googled Pokemon
whole life no no no Pokemon Monopoly
my whole life would be cool too sounds
nice
there is Pokemon Monopoly
oh cute
oh the fingers of Pokemon
okay 40 I take it I take it nearly I'm
missing
there's also fortnite Monopoly
there's the credit card one there is a
fortnight Monopoly
what the books of course oh is that good
or bad is that good or bad now look it's
on the bad side because you're entering
uh housing Lane I was so close to jail
[Applause]
what do you mean don't give up
oh what do you mean don't give up is
this a joke to you or
I can't I don't think I can even if I
mortgage all of it
I would have to keep you in the
window fauna
yes
I don't know why do you want to hurt me
so much
I'm just trying to make a living out
here like I this is
Dark World
I'm more advanced at all
um so I can only trade but I don't want
to give into it no
um I would buy some properties from you
only for light blue and some cash
or just cash
on my easy properties for that yellow
potentially
let's see wait so wait how much do I
have to pay again I forgore I'll give
you
wait is it 450. there's demand
how much was this 450 and I'm now at
like 200 something 208. okay I'll give
you 250 for yellow
final off but then you'll just start
trading with Gouda and make more money
no no no I'm doing this directly it will
end up in good as hands anyway so I'll
do it directly I don't need a middle man
here nor a middle woman so
um I am offering this one uh
I need a
450 minus 208 how much money do I need
no
I don't want to do math 150 minus 208
okay I need 242. good that's all I need
that's all I need
and and those properties of course
oh
yes yeah I'll trade you yeah
so the game
can you look 242 242. it won't even hurt
her she won't even flinch
you'll see she'll finish that shark road
and it will be the end of all of us why
does it take so long to choose this
amount of the future that you want
well if I have to stop it and all of us
have to suffer
uh this is this is kind of stupid uh can
we not just put in numbers and what the
hell with this yeah once they have like
digit you could just put it in so close
so close so close 200
maybe three bucks or five extra
I hope I'm getting the money this time
though okay well you didn't impress uh
you didn't press the amount Kiara please
go I'm not gonna get any money
you try thank you at least you've tried
sorry
um
[Music]
at least you tried huh
why does why do I have to press to
do that
hey what if I refuse this offer though
[Music]
I am having second thoughts because I
need to [\h__\h] my own bank account
before I start making you save another
plan
[Laughter]
I'd watch there it is okay you're fine
and oopsie
let's see
this menu
add money
damn
there we go there you go
oh that would put me almost in
[Music]
you're getting ready to play it's gone
and land on red immediately don't worry
will they go yeah yeah
[Music]
um
what what
a counter offer
it's getting interesting
but how would I pay it could I will have
to go bankrupt then
oh no and then you're yellow
well now if if this trade will end up
making me bankrupt anyway then I'll just
go bankrupt about giving you my stuff
okay
okay one more time when we're done
uh hi and oh
Hi and hi and
corruption there and the deal there huh
no no well how can you just re-mortgage
yes
we we have uh come to an understanding
we've reach the understanding
when you get kicked out of the game does
your property go back to the bank and it
becomes free for these things
eventually it ends up that way um
huh
[Music]
you you prefer it doesn't mean that you
prefer me to kill bankrupt right now
well I would lose less if I just wasted
you to go bankrupt and then I just need
to get the auction piece
you
what
[Music]
wow okay friendships do end with this
game
oh no
oh no no
[Music]
I'm out
no
no I'm gonna order some food did I get
everything have fun for now I support
you whoa
oh it gives you everything
we pay the Morgan whoa oh that's how I
did it wow
oh wait it's all oh oh I see oh yeah
that makes sense okay
um why can't I afford all this
oh
why is it so expensive
she has a lot of mortgages I can save
you man I'll give you some money for
that yellow oh it's so expensive
car she's still in jail oh yeah she's
chilling no I got one more
I think I want more
I think when I had one more left that
was the turn that I had to get out in oh
oh you get to roll once more and then
you have to leave if you don't roll with
dumbbells
oh yeah they do
[Music]
free the dino
thank you I'm about to die though
I don't know I feel like I'm next
I'm getting close
[Music]
that's a lot of properties on your
wallet your uh wallet looks like but
your load looks heavy would you perhaps
care to
I don't know well we'll see where I land
how in trouble I am
what are we feeling like pizza
Asian Pizza
Austrian
is it my property I am saved
for another turn all right someone wants
some burgers
[Music]
pour some pizza
okay you know what I said before we
started the stream how following girl or
completely strong I was not wrong I knew
this would happen
I don't think I'm in a great spot
no no oh
oh you're feeling okay
okay
Advanced to Illinois Avenue
I have no idea it's not life
oh oh
it was like two spaces ahead
it's my own place
I feel my end like coming here
by world
oh it's safe
for now
or now you're gonna live another turn oh
I live another turn
I like how there's a piggy bank balloon
that's warning you right before you go
around this corner
like that's gonna be you oh
no your wallet's so light you're gonna
float in the air uh-oh penguin house oh
hello at least it's the cheaper of the
three
okay I can easily pay that
but what I can pay is what's about to
happen next
oh I can feel the end coming closer
yeah
[Music]
Fried Chicken Boy
girl water sure this walks past
everything you know it's just Wonderland
she owns this place
hmm
[Music]
can I do anything I don't think I can do
anything oh
what why did you
oh I don't know stutter no no I'll steal
you the yellow for
a thousand dollars a thousand dollars
sacrifice your advice to cheer me up
with some good fried chicken
so that's a high income property
blue the dark blue
oh
I don't think we need you
you can easily get a thousand dollars if
you just saw some hotels
all right
aha
oh no oh no
no no no no no no no no oh lucky where's
the juiciest eyes
[Music]
oh that's a lot of money to him okay
that's not bad not as much as a thousand
not as much as a thousand
all right let's go what was gonna happen
huh oh I landed on it all right all
right it's time you leave home at least
it's not the hotel
maybe a desserts
[Music]
oh I'm sorry
chicken covered in chocolate
I don't even have any more you'll have
to like sell houses and
um if I still beat no no Halloween
I love this part of town no we don't
girl loves this part of town
I don't owe money but I'm inactive if I
do not play with 70 seconds something
hold on oh is it ending for you too
bankrupt everything
okay oh
wait then why would I want to trade with
me if
what are you gonna trade here okay girl
how about how about this one is the end
near
I don't think so I'll be honest
I don't feel way too no that's that's no
just giving up everything no not too
easy that's what yeah all that all that
stuff that I left you everything
don't make it go to waste farmer don't
make it
fight on fight on look you have to give
me a look you're gonna get a ride back
okay because I'm paying it to you that's
the same logic that I offered her but
she didn't accept it that time
it's free it's super yellow
that stupid yellow take it take it take
it the pillow
what if if like I don't know the rule
though like what if what if wait is this
you're gonna have enough money to pay it
back though are you just gonna suddenly
I don't know I might have to sell some
stuff let's start
um
what if I don't
I mean you don't have to
you can you can end my suffering right
now
you can put me out of my history
shoot I don't know
trust yourself this is what it means to
be business mogul
I have to make tough decisions when
you're at the top I'm scared I don't
know what's gonna happen this game is
confusing what is gonna happen is she's
gonna go bankrupt I know what to do I
know what to do
um
yes yes make Ina strong insteading
I don't know
but I'm not really ready for this this
is cheating
no no
I actually don't know because I I mean I
thought you could auction the properties
afterwards I didn't know
whoa I'm giving it all away
you're gonna have to pay for that though
aren't you no
just
take it it's gonna be part of umisi up
against each other
the battle of the Giants of the sea
I don't know if I'm ready for it
oh my God it's not ready for this
if there's demand there will be I'm
sorry guys
I'll carry on you will I don't know for
how long
still Indians I mean if that's not a
deal then I don't know what it is but I
should have given you my money I don't
know if that's even though oh oh dear oh
God now this is interesting
how is that gonna
play out
I honestly don't know
interesting but avina wins then I'll
feel bad because I basically I don't
think I'm winning I'll be honest
they both have some chances now
um
Goodbye Oh yes
we saw they went to grow ourselves
even
okay
what are you eating for dinner tonight
huh I don't know I haven't even eaten
lunch yet so first I want to share some
some fried chicken
um is it tofu chicken oh [\h__\h] yeah
you're right you're a vegetarian or
vegan vegetarian right
[Music]
of course it is of course it's tofu it
always was always has been that's what
you're saying but I'm not so sure
right Cafe you want to be eaten by fauna
don't you
no you've got property and houses I'm
tofu I promise there you go
races make my stinky taxes
honestly I'm quite scared
from now on wait what does this board
look like this is mostly you you know I
mean look what your spaces have houses
yeah I am very strong houses
I split my earnings equations
unintentionally but that way
through the land
foreign
Passage
please
oh okay not bad
okay 25 25 I'll take it I'll take it
[Music]
away your turn Starts Now
I mean I think I have like no properties
and wait what the [\h__\h] the rest so I
feel like we're just dragging this out
yeah
it's gonna end pretty soon
to turn around though
maybe Greg can trade all her properties
to enough for no reason just for funky
quirky girls quirky girl things
I'm training all my properties away I'm
just so different you know
hmm
your time has come
[Music]
where is girl I see hello
you know I feel like
I can't sell property right that'd be
you could sell it to grow up
hello
you could you can start a grin then if
girl lands on on orange she'll be in
trouble
good
what do you want girl
what do I want
but you want it all
every last property
we can decide after two
I just realized they at least the place
you go to oh I see yeah
oh
safety
just barely
just man barely who could have been mine
this could have been mine it could have
been yours
now I'm what happens when you're
bankrupt maybe we get to go into a nice
deserted island or something live off
the grid for a while maybe I'll buy a
sailboat and sail around the world
around the world
a world travel
yeah maybe we can get a little sailboat
a fixer-upper
you
oh oh that's actually a good
um segue to start playing raft let's
make a raft
right right we don't need any money to
build a raft
let's start eventually we'll have some
goats and stuff on on the raft
will be more
much more of a happy game right we're
Cooperative unless we start throwing
each other off into the ocean no no one
does that in rap do they I don't think
so there are sharks in the water though
yeah sharks and Monopoly and unwrapped
we're always waiting to eat us up
yeah
it's just so tasty hmm
thank you
it's the gravy it's the gravy that makes
it so good well let's see if RNG can
carry me
it's now or never
let's go let's go oh my God
mortgage off the previous land so I feel
like it's gonna end in like
a rounders or one Loop
you mean you're gonna mortgage cockroach
Ally oh
thank you oh okay oh no my Heritage Now
or Never my beautiful heritage
[Music]
okay that's already mortgage
oh I can't okay
how's the business going in yeah
about four houses
[Applause]
[Music]
honestly interesting
[Applause]
okay I think I can manage one more
time
no what's foreign
It's All or Nothing
Tennessee let's go Tennessee
okay
I'll never I feel like you're just gonna
go fast
[Music]
Tennessee
oh it's not it's the free part that it
costs everything
[Music]
ah I mean it was All or Nothing
All or Nothing
I still tell you something
oh never mind
still
uh oh where are you going all right this
is it this is it in the end
um
[Music]
I don't think I can make it out of here
alive
oh thank you install
[Laughter]
I did
yeah
we love it but
GG girl that was a monopoly yeah
you destroyed us all
mogul
oh
I unlocked the tortoise I unlocked the
horse now I can be the horse girl I've
always dreamed of being a horse girl
um
[Music]
just trying to order food I can't even I
can't even do order food nor can I get a
monopoly
unfortunate
well you should play a game of life
live
I like life yes I have a little less Cut
Throat I've never played that before
whoa I don't think I have ever played
that before I don't know how to play
that it sounds dangerous though maybe
next time if we can all just like off
collab like one big off collab we can
all play a game of life like a box
this is
um yeah oh well uh thank you for
joining this collab
um uh it was beautiful uh I'm so glad
this happened uh wow yay
yay
at the moment but it was fun and bonding
time
I have no resentment towards anyone here
yeah no no no resentment no reason
I didn't want to be in business owner
anyway
honestly honestly I have another
business I hope that one would go
bankrupt my kfp business yes
successful I gotta say you know yeah I'm
counting on that one I'm putting on all
my stunks into that one hoping that at
least that doesn't fall apart
uh oh yeah well
um
okay so that's it um yeah
yeah there's someone gonna say something
thanks for watching this part of town
yeah
[Music]
um
yay let's play Monopoly again someday
with other people
let's go separate away sometimes yeah
with other people rematched with other
people
no actually I was really thinking to um
next time because this time I invited
like you know N A Time Zone girls I
wanted to next time invite sea time zone
girls do like um a round of the
Australian girls or whatever
um I'm getting some Japanese Yeah
country living girls and so on to switch
it up
um that was already planned that is not
me being salty although I I will admit
there might have been some saltiness but
that will be sprinkled on the onto the
Fried Chicken then I'm gonna be eating
Urban spices
tofu of course but I will need some time
to heal the salt is hurting my my veins
it's good okay you'll recover I believe
well it's very dramatic though I like I
like to when everyone else went bankrupt
that was nice oh yeah so fine I really
like my final struggle isn't it moves on
a Pokemon I started struggling that was
that is
like that is that the only way a
Monopoly game ever ends just by having
everyone else go bankrupt
well then it is what it is
there can only be one who rules over a
city yes this is the modern day and age
now hope you swim yeah
okay well thank you
thank you girls for joining and thank
you for having us you know thank you for
coming
thanks for inviting us thank you
I hope you had fun as long as as long as
y'all have fun everything is cool yay
thanks for watching I'll see you guys
soon I think I have a day off tomorrow
so I'll see you the day after tomorrow
that's right
what's up thanks thank you
bye on Saturday guys
coming back
yes yes I'm waiting for you bye-bye me
[Music]
foreign