[Music]
a
the
n
[Music]
the
now
the and I'm home
finally you
I
[Music]
even in the dark times I hold my hand up
right to the light I see you and you see
me it's our la la
brush
K KY
k
h wait my
chat what are you doing up there I told
you don't go up
there
chickens you have to sit in the usual
place K I don't know if I'm a rudol or
or Santa today I might just I'm just
both today
[Music]
okay guys do you think it's safe let me
let me stop this now it's so beautiful
um this is a new 15 hours ago this was
put up on YouTube this is a new uh uh
remix or the first remix ever of one of
my album songs love
brush it's a it's a holiday remix can
you believe it oh my god oh I love that
it's so beautiful it's called it's
called Holiday Rush not love
Rush Yeah by Jeremy Robson if you guys
want to check it out look it up on on
the YouTube it's so pretty I might be
using it uh until like end of
December I don't know if you're
listening Jeremy but thank you so much I
really love it I love to have like like
holiday or season of remixes of my songs
and nobody remixed love rush or any of
the new song no wait never mind that's
probably not true
or no it might be true because I I think
I I I saw like a f ice remix but I don't
think did I see a remix of any of my
other songs blah blah blah I did I Tew
maybe okay maybe they do okay okay well
anyway do you guys think it's safe to I
have I have uh steam open on a browser
on a browser that I never use Microsoft
Edge oh what the is that go away
what was
that is it Edge I think it's Edge yeah
is it safe I'm not logged in and it's
like something I've never uh the browser
I never used it
before e
Ed I I want to lose the edge
perms yeah we're super edgy
today uh oh should be fine should be
fine should be fine right probably yeah
and just so you know like we're we're
just going to I'm going to write all
these games down um we're not going to
like buy it immediately I'm going to
write it down because I think I can't
even gift it like immediately to the
girls because I don't think I'm friends
on Steam with all of them and I have to
be friends right or at least know their
accounts
I suppose uh cuz I I I can't just get
game codes right I wish I wish I could
just get game codes that's but that's
only like if you if you're like a
publisher or so right so we're just
going to write it down and then I'm
going to behind the scenes going to get
everybody's friends uh uh on Steam and
then
yeah oh by the way if you hear what
do you hear this maybe not with the B G
but if you hear like loud weird cranky
caky crank sounds
like in the background that's um not my
cat's snoring it's
uh weird sounds in the walls when it's
windy it I hate
it what if they already have it well
obviously we're going to try to get them
games that they don't have um okay well
yeah let's explain the
stream um
it's totally not a coincidence I totally
pled this on purpose to fall perfectly
into the beginning of the steam winter
sale um I I wanted to do this um stream
where uh because it's almost Christmas
I'm going to buy games for all of the
whole life English members because if I
just gifted for certain members then
it's going to be like yo she hates the
others so I have to gift 14 people gifts
uh but we're just going to go with some
cheaper ones here and there but that's
no problem because even the cheaper ones
are really really lovely I have some
ideas maybe maybe maybe I also want to
discover some games that I don't know
about so we're going to be like browsing
for steam whatever they throw at me
whatever you throw at me um we can look
at the trailers and all that I have
permission for that as long as it's not
like ba like I don't know porn game or
so that would be a
problem um so I wna I want I I think
like I want to mainly aim for like
Charming um Indie Games yeah and I'm not
even going to think about permissions um
it would be cool if it's a game I have
permissions for but I don't want to look
up each game we can probably um get
permissions even if we don't have it at
the moment uh can probably start that
process afterwards
in my opinion there's
one well let's say number one gift that
would be like the the biggest prize to
get in my opinion and it should be your
opinion too whoever gets
tunic somebody will get tunic whoever
gets tunic a hi Lissa don't you're going
to see your
present no I'm not I'm not going to I'm
not going to do yours now m but whoever
gets tunic will be the winner basically
because like that's just winning in life
I I wish I could give everybody tunic
cuz tunic is the best have
fun love you don't go don't look yeah
it's presents you can't
look yeah so I I I have like uh steam
gift cards ready to buy the games but I
I don't mind if it goes over the budget
of that I'm just going to get more steam
gift cards I can only use steam gift
steam gift cards at the moment because
of my Steam account being weird hi steam
if you're watching this help me out
please oh yeah tunic tunic is also oh
you say only but I I mean better than
nothing I could probably get tunic for
free
though I might try getting a game
code I'm straight for tunic in it's the
F that counts okay um if I do you guys
remember when I play tunic didn't they
like offer
me like steam Cates for tunic to give to
others I don't know I don't think I have
any like ready to go it was like more
like oh if you need anything let us know
I think that was a thing what if I give
everybody
tunic no no I want to give tunic to to
people at least who who I think will
might play it if
I I I honestly think me giving them
games we might really get them to play
them so we got to think hard about this
what do we want to see them play and we
also want to see them enjoy the
games tunic sponsorship no no no I don't
want to be no because I love tunic and
and they deserve free advertisement from
me oh you know what I forgot to do what
I wanted to do I'll just do it on the go
um like let's we're going to focus on
one member each and and like think okay
let's do groni and then we go through
the library to find something for cron
like ideally if you find something on
the way for someone else we'll go back
to that but I want to go like one by one
so who should we start with cuz um I
want to look up their debut streams and
make take a screenshot of their interest
in Gam from when they first deed hi
M A
Spyro interesting you're you're
Spyro create a wheel to choose uh uh
okay well
no uh Su go in De okay okay K oh her
D her deut
stream M deut okay I I'm just going in
like quickly oh
God I
just oh my God this lo oh this loading
screen oh
oh do you remember oh does this sound
familiar to
anybody it's the the yeah you know what
this is the introduction trailer for
myth back then our trailers were still
pretty um low budget but it was cool it
was cool but compare to
now compare to now you
know oh she doesn't she jo like
immediately show up and sing something
now I'm kind of interested in making
this into a reaction
stream
wait oh oh remember how the smoke like
killed her uh laptop or whatever
whatever she was streaming on oh
ding
dong ding dong oh she's so
laggy she's so laggy and she's using a
shitty
microphone I mean for the
graphic here we
go
why am I watching this
um
hello on
[Music]
no
no I can't do
sorry I can't do this let's skip to her
game
interest talk to me anytime about mafia
movies out here okay
there we
go all right this is what I need
screenshot I mean I feel like you know
some of their interests may have changed
and all that but I just want to use it
as a guideline games
Cali okay shut up I have Casper
in my walls again it seems
oopsie okay do you hear this this so
up do we hear it it's like
somebody's
like uh going back and forth on a on a
on a on
a sh on a shle so here is good old CI
from three years
ago she said she likes from software
games not buying you that ghost of
tsushima no Castlevania I mean okay
we're not going to buy those cuz she
already has them or played them so weird
RPG Mega games or platforms especially
oh I already have the perfect thing for
her
I I already had the perfect thing for
her Orie can I give her
aie oh I want to give her
Orie because it's sides scrolling right
and I feel like it's kind of like with
her loving jump King and all that I feel
like she she would like this
yeah I don't think she ever played it
and I I have to support or how much P oh
what 5
EO
wait waa what a steal what a deal what a
steal what a deal let me make a let me
make a list here I need a I need a
list
okay I think that was too easy that was
too easy Callie or should I give her
both is the second one cheap
too uh wait was the first one is blind
for blind for there so ah it's it's 10
wait what ah yeah uh 10 and five yeah
yeah yeah of course okay okay let's give
her two
games and Cali gets uh aie one and two
you're welcome it's a really good game
for people who don't know let's watch
the trailer cuz I'm allowed to do that
actually so
yeah um from beginning please from from
the beginning wait my music shut
up is there a bundle I don't see
one maybe if I go to this one maybe it
shows me a bundle
oh a yeah that's a bit cheaper this way
I'm saving like maybe uh one one or so
the bundle okay okay okay well let me
show
you you guys know is there somebody who
doesn't know
[Music]
aie it's so pretty and austrians made
this game Studio from my
[Music]
country music is beautiful Graphics are
beautiful gam playay is really really
dope I I played this uh on my
channel a long time ago it's pretty
[Music]
sad
oh
Mom yeah I'm like really hyped with your
new
game hey is it up on their steam page
I'm so curious okay this is so exciting
that I can do this
literally window shopping together um
wait wait let me show you here look at
this it's so
[Music]
fun
ah ah that
[Music]
yo hype hpe Hye I can't
believe bastard I can't believe that
austrians made this and I think I
remember like I really struggled at
first cuz I was really but then I
got really good right and then then it
was a lot of
fun
Studios is there a new game up here
already like for pre-order or so no okay
not a
austrians
yeah wild don't hate oh
[Music]
M okay that's that's that's the first
one then no that was so quick I'm so
sorry and after Kelly was me but we're
not going to give me any games at least
I don't know maybe we can but not now uh
and then was
Ena let's give Ena something
maybe H oh yeah wait then let me go to
ena's debut stream
in this
Deb
debutante
deuto yo remember when like throughout
this whole debut stream people still
didn't know that she was the crazy girl
who drew that artwork from
myth and then at the very end she
revealed it or
[Music]
so it's not n it's
n oh well might
say sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry she she sounds so shy she's
someone I looked up to for a really long
time so she sounds second thing I like
doing is
drawing I think some people might have
seen it on Twitter what I
posted
I my version of uh yeah she's trying
make it seem like she can't
draw can't believe it what a
troll I no she revealed it already then
right after that okay okay screenshot
to games
Ena so Ena I'm can delete this Ena likes
near series likes Final
Fantasy I already have an
idea cuz she likes she likes RPG games
and
stuff what if I give her Tales of a
rise no not Apex wait why the is
there Apex in she never played Apex
since she joined did
she
huh Apex Ena and
Apex is this edit like when what I don't
even remember this she doesn't seem like
the type to like Apex what the man
what I'm so broken right now I can't
believe this she's known for she's not
known for
Apex fgo recently she played this new
fgo game I was so surprised I didn't
know that like a game like that came
out n Nar N I do feel like she would
enjoy like a big variety of genres
anyway can I just see how
much how much the discount of tales of
horiz is right
now Peggy 12
[Music]
50% I'm so biased no okay I can't do
this I can't but I I am the ambass
of Tes of
arise I'm so biased
[Music]
though but I feel like she would like it
I honestly feel like she would like it
well I can only be biased for so
long until until tails off arise and
tunic are given away and Orie I can only
be biased for so long don't
worry do you guys want to see the tra
trailer look this is the game that I'm
Ambassador for
mhm I have friends who accept me it's so
good and one thing I'm certain
of they accept you
too wait that's DLC spoilers I don't
want to see anything like that why is it
why is the DLC trailer oh no oh no no no
oh no no no no no I'm not ready for that
yet that is wrong wrong wrong wrong but
yeah you see how beautiful it is I think
that's exactly up her alley I mean she
just played the new Final Fantasy game
oh where I was really surprised
it oh yeah right cuz she didn't say in
that stream that she likes Final Fantasy
in general she only put up Final Fantasy
14 huh cuz I was really surprised when
she said that the Final Fantasy 16 one
was her first nonf 14 Final Fantasy 2
right like just like me right I was
really shocked about that I thought she
played already like a bunch of them okay
sorry Ena I'm already done with
you I'm already
done I'm already done I'm no I'm so bad
I'm so
biased what if we give her another Final
Fantasy game instead oh no I don't want
to do that because like as an ambassador
I don't want to on my stream right now
replace Tales of r with Final Fantasy I
literally that would
be maybe I would get
fired no no no no this is now set in
stone okay by the way just out of
Interest I want to look uh at these ones
like there's some special big ones that
are on
sale they look like really wellknown
games
skyn
8 maybe I should get it for
myself let me put the BDM back on for a
moment okay
uh battle bit never heard
Diablo who still kind of expensive
though I know I
know kind of want Remnant 2 don't know
Call of Duty Modern
Warfare no no Dia have fun yes it
is Lords of the fun what is this so
Souls like RPG dark fantasy co-op
Act what the wait is the souls like
maybe this could be good as a gift for
someone no oh but let me let me look at
the let me look at the
trailer I look upon you with pity my
Lost
Child reject the fanatical
Crusaders and the div servants the
self-proclaimed judge
[Music]
and the torturous Mission that's a
cinematic trailer is there
a this
trailer
[Music]
whoa
wa Lords of the Fallen is the allnew
Epic dark fantasy action
RPG
wa
set 1,000 years after the events of the
original game prepare to Embark Upon A
perilous Adventure through the vast
lands of morstead a prominent region
within this sprawling World on the brink
of demonic
[Music]
desolation it's the Orie B stretching
across its Skys scorched Horizon lies
the it looks really
good steam there's steam w
what interesting interest wait let me go
back though I want to look at the other
ones that were on the front
page oh oh oh big big boy games I never
played any of these s
Starfield risk of rain returns elen elen
r y truck simulator let's go five bucks
M that could be a game to gift
myself Stellar is what is
[Music]
this
space do you dream of the
Stars the fast unknowns waiting to be
discovered this is good it's fun RTS
this is no single Mission but
a
oh I don't know if am would enjoy that
like the space is kind of like
interesting to
me
but it's it yeah I don't know would she
like this prob maybe
not what 4x game when's that mean what
what 4x what what are you guys so much
comments are so
fast holy
uh 4X what's 4X whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
good but 4X so really long what's
4X
civilization ah explore expl explan
explore explan explored exter that's so
hard to say to a Galaxy why did you
start the trailer again huh why did you
do that interesting
though what is this what is this it's so
cheap this also oh oh oh I like I like I
like oh it's
pretty we
pretty you're plotting a new course
again aren't you currents before is kind
of freaking me out we must adapt our
eyes look like they're popping out if we
are to see our journey
and and how will we know when we get
there I don't know if she's cute or
[Music]
creepy
oh where are the
nipples
o cute medieval
what okay but what does the game look
like
oh it's kind of interesting is there
anybody in Ian who would enjoy this you
think expand your
Empire M well
yeah so wait there's like this is Civ
six ah when I played five oh how new is
this uh wait it's already what it's been
released since like
2016 it's so cheap so
cheap when I played f m play five oh I
should play a Sith game God damn it this
is difficult to choose okay so I'm
actually glad I had such instant instant
uh ideas for some of the girls lies of
Fe I never I everybody's talking about
this game right but I've never heard
about it ever before let me watch the
trailer no go
[Music]
away gorgeous bloody
foring s
life
[Music]
but they had no woba rating up there how
can I make an
opinion how can anyone make an
opinion it's really good looking and I
know bals is or was playing it and
finished it right
how much W still so expensive no deal no
deal n no no no no no you got to give me
a bit more but it's still a new game
that's why they probably can't make it
that much cheaper
right oh okay okay
payday payday
[Music]
oh
Peggy
18 in engine
footage have has someone played a Payday
on stream
before
really 72 you guys took you some time to
do the math took you a
while I I mean in Ian girls only in
Japan
side crony
Iris Amit did Amy play it or did would
you like
it oh crony Iris as a group oh is it fun
is it fun as a
group what if I gift it to am and I say
we have to play together as a
collab
very fun it can be very fun yes but get
two oh cuz I needed two then
right
yeah is it like
GTA I've done heist in
GTA that look
fun yeah I've done the same exact thing
inine what is it Payday 2 better
really
really oh it does say mixed why 25 maybe
Payday 2 was cheaper anyway Payday Two
uh
payday 99 cent what what do you mean 99
cent
what what why is this game so cheap why
is this game so
cheap it's basically free what the
what 10 years old so what is it why is
it million do I need DLCs to make it
good
DLC in famous collection
90 no no what which which DLC do I want
you get a Payday and you get a
Payday uh there's lot you don't need it
the DLCs are where the good high St
oo um games like these depends on
multiplayer so if people move away from
the game they need to reduce price
oh I guess so or do they have like a
random Lobby where you can find someone
to play with you
huh bundle yeah bundle is expensive
they're like f 5,000 DLCs you don't need
the DLC to have a good time of it okay
but I like I wouldn't mind buying one
they're like really cheap like which one
is a recommendable
one crude Awakening China no wait crude
Awakening oh wait it's uh not all of
these
are game packs I
think Hotline Miami hotland Miami wait
is it like a collaboration with hotland
Miami the game that I
played okay okay nice nice nice nice
nice I'm Payday Two for me as well so we
do a collab with Hotline Miami DLC how
much is the Hotline Miami
DLC pain day
hotline so
cheap
so oh interesting I think I can enjoy
this too well let me watch this how is
it hot like
Miami do the characters appear
look what you've
done my
stomach
out what the is this
inviting game trailer hey enough okay I
have told you everything I know if
commissar don't want to be found he
don't get found understand four people
better
idiot
what's this
ni Bell is it the same voice I it
does sound familiar like I but that
might just be the
accent they didn't played it before okay
how about we just the the one that crony
and Iris played is it the second one or
the third
one what the is he
doing oh chicken
okay
yes okay we'll just we'll just play with
crony Iris am me how about
that right they can guide us I'll get it
to him I promise h
let's go you get your B I promise yes
[Music]
please yeah I like this way of
going back to Hala
Miami in case somebody doesn't know I
played Hala Miami one and two on my
stream I finished one and I don't know
about two but um yeah I don't know if
I'll go back to it but yeah
the music hits so hard oh okay
that's that's that's y yep I wrote it
down okay okay so kiata see there we
have a gift for
me with Hotline Miami
DLC wonderful
wonderful Skyrim yeah possi Skyrim too
it was cheap right it was pretty cheap
okay okay okay now uh the one that's
left is
go good debut did she say what games she
likes on her debut
stream oh my God
Nostalgia did she say
[Music]
girls no I don't know she doesn't have a
games I like list on there it's okay
we'll figure it out then
without rythm games okay is there any
rhythm game that she hasn't played yet
that she might
like Rhythm
Heaven
Rhythm metal hell singer okay
metal hell
singer let me look at that you think she
would like this slay to the rhythm of
metal and Vengeance on an infernal
Journey Through the eight Hells wow okay
that's wow
intense already just by reading that
make them fear the beat a rythm FPS
bursting with demon badass weapons and
heavy
metal what's the price 12
bucks
death
holy
shitties
Tor are you oh this reminds me of a game
[Music]
beond
walking
[Music]
[Applause]
Unown he isn't this like what this game
where you have to shoot on the
beat BPM is it kind of like similar to
that oh do you guys hear my walls
creaking the whole time it's so
annoying
hord mode update yes yes do you really
think she would like this is this not
like a little bit too like
intense sorry that's me and the walls
get out of there
hell don't know about this high five
Rush high five highi
rush highi I know I heard about that one
before do we have perms for
that I can I show
H be
Festa be
Festa be Festa should be fun what's
[Music]
this oh looks good Ka already has
it she said she didn't like it no way
what she said that
okay can I wait is there is there a
category that I can look through
Rhythm nice nice nice
okay oh Rock The Rock I love the
pun lead your Viking sh to Vikings I
think G would love
Vikings I'm like immediately already
convinced Quaver Community Driven and
open source competitive Riven game with
two game ones okay okay qu dance of fire
and eyes I think I've seen
that Rhythm doctor oh
cute valheim it's a vking game but not a
rivon game is
it C I heard of that one too Geometry
Dash
cute oh there's a Riv game in the
jackbox party pack
10 DJ Max respect five
IR Rush beat
saver mustach R let me look at
this yeah
Viking I a be
[Music]
game on the
us to
beandy
D yo Viking Rock is my new favorite
music
genre
oh yeah meal santies
you
fre I want the
[Music]
soundra if only it wasn't VR because GAA
gets sick with v i don't know if she
would enjoy
that but that was bopping
[Music]
she dmca yeah I don't know I might get
dmca for the stream yeah but it's
okay
[Music]
um wait this one Ena was playing it I
feel like good I would like this like
the visuals the Aesthetics and she can
play with the chum
bus I this is the first time I'm
watching gameplay of it I want to play
oh ga Dino
Dino oh this this is a must for her I
[Music]
think it's like Fall Guys
aesthetic and like
Community uh aspect of Fall
Guys is it made by the people who made
Fall Guys by any
chance is it I don't know I can't tell I
want to play it too I want to play it
with you guys fall guys but rym game
yeah okay I think I I'll take this but I
want to watch more of the
[Music]
trailer it looks fun that's
cute I would be so bad at this even
worse than in Fall Guys cuz I just stuck
at Rhythm
games and it's burs oh I need to play
this at some point wait how much is
it it's pretty cheap I mean it's not
that much cheaper than before but it's
cheap by default
so it
looks okay I think I think I'll do that
I think I might do
that I think it's even kind of blue like
she's also
blue what's it called
Headbangers uh rivm we even have
permissions for this rivm Roy what rithm
Royale okay okay okay all right all
right we got one generation down
y now we'll do
Iris Iris Iris Iris Iris Iris Iris IR
debut
stream Where are her game
likes it's like you know since I'm a how
I don't like numbers don't ask me math
questions I saw math questions in the
comments no no I will probably answer
90% of them did she talk about the games
she
likes no I don't think she did I don't
think she did visual
novel a visual novel do you think she
would play that on stream I want to
choose something that there's like a
reality of them playing it on stream
though a lot of mea stuff true true
[Music]
true what is
this oh is it another RTS game a 4X yo
what's with all these 4X
games what's this what's this oh
cute
I just want to look at it for myself
really
quickly just really quickly just for
myself it looks like it looks like trick
begin guide to ecosystem restoration C
this video will serve as a general guide
to the intricate process of restoring an
environment from Wasteland no this part
this this was what caught me in the
trailer because it reminds me of
something I played like
um so many years ago that I probably
shouldn't
say um and I've been trying to find out
what game that was maybe if we found it
out before cuz remember we like kind of
I feel like we talked about it before
and you guys always like teach me about
games that I'm trying to remember it's
like really old and you were
like digging into walls on the ground
and stuff
like a million years ago so it must have
been like really bad Graphics really
[Music]
old D dungeon keep driving Dungeon
Keeper wait do they have steam dungeon
keep D Dungeon
Keeper keeper
dungeon that's something
else
that's something
else d let me Google Dungeon
Keeper maybe that is that
it no no is it I don't
knowy no I don't think so no no whatever
yeah Dig Dug okay I'll look that up to
dig
dog no not that not Pac-Man Style
old no don't don't keep
her no no no no probably not no
no oh well oh well whatever forget about
it uh what do we get for Iris the people
who are saying in the chat Catherine are
you telling me to get caffine for Iris
or what because when I think of
Catherine I think of that game with the
guy in his underpants right which I kind
of want to play as
well Peggy 18 and we do have perms down
for it I was I was yeah I can see her
playing that I mean I don't know if it's
her genre but I like the the her playing
that the idea of it is kind of visually
[Music]
teasing you must like what you see wait
can I even there's no nudity in this
trailer
right snap J out of
it
yeah I've been interested in this game
since forever she finally wants you to
tie the
[Music]
knot who's that what are you doing here
oh God this can't be
[Music]
happening five bucks
what a
deal what a deal what a deal you think
she would like
it where are the where are the
aristocrats you think she will like
this who wouldn't like it
honestly and let me check my perms
really
quickly just to make
sure
uh my perm list
um oh my God shut up
walls
cine I think I yeah uh uh for
Nintendo uh I might only have perms for
the switch and the PS4 version but that
doesn't mean that I could possibly
request the PC
version
I might be able to
get I mean probably fine because in the
end it's from the same people right
so CRI are moste which yeah
mhm for the
re-release it says Catherine full
body is that not
on what's the difference for the
re-release and this OG the full body
one okay then I'm only buying Steam
games today so okay let's think about
something else unfortunate
unfortunate we might have to choose
something else Dave the DI people keep
on bringing this game up I'm not I I
might get it for someone but I'm not
sure for
who oh
Warhammer cool
near or Mega Man Mega Mega
Man good day for fun
H you know what would be really shitty
if somebody doesn't already has the game
that I'm choosing for them which is
another good reason for me to just wait
and ask them
first oh War what war she does love Mega
Man
Mega is there Mega Man
game which one would we be getting
Battle Network Legacy
Collection ah is this the
same she has the
collections okay then no no we can also
give her something surprising that isn't
quite you know like on the knows what
are these oh my God what are these
games can we give this to
Bales
ratopia oh it's actually kind of cute
looking
rattis it's kind of cute
looking valheim St you Valley what is
this
cute
give me
more
get depends on the
[Laughter]
price we who are about to
die
oh interesting that looks like that game
I played on
GameCube cold vein cold
Vin you think that's a game she would
like and doesn't have yet cold
Vin oh oh oh BM
co wait it's
cute I didn't expect that hello
hi ENT
present all right it's all right
oops she
cute
hi
o o white
tree so it is you anime Dark Souls the
Red Mist showed up after the queen was
defeated the jail of The Mists that was
the name people gave to the world are
you guys recommending this for Iris or
for Bales
inside we think there must be a source
somewhere your power can clear the
miasma if you could help
us B well then you're one of
us B boo I like
it IIs like Souls like games what the
plan now you know the
plan yeah the Queen's regeneration
couldn't be stopped
likese locked her away God fragments of
the Queen's body were locked inside of
successors you have the power to quell
the relics at last I'm interest I beg
you relieve them of their
suffering I'm here to take back all of
the relics you stole oh my such an
important
job oh I like
this you drink
blood you
revive let me fight some more this looks
like tals of arise to me sorry bumco
but I love that kind of graphics and
visual we were all human
once I'm I'm saying it in a positive
way oh oh wait who do I give this I want
to give this to
someone we should do a poll we should do
a poll a PO Paul let me do Paul because
there seems to be three options Iris
bells or bioo but for people I kind of
want to give her like a Yakuza game
maybe if they're not too expensive code
vain start
po
yeah
mukashi oopsie I started
again it's a
difficult difficult
Choice ah most people would go wait how
much is this oh it's so cheap oh 10
bucks yo this is the perfect time for me
to do the stream I'm such a genius and
wait and then was uh yaku she's playing
uh she's
playing zero right now isn't
she is she playing zero right
now there's no seven here but I could
give give her like a dragon or wait is
it like a dragon
seven yeah she's playing zero right I
played both zero and like a
dragon oh it's also so
cheap okay she will appreciate this I
think judging by how much she likes uh
Yakuza we have a member called Yakuza
how much she likes zero yaku
um like a
dragon and I sorry guys the Paul you
know in that case bibo kind of won
but and people like Souls like
games we could give her cold
vein possibly unless we find
something better that we like for her I
think she owns it yeah I'll check with
her first um before I buy it um if she
already owns y CU I like a dragon
because she plans on playing it too then
then we're going to change our decision
but uh you
know damn now is the time to buy games
guys there's no time like
now
Skyrim I want to play
this literally baby sells too easy for
people too easy for people who gets
tunic ah tunic I will didn't I already
consider somebody in my other streams I
was talking about it was I going to give
it to
crony was I going to give it to crony
right how much off is Tunic right now
May 20
20 is there a
discount a
30% this is one of the best games to
exist ever guys please I will force you
now to watch the trailer with
me cuz I feel like there's a lot of no
KP here
too it is so good my game of the year
last
year because okay let me let me tell you
what's so amazing about it there's like
you play this game but like there's no
like you don't understand NPCs you talk
to and you don't understand this this
like guide book that you're given
because it's in a language that you just
don't understand and you will never
understand because they don't really
okay I almost stumbled into a meme there
um but so you're you're trying to figure
it out um that's that's like the that's
the cool thing about
it it's like it's like a Zelda uh game
kind
of it's so good it's so
smooth they're developing new
game it's so eye opening
it's a Zelda Souls lag
[Music]
basically see they always throw these
like letters at you that you just don't
you're not able to read
them the boss fights were so
difficult I might even say go as far to
say it's not only my favorite game of
last year it's also my favorite game in
the past 10 years my whole life one of
of my favorite games my whole
life oh the golden
[Music]
P totally understand totally understand
these letters
tuning it's so good what a blessing to
this
world crony please don't disappoint me
please play it cuz this so
good yeah
yeah
okay still got nothing for Iris we got
to go back looking for something for
Iris I I really don't know is there a
mega
genre is there Mega genre uh
categories probably
not Titan Fall there
is uh would it be here is there more
genres than just what is
here don't see
one try Mecha there's a mecha tag what
do I have to write like
this does this
work it just gives me games that have
meca in the in the
name I don't necessarily want to do
that oh
type
it
what
without oh okay oh I guess that works or
does it wait no it's also still just
games that have me the
name narrow by
tag
what narrow by narrow narrow by tag I
here sorry I'm
[Music]
blind no it doesn't work that those are
not Mega games armored Core armor what
arm did she not play that
before did she
no 60
bucks
n she did okay thank god um maybe is
there like a similar game
[Music]
section more like this is that really
more like that Titanfall people have
been mentioning Titanfall haven't
they oh yeah I think it's a good game
right overwhelmingly positive it's cheap
I'll click the tag but what about
Titanfall she already has
it
okay where's his tag Mex I'm
ma Max Mobile Suit Gom battle operation
to it's Gundam wait mostly negative oh
mixed a oh Fantasy
Star Mech Warrior online
Legends uh generation zero mostly
positive stealth Action shooter where
you wage gorilla Warfare against lethal
mechanical
enemies yeah PSO2 seems kind of like out
of
place
wait
H what if we give her Stein
skate wait which
one cuz the visual
novel she probably didn't play it before
did she I
mean
OG a there It
Go
[Laughter]
I don't know if you can stream it a
true I mean wait who published
it Spike tun soft wait I think Spike tun
soft
is does it have hav no oh wait I wrote
it
[Music]
typo
Stein oh I we could
do uh real escape games Stein skate
that's not a real Stein gate game it's
like an escape game DLC I
guess she's interested in Ace Combat why
why am I struggling so much with Iris
game 1
Sentinels okay okay
okay wait
what is that game even on
Steam did I do it wrong it's not on
Steam we need Steam games
guys Strike Suit Zero that sounds like a
mega
game strik Suit Zero oh oh
okay
metal
[Music]
okay
woo
oh my god
[Music]
soundra oh
wow I
mean this genre doesn't really do
anything for me so I can't really tell
if this would be
[Music]
good
like you think she would play
[Music]
this looks good actually it does look
good what was this met metal wolf metal
wolf chaos XD so this one is mostly
positive and three
bucks this one's a bit more expensive
and very positive what's more positive
very positive or mostly
positive Devol a digital
probably already have perms
fors from
software by the end of the first quarter
of the 21st
century very better beginning with a
large scale military cud that erupted in
various cities throughout the nation
Freedom was dead are they make armor
po it's a mean game it's
funny
however oh it's in Japan one final hope
in opposing the cudar forces
remain this pretty old being the US
president himself
what we become the US president for
what but you you are this is the
president it's kind of funny yeah looks
funny
Richard was that a l reference Michael
be certain of your death the way he
screamed
that now come at
[Music]
me die that's pointless Mr President
nothing is pointless and the reason is
because I'm the president of the great
United States of America
Amer this takes itself not very
seriously I see always make the
impossible
possible okay that's pretty
funny no one can
you what is that supportive
voice The Voice in his
head this is dorky all right all
right we got it we got it guys we
finally got it I'm so happy metal wolf
chaos
XD perfect thank you I think she like
this even as a one off joke
stream yeah that's good thank you thank
you for showing me this oh I'm so glad I
feel like you know we went we we've been
going for a lot of like big name games I
I want to you know put in some more like
kind of you know not so big games so
let's do fauna next how about that
[Music]
Faun FAA let me check does she have a
list
[Music]
F oh oh Teran slay the fire you think
she would like slay the SP really cuz I
like slay Spire that makes two of
us um
[Music]
let's see what does this say does she
have game ah she likes N9 hours nine
persons nine doors Animal Crossing Okami
Som and Super Mario
Odyssey what's what kind of games Dave
the diver yeah she likes inding games
right let's give her a nice ending game
Dave the
diver da the
DI Teran Neal
we looked at the Teran right a moment
Meet Dave an interesting little human
with a precarious love for the
sea he spends his days diving the
chilling depths of a mysterious blue
hole and when he isn't merely surviving
or rumaging resources he's often found
snapping photographs racing
seahorses and really anything what it
people joking
gluttonous appetite for adventure that
gets him into all kinds of unique seems
like a game she already would have yeah
I feel like that
[Music]
too stardo
Valley timberborn coffee
talk
oh what's okay let me look these up up
Coffee
Talk coffee being heart to hard talking
simulator a talking
[Music]
simulator
oh you think she'll like this really
would you would you play it on stream
though oh oh
yummy oh oh oh yum yum yum yum
yum
inscription oh my God people are so
excited to recommend
games
wait inscription is an Inky black
card oh card based game ody you see that
blends the deck building look like
escape room style puzzles okay so it's
like
a I want to play this I've seen this
before ah it looks so interesting a I
want to play it put it on my list
[Music]
too
she likes organs so this is kind of
terrifying too why is it still
spooking CR you played
it I think I saw that
yeah oh this looks so
fun does fa like card
[Music]
games it is a spooky game o then perfect
Vibes she loves Rog
like don't scare me stop scaring me we
could give that to her oh hey it's
devola digital what's up what's
up oh oh oh 10 bucks 50%
off what's that people say what's
this
for say
we go there and get the town up and
running it is time you got your first
taste of command we are about to face
Sous
challenge don't know if want to give her
such a similar
game Val Val
why do you write this like this cyber
Punk bartender
[Music]
action I've heard of the
name in a c City that should not
[Music]
exist where individual liberty is
nothing but a
Daydream this one's good
Only Hope
[Music]
remains would this be good for Irish
to this is the goat in the
genre K played
it people daring to
[Music]
survive what's happening in the game
what do you do you bartending and
solving people's problems or what why
does this give me a needy streamer
overload
Vibes oh they Iris KY and Rea played
[Music]
it okay I mean I I I don't really I
wouldn't really connect this with fauna
but let's do a
poll uh Val what how the do you Val
Hall
while Hall a or something like that or
incription you guys can choose for
funa I hope she would like these
[Music]
choices um pronounce it Val yeah
inscription I if anything I would
probably go for
inscription for her but I'll leave it to
you guys
description more of a final
[Music]
game yeah yeah yeah I think we
agree yeah
huh she obviously played B she
did you should try incription yourself I
should I want
to she might havep it's okay it's okay
like for these cases I'm gonna like I'm
gonna contact them anyway for like
friend codes if I don't have them yet
and then uh I'll be like yeah I want to
gift you this game but like you know we
could give We could decide on like
backup games for everybody or at least
for the ones where we have a a a doubt
that they might already have it inscript
inscription
[Music]
yes backup games more
choices well I we need one for bals I
think maybe one for fauna for these I'm
pretty sure they don't have these games
so that's
okay I'm so hungry Oprah D
[Music]
oh we don't need a tunic backup
or or tunic as a backup for everybody
else you
mean here play tunic just play tunic if
you don't if you have these games
already just play
tunic
obra Oben Oben obra perfect for shieldy
oh oh oh are we already making decisions
here
uh I want to play that
too just get everybody tun and you get a
tunic and you get a
tunic be already has the game what
she does how do you know how do you know
did she say
that okay
tune we're not there yet we're not there
yet
okay let's wait we have to organize this
we have to organize
this end Pole
okay let's get a backup for
fauna
but not not not necessarily
this let's look in the Casual
category cross code I played cross code
before it's
good
spirit this is so difficult and what if
we give backups SL
despire I don't want to rely too much on
games that I know but it's kind of
easier for me to confirm that they're
good you know but um see the
skylines yeah cuz she likes games like
that right like she played that
um
uh those those
games what are they called the the one
where you make a zoo or the one where
you make a roller coaster or so one of
those she played for sure
oh wait it's
expensive wait is this a new W this is
really new wait let me watch it I never
I didn't realize there's a new one
what there's a new Sage
skylines look like
GTA and b reviews really it's like Sim
City on steroids
[Music]
wow it does not run well
yet yeah maybe they'll make
improvements had a rough
[Music]
release oh maika we'll get back to but
recent reviews are mostly positive maybe
they already fixed it but the
price the
price let me look at casual ones da the
DI were we considering this for funa
were we weren't we weren't
we coral island she likes farming she
likes Animal Crossing doesn't she what
about this coral island
[Music]
I oh we thought she has it okay what
about
this
[Music]
where wa whoa whoa whoa against the
store against the store damn you guys
are like so certain about certain games
against wait is this the
change these visuals look like World of
Warcraft the world is all about
change and the way you handle
it is this a World of Warcraft Thing
game no no even the logo looks like like
their thing we are viceo Elite settlers
serving the scorched queen look nice our
job is to establish colonies and gather
prous
resources every we build is governed by
its own rules there's no single path
Prosperity some succeed by like arus
some by serving the crown oh interesting
oh is it Rog like in this kind of wait
what's Happening
Here what part is Rogue like is this
part by venturing bravely into the
unknown
apparently really good
excellent each one you have to make your
city again oh okay
okay there's also Timber
B new
settlements shut up
[Music]
walls I hate it I hate it so
much F wait oh oh the com through so
fast holy ah let me scroll back up
oh F such a game that makes it hard yell
f is interested in too oh
really did she say that recently F might
like portion nomics
ah that seems like a game that she could
play casually for a stream or to
yeah but this game looks really nice
too slime
Rancher potion craft or potion
yeah which one am I thinking
of P craft or potion nomic
potion
craft this one's
[Laughter]
cheaper I ah wait I have I've been
having my eyes on this actually I want
to play this
too this is so
cute yeah Ena played it right I think
Ena played it I'm we played it
too it's
cute I love the
visuals potion
nomics what's this tiny build thing
potion potion
nomics customize store higher ha and
gather ingredients bef friend or romance
fellow vendors to learn new haggling
strategies
ah sorry it's a little bit cut
[Music]
off oh cute oh isn't this game
new that's why it's not much
[Music]
cheaper Ricky what what the is that
all right it's not that new just a one
year Rick I'm never going to make a
decision oh it started so
good
re free
bucks what what this is old as
[Laughter]
capitalism what what what's what's what
what is this what is this a meme
capitalism
ho this looks like something that I
would give to Fu
moko
what what's this capitalism
thing
what pretty classic
game is there a video there's no
video that's cute that's kind of
cute imagine F playing Portal 2
together I can't de
sign myth was so easy CU I just I was
super
biased uh let's just let's just wait
what is there like a history um what was
one of the ones I looked at before
um against the should we just okay
against the storm or
potion craft or
potionomics I would choose between those
maybe we're not we're
not po should I do another try you think
she would like it I love
try uh I actually have on on my switch I
have like I think all of them
cuz they were on sale too this is like
crazy
sale it has online co-op I don't think
we have um perms yet but I want to play
this with
someone yeah try collabs who's this for
fa I don't know is it for FAA you guys
know
[Music]
try
try bundle
[Music]
cheap TR for anyone love TR
yeah best of free players
oh try is nice TR is nice
can't the try bundle whoa
you can get free games or or oh you can
get you can get the shrine verse five
wait what the is this this is not
Shrine the is
this what is this dear Mom and Dad there
was an incident at school which is why
I'm going on an
adventure the astral Academy's magical
spells have gone missing and I'm going
to recover them Moon lighter what's
moonlighter what the is moonlighter
moon like Sims 4 moon like
sh what what what
what sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry
what who what's this pirate
music is it about Pirates
[Music]
enjoy the game with it with all up
updates oh
oh oh this reminds me of a game I played
I'm so sorry that I compared but I'm not
even not even going to say it but like
this screen and I'm guessing it's a
rogue rogue
[Music]
like
Co
oh it's so cute I love the graphics
actually the the
color uh palette is really nice let me
go to faa's Channel right now because I
am so indecisive let me look at the
games she's been playing
recently
signal Binding of Isaac
Hitman Delta
rune
dredge I don't know most of these
games there's I don't know is there a
pattern slay the princess world of
horror maybe she would enjoy anything I
give
her cross cat you think she would like
cross cat cross cat is
um cross code is pixel she does seem to
like pixel
[Music]
things
and it's good for
gamers I know it's by German devs I
[Music]
know
wait maybe I was thinking of a different
game
actually I know this game but I
think I was thinking of by the way love
minoria I was I was thinking of icono
classs I love this game rated T for
team this so good
too do you guys know
it having fun shopping no I'm losing my
mind right
now
cute can't possible call me beat
me this I love
this but I didn't get very far it was a
long time
[Music]
ago cuz I'm really bad at the
game W
buff he so
buff isn't this a
great you get a kill
girl oh slap
wait doesn't fauna like
slapping isn't that her thing
I
mean I
mean that was very
convincing that was so convincing right
now that's probably just like like
0.00 1% of the game um
but do you think she would like it
besides the
slapping I'm losing my mind I
want to rage quit I want a rage quit
[Music]
you that kind of probably not she would
yeah just get everyone tunic
easy she's not really into Metras I feel
she could get into
it um okay okay you know what you know
what you know what let's look at the
road
like genre cuz she likes Rogue likes
right we should just give her slate a
Spire
honestly wait I want Rog light Rog like
Rog
like oh she like
this
oh she like it right but that seems like
such an Easy
Choice against the storm is a real wait
which one was that didn't we already
look at
that annoyed the people mentioned this
game
[Music]
oh it's so dark but it kind of fits her
recent game choices oh
very difficult but perfect for
her NOA is a science in itself never
seen it before but it looks uh
interesting very interesting every pixel
wo wo wo wo
explodes bleed spills oh my God
suffocates ble
ble
ble interesting
I can't I can't I
can't oh there so much input I need to I
need to I need to make a decision what
you think it has big fun energy
a good challenge for her what was the
game you found at the started the nature
game I found at the start of the stream
nature
game was it up here probably not
right Teran a tanel should we just give
her tanel doesn't she have that already
I'm so confused Terra Teran
nil oh yeah yeah it's already
out give that to
am oh oh you're right I stopped it there
cuz I got curious about something
else oh oh I love that oh oh that's so
satisfying
MH well do you have to like make this
place livable
again oh oh that's perfect for fauna oh
that's literally fauna that is like the
fauna the game it's her she makes stuff
green look at those
[Music]
Ducks no no don't BR it what the
that's
antia this
amazing
she has it on why do you know did she
play it or does she just say that she
already has it too much on the nose
it would be so nice like I feel like
that was so peaceful what is this what
is
[Music]
this w oh it's on a
dinosaur that's so cute wow I love this
visuals am I was playing
this no way not on stream
right eat this eat
this
this is good for
fauna fauna would love timber B but what
about
this what's timberborn
again why is sp so difficult for
me ah cute when you were born we knew
you were gifted by the time you could
lift a hammer you were already a master
builder now it is time for you to join
our team of brilliant Engineers
Believers to plan and construct
everything a beaver needs small things
that improve
our and incredible structures that reach
for the clouds that looks really
intricate she would love any of the last
dozen
games uh as far as stop stop re
commanding new games
no I have to look at them as far it
doesn't even show up as far as far as
far as the
eye F fate build a mobile Village and
travel with your tribe toward the scent
of the world called the eye this Ro Rog
likee turn-based resource resource
management game Rog like and
building
show
me wake up it is time
sigh whisper their new path to my
pupils they will listen they will know
who you are you have to make them leave
you have to get them to safety the water
is rising fast and will flood all this
only you can be their guide side only
you can and help them plan this
nice will you ever decide no their long
journey awaits them and their trust in
your instincts will lead them across
wonderful
Landscapes new lands to discover and to
pay respects to New Horizons to admire
and follow you'll Inspire them to create
marvelous new homes but the journey must
not stop they have to keep
[Music]
going you will find them hardworking and
determined you will Breathe new
knowledge into them and surely
appreciate their potential to learn as
they care deeply for the connection to
Nature through you they will bring to
light ancient ways to get help from
Spirit gorgeous vagaries may appear on
the way hardening your mission to save
them all and as some may be taken away
some will join the Caravan and do part
of the way with you never play Whispers
to their ears the wind that pushes them
forward forward and your journey
carrying them to me has just begun that
looks so
good
cheap why
why trop okay no no more we have to
choose between the ones we already
looked
[Music]
at
no Timber okay let's make a poll let's
make a poll between a few
ones
no timberborn Nora was that crazy
difficult looking one though timberborn
was this one a that was cute though yeah
that was really
cute wait Early Access what what do you
mean it's early
access
it's not
finished
oh against the St which one was that
again against the storm was which one
again this like World of Warcraft
looking uh Builder game
uh Against The
Storm should we choose from
that potion
one of the potion games W so many
choices though
potion potion
nomics
po stop why did we rule out inscription
oh why did why did we why did we rule
out
inscription
uh ah it's just a backup guys it's just
a backup up because we thought she might
have it she probably has it oh she was
spoiled on it
really just a backup yeah we
forgot but inscription might end up
being the backup because uh yeah
although oh look at this look at the
Paul oh it's not so clear but most
people vote for no all
right
n they
okay
okay timberborn doing pretty good too
but seems to be
no okay guys um we maybe need a bailes
backup game
too the stream is longer than I
expected
H Bales what do you think what were are
some more ideas that I didn't choose I
think we went like immediately for
Yakuza
Yakuza no can we give a recommendation
that's not
Yakuza perhaps is that is that
possible oh oh oh
oh something in my eye a yeah the
r the r that was kind of a joke but I
feel like you
[Music]
know r Wait
retropolis
afterwards
oh is that a game she would
like is that her kind of
[Music]
game maybe not I don't know I feel like
this is not the kind of game she would
go
for it looks cute but I don't know about
the
genrec and beat
saber she could do that in VR with her
cute VR
model a plag tail is also a rat
game wait I know that
one wait that's not what I
[Music]
imagined there's a storm coming
how can how is this a red game you
tell trust
[Music]
me I heard the same thing happened in
Guan the
rats
rat I knew we'd have to pay a
price okay giving her this game is kind
of a joke but at the same time it's it's
it's a good game right
damn it's for the corruption of our
[Music]
souls I'm happy to be here with
you sequel what's the arum a plag
tail
innocense it's much cheaper dead you'll
never see her again are rats here too
you can't running forever you are a
monster a monster
you have yet to see
just oh my God
[Music]
disgusting be sure to stay what like
visually I I didn't play both of these
games but visually this is giving me
lives of PE like
similarities so I feel like she might
enjoy
it should we get it for her
I'll write it down as a
backup a plank uh tail
innocence might be good not the backup
it's just the
backup it's a solid choice I think
yeah good good good good okay okay we
can finally move on and go to
m and people were already making some
suggestions for Moon um ho ho
ho oh ho ho ho what's
this sift six that a new the new sift
game Frost
punk I yeah C of the
[Music]
Lamb that is such a good
game c of the lamp how much is it off
right now h
oh it's not that much I know 40%
40% and they have I think they have
chickens now way later than when I
needed them but it seems like they have
chickens not that it matters to
M skateboard Ultra kill Ultra lots of
ultra
kills Ultra kill
that's a moate
game that already gives me this two
seconds of music and UltraViolet retro
FPS tells me Hotline Miami but no no
wait hot how long is not an FPS game
best Shooters rip apart your foes with
very
destructive
weapons do like shs yeah
true
W wo wo wo
[Music]
W wo wo wo wo wo the more difficult
Doom this is so moon
[Music]
really
motion mustion gets motion sick uh
mustion M gets motion sick easily that
does seem like a game that could get her
motion sick but I mean Isn't that with
all FPS games uh a
thing motion Frost Punk what's Frost
punk I heard of that I
think isn't that is that also a FPS game
no Society Survival game as the rule of
the last city on earth it is your duty
to manage both its citizens and okay
okay so another so cheap another one of
those kind of
games ah yeah Cy played
this looks
[Music]
nice this looks like a high quality
game Choo
Cho okay I I want to put this in the
back of my mind
uh and then look at
[Music]
this
cute so
[Music]
cute
cute oh seems like has good uh a
good
reputation it's cute oh
boy yeah but I don't know if this is M's
type of game like in terms of genre is
it we should do frost
Punk we should do frost
Punk M gets Frost Punk and as a backup
Al boy I I don't think she does I
wouldn't expect her to have Frost punk
though but
yeah let's go let's go that we can move
on we can move on let's go finally we
are done with promise
so for f should we get one game or two
games if they're cheap we can we can get
two games how about
that if if the game that we're choosing
is
[Music]
cheap it's so expensive
also add games on stream I don't have
uh like they can't even monetize it so I
don't know I don't
know a
way but we can only make them play a way
out once they have a 2pc setup properly
working and then they might even do it
on their
own a way out they love R yeah that game
I was thinking of uh for when I when I
watched when I looked at the screenshots
cuz there's no
trailer it's
like
[Music]
H TR
for oh wait could they do it split
screen they have it takes
two
uh uh portal two is
$1 as as a fellow Portal 2 or portal in
general oh my God
appreciator I will gift them both
because they first have to play portal M
please yosu cuz moku is the gamer
usually and then once they're done
together they should play portal
too
right and it's cheap as so it's
it's following what I said before nice
let's go yeah let's make more people
play portal games let's go okay I don't
even have to look at the steam page but
damn those prices what the how many
percent off is
that 90
90% wait portal bundle is even cheaper
the portal Bund makes it even
cheaper
she that's in that's insane that's
actually
crazy what a deal what a deal what a
deal what a
deal channeling my inner inner moku
again okay that was fast
um seems like we already decided for
shiing let me look at it again though
for a
moment I think this is good for sh
though I want to play this too
[Music]
though this is what we're giving to
shieldy it
seems perfect for shiy this very shieldy
well awesome then I couldn't judge
because I don't really know what she
plays
[Music]
normally I only like paid attention to
her like hand cam streams and stuff so
far
okay
a okay we're happy with that choice
aren't
we we should do is last let's think
about
B B B B B Be Beaver what if we give her
a beaver
game Deep Rock a lot of people say deep
rock Galactic interesting oh wait she is
a that's why Rock cuz of the Rock in the
name
huh what kind of game was this oh oh
yeah okay yeah I can see her playing
this danger darkness dwar hello miners
it is time for another dear that kind of
f we back with a new rundown welcome to
season 4 critical
corruption though we have gained great
ground against the rampaging lith ofage
in the past months it remains a constant
threat on ho
our best efforts and to make matters
worse reports of alarming new mutations
are starting to come in clearly reacting
to our presence and our endeavors are
getting even more hazardous moving
forward let's get right into it the bad
news first the play carts you have
encountered previously have evolved they
will now turn into lith ofage corruptors
R
mile rockx wherever they go they appear
imperious to nor gun TV program is way
of telling us about the game right so
you will need to use the cleansing
equipment to get through the exterior sh
oh okay okay okay oh I'm so
confused
oh one to four play a co-op FPS oh I
feel like she would love to play that
with
Kyla 100% destructible environments
procedurally generated
caves Pro what does that mean proced Cal
generation what what's that mean
procedur what does that
mean random oh so it's like is that does
that not mean it's Rog
like isn't that Rog
like kind
of
oh ah cuz Rogue like is
not
no it's also
random H but I guess that this is like
more like completely like like a PC just
randomly throws stuff
together and you get something always
really unique I guess more like what ah
okay yeah yeah that's how I imagine it
now like how Minecraft would create a
new seed of
world a no hold
on is this a normal
[Music]
trailer
oh would I like this too can I coers
people into playing this with me and KY
and whoever else
maybe heroic get
ready spunking Co-op
goodness
yes I won't buy it for crony though
unless un if I get tunic for free then
I'll buy her this game how much is it
right now oh 10 bucks nice can somebody
like calculate what I'm paying for all
of this in the end after the stream tell
me what my final bill
is look this is awesome awesome I I like
this with the idea in my mind that we
can make a CO a collab with it too it's
a nice opportunity with uh K Ka crony oh
my God all the
ks sounds
good 5,000 I doubt it these games are
really really uh deducted I wasn't even
planning to be honest when I first
planned the stream I didn't know the
Steam Sale was going up uh unlike what I
said in the beginning of the stream so I
was ready to you know spend a bit more
money but this is
perfect
yeah that would be a great collab I
think yeah that sounds like fun I mean I
don't really know what you
do I don't quite understand
yet what else do you
need love the mining alien style BL
valy looks like fun together
[Music]
eat wa it's going to
blow
wao yeah that looks like fun has there
been no Deep Rock Galactic collab so
far if yes then why not do we have perms
for
this probably could get perms no no
matter what but uh oh both on ID played
it
then we must have oh I I don't see it in
the
list but I guess we do have
PBS oh okay okay
y okay
now last but not least
Nisa we could give anything to narissa
just something really selfish that I
want to see someone play even
[Music]
but NOA she likes like uh she likes
pixel games too right
[Music]
and what kind of games does she really
like though like as a
genre what's kind of genre tunique
backup of course for everybody tunic
backup G gun signal
valala also she likes really chill games
too right like unpacking I remember when
she played that back in the
day she likes horor right we should give
her horror
game is she still doing her was it
weekly horror game
streams she should play a horror game
but I know nothing about horror games
Darkwood is that a horror game do I even
want to watch the trailer I don't want
to I don't
perspective on Survival horror A New
Perspective scavenge and explore a rich
Ever Changing free Rome World by day oh
interesting then hunker down in your
hideout and pray for them oh
interesting that's actually
interesting please do not scare me in
the trailer I
[Music]
chickens
H signal all right I'll look at that
wait that's the game that funa is
playing right now right like
recently wait that's exactly like how
you play Hotline
Miami that was literally a scene out of
hotl Miami this is PTSD to
me I've done that a million times in h
Miami
[Applause]
e wow that's really
interesting my
holes my holes she
says you don't want me to pooke into
them
e
Wow
E this seems like a Nissa game to
me I I mean I won't watch her play will
[Music]
I but you know what I also want her to
play 12
minutes but I'll just tell her to play
it and she will do
[Music]
it I feel like she would like it the 12
minutes but also this
game I it's kind of sad if I if I put
this down now then we're
done do you know what that means guys
you know what that means oh let me look
at signal okay before I make this
decision how much is this for four
bucks that's
nothing i' I've I've heard of this like
okay is but is this a horror game though
wait what is this
genre oh it's also kind of horror
survival horror sci-fi dark a classic
survival horror experience set in a
dystopian future where Humanity has
uncovered a dark secret unravel a cosmic
mystery Escape terrifying creatures and
scavenge an offworld government
facility
wow I must play this
[Music]
game maybe next Halloween
lesbian
HRA no please wa no more
lesbian you
understand no more
lesbian sorry that's an Insider
meme no more
whoa looks really cool but between those
two I feel like I would actually choose
Darkwood it it
it I don't know that
one German game oh this one's
German I can see
that like now this is
easier wait how much is this one this
one's more
[Music]
expensive okay I
see okay
I I
guess I not the not the
calendar not the
calendar
uh I I I I prefer the vibe from the
other
one oh I could make her I could let her
choose but no that's no you shouldn't
choose your own Christmas present unless
you're the one buying it
yeah okay I'll trust my gut thank you
for giving me confidence I feel like I
like the vibe more for
narissa I mean she should play both
totally humble games winter set what do
you have wait is
that what do you
have
[Music]
games head and
time isn't this a co-op
game oh no it's
[Music]
not it is say
Co is it there's a CO mode
she played it
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I saw that yeah yeah that's
what I what I was thinking
about wait sh the
[Music]
mother oh I was like why did I say
German in the trailer but it's just when
I go in with my mouse then this is from
the browser being German okay
okay I was like is this game made by
[Music]
Germans it's going to be really excited
again how do you play this with Co-op
like is there a co-op trailer where I
can see
that guess I should just play look at
ena's and am's stream
[Music]
cute just like me for real for real
always yawning
uhoh I'm just thinking like I want to
play more co-op games of girls and like
I forgot about the existence of this one
so I need to remember Split Screen
Co-op
but not it's not necessarily remote
Co-op right uh uh couch Co-op it can be
remote
huh I should I need I need any need
co-op games anyway um especially couch
Co-op because then we can play those
with
narissa uh in the males just
saying because remote Co-op I can play
any time with people you know and then
couch Co-op I'm always a set that I
can't play with
anybody my total for the games is
already over 100 oh that's totally fine
I I was expecting
more that is even within my
already existing budget of the the the
cards the steam cards that I already
[Music]
have 140 or so could be all of it oh
let's
[Music]
go you know what this was actually so
fun and you you guys seem really excited
to bring out recommendations if there is
another Steam Sale upcoming at some
point let me know whenever there's a
steam sale now that I know that I have
permission to do these kind of streams
um let me know cuz I then we can go
shopping for new games you know spring
sale yeah yeah yeah yeah let's do it
again I want to do it
again please I'm excited there's one for
every season all right then we should
get together like this not that I'm
gifting everyone names each time maybe
sometimes I just give them to
myself and if I find something that's
perfect for someone I could also
additionally gift it to others but
yeah yeah that would be fun then we can
make a plan for what games to play in
the upcoming months and all
that sounds good sounds good shopping is
fun yeah I like looking at these games
like the opportunities and then it
reminds me of games that I wanted to
play before and I forgot about
them a slime Rancher is so cheap who did
you guys say would like slime
Rancher
this what
this what's
[Music]
this my
god wow like a a game it's an a game
[Music]
for cute can I play
this you know what I'm thinking this is
a combination of um little witch NOA and
ater
game
sleeper hits this year I think I've seen
it like in the past couple
days I was like I got to remember
this in the chat we
want she is she
modded I think I gave her mod before
didn't I I can't see
her here we we
oh cute and we are write something again
let me try to find
you I'm I'm staring at the chat so I can
catch you and we we we W there you are
you like this
game did you play it uh add as
moderator
uh there we go
W yeah this this for me how much how
much oh it's still new so they they
don't um drop the price that much but
that's
fine just for
myself just
uh
extra cuz I just I don't want to stop
yet which spring
R I hope I can get per for
it
nice treat yourself just for
research's just do a bit more
[Music]
research
research I want to play
an
wow is this a remake of an older
[Music]
one all Germans like on it's in my
blood it's calling for
me isn't it like really ship heavy
gameplay
I only remember it from when I was like
tiny tiny small
waah looks
[Music]
nice this one was originally released
shut
up no it's
building
oh this is an austri I know is austring
look m
what you isn't it German I think it's
German not
Austrian what it's
Austrian has portal how do you
know
no how do you know no they have full v
no no yes because then I can look at
games a bit more okay F go back up they
told you
my genius
plan all right all right we're not done
guys we're not
done portal would have been so
good they probably already planned out
like a ton of co-op games for them
to play in the next two
years cuz they plan ahead like crazy
read rich
rich that
game
really why do we keep on going back to
this
game however the you say this is
the story of an item shop a girl who
lives in it and the fairy who turned her
life upside
down okay or we could also give them
which spring are
cuz they played no better didn't they
okay this is kind of a crazy pick to me
but it's funny and I I do agree that
aesthetically it suits them very well
cuz that's the first thing I said when
this I saw this
game why no portal cuz they already have
the game I guess they're planning to
play it at some point which is exactly
what I wanted so
awesome how the is it so cheap
though portal is there any more games
that are this cheap that I should get
like now before it's gone God of
War I want to get God of
War I was thinking about that for a long
time and Skyrim I need to get Skyrim but
which one isn't there like sever ones
it's so confusing to
me huh
special edition don't get
anniversary a special edition okay I'll
remember
[Music]
that oh man was this was this
Witcher
two where's
One
what didn't you guys tell me anyway to
just play
two okay I I need to put it on my list
so just so that I remember to buy it Red
Dead Redemption for
myself before the steam sale
ends o
Mafia Mafia maybe for for the future I
should get Mafia
too I really liked it when Amma was
playing it I only like peaked into it
every once in a while because I didn't
want to spoil it myself so that I can
play it myself
sometime oh also
wait you're your truck your
truck I need to get your truck for
myself five bucks right
now you Truck simul Simulator 2
damn spending spending all this money on
[Music]
me spending oh spending all this money
on me on me on me what you going to do
with all these games all these these
games in your library I'm going to play
them on my streams on my streams here on
my streams my streams my streams my
funny little
streams what is this this what's this
welcome to an exclusive look at what's
new and grounded make it and break it
1.3 update it's packed with features
improvements and content that will
revamp your entire experience in the
backyard so sit back and let's dive deep
into what you can expect in today's
update introducing playgrounds our
ambitious game mode that allows you to
create share and play new grounded
experiences with a new suite of tools
and features built right into the we're
on
trailer
Xbox in a
world where terrifying creatures rule
the
land where danger look works in the
shadows you become
[Music]
small and we everything is to eat you
yeah I think I remember when I first
watched this trailer I was like oh
co-ops Co-op
dream to fight the forces of
nature and solve the biggest mystery
that's ever come to your
backyard
if they can rebuild the memories of a
helpful
robot they might just be able to unlock
the
truth before it's too
late is that free to use that song
starring the
teams featuring
burle Dr Wendel
tul the rude
mother F have why are you pulling this
out of your ass f m have that
game where do people get this
information you're kidding
me what do you mean they have that
game no
way let me DM
them f f
do do you
have my God they probably have the OG if
that is just a a like a what do you call
games again when you put them on a new
platform they prefer to play the games
like on their original platforms
anyway a port yeah so if it's a port
then they might might actually uh have
the OG I can see them having that they
have a lot of like old
games is this couch
cup or why did you recommend that just
now would be great to give them a couch
Co-op game oh there local co-op and I
love Rayman can I give them this
I love Raymond ever since my
[Music]
childhood wait I want to play with
narissa oh wait also H what's that game
that one uh like a game award or
something like that
[Music]
uh difficult
game uh 2D uh cuphead
yeah but maybe they even have cuphead
who
knows where's the
I want see how to
co-op song is probably copyright Co-op
to how how would you Co-op um in what
capacity how much
cheap two people playing at the same
time on the same screen do you play
together
like in the same world like
level different characters it's like
Mario
Coop
screenshot
oh oh are these like uh the different
characters that you can
play h
I don't know Fu's game choices are
pretty interesting and all that but as
far as I know they're not
particularly the greatest gamers are
they
uh so isn't cuphead like really
difficult from what I
hear you know yeah isn't it like maybe
too hard for them just worried I'm just
worried you know I don't want to throw
this at them and you know they they go
mad like I can already imagine forever
being like
no they would be playing together in in
my head
shots fir I'm not trying to shot fire
them but uh I'm just trying you know I'm
I just want to get them something
fitting do it for the cont it would be
funny it would be funny just to see them
suffer
yeah all right all right
cuphead don't think we need to watch the
trailer we know what this game is yeah
they maybe they'll even feel feel like
forced because I gave them the game that
they have to play and then be good at it
and then and then finish it and then
this will be the biggest suffering Arc
of fuu that you will ever
see and we there's free people now so
you can join them
too what does that mean you mean you
mean cuphead can be played with free
people
now oh no no I I don't need to be part
of that don't worry I don't want to be
part of that I don't I'm I don't want to
play cuphe
head I would be at least on the same
level or around the same level
of yeah skill
AKA lack of
skill which I mean would make a great
team surely no but no I don't trust
myself with this game
[Music]
no I'm not not necessarily the gamer of
ien I am the game finisher of Ian guys
don't forget you know I like I like both
titles but uh if we a realistic I am the
game
finisher I have no confidence
no I think this is good and we'll leave
it at
this this this this is my list uh this
is just extras for me to get for myself
and possibly you know to co up with
Isa um Raymond Legends I wonder if I can
play it on my gaming laptop surely I can
right y let's
go that was fun that was kind of fun
it's like going shopping for real for
real I love going
shopping yay great list I hope they will
enjoy the games although I feel like
I me keeping Ena tails of eyes feels so
freaking biased and and is so easy like
almost too easy feel kind of conflicted
about that but at the same time I do
think she would really like it and I
want her to get into tales off
games
what what
what you think am has payday do we need
do we need a backup for
Payday for
am do we need a backup
perhaps
what she already
played okay that is very sad because
that was like an invitation to play with
me just get her deep rock Galactic
too but that means I would kick someone
out of this
group oh we could do Ian but and I feel
bad I already decided on this
group entropy
Center another one of the games that I
am biased
[Music]
about uh yeah she probably doesn't have
the
DLC just do multiple collabs yeah but I
I feel like it's not so interesting to
give people the same games here we
should have some
variety just get her tunic I really want
Tom to play tunic but I don't think it's
happening
represent it's a good choice right crony
played it without me begging her to play
it but it's kind of a good choice I
think for
am
and the depths are really
nice in case you don't know I played
this on stream fully it really
cool cuz like it has these
rewinding and four
winding
mechanics that adds a lot like yo look
at
that it's really cool
yeah they even watched me play
it yeah am would love am waying tunic
you can't you can't Amma way tunic you
can only golden path
tunic
[Music]
h
no she said I'm a away the entropy
Center okay you know what she'll get the
Hotline Miami DLC for payday cuz she
already has payday but I doubt she has
Hotline Miami deals she should play did
she ever play Hotline Miami I feel like
she could have fun with hotl Miami too
and I'm a way way through hotl Miami as
[Music]
well I did check cross code already yeah
yeah that's saw her kind of
game I don't know I feel like it might
be so I said uh okay the DLC and entropy
Cent how about that how much is
it 10
bucks I think I could probably get a
free
code
maybe yeah two gifts for who who who who
who well tala's
principal I'm pretty happy with my
choice here but uh let me look at that I
heard that name before but I forgot what
it
was puzzle
game devolver digital I
wonder who will you be our
children will you love us for having
created
you will the world you build be like
ours or so different that today we
cannot even imagine
it step into the light
child is there anything that we
associate more closely with intelligence
than
curiosity our mythologies are full of R
you may go freely to all the worlds of
my
garden but if the tower tempts
you be wise do not let yourself be
misled by doubt
W for it shall bring death and the end
of your Generations
interesting waa
Sublime magical let your will be
done
[Music]
2014 for weeks an artificial
intelligence okay that is interesting
and I might give that to her because me
gifting entropy Center is again very bad
biased didn't you not play this
really did she T's principal what if we
GI her free
games ENT
presenter no
no h Lego rings has local
co-op stop stop
stop stop ing me and and baiting me and
and and and all that oh my God play that
with narissa which
one
Lego don't tempt me that's what I want
to say stop tempting me don't tempt
me I don't know if we have Lego
perms it's kind
of I don't know I feel like Lego
wouldn't give us perms let me look it up
Lego
go oh oh we have Lego Star Wars
PS and Lego 2K drive whatever that
is but you know how I feel about Star
Wars play Star Wars of
cor better than Mario
Kart
guys guys guys yeah no I think I'll
leave it at that um
uh we're I'm pretty satisfied thank you
guys we should keep it there so it's a
compact stream I want it to be a compact
stream
okay a backup I don't know if we need a
backup but um if she has this already
then I'll give her the entropy
Center thank you guys for helping me you
guys were a great help
uh if any of them who don't have a
backup have one of these games then
we'll have to get back to
it I'll I'll ask you maybe in a
different
stream backup tunic for everyone please
please audience you guys in the chat
please play
tunic thanks thank you that was fun that
was fun and gets you into a Christmas
mood doesn't it snow is falling speaking
of
Christmas
[Music]
uh no wait no tomorrow is members only
then the day after tomorrow is my
Christmas car okay and oh yeah I wanted
to say
tomorrow I've been you know kind of I
realized
how difficult it seems uh for me to get
the sock puppet stuff going and lot a
lot of other stuff uh family stuff and
so on so yeah I think tomorrow I might
only be members and I'll do I'll have to
make the sock puppets
tomorrow yeah no Hokkaido game for now
cuz I need to make five sock puppets
tomorrow and then yeah I wrote the
script for the sock puppet finale
yesterday took me like 2
hours and I hope it's okay cuz I haven't
written something like this in many many
years I don't even remember when I last
attempted to write a proper story it may
have been in
school yeah uh it's it's
uh everybody's involved
so it's an epic
tale uh epic I don't know if it's epic
it's a little bit cringe for
sure will you make the sock puppets on
stream no I don't want to spoil you guys
too much about the sock puppets cuz
they're really they turn out so funny
and that's a nice surprise and um I I
think I can do it faster off stream
especially cuz like with gloves it's a
bit
challenging
yeah cringe is based cringe good content
really well I feel like there's good
funny cringe and then there's cringe
that's just cringe you
know I hope it will be the good funny
kind of cringe but I don't I don't even
think it's
like I was trying to make some jokes and
all that in the script too but I'm I'm I
might be pretty bad at it but please go
easy on me I tried my
best you'll see in the finale hopefully
it won't be late but uh I already got
some voice I just sent the script out
like 24s hours ago or less than that 20
hours ago or so and I already got voice
L
from from
crony and from
narissa Blue tall ladies are on my side
guys they are on my
side oh thanks for the membership gift
thank
you yeah but but I'm going to try my
best to keep
everybody on their tippy toes and
tomorrow members only we're watching a
very very special movie there's a new
Chicken Run movie uh that just came out
and we're going to watch it it's on
[Music]
Netflix
dawn of the Nugget yeah a new chicken
one yes yes yes yes yes yes I think it
fell under the radar of a lot of
people yeah
exciting cuz we also watched the first
chicken one together didn't
we who would have thought that they
would bring out a new chicken run
that's crazy I got to decide what to eat
now I think I'll leave Super Chat
reading for another time oh also one
more
thing uh polar Awards Christmas poll
Awards I'll be doing that next week on a
Monday stream the 25th I'll most likely
be streaming and whatever stream that
will be will be you guys will be able to
get a polo
Ro a Christmas Edition Polo of
roid
yeah I said I was going to take
Christmas off but um it it ended up
being
like Sunday the 24th where it's really
Christmas for me uh in the morning I
have the stream the Among Us
stream and then on Monday I feel I feel
like obligated to stream as well in the
evening so I'm probably going to stream
in the evening too I'll be fine I have
all day of Sunday and like you the first
half of the day of Monday that's
plenty yeah it's okay I I I want
to
[Music]
I no my my mom is already here she's
staying with my
brother and they're like doing stuff uh
and they're prep prepping the Christmas
dinner that we're going to have
have on Sunday but don't worry about it
we're we're spending time
together
[Music]
mhm yeah so in German we s v in I guess
and oh yeah cuz Monday 25th is not
Christmas for me anymore really we don't
see 25th as Christmas anymore so it's
really just the
24th don't worry about it don't worry
about it
thank you see you tomorrow
[Music]
membersan and if you guys are bored
check out the the fixed camera angle
version of the great wand that I
uploaded randomly yesterday on the
YouTube channel of takanashi kiar from H
life English
myth H it's it's pretty dope I actually
watched it several times cuz it's just
oh it's just such a good
song and you can appreciate the corio a
bit more yeah watch it again maybe I'll
upload something tomorrow too for all
the
non-members yeah if we're not having a
public
stream I might do that tomorrow or the
day after tomorrow because the day after
tomorrow is an unarchive stream so it's
also a possibility to put something up
on the channel oh anyway thank you so
much for helping me out my dear elves I
guess today you guys are elves because I
mean if you help out Santa
wa I guess that what what that means
that that you are eles that's that's
what that means chicken
[Music]
elves
a thank you
byebye ho ho ho ho
ho
Merry
[Music]
Christmas what what ho ho ho that's what
Santa
[Music]
says
wo
[Music]
w