[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
pap
oh that was
Sun there's no
transition k k k
k welcome hello good morning afternoon
evening C it's T day two oh day two day
two I'm
scared and no wores we are in best
condition to finish this game I don't
know if my brain cell is working
today will be fine will be fine it
started good yesterday just went kind of
downhill we'll just we'll just warm up
for a couple of levels
right no we be fine we'll be fine we
learned the basics yesterday okay okay
yeah hi guys hello how's the audio by
the way yeah how is it I mean I heard I
was uh when I screamed yesterday it kind
of peaked I don't know if it will peek
again today possibly it
will I think I think it's okay if we
peek cuz we're we're not using ena's
normal microphone we're using those tiny
lava Ms that you put on your shirt yeah
CU my normal microphone I Lally speak
like a few centimeters away from it so
having both of us will be even
worse yeah but they're so cool I want
them to they're so yeah they're pretty
nice they go for like cooking streams
and stuff
oh canel oh don't disc no I accidentally
pressed the button n actually for
cooking streams I want to get like an
ASMR microphone even though this would
be useful yeah but maybe for like
dancing streams I could get one of those
yeah yeah yeah there's you know the ones
we use in the studio like the ones
attached those look pretty good too you
can attach it to like this thing just
the mic no you know said the batteries
are maximum 2 hours so maybe if this
stream is longer than 2
hourss might have to switch microphones
maybe maybe I mean I think last time it
wasn't charged too full cuz I had it in
the baggage for a while we'll see we'll
see I mean I think it's it should last
until we finish so
hopefully so yeah fluffy cute microphone
and and oh somebody was asking if takor
is sleepy I'm not really sleepy what
about you you know I'm okay I see you
have a just opened Red Bull in your hand
Taco bll you mean Taco Taco cow I don't
know what to call it I'm confused why do
you the times I've seen you drink coffee
it was always um
decaf I just don't have Caffe needed
coffee in my house other than the ones I
have to like actually grind the beans
I'm lazy
because I think if you drank coffee now
wouldn't that be healthier for you
youa it doesn't have the same kick
anymore oh you need a kick I can kick
kick you no thank you maybe would like
that but I don't know
about gety kick to start the day
anybody the famous k k k k keep it away
from W oh yeah I actually when I open
any kind of energy drink you know
they're usually like this small yeah I
just need like two sips and it gets me
incredibly energized people think I
drank like five Red Bulls even though I
really only drank like two sips and
usually I don't even finish the bottles
the cans because I just don't I don't
know it's very intense The Taste is like
probably it's probably for the better me
some people just have like more Toler
cfee so maybe it's because like I never
forc myself to always like drink like a
can yeah coffee too so I'm like still
very like sensitive to all of those
effects yeah it's like look like with
your bladder when you don't strain it
too
much I know go very minion if you strain
too much and it extends I guess let's
go you mean when you go ID don't meeting
so much right
just because I have a bladder doesn't
mean that I pee I go to idle meetings
just like you just like all of you guys
right chickens right they all Idols yes
there we go want
to where's the key right there though no
no I don't want oh okay I got the silver
key wait oh so if you do the blue one
yeah then it blows us oh I can't see
that side
wait I need to get the gift you think
I'll die oh oh I can't go
there got
it w starting strong today come up here
okay I can't CL I can't climb the oh are
you going to I got to take the flower
yeah and then I change
to we're
so e a good start today good start
flower do you have your favorite
[Music]
flower do you have a favorite I like
all I mean oh we can't really get
there need to press the
Buton oh you to press the blue button
huh I need to move this a little bit
more can I
see and uh okay wait one gift get the
what do we press uh the blue one the
blue one so that we can get the
there hi shyy Jo you know what's your
favorite flower
[Music]
um look you used flowers a lot your in
your motives I like hydrangeas
hydrangeas hydras are nice my mom has
like so many hydrangeas in when when
it's the season in her garden so
many beautiful just because I have a
song named V Des me is my favorite
flower what what there's a there's a
flower called Violet so they're like oh
it must be your favor I'm just like
no if that's the case then what make an
off it's also so
F oh yeah right yeah you naming your
songs after flowers well that go on
forever until you have like a full
bouquet and then you make an album
that's called bouquet but we already had
a bouquet like their
Liv whatever just call it the same maybe
the same thing but like maybe in in in
German in German bouquet is
St just call us in a different Lang this
reminds me I think we were in the car
and you were talking about freeden
except you said it in a German accent so
I was like I was like did I just hear
freen but in that's how you you really
pronounce
it German
for how's my German action say it
again St first
f not bad not bad good R pronunciation
okay uses a lot of German lels yeah
generally all the character names are
actually German and then a lot of anime
and games like just sounds cool yeah
they love to use German stuff but like
sometimes I I it really um sounds funny
to me cuz like yeah they use German
words but in a way that we wouldn't
really use it like they use um they they
combined certain words like whatever
like flower day or so in German and then
call a city that when often it's it's a
word combination that's that we probably
wouldn't really use I me but then again
if you think about it even the like
Japanese names they like put in like you
know like random vocabulary sometimes
and then it's their name kind of you
mean like jaanese
Kani like meant something else like
let's say let's say uh Yamada for
example is Mountain
field it's kind of like that
no
yeah
yeah yeah yeah I guess yeah yeah but
just I I just feel like they they for
example they would use Yamada put it in
the Google translator and find uh
befi befi yeah the translation and then
they will just like call the plus next
time you be like
hey that's a German you should ask her
you should ask her like do you want a
cool German name oh maybe I will and
then the I feel like the Japanese
pronunciation for that would be ber you
think she like it that sounds
cool it sounds very like you know
cheting it's
like
exactly she's not going to know what it
mean she'll think it's awesome she'll
think it's cool I know it sounds cool
more
exactly
Y no what does that what's the like
English translation for that uh you got
to know it what comes before two what
comes before
two oh yeah I guess so that's the very
direct literal trans ation what's is
there not like a more
like like not literal what's the more of
a natural translation natural
translation is there one
one
one okay what comes before two would be
before
for
in
that's your new name it became even
longer what v v do you want say Z plus
one 0 plus
one uh n plus n
plus you sure it's not a spell does it
sound like a spell to you maybe
bewitching you maybe if I need a cool
you know I have the what is it raging
Taco kick no the sorable taco kick and
raging Taco punch Maybe funny another
move can you can name it for
me raging Taco kick no raging Taco pun
and sorrowful Taco sorrowful Taco kick I
know where did that come from
holograph okay let's that's they made me
shout move names in holograph H we
should use you should uh try to use the
sorrowful tacle kick against Kik kick
and see which one wins I think kick wins
no no no but that it depends okay in
fighting games guys if someone does a
high kick and someone does a low kick
which one wins low kick wins doesn't it
cuz they
Crouch when it comes to hit
boxes I guess so I win cuz sful tle kick
it's like a side kick
like
[Music]
just okay uh video game knowledge well
I'll come up with some new fighting
moves too is it next time you get to be
in holograph you should be like can you
get an ultimate move is there ever going
to be a next time we get be holograph
honestly sometimes I just get told I'm
just like oh by the way you need to
record for Hol I'm just like what like
the only times is like the countdown
holograph for example that's true I had
that one other one where I appeared but
I didn't have a line but was that it was
like a recent is
one what CH probably knows was it a what
purpose was it oh I think it was like
the one with the no Senpai and SP
Senpai Umi yeah
Umi well
yeah was it the sponsor Nina when are be
getting more I don't ask her that I
don't know probably doesn't know yeah I
don't know the one nor nor was taken to
prison oh yeah cuz nor was doing all
kinds of you know
um
um but was that an official holograph
yeah it
was but only like sub members appeared
like if you didn't even get align I feel
like it's you know so I literally got
notified like like a day or so before it
got released I like oh by the way you're
in here but you didn't have a line so we
didn't tell you but I was like oh I
think they only many times I was in
holograph was the the debut holograph
and the countdown holograph
H1 be nice ah ah and uh there was a
there was a us the Holo summer holograph
of like caner too stuff like that but
like that's only because the you know
Japanese uh groups so I don't know if
you're lucky and you're in one of those
groups
like then you get included yeah but we
have our own cool stuff now yeah hold on
Ian repeat those are cute those are so
cute I love them I still haven't checked
on who made the Red Bull can
one
oh who made the Red Bull can one they
were like oh yeah by the way we chose an
episode of your your stream for the Holo
oh Ian r was going to be the Red Bull
counting one and I was just
like I remember that one St
s excuse me they made one of me recently
that where it was so old it was in the
first six months of my whole lifetime an
incident where I fell from the chair um
and then they animated it kind of wrong
uh so it wasn't how I actually felt I
fell more dramatically actually was
standing on the chair but they just uh
animated me sitting on the chair and
reaching after something and then
falling but I actually stood on the
chair and then like just balanced and
then fell and I I don't know they
couldn't change it anymore but the truth
guys the truth you know it you know how
it went down don't let them gas light
you they didn't let the cour back Heaven
no no no they just misunderstood they
didn't know it was more dramatic but
yeah guys check out the H and repeats
are quite
funny and Nostalgia yeah
all right next one we got this what if
we forgot to play drink
the it's okay that's people people
really want us to talk anyway people
will say anyway oh you should just do a
t don't play the game I want to play a
game I like video games yeah and
especially cuz it's a you know local
only thing wait you stayed there okay
what IAL only thing
oh car this uh somewhere
like yeah where okay and then if we oh
maybe you can jump using this on top to
get to the
red right and then I bring this over
here but what about wait I I do again so
that you can get the present ah oh wait
well I think you have to jump wait okay
okay hold on maybe I can get up oh yeah
that should
work oh you got it you got it toad is
more bouncy okay today feeling very
bouncy I mean have you ever touched
mushrooms there
bounce like mushroom touching is maybe
okay eating not so much did you ever
have mushrooms grow in your like
backyard and
stuff no I don't I don't the only
backyard I ever had was with my grandma
oh I remember there was like sometime
places where it was like really humid
and
stuff
I have helicopter record helicopter what
do you mean I'm still very embarrassed
about how they depicted my movements in
the countdown holograph that was pretty
embarrassing to me you need to go down I
think
yeah you guys know what I mean right
those those W movements are so
embarrassing wait I got to okay then you
can come
up koi Kai easy easy
Kai jump jump
jump you got it you got
it the why didn't that go in go
in did you just die twice in like 5
Seconds your skirt was right wrong yeah
cuz it wasn't tight anymore my skirt is
a tight skirt okay it may be difficult
to dance in a tight skirt but it is what
it is is is this flower not on no
somebody turn the flower on I think we
need to we need to
jump get up there for
sure oh my God the the
crocodile and then
oh it could we might not need that
anymore okay yeah come up
here then what do I do
ah okay yeah you probably need to press
a button for me
[Music]
P L's cover of do you is the most
rewatched part of the shuffle
[Music]
manly he really I guess that left the
biggest impression oh you can't go there
maybe I have to get
it but even then I think it will blow
you away will it no oh nice nice
[Music]
okay what about the blue present oh wait
no uh wait can I like the crocodile can
go through oh maybe you can get the the
spring from below with the
yellow can you bring
it oh yeah oh my
God what
fall oh
[\h__\h] good thing you careful why why am I
yes
crocodile and then the little Mario
Mario sorry I stepped on byci how do we
oh I guess we just used that
huh oh I didn't know you can get through
these so
easily we did
it we're good
[Music]
nice it can't me fans watching many
times this year well thank you guys uh I
mean I wasn't in it just my song but I'm
on it good good I'm still shocked when
it sent you oh yeah oh my
God that was that was shocking on many
levels
MH oh yeah we were both featured with
our
songs our outfits well yours yours was
stretched mine was SE smaller yeah have
you did you like get a a sress sress to
fix it seamstress to fix it after my
S
um I mean I had extra of the same outfit
so it wasn't problem you're like you
know those anime characters who just
have the same out oh we need to Le the B
over here mhm or
or did you I we have to lift it up maybe
have to stand
oh help
me get out of there love that Trope yeah
okay we have to like jump on it can we
actually jump on it I right jumping and
then picking then we break the from
yesterday oh
God okay go go go go go go go go ah get
it it's okay it's okay as long as we
break two more oh wait just by Instinct
I just try to pick it up from the side
but that's not how it works
huh
nice oh we need one more to break the
see see see see a tiny boom it's going
to it's going to it's going to explode
it's going to explode is
it oh you're so good explosive yeah well
I know how to I know how to work with
bombs cuz I myself am a bomb a sexy bomb
wow sex bomb sex bom my sex
bom sex bomb sex bomb you're my sex bomb
I need to look up the lyrics you know
you turn me on sex bump I don't know I
really don't know the lyrics drop it
right know the lyrics enough I've never
heard that song what wait we need to get
that b well now that's really
embarrassing you never heard it before
no we need to get the gift it's up there
okay you're
last that's so
embarrassing never heard it
before I'm always embarrassing myself oh
I need to jump on a bomb I think
otherwise
okay okay it's time it's okay you got it
you got it nice well getting the job
done I don't think I've heard that song
what do you mean why
what oh now you're embarrassing people
that wait wait how I mean
it's who sang that
[Music]
sex song by Moose T and Tom
Jones from
1999 it's really famous is it only
famous in Europe or what maybe what the
hell I don't know how to get it's pretty
iconic it is is that the new ke original
exactly that's what I'll perform at
fifth Fest go
here okay Ena needs my brain guys sorry
let me let me try to figure this out
yeah push that button that will there's
that but
oh I know okay I know but it's on the
red one we push that so it falls down
then we can
Kaboom that's right yeah all at
once yeah platforming
woohoo what this do uhuh what this do
ahuh okay
ah totally not AO wait did this flower
turn on it does
okay okay so got to jump to get the blue
one as the platform Falls jump it I
didn't first try
no
Tri uh-oh I'm a bubble
[Music]
run okay okay you to try again
yes
wait sorry my brain my
brain oh now I'm too
early
wow come on okay from this
one okay now we got to do the the
Whatchamacallit
the the bomb and then bring it using the
yellow and the red okay I can maybe help
where are we oh God time
press the red and the
yellow and the
yellow oh oh it turns that off
okay okay maybe when it's on the red and
then you press the
yellow like when it's past this point I
you want another B I have to you want to
carry it all the way up okay okay okay
and uh go yeah look at that oh oh it
just
yeah [\h__\h] I can't from the
side okay we got it we got it got it I
how did that happen I didn't see we're
fine we're D over okay okay um okay you
know what to do
yeah hi
careful Tim Allen being
like so you know uh home improv friend
uh the TV show yeah somewhat y one thing
we
no it's only cuz my my mom or used to
watch like the uh the Home Improvement
things cuz she likes doing DIY stuff for
like my my family home literally every
corner of the house Mama nie has like
renovated herself oh really like if like
what kind of stuff like tiles floor what
well well we did I mean they did the
basement like Flooring by themselves no
wait I did it again I want to pick it up
from the side all the time sorry it's my
no
that okay tell me about your mom's DIY
okay okay we got to start hey from here
I forgot this thing already what did we
do
here we got to break the bomb throw it
throw it like right here go
away you were so invincible good
job good job it's still being
Invincible [\h__\h] it's
okay hit box polities don't do this to
me what if I stand here oh I can't stand
[Music]
here no is that too
far perfect okay now I go oh we need
another one no no no no we need the red
one uh-oh are we good I can do something
up
here first of all I'm gonna get the
gift and what's this ah nice okay okay
perfect we just need to get the uh bomb
here oh that's too
far I
don't
why kind of ran into it
[Laughter]
too okay okay okay don't
move oh all I got
this my n
okay now you can
go I guess I can take the top one
yeah hi hi
hi
Kaboom hi hi hi I can press the
red okay it's fine oh don't go I'll go
I'll go I'll go oh Hy Hy Hy
Hy it's okay as long as you get the goal
it's fine all right go go go go Toad's
on the way toad leave me
behind go on without help me this should
be your new catch phras it it's kind of
been when I was starting my okay we know
what to do here yeah totally
totally totally oh it did it work oh no
I just jumped because it looked so nice
you jump on it okay you got it jump on
it God damn it I on top of
that got to do it again we need one more
bomb Jump On
It b
[Music]
b careful bomb
away yeah
now nice okay PA is clear I I'm going to
get the blue gift
first wow beautiful
oh and now I'm going to get the yellow
gift uh but no it was like this
yeah okay uh okay I'm ready to become
Santa Claus of all these gifts oh just
press press press yellow
nice beautiful so smooth so smooth so
smooth she's doing it we got everything
I'm ready to okay let's go easy
perfect what do you mean you're not
doing the heavy lifting in this map
we're both doing it I think they're R
sarcastic oh okay okay
okay oh I didn't even see that sarcasm I
just immedately think people are all
against me the world is against me I
must fight the world with my
k you know do you think you're you're
good at picking up sarcasm generally
somewhat really depends on the context
though you're atic
person
[Music]
um oh and then you got to go get the
thing and then jump
oh you got to you got to fall and then
jump before you hit the spikes you think
I can do that
yeah
I swear I pressed jump it didn't work
all right I I'll give it a try I got
this show me then show
[Music]
me and uh hi I'm here hi what do I do
now oh e the red
[Music]
one
nice now I just need
the the yellow one h
a oh wait I activate here you go oh did
you already get the gift yeah go go you
can do
it okay
nice and then I just need to do this and
go wait oh okay
nice cron is a good example of
sarcasm
I don't know about sarcasm but I I
really have a hard time like reading
crony I love her but like uh yeah I I I
have a hard
time cuz she she always
talks so Jill and she talking riddles
with not much emotion in her
voice she a mysterious woman okay I
think I
know I mean I think she I guess she is
kind of sarcastic most time
yeah why do I always go too early I
don't even think now okay and then you
press the button which button the blue
one oh okay and I get the
gift right right what's
inside
C what is inside you know you know it's
guys to the Taco does Ena ate your
cookies today herself I didn't even
finish it it wasn't that great what wait
where's the rest of the cookie can I eat
it in the trash
what she didn't even I have standards K
you have cookie
standards okay now I can get the make
sure to get the
[Music]
blue
nce was chocolate chip cookie it was it
was but it wasn't what wrong with the
chocolate or the
cookie balance of the cookie part and
the chocolate and the texture was not
that great oh and yeah the Judgment has
been passed it was not good enough I
mean the bare minimum I'll do is Subway
cookies okay that's the bare
minimum I still remember there's a hotel
mhm that I've been to in London but it's
like all over the world uhhuh um where
it's it's from the Hilton chain I think
it was a Double Tree or something when
you I don't know if it's all over the
world but it seems to be like their
basic procedure when you check in you
get a fresh warm hot cookie for chicken
and they were so good they were like
chunky chocolate chip cookie they were
soft inside and they were warm and they
were so big
too absolutely amazing I went back for
more and even though you only get the
checken they were so nice to make more
for us oh that's nice and then I even
found a recipe and I made them really P
myself at home in a in a stream actually
we made a cookie stream yeah the double
tream I love I love making my own
cookies
honestly Ena can you make your Ena
cookies for me to test while I'm still
here I don't think there is enough time
of course there is cookies don't take so
long hours I will regret my whole life
if I don't get to eat your cookies while
in here I can make it other time no what
how long did you just say how many hours
six hours
hours but what I'll help you wait
what I'll be your assistant how about
that I'll never have the cookies I mean
I still make GI to some other time when
I know you can come over again or if I I
can go over it's best to like bake or
cook in your in your own home I would
say right like in other kitchens you
have to like get to know the kitchen and
all that and that's
[Music]
like H how do I get
there how do you get that
gift is there a pathway we not a cuz
there's an extra life over there too oh
oh oh look at oh look at where I
am now can you press a a uh some button
any button
really just want to see what happens and
now the
red yeah but like how do you get there
it makes no sense maybe you have to jump
on the bird maybe you have to time it in
a way that you can jump off the bird but
that would be ridiculous too
it goes through the
stairs oh there's a jumpy thing over
there that makes more sense oh there was
there was at the very corner of the map
Corner oh why are we so
blind maybe Love is Blind hold give give
me the boy here oh
ow and then can you press
the sure
wonder what this does I will be your
jump pad now
oh
what that's not fair I wonder if you
could have from there jumped on the bird
and then used the that's what is never
jumping
platform okay I'll be the sub subject
this
time you're taller so I get more jump
momentum too oh wa this is this pretty
good actually even without the bir
[Music]
G
okay absolute
skills oh oh
oh okay I'll get the I'll get the door
okay and then maybe come back and I'll
try it the same way to get the gift oh
careful
[Music]
careful we have two lives can we bring
the bu somehow I wonder m yeah possibly
yeah for the no maybe not actually no
maybe possibly not okay I jump on you no
no no okay no stay didn't want to go
there I always love seeing new play
together one of my favorite face in the
world thank you yeah okay okay you got
this I love to see it too we love to see
it what are we going to we going to try
from here okay okay I press on did the
hand stand jump up
there do you want me to go to the key
the golden key yeah wait I didn't I was
looking no God damn it no don't tell
have to do from the start again or was
this the start of something the start
okay oh god wow we
are cute here we
[Music]
go you know we have to get a long to do
co-op no fighting oh
[Music]
oh bounce bounce bounce bounce wait can
can you carry this ah okay
okay you can try carrying the jumpy
thing and then jumping on my
head yeah then we can bring that over oh
nice I hope that bird never comes back
bring bring this
[Music]
over okay open once
okay bring this over I don't know how to
bring it over though careful oh no no no
you carry it and then you jump you jump
on my head again okay
okay ni okay
I'm still alive okay aming it's okay you
can get there and then get the bouncy
Point bouncy Point uh
okay uh right you want me to take it
yeah yeah yeah grab it I can't
unfortunately okay well I'll try but can
you press the blue button anyway or
maybe we shouldn't oh oh oh my
God and then we can use that to get up
the L wonder if we just made it a lot
more complicated than it needed to be
because couldn't we have dropped it like
already in the first red thingy and then
just carry it from down here all the
way oh wait this need the red present
though don't open it all right right it
I think it uh won let us do the thing
all right I'm but how do I get this back
up uh we don't maybe okay I think can
you put the ah okay
I think I I would need your head at
least oh well oh that's okay it's okay
we can ret try this we know how to do it
faster
yeah
oh
cannonballs somehow I feel
like it it was like a Hing
Cannonball that's not fair like eating
MERS now oh that sounds
[Music]
nice what I do from here okay you go
down and press the blue I
think can I get the okay I got the I got
the
present and then you can I
think I think you can carry The Bu down
here across and then bring it
[Music]
up nice
nice and then if you press the red
you'll be able to go to the other
[Music]
side I think the the springy thing it
protects you from certain death nice yes
okay and then you can go up and get
the
you stay down no I want to
go I I don't need the big Mar I'm just
going to continue life with the small
mini
Mario do you want to go back now for the
gift yeah okay do we have to get all
three or we just have to get the red one
now maybe all three I think yeah just
the one just one we had it before
yesterday okay let's go and it's okay
even if we die in the
level
surely surely
okay we know what to do now yeah the one
on the top over there all right grab the
[Music]
thing do we need to what if we yeah cuz
we need to bring it over onto here what
if I just use you as my
my my uh spring bread I'm a spring bread
yeah spring
bread oh I I was going to just anyway
try with the spring bread the spring
bread
oh okay oh wait we can get extra be
would be helpful
sorry we got
it I should have held on to
it oh maybe I have to turn it into blue
and then you can jump yes yes
yes I'm scared of the okay oh I got the
first key nice then we can leave this
place also safely eventually okay um uh
yeah wait do guys do we need the wait
the other gifts aren't even yeah it's
just that one huh we need a key okay
yeah
[Music]
uhoh it protected you oh we need to turn
on the red first
okay
kaai careful you will be cornered if you
go there I have nowhere else to go
okay okay get up here I'll step on you
okay oh okay
jump okay go go go
go all
right it yum it it's okay we're here
we're here okay and the
red all right
[Music]
all good all good y take all the
presents are saved Christmas is Saved
Christmas 2024 is saved did you believe
in Santa when you're
little if anything I believed in d
k huh in in Austria oh I'm tting it's
hard to not die
in she was just listening I was I was
listening okay I was paying attention in
Austria um wait how come I can't go but
you can are you is it cuz you're short
yeah okay and a we were made to believe
that there's a a a chrisin child of
Christ which is an angel and I think
it's supposed to be a girl like a cute
young girl Angel o and she will in the
night of the 24th she will fly and I
guess bring presents more or less and
that's why at night time my mom uh
[Music]
would would make us go outside and wait
a little bit and then we come back and
we get the gifts in the evening oo
there's no no I mean we we know about
Santa Claus because he's being he's
being
advertised just
like why did we have to do this level
again we did it anyway already did we
not we have to get the red gift oh okay
we have to do this too
okay yeah mean I was like why do I'll
finish it right Krampus is not on
Christmas guys Krampus is on Nicolas day
what campus is a really evil evil man
who is evil so it's like Santa
alter no no campus is evil there's a
campus day where many many there's one
compus that that walks around with the
Nicolas Nicolas looks like a Finn Santa
like Santa who just had a
diet
um go oh get the key get the
key okay okay
okay he punishes bad kids yeah K pun
punishes bad kids he's really scary
looks like a devil why
Luigi more scary more way more scary and
like they dress up in like like fur
suits kind of and and they look like a
devil like a yeah like I guess a
furry and then and then people in in The
Villages and so on will also dress up
kind of like that and then they will run
and do campus lare they will run in
groups and like punish anybody who's on
the street and like yeah like whip him
and for real for real it's for I I'll
show you a video later it's so scary
nothing scarier
than
good furry yeah they beat you and they
smear your face with dirt and and some
people probably into that a lot of
people are into that they find
entertainment by being whipped by the
campus and just go out and seek the
torture oh the fun
what oh we have to throw it in the air
cuz like we can't press the blue button
now no no we carry the bomb into the red
and then oh yeah right okay big thinking
big
brain oh
know look at probably do the same thing
for this one
too
o go go go
go go oh [\h__\h] I was too far might be
okay oh
[Music]
too
uhoh okay now we got to get the key
somehow is there a jumpy jumpy somewhere
oh we need to get the bomb down there
okay okay okay and then we can get the
red gift and then we can open the path
the blue thingy come here come
here
run no I need another one I need so
many short
to
[Music]
you say that you know what that reminds
me of what does it remind you of a
song um a vocaloid song Vocaloid song
Hoodie Hood H
hone it's a I think it's something
called something like
[Music]
Sam I think um what's a a Kito Kito kind
of song Nobody Knows
It I see you me I can't get the key it's
okay although we only have two seconds 1
second okay let's do it again without
tangents and then we can do it in 5
seconds but but call it
the what song I I don't think I've heard
it before I'll find it it's so fun it's
such a fun
song I to all right I got
[Music]
this
okay ah now it's from the side
W
uh one more please can I have one more
scoop of BB
please thanks I wonder if I can press
the blue what happens
fin the blue right way uh
uh the blue no I need get the yellow
okay okay okay it's fine go go go no
press the yellow
first Style with a back flip away from
the
bomb still got some stuff to do here oh
there's there's one like right there
walking
around Dam it
no you got it I thought if I just throw
it while like immediately after jumping
out of the teleportation and maybe I can
thr that way
no nice okay it's open
a uh and then we do this oh sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry we do
[Music]
this okay got this key I'll get this
little
one if it gets a bit
closer okay okay and then press oh no we
got to go to the yellow
one oh no
hi let dro the
K here jump on me okay you it
make 20
seconds that's plenty we're good two
more gifts guys did you hear the new um
like whole life song for that was
revealed today yeah there was a in case
you didn't know there was a re a reveal
of the preview of the new song which is
like the The Bu pal P song from before
the shiny my story and so on we have a
new one yeah yeah just a preview
o why must we die at the same
time uh yeah they played it on the
official stream today on the official
Channel guys where the jum thing come
from before jump oh it's cuz we pressed
this and then the jumpy thing fell down
oh hold on hold on let it shoot the
thing go
here press the blue press the blue
okay oh not
aood oh I think I got it and then and
then you
[Music]
press press the red okay
oh oh that was not what I expected oh
can you the
blue I want that gift how's that
possible we need to quickly press the
blue and then the red really fast I
guess up there it could be possible but
how do you get the yellow too yeah
come oh okay okay we'll figure this out
um I don't okay brain brain brain we
need the jumpy thing to get to this one
uhhuh okay I'll bring the jumpy thing
[Music]
back okay let's start with the yellow I
feel like yellow is po how I was just
chilling wait I feel like I have to rest
start we can't get the jumpy thing back
up soft Lo what do you mean
maybe yeah unless there's a way oh maybe
I can hurry up
[Music]
here let's restart I mean we can we can
at least get this and then and
the oh yeah okay oh oh okay it's okay
we'll think we'll think jump on each
other yeah I guess but what do you do
when you're not playing Co-op and you
don't have someone to jump on top of
exactly m cuz I think it's the same
levels right
so Keys we have two we have two brain
cells okay try again oh this is the last
one of this map and then I mean the last
normal one of this
map Donkey Kong you will not get away
with this forever here we go oh why do
we have to redo this one too
it's okay I don't remember it
anymore okay I'll get the other one okay
come on means I can get the yellow
[Music]
speed
accident oh you want that
huh
bab
okay okay
uh y I got jump from the cliff from The
Edge yeah yeah you need more of those
huh maybe I can bring me one or you get
it I got it I got
it how to get up there
again ah the blue
one
uhhuh okay okay uh can you jump on the
on the blue oh now you're up there okay
I'll get I'll get it okay and I bring
the I'll bring the
bomb
te remember everything I'm ready for the
test okay I'll take the golden one this
[Music]
time
okay using Ena as
it's good my head is patted Hur my head
test there's a test there's a test every
level is a test there
skills if we paid attention it's my
birthday average Taco happy birthday
happy
birthday this the one problems yeah
first we got to we got to drop the
thingman jigy now okay okay
right and then you press the red again
mhm and then you jump up there ow that
was so easy right right
right and then uhoh then don't
[Music]
die okay and then we bring that one over
put in
the
yeah ah oh and then and then if
we and then if we press the red again
right
make
if I jump on you yeah
exactly nice cheating absolute cheating
but why not we got to make use of what
we have can I take oh is that okay we
got it we got
it it
worked two brain cells two power is it
possible for our two brain cells to make
a four
one together cuz we seem to be SM
doesn't doesn't it like
cell split so we'll end up with
four so perhaps our brain cells have
multiply o and brain cell
babies I don't think that's brain mosis
mosis is that what it's
called Waites brain cell breeding yeah
maybe our brain cells weren't the the
smartest choices to use to breed with
each other there would have been better
combinations don't bre let me cook let
let me
[Applause]
cook could have been could have been
worse combinations maybe if I breeded my
brain cells with K maybe are you are
implying
that some brain cells are not like the
other yeah oh I see okay press the blue
hi
okay yeah press
they're cute they're cute and then press
press the yellow press the
Yellow Nice uh no uh can I not pick that
up no we need the r picker okay so we
need you to
press the up there is
[Music]
blue okay okay they're
back all
right
how do
I oh maybe maybe we go make them go down
and
then can you bring them up here for the
wine up here yeah I need to I do need to
bring them up there but uh oh and then
just go right
side nice to to now we just need the
key
okay
and
yeah I I will I will let's do it again
and I press the no never mind we need
them to go across again huh or you need
to go
across we need to go across to the
bottom fly across can I I can't fit you
can't fit it's just the Mario okay I'll
bring them down let go guys bring your
kids there don't lose them get out of
here
guys all
right
ah
yeah and then then we press the red
yeah and then the
yellow yeah and then we just press and
you come but like how do they not fall
down from
there I guess they have to fall down oh
no you can get that okay
oh all right they they don't have to
bring the key for some reason I thought
they have to bring the key we need them
to come here ah okay we red red red red
okay no
time it's okay we got it we got it now
we got it we're good it's difficult to
take care of so many kids I know how to
coordinate them all all right got to go
and press the blue the
blue
okay
the red
good when they're up there press the
yellow
yeah then when they're
there okay got the key got the
key smart all right and then and then
and then you got uh just uh like
anything think I need
uh
okay
okay oh I didn't mean to do
that
it's I mean it works it's totally fun
and then they can come over here Works
nice Mario maros a big adventure B you
in the Box wow
speed it
works if it works I'll take it no that
was how I would have done it
nice guys I've been drinking something
nice that reminds me of Dr Peppa but
it's not Dr Peppa I'm kind of sad just
like cherry flavored yeah it smells like
Dr Pepper though but then I drink it and
it's a bamboozle it's just it's just
water Dr oopsy oh no it's spying up we
need to bring the red I thought you
would
[Music]
have bring blue trash can up the blue
trash can no oh it's
gone
die big monkey be careful now who you're
challenging the toad will take you down
no wa this is hard can I just punch him
with my big mushroom
[Music]
head
okay nice did he lose two lives okay
yeah he did okay okay okay from both
sides he didn't see that one
coming
nice one more
ah I go
[Applause]
[Music]
I you wanted
it's okay it's okay another time next
next World next next
fight kill SN no it's okay she deserved
it to get the
kill we don't have the perfect it's cuz
we got I right okay next mini land
cleared woo so that was world four right
yes we're now in world five spooky house
oh no do you like
house do I like I me like if I go to
haunted house and like Amusement Parts I
don't really feel they're not so bad
there yeah you know when I was a kid in
like Elementary School like my family
would go to like the haunted house and
like my sister would be scared but then
like when someone like pops out I'm just
like
hi you just chill about it yeah I was
just like
hi but we we're in amusement parks we're
the ones out of myth who like are in
sync in terms of what we like because we
you also don't like the rooll right so
we were happy about the
minions I like I still think about the
bun the curry bun oh so good yeah I we I
love curry
buns so good like I know there's like
ones with like red bean in it and
there's like the more Savory ones I
really like the Savory ones better M
yeah yeah yeah me too me too although I
did want to try like sometimes I see
really nice uh new options that I've
never seen before in the clan stores
like a a Nutella bun or something like
that I never had buns in the K though I
don't think just like Amusement part Pon
and Kon and Nikon and K are super yummy
like oh pizon especially oh I love pizon
so good I usually just get like the
frozen ones or something no try them
fresh at the colia store C bomb sex bomb
sex
bomb
y they're
bumped sorry sorry
sorry he what about horror movies don't
you like horror movies I forgot I like
I've watch them okay not me not me not
for me haunted houses are still
manageable cuz they're usually pretty
not so scary kind of
lame thank God okay PR yellow oh oh wor
about interesting oh it like blocked
okay okay oh it can't go up
anywhere your Corners nice okay now we
got to get the uh has you under
control oh you can't yeah okay okay wait
what is this level it's too easy it's
the first level yeah but like fifth
world m
no okay this is
all okay that's why you can make one
mistake uh one
more okay there we go I want to go too
wait for me play my door my
door I'll hold the door for you if you
say door you didn't watch Game of
Thrones though did you I know the memes
or not the memes but like don't you like
these kind of shows at all you're not
interested you lost that
oneup maybe the spike can pop your
bubble go to the Spike oh maybe maybe
here maybe this
[Music]
thing damn
it this is uh looks a bit
tricky do I disappear what about the
yellow gift we got to get it with the
with the blue I never saw a baby baby
FL baby flamp baby
flamp go in a go go in a
go
yeah
okay
and no you if you
go hi I I already prepared where the
breed
gift next level but we're done oh was
there a red
gift see we was the red gift yeah but
then we got two gifts in this level was
it in a previous
level was there a previous level I don't
think so it must have missed it
somewhere it must yeah it must have been
in the pre oh oh oh it's okay okay we'll
clean this and go back clean this and go
back in the first part
yeah so we didn't collect any the first
part I guess so that that's seem too
simple
yeah
oh you already had so many gifts you
guys are you are my
gifts oh I said it to the chat you said
it to me okay okay wait here wait here M
oh all
[Music]
right what's the plan you know uh
survive okay oh ke oh oh oh that's
probably not the best
idea uh wait I I'll press a button so
you can pass um oh
but getting exercise oh wait okay wait
no problem I can do it from here
yeah I jump on this oh okay
woohoo
bye and to complete the circle Ena is
our
give okay is my gift okay KP says that
okay
oh what are
those can I stand on them oh I can I
can't grab them
though oh how am I supposed to can we
make him run through yeah oh but he
doesn't
fall what is the purpose what is the
meaning I know okay he can push me
through maybe oh can he
no oh oh
no that would have made it work with to
but not with Mario cuz Mario's way too
[Music]
big
what what hell what is this you can push
you through the What can you can be push
a a big ah moment aha wow well it's a
new gimmick it's okay that we didn't
immediately know how
to start from the bottom now in
here
you you got to catch up
[Music]
try okay what's up up
here
oh I see mini Mario see I see I see a
life oh and the gift and the hammer
there's a hammer there why is there a
hammer
candles okay okay okay
where's the other gift oh we got all the
gifts nice Sho yay I love that
H
fun perfect now let's go back and fix
our mistakes too bad you can't go back
in to the past and fix your mistakes in
in real life happy
accident happy
accident okay where is it it must be
like on the top pop somewhere huh redo I
can
redo wow oh you should
[Applause]
have we need to get the key first
ma'am oh there's the gift behind the
thing Mig he's hiding
it okay that was pretty easy to miss
actually unless you're like oh okay okay
okay
ah wait
okay is it possible to grab it now I
think so you got it last time like
this what was that sweet
message we can get it I just I took that
okay uh no that's not what really what I
want to do I want to save your
fall when when you jump I want to press
press um the red butt hold on you're
going to get crushed wait how did we do
this
before oh got it okay okay
okay
okay but let me pass let me
pass wait PR PR let it go
[Applause]
down yeah like that okay sorry sorry and
chose the farts again a damn it
come on yeah nice
stay uhoh uhoh it's okay what about the
gift though okay we got to let that drop
and then and then turn the yellow one
yes oh does he need to be baited yeah
okay
nice okay 17 seconds do we do we have
the gift even if we don't open the door
I think it was fine is it pretty sure
but we can try
I thought it didn't count if we didn't
clear the let's see hold
[Music]
up M I think we do have to get the get
the they're forcing us anyway
[Music]
yeah yeah okay key time wonder if I can
get this
like
okay I got it okay okay
okay come
down come down come
down
nice and
now he's down nice gift is ready now we
bring him back up and now we perect cap
we captured a
moment Capt the
key ready to go through I'm waiting for
you no toad Left
Behind thank you I'm a Happy Toad I'm a
Happy
Toad oh this one we did too right so
yeah now we can get another life and
Hope
not uh lose it
again got the gift though worth it got
the
gift well we didn't need to get it again
though damn
it it just came back okay we're done
right okay
[Music]
[Applause]
we
good the hiu are really cute you did
some kind of hiu right yeah it was for
the pr what was it do you remember it
uh uh remember your lines Ena it's in a
script in front of us in on the screen
right because we're streaming with a
script read
it oh read oop counting with her fingers
dad help me remember use your frame
use your multiplied brain
C they don't seem to
no we don't have a
script SCP a
script it's right
there I don't I don't
remember I watched it yesterday but I
forgot it
the high has been
forgotten
uh is it English or yeah it's English
English watch a long time The Long
Winter ends Warm Winds make it's h of
time did you come up with that yeah oh
wa that's pretty now you heard it repeat
it
again it just
started no don't scroll chat is our
script where's that she's trying
to she's retrieving the chat message The
Long Winter ends War WIS make us sing
and dance it's Hol Fest time I like it
you should write the H Fest times and
like just like how you know we entered
and we were we said it's Hall Fest time
and then Hall Fest all over the
place yeah like being part it's it's the
first
time
nice just like the meme can you believe
it's like so soon yeah oh my goodness I
I I was made aware of it today today
today by staff they're like oh it's been
so so much time left this this is how
much time is left oh my goodness yep
yeah yeah it's very
soon it's okay today I today I played um
something special for
Ena my next song oh yeah I talk about my
next song all the time of stream it was
the Eurovision uh uh song people know
that too super good you like it I'm sure
people will love it mhm love it I love
it Ena gave me some good
prizes I'm excited I'm excited it sounds
so good and the cor you yeah
yeah W dance speaking of
Praises I was quite happy yesterday
yesterday I showed Ena some really old
Arts from many many years ago cuz I was
more you guys know right I I kind of
used to draw more in the past but now I
don't because no time and also stream
like drawing while streaming makes me
really nervous and you get used to it
yeah so I didn't drive a long time but I
didn't realize I didn't show you my old
art before yeah you never did but you
know when she saw it she was like oh you
have to draw more I know she should keep
drawing it was so
good got to keep drawing honestly when
you said that it touched my heart and I
did feel like motivated to draw hearing
it from you the artist of all times the
gold so good the potential guys the
potential potential potential
M thank exactly CH you got to make a job
more okay thank you that's so nice the
potential yeah I feel like dra again I'm
kind of motivated yeah she's motivated
I'm motivated she's motivated she
doesn't believe us I don't know I mean I
I know I have like like you know good
like shading and highlighting skills
like in terms of I love drawing hair and
all that have so much fun coloring you
know I always say this to my viewers who
are like oh and I want to start drawing
you know where should I start should I
like start with like studies I'm just
like no start with drawing stuff that
you love to draw like let's say you love
drawing hair draw lots of different
hairs and you know flowy hair short hair
anything just draw what you like first
STW chicken yeah and then when you get
to the point where you're just like you
know what I feel like I can step things
up a little bit like i' I think I've
been drawing stuff I really love I want
to draw the stuff I love better that's
one thing that always scares me is
backgrounds don't worry about
backgrounds like don't worry about
finishing art pieces at first just draw
until you feel like you know just draw
what you like and then you can be like I
kind of want to you know challenge
myself sometimes and you know maybe I'll
draw or practice backgrounds and
stuff
yeah background sounds optional I wish
they were I always felt like like I see
so many other artists like uploading art
without backgrounds and I I like it I
like what I see and honestly for me as a
YouTuber when I look for material for
thumbnails I'm grateful when there's no
background cuz then I can cut it out and
put it on top of the like whatever like
the image from the game or so it's
actually really useful um so yeah maybe
I don't have to feel bad about not
drawing back no it's it's not a
requirement it's not like you're you
know you have a client they're just like
we need you to draw a character with the
background everything it's like no
you're just drawing for your own
enjoyment you don't have an acquirement
so just draw what you like you know with
no background you can just put random
you know solid color or like pattern or
something it's fine you don't really
have to like it's not a requirement
maybe may do some drawing member streams
yeah don't like push yourself without
being comfortable with what you're
drawing first is what I think cuz I
think you just get overwhelmed when you
think you just have to finish these like
so
polished you know illustrations and
stuff like one the quotes I've heard and
kept it close to me close to my heart
it's like an artist only ever releases
like less than 1if of everything they
draw in their lifetime you know the
public cuz we always doodle and like
practice and stuff behind the scenes and
people think you know we always end up
finishing all the art pieces that we
draw I feel like that did that statement
did didn't apply to me but I feel like
maybe it should maybe I should do it
that way like not like you have to
release everything you draw to the
public just you know draw more sketches
and you know keep them have a million
working progresses
exactly and sometimes what what's good
about having those work in progresses is
because sometimes you're just like stuck
on ideas and stuff and sometimes you
just revisit those ideas you had before
and you're just like oh yeah I remember
I want try this and that and you could
add on to those things
so yeah
interesting Taco wisdom in of the floor
or in of the mountain in of the spooky
house what is your wisom
oh know of the spooky house scares me oh
I want in know of the mountain back
please okay in off the
mountain okay
yeah motivational motivated yeah maybe
why I make more art yeah but not
necessarily on stream because make me
nervous and make me
slower makes me slower I slower I think
when I'm drawing on
stre sometimes I rush things but at the
same time I just
think sometimes I don't want to finish
stuff on stream cuz I like taking my
time with drawing
so
know next up all right let's
go you're doing great oh yeah I did
recently finish a Cobo drawing that I
started like a year ago like I started
when she debuted and then recently when
she had her frd showcase I think that's
when I suddenly decided oh okay I'll
finish it now and it was like looking at
it like so much that time later I was
like oh I see so many things I want to
fix actually I was feeling
pretty pretty frustrated about how how
shitty it looked to me like a year later
oh I think I pressed the wrong thing
that's okay oh we're just in the menu
we're fine okay okay okay okay okay okay
sorry that was a bad start we were we
were still talking we're still stage it
seems like we have to keep the talking
to the the the uh waiting screen
thingies you go Ena you go do your thing
there
oh you missed to Train F these jumps
they're totally possible I think they're
possible aren't they maybe they're not
maybe
that's oh oh
byea I'm going to get that King I'll get
it nice where's the door door upstairs
where is the door where's the yellow oh
you have to get the yellow button now
hold on let me get the blue I got oh
it's there's
more oh you have the gift okay
yeah got get the
key he jump jump jump I looked at the
test I was just
chilling oh where should I go uh
do I activate the hold on hold I need to
get up there first I think
yeah yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
nice um I need to press the blue first
huh oh there's another gift there
though let me get the gift
first can't
see no no come back go no
sorry I was like trying to figure out
how to back up the king the king it's
[Music]
upstairs the maybe
oh we're running out of time too oh no
it's okay we'll know what to
do I'm going to miss
you oh don't know oh I can't catch you
on the platform H okay come here
Mario 20 seconds nah it's not going to
it's not going to
happen oh no go that it's
okay it's not no 12 seconds no way no
way okay okay okay restart restart
absolutely Flawless
one
yeah anything we do is
flawless
let's see what are you going
for oh okay I'll I'll get the I'll get
the
button and the
gift
[Music]
byebye
oh I know okay okay I can get the golden
key I think you got to get the golden
key cuz I can't oh yeah
right old isn't it
y
what I
know wait wait
uh okay you go to the yellow button
hopefully it won't be crushed yeah
oh nice
okay now we got to get higher can we get
much higher what do you think yes I
think
so okay okay okay
okay okay I can get a yeah yeah that
will be helpful okay okay I stay I stay
I stay and I jump on blue and I jump on
this and then I'll come up to yellow
button
perhaps and get one of the platforms ah
can I press yellow right now to get the
present uh ah can you jump on the
platform yeah and then on the yellow yes
to get the gift yeah you need to get to
the blue though cuz we need to get
the
yeah she did it she saved us I'm doing
it
MH H H okay we got to press the
[Music]
blue I was going to jump on the platform
from there sorry do
do I go to yellow PO okay I open this
[Music]
first no PR okay go go go it's too high
I'm too
[Music]
small from here
no no no oh this level is difficult oh
it's okay it's okay we got it now so
much to do and so little time oh
oh jump off okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
M oh oh it's okay it's okay you can go
to the yellow okay I wait
here nice oh okay okay
yeah what oh no no my silver
key hi okay we
press okay both get out it bgm yeah bgm
is
beautiful okay okay
okay I may stay here until you press
does it work
no wait I'll revive you up here nice
I'll revive you yeah okay shortcut oh
but you have to get the key again
huh silver one
yeah a what we going to do I'm going to
chill here for a
while if you need the blue button let me
know
oh yeah I I have to go to the yellow one
I can get the gift okay and once you're
there I'll make the platform so you can
open the door later all right all right
after after you cross the yellow stairs
okay no sudden button pushing from waa
don't
[Music]
worry oh we got to get the gift uh yeah
but no already open open the silver one
yeah okay yeah and then I'll maybe I'll
press the yellow button for you so you
can reach
the or can
you
yes Mario is an independent
Italian y y
y
no okay it's okay it's okay W
level just extending my time with Ena
honestly long cat long
scam what do you want to do what you
want to get the okay
dangerous
present
okay how did that Miss sorry for not
giving you a
hand help me and now I need to press
the do we want the blue yes so we can
get timing nice timing nice okay
okay waiting for
you don't let Donkey Kong win no I don't
although I think Donkey Kong fans are
there any Donkey Kong fans they surely
would be happy if Donkey Kong Won for
once for once maybe he would get a game
a new game cuz I I hear Donkey Kong fans
are waiting you Donkey Kong games it's
been a long time really yeah it's been a
long time since you got like a proper
Donkey Kong game a new one
oo I got the gift
nice okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay I'm safe
I'm safe I can open the door
anytime
yes
ch okay easy easy first try first try
wow that was emotional that felt so
dramatic emotional damage that was life
changing oh there's a oh ghost shy guys
are they shy shy
shy M they're ghosts I feel like you
would fall through how get across right
wait they change
oh that reminds me of Super Mario
Sunshine cuz the ghosts turn into blocks
in Super Mario sunsh shine is so cute
okay we got to the timing get out of he
up the
essence maybe where do we want them here
no here where do we want
them oh that's good nice oh almost as if
you calculated it
calculated nice W free
gifts okay we just got it clear now
right follow me follow me
maybe we can get the one up as
well I think so maybe yeah it's too far
you sure is this oh
doable
yeah totally
yeah got go
we made it wait Did we do this one first
try and the previous one like five
tries don't worry about it statistics
don't match up it's
confusing ah Lo skids fre the mini Mario
yes all of them oh it's our chance oh we
currently have 10 lives cuz we came over
does it really matter to get these if we
G over and that's what I've been
thinking yeah like game over doesn't
really hurt that much here we go here we
go
par why does it go up there
too I go down here I forgot what's up
there now we just need to
ke there it
is
nice easy easy hi high five kfp high
five high
five 18 lives we got eight lives from
that oo cuz we have 10 right so many
lives to waste let's go let's
go that's like two cats says life's
worth
yes at the math oh there's a balloon
goes like kind of
looks fin get he won't come I just look
at him
forever and you can go I'm just the
looker that's my job I'm the Observer
it's so
cute I still don't understand why
they're called Teresa in Japanese really
yeah
Teresa maybe it was their
name before they turn into ghost oh oh
that's sad
somehow oh no it's called T it
[Music]
now we look at you from both sides how
embarrassing is that for to you okay I I
I'll get the button does that embarrass
you huh how's that feel you feel very
shy now don't
you I just look at her or him okay
patience patience yes yes solo run
Ina go go go go okay we're good we got
it oh they're so cute they're so
cute okay oh there's a pusher there
again I
see are you staring I'll stare okay what
can we
do gu got to go is there something oh oh
okay okay one
and I press the
button so that didn't help okay okay
works you jump on that okay get the gift
okay okay and then you can you can get
over there and then we already have the
GI okay that's it that's it hi I feel
like I totally walk
past I feel the same way but it's a
matter of like 2 cm 2 in 2 c 2 cm is
smaller is it I really don't at
all thank you
[Music]
perfect wo that was the fastest clear
ever are you timing
us for
one I hope not I'll time you guys then
too for how fast you can fry a chicken
thigh oh chicken D and if it's too slow
then you're fired oh but that would that
would make you happy wouldn't it right
you want you want to I need to
oh okay no firing just going into the
usual room
[Music]
guys don't get smashed again Ina I think
I need you to press the
uh
har get someone to okay it's it's just a
tread
okay
okay but the okay okay I need to press
the wait I think I can send it over here
here take take it take it
oh okay no oh oh wait I wait oh
no wait not go again I have to go again
too
what wait this one was also
easy Lu show oh I just can't walk okay
nice okay okay I'll take those now even
the keys are timed everything's
timed life is so
stressful oh maybe we got to like trap
it oh oh oh oh the yellow one where do
we want the yellow
one
ah no okay oh I see what you're doing
Ena
oh and then and then and then
oh okay okay we got to we got to send
the wait wait hold on don't go up don't
go come down the L okay okay I don't
want you to die
okay uh you might not want to do
that I mean you can if oh no no you can
stay that okay yeah oh I forgot oh he'll
come back around what comes around comes
back what what comes around what goes
around what goes around comes back
around what comes around also comes back
around
oh the
Puppeteer now I got ping the
strings waiting for you I could also
push buttons for you if you need or you
need to yeah okay but then how oh oh you
have to be on the on the on the the the
the chain
okay you can go back up but even if we
turn the blue one into a block you
you'll be on the thing right so you
won't get hit by the okay I'll see oh
wait
maybe oh there's more blocks over there
so I can hit it from there okay I just
have to go up yeah as long as the yellow
one is a block come up here
yeah yes yes yes yeah you know it cool
oh
okay it
worked okay go go go okay it
worked the wind pixel you can stand on
nice nice okay we're kicking this game's
ass does it have an
ass Donkey Kong surely has an ass we're
kicking his ass a butt lift just like
that
do
mhm maybe that's what he needs for a new
game maybe they will only give him a new
game with a nicer bigger butt but Donkey
Kong okay we'll support you in your
endeavors you don't need to have a
bigger butt you're beautiful the way you
are you get that game no matter what
this game is just the first step to a
new
game okay I have to get on yours
first but like it's
so oh I I didn't even dare to make that
jump you're so
far how do you make the okay but this is
also so far
oh we can all come up
here okay oh I even got the key on the
way okay huh cuz I can get the gift by
jumping down and then landing on the
thing so this again
[Music]
oh no oh no oh okay I kind of oh had to
come so I was going to die I
think what's your plan you know up the
mountain go back up okay okay
yeah oh what did I put down oh no it's
okay you can prob me back up here okay
come
here how do we get the we need to a
button so that this
one opens up I need to press red but
then like if you're okay maybe if you
stand here
yeah oh no oh no oh no no yeah all the
buttons are
downstairs wait hold on let me see how
it
looks I can't get
down yeah that way oh maybe this the
only
way and then yeah like the blue button
wait
where yeah can you open that and you
come down here using the it's too late
no no we got to still figure out what to
do it's okay we got to figure it
out don't cry
Mario don't cry you make me cry too oh
that was
fast double jumps
skills wait for you maybe should I stay
down here so I can push the blue button
for
you
I
hey now the key it's okay I'll get I'll
get the red GE
okay and the key and the key but like it
can you press the button blue the blue
one quickly quickly
quickly don't
die
I I jump too far if we do it fast then I
can fall down fast and I'll be in your
vision and won't die up there should we
uh can we even do it
now we up getting
away ah close I see what you're trying
to
do it's what
no here
I'll the blue if we activate it now it
will hinder us from going up
I
[Music]
nice
okay you want to get the gift or should
I
uh I'll get it okay and then I'll press
go to the red red thing quickly
really
quickly
oh uh now uh yep now we can get the one
up
okay hello go
for get the one yeah go go
for yeah
yeah I need to get there
somehow
a look key oh yeah I can get there now
okay okay we're good we're good and you
can go up the go oh no hardy hardy wait
come down C down no I'm stuck oh no okay
we still the key okay oh thank goodness
come come come come confusion
worked I'm good very
[Music]
complicated cheese Str that was no
cheese okay we might have to uh hurry a
bit cuz mama needs to to bring food
oh uh you you mean we have to end it no
not right now but we should we should
get as much as we can done she's she's
ready for coming over for din oh okay
Mama yeah she she said she wanted to
make dinner for wa
so uh oh oh I think I know okay okay
okay so okay okay I
know
MH bring him down get
ped
oh no we we need okay you go you go you
go
right
what what that's a
possibility oh okay okay okay okay we're
good and you have to I think maybe stand
on top of it afterwards to get to
that maybe I don't
think
okay does this do something that we
needed to do
uh oh wait I can press the red so I can
get oh the yellow gift right I'll try
get
it and now I think I will
die guess I'll die okay it's okay I
guess I'll die it's
fine guess I'll die wait then I to get
you back up there again maybe I could
have done a handstand I wonder if that
would have been enough
momentum it's okay we're learning the
stage it's a pink
one
okay okay okay I just got to time the
red very
well
uh okay it's doable
right I think so anything is doable for
to wa toad CH wait you got to get the
boot oh [\h__\h] where is see it right jump
nice and then you can
go does that mean I have to go up oh
yeah I'll need you to get a little bit
higher so that you don't die down there
unless you can die and I can top okay
guess I'll die guess I'll wait the focus
is on you though I don't want that okay
go go go
go what a strategy that is kind of um I
guess oh oh oh yeah that's fine that's
kind of a cheese Strat indeed we got all
the gifts so all there's left to do is
get the mini
Mario just can't too oh good it worked
out you're not allowed on The High
Ground I've Got The High Ground She's
Got The High
Ground using game
mechan not cheating no no it's it's in
the game it's not cheating MH
mm oh oh that was the end of the world
okay oh let's go surely this one will'll
get and we'll try cuz we are
geniuses
po somehow they always spell the same
thing I by now I know how to spell toy
no need to spell it out again for
[Music]
me they press the blue
okay oh wait but
I oh oh oh and then we press the red so
it's all the way up
there oh yeah get him Stu yeah yeah
brain now they can climb a baby steps
baby
steps
okay oh oh there's a key there oh
perfect
Wonder should I press yellow again so it
comes down and yeah yeah yeah
and maybe we're going to press red again
I got to bait it first
yeah nice okay okay okay and then I can
go
here there nice okay okay the Toy Box is
open and then I press yellow oh Get Up
Get It
Mario no no we lost one did we ever lose
one like like this before I think the
first I think so but it's okay it's just
a
toy it's not
real doesn't have a heart I
think maybe it has a soul I'm heart not
a
heart the
oh can
they they can't jump on the bouncy thing
right they can they can then bring them
up and then let them fall down down on
so that they can go to the all maybe it
does that work but they might wait they
might get bonked by this thing again so
let me press the red button okay so that
we we can stop it I'm doing
that oh okay okay okay ah 5 Seconds no
oh I need to bring them down here oh
no yeah but the red and then maybe the
yellow I don't know okay
beginning we know how to do the
beginning
okay blue
[Music]
H oh the key is on the right side oh it
FES all the way
around um do you want oh yeah I got to
press the r
okay okay
okay first try yeah so much about first
try all right can you can you can you
press the red when it goes up
yes oh the red oh oh never mind there
you go and then not red
righted okay perfect I
think and then you can press the yellow
okay oh no the key I wanted to jump from
lower see the key is easily
retrievable
fight is that what you
wanted
[Music]
bouncy Mario I guess I could grab the
key
oh drop and then to the right side and
then to the left
side I didn't see oh the platform was
gone
oh yep yep yep yep and then perhaps we
press the blue no we got to bring him up
again to the middle level I would think
like bounce him up that's just my one
brain cell
idea and then oh God oh God it's not
enough time again I would say like you
bring him back down here and then when
they're all all down here no when
they're all down here yeah I go on the
red as this thing is going up and then
you press
the and then as soon
as we we'll figure it out we just got to
be a little bit faster a little bit
running wrong
job bring me back I can't I can't I
can't uh raise oh I can't raise all your
children you're you're their
father
yeah they don't even look like
me I think the genetics has a a playing
this uh do you want a button uh you want
blue button oh no I go here and then you
press yellow yellow yellow yellow yellow
okay here go yellow yellow yellow
okay I wonder if I can just walk over
like this and then
oh that was not what I wanted to
do
out no they don't want to go all the way
and open
it open it maybe I do
this
get
uhhuh can you baain them any further
or like oh maybe I can stop it when it
goes
down Hy Hy Hy Hy oh
yeah bab going run the time again yeah
yeah yeah now you got to bring him up
can you
press yellow when it's like yeah
here okay okay
oh he has been
imprisoned oh the guys come on just just
oh no
you don't wa this is not enough time
okay okay once again once again I think
I think we know what to do now all right
go go go and I won't die to the spicy
SP we need the perfect
coordination I'm just chilling to get
the key this one is St no Mario
stop well one less Mario to lead to the
goal maybe that makes it
easier yellow thank
you one less child to pay for for food
and for bed and for
electricity and for
diapers and
[Music]
booty got it you got
it what oh what are you doing here where
how to get there oh we got a lot of time
now at least um well that's a problem
should I raise this one on my own I can
take one not all of them I you it won't
listen to you right now just uh I can
try to bring oh
sorry we lost it's okay for the for the
greater
purpose yeah
we don't need that many lives
anyway I we going to carry them over to
that side we have to go from the other
[Music]
side oh we have to go from the other
side we have
to I
let's two lives left it's okay we're
done anyways wait we can't go from this
side either no
how do we get them over there
[Music]
um
okay who what is this what is this
riddle it's playing us like a
fiddle um let's think once cuz I don't
think they can climb this thing no
probably not no they can't m
how would they get if you like here or
up there even like I can't I don't
think
interesting we missing
something is there anything you can
carry around can we can we carry these
is there something there no
[Music]
M maybe there's
something oh okay one
task no was there something down here no
oh go there little boys come over
here they can jump over when Red Blocks
are
up okay let's just try it like when
they're on the blue then we change it to
red and see what happens or so I guess I
don't
know should we just
restart ret try okay all right more time
it's so
confusing okay go go
go like this level should also be doable
alone
so I don't know if you get more time
than alone but it's kind of
crazy this is kind of crazy
uh
uh wait that's that how was supposed to
go
[Music]
down can you carry them no
no all
right oh oh where do you where do you
want it
okay there we
[Music]
go oh that's perfect
now okay okay we can get the
yellow
careful it's okay it's okay oh
all right let's go let's
go this beginning we got that
one, okay
okay sorry guys sorry sorry sorry I felt
I felt very connected to that one
specifically cuz that one I thought it
was you that was Timmy Timmy no and he
did not Des to live such a short life
and go down like this that was not
planned for his
legacy Timmy deserves
better okay you got to save
Timmy eyes on the
road oh I should we should let it uh
should I push something over there no
it's okay it's okay we just got to
run as soon as it
start go go go go go I Believe In You t
t okay wait I think I can start off by
getting the
Y
wait oh do you want do want okay okay
okay then oh you can get key
okay
uh think okay hold on hold on
okay that's okay oh wait but there yeah
yeah
yeah I did not take
this Timmy and Jenny and Finny and okay
let's go
Minnie they all R yeah I don't know
Mario did not have really good ideas for
the names
okay what went
wrong why do we go wrong happened to
me I can't we okay there we
go children run oh oh good job
kids
okay oh that was not damn he a jumper
okay that worked that worked you want to
bring them up here and then drop them on
the middle platform right think okay I
need don't don't listen to me
necessarily oh no no no we need we need
the yeah get
yeah okay press
hi this ends now no more funny games yep
yep okay yeah yeah that's that's good
that's that's and then people say and
there has to be it has to be like it
otherwise like how is it going to work
people say that they can jump on the red
one from there let's
see is that
true like yeah let's see no they can't y
children how do you bring them ah maybe
they mean they can jump from here all
the way to here they don't really jump
though they're not that far right that's
crazy can you press the yellow for the
yellow you think we I thought we going
to retry okay you never know you know
okay yeah that's enough that's enough
children okay
[Music]
okay what children oh my that was too
early I guess do we want to bring him
down
oh y y can't press the
[Music]
r okay R try R try we know we know our
goal now is to make him do a long jump
if that is possible possible we will see
at the end it's it's the only option
yeah all right all right I got this we
got
this mini Mario's
throwing you want to get over here you
can yeah okay now okay Mario's guys
please let me it's okay I'll I'll press
oh should I press
now
no it's okay it's okay it's okay okay
keep going keep going sacrif be made
especially when you're Invincible keep
on
going no I don't want you guys coming up
[Music]
here I need them to come down okay won't
come down the ladder I guess you're
going to
them
yeah okay that okay okay okay
okay yeah so this n we got the we have
50 seconds
left we got to get it to go all the way
down blue blue yeah okay okay okay you
go get the key what no I miss
this
is what
what happened it was going so well maybe
mama need can try this level for us she
can be
[Music]
better W all right all right all right
we got
this just grab the key the other yeah
I'll get it
press okay
okay
insanity
and okay
[Music]
okay wait I need to get them on
the okay never go going to judge don't
the waya again okay press
[Music]
the no when the when when this thing
goes
down you might not want to be jumping on
my head okay just baiting just
baiting
[Music]
oh one more but okay wait first uh let's
make
it okay red no yellow yellow it has to
go all the way down oh
and making stu a it damn it no no can't
down like this okay there we
go height height and now we bring them
all the way back to the top through the
jumpy
thing and AC jumping oh I guess they'll
follow
okay and then please
please do this y they do the job we
should never have doubted them let's
go
[Music]
M how many did we lose in the last one
we got them all in
this that's something nice that's
something good
about this how it went down we got them
all all children save no children lost
unless we lose them here
not
guarantee it's okay they're meant oh oh
one's down
already so what is see what oh I guess
we have to jump on
them but how do we jump on the how do we
make him feel
pain oh no wait why are they overlapping
like that pain we just punch him you got
to lift them up and then throw it to the
the color that's like you
know we can lift this like when when
we're on it remember okay I don't know
we could live them I got one
nice woohoo my time has
come what press Red Donkey Kong press
red he did it he listened to me
[Music]
no don't come too close
come he's getting
red go Mario
go maybe he'll nice one more one more on
it
Jimmy
Justice Pap Jimmy for you all of this
for
you big how many oh my God what so many
left this one was
hard I didn't realize they won't turn
back if you're holding them
so it's okay we tried we didn't but it
was cost what
goost all
right did you pet your cat today Ina did
not pet me today but I gave her a
massage today oh she did that was very
nice so I petted her in a way oh the
en she was
saying e the whole time but I like the
pain is good right it's good pain good
pain yeah I I could have I would have if
it was me for myself I would have gone
like 10 times that
strength
m
m please I've become a masochist okay oh
slippery summit we're in the winter
world now winter M what's your favorite
season
Autumn cuz like after a hot summer I'm
just so relieved when oh can we slide
like but it finally cools down after hot
Su you see
that
oh here key you take
this and no
oh
slide a that's fun that's so
fun I we're faster fast we can already
clear it yay is there no present here oh
we got we already got it okay oh my key
no
no you guys SL through oh gra the okay
go what are you
doing
yes I'll wait on the other side to pick
it up next time no no you just have to
press the red button so it doesn't
fall oh
true oh you have to go from up here huh
yeah okay
press okay you you go I I okay that's
fine and when you're ready I'll you have
to throw the
key so
slow it's coming to
you okay right yes
yes I like it's cute I like the slippery
H H nice just wait till there's enemies
on the track and you just like oh yes
yes that change
anything oh look at
that look at what I
me but they will not stop us they cannot
hinder
us why it seems they stopped you why why
oh I can like ice
skate can you ice look I'm doing
Twirls wait let me jump jump okay easy
can you skate wait there's an extra life
here can you ice skate can you yeah like
IRL yeah you capable of ice skating
yeah nice what about you of course ice
skating I can ice skate better than I
can ski same what I do with this can I
do something with this
one oh now they're moving
yes
fished go back up again
you
oh no you can go up to mini Mario
where's blue oh can we bring this
[Music]
yes nice okay Tak ice skating
day I take when people visit me over my
place in Austria I I take everyone ice
ska I took waya ice SK I took Nissa ice
skating I took
my BFF ice
skating out skating I think that's it
actually I haven't skated in many many
many years
though it it's fun you get back into it
like after minutes as long as I think
you know know the balancing get used to
it no take Kelly did I take Kelly here
we
go no I don't think I took
KY I
should C's always down for everything
anything
okay can you bring one of them I'm
trying why do you want them oh I can't
okay cuz the the blue lad oh actually we
can just jump on our heads just jump on
my head when in doubt nice jump on each
other okay where's the
so uh up there oh okay get the silver
key first oh there's the bled gift uhhuh
oh
okay toad is trying to be a pretty ice
skating
[Music]
princess okay how to go I have to go way
down oh
maybe and then you can bring
the oh no next
time all right you trust me with that
mission again oh yes of course thank you
this time I'll do better I redeem
myself uh wait I wanted the red right
did I want the
red did I want the red is is the red
necessary uh no oh and the gift is
already taken okay okay and you I I
could shoot the the yeah you you could I
shut it down before I get the silver key
but no this kind of scares me let
me just just fall down
okay I'm too
slow I'm
sorry I know you kind of gave up hope on
me there I I
believe it's it's on it's on the
edge Fury probably one could get it wait
are you di
again it's not enough time oh no
yeah oops I pressed the wrong
button it's
okay
[Music]
Cal see you later
Mario okay I I um I think I'll focus on
the other key
[Music]
first and the gift is necessary again h
nice
smoth and
P and
oh not this again wait I'll jump on him
I'll jump on him and yep then you want
this
right d
it come on oh hold on I can I can a
there it is there it is there it is
ready for the
taking m I can prob it them over
[Music]
too all right all right okay golden key
come
over you want to be part of this right
part of the success okay we just got to
go back and get the key again huh that's
all that's we press the red
button yeah just make your way
War it War it oh oh
[\h__\h]
uh I don't know if I can get there in
[Music]
time as Ena would
say this is not
enough you can probably move thing if
you
want I I can't believe you're like after
all these fames you're still making me
get the key like what kind of trust how
you placing it onto
me are you still letting me do this Ina
it's a mistake it's the biggest mistake
of your life okay I'll try I'll try
[Music]
it
so I I I'll just be um chilling this
time you've seen um the basics from me
and how things are supposed to be done
up until a certain point oh I think I
think this is how you're supposed to do
it oh I guess you could get the
trampoline now already from
here
[Music]
yeah oh I need to press the
red
okay
right okay hey hey I mean yeah I deserve
it but wait I should you you your turn
you can go you can
go but that I'll be your oh she cut me
off oh I should have just
[Music]
okay oh no no it's okay bring me back
over
[Music]
there I got
than you can probably wait over there to
get the
key or both of us can
[Music]
go that is my my biggest
enemy oh oh thank you
I'll carry the
key you want to get the
gift I'm trying
okay nice okay I'll
press
[Music]
nice
okay oh hi
Mario
oh no get the key get the silver
key don't
worry easily retrieved easily easy easy
easy easy easy easy
easy go go go go
go it's too
[Music]
late press the
R I think
um I think we should take a break
probably not going to not going to
collap for a long time after this
why Ena probably lost all her brain
cells due to me I think we're just tired
from excessive brain cell use this isn't
even so difficult I don't know what's
wrong with us it's not so difficult just
clumsy clumsy clumsy like
[Music]
FY tripping oh stumbling oh tripping oh
tumbling of course I was joking there's
always T
[Music]
collapse there will
be wow oh sorry that that was an
accident that was such an
accident I'll throw this
away golden key will be your
job oh thank
you oh you need to press the red before
you oh I guess you can climb yeah okay
hey we got one door open I don't think
we ever did that before
wow
amazing you you go go get the get the
golden one my Golden
Child tell me if you need
[Music]
something
okay M mhm mhm okay press blue uh blue
blue blue blue blue blue oh oh wait wait
no no I guess I guess I don't really
need it never mind grab the key when I
throw it down
[Music]
okay
it's okay I'll just grab it
this
this we're
good I think everything after this will
be easier
right this was just a difficult face but
this game generally does have like
difficulty spikes so
like it it's it doesn't stay on the same
difficulty all the time so it's okay
it's okay it's supposed to be more
challenging that was fun
interesting wait I can't reach that oh I
did
okay yeah we want a dare huh
oh
yeah the pain feels good wait we need we
need both gifts how are we going to get
the blue ah with a
trampoline Okay we can get the
[Music]
yellow no it's okay can you stop sliding
BL
please no no you're not supposed to go
there maybe it's language W that it's
okay on my channel it's
okay it's normal I don't know if it the
can of slide okay
yep maybe I'll just jump on
you that's enough we don't need this
stupid
trampoline together we strong oh I
missed
okay
what you the way Mario just threw that
thing is exactly how I threw balls in
physical education class with like when
we played ball games when we were
balling oh that's okay okay it's okay
I'm still here that's exactly how I thre
balls any kind of
ball was not in fact
balling
okay did yeah finally did
it brain is shutting down too much work
that was just the second one from the
slippery one just the second
[Music]
one all right
interesting we can do this I thought we
finish this today but if your mommy
comes for for the food then maybe we
can't finish it today I we can see how
time is
tomorrow oh wait so one will like appear
here
too oh
not oh I
see I understand oh maybe
oh you fall down with the spike to get
the one
up okay go all the way around
okay okay I got the gift
okay I got this i got this but
uh I'll come up higher so you can go up
higher without me dying good yeah oh
there's other gift I can try getting
that
oh oh
no I'm going to get this
over yay and I will get the
gift although okay is that no that gift
is not certain death okay good okay okay
W redeeming herself once
again o o oh why did I come along
actually just my mental support wait how
are you supposed to get across just
using ah yeah you have to jump over the
spikes where's the door at the bottom I
think was wasn't it at the bottom like
somewhere there wait
oh don't go to the right side go left
side
yes easy peasy lety we did it we did it
not a m see see this not bad not bad
first level for
example we did it even first try oh
what's are these cute they're
cute it was science
science
okay
you're so skilled en know how how do we
get rid of the blue for the
blue maybe there's a um maybe the turn
into blocks in some way no probably
not got um squeeze through that's what I
was trying to do but I was a
little you get a second chance
oh
the okay we go for
the didn't finish the name we will know
what we're talking about if you don't
finish
it that's what we're going for my
stomach is growling I'm so
hungry your stomach is also
saying there it is there it
is stop okay now we just got to
finish it's not Invincible don't don't
do it don't do
it I love it
s how long oh there it is
gone you can't jump with that thing as
far as I remember right
yeah oh they me oh
easy
uhoh traffic J okay it worked yay that
could have gone wrong that could have
gone so
wrong
perfect I agree I agree with that
perfect egg we are perfect perfect egg
perfect perfect egg oh wait
oh life more life more one UPS two ups
three UPS let's get eight UPS or seven
let's get seven
UPS not be confused that I I don't know
what it tastes like what does seven up
taste like
[Music]
spr one
more no come back here you
little I got it yep it okay I got the
life please proceed to the Finish Line
Ena
Sho a sweet or Sprite M isn't Sprite
already plenty sweet yeah
exactly I don't I don't I think I prefer
like different type of like
citrusy drink different type as in you
don't like the I don't like the yeah not
as much probably what kind of different
type is there they're like too sweet and
it's like not enough
carbon I'm like a Sprite every once in a
while how are you supposed
to I wonder if the key can be
transferred hi I'm
here no no no no wait there wait wait
there here here no no no no like I'll
throw the key and I'm just wondering if
it goes into the
red
ah oh maybe I can pick it up oh yeah and
then you can go in the red
okay
okay supposed to get the uh and now I
need to leave all the other stuff to
you otherwise if I leave it here un the
companied it's going to disappear how do
you get the gift what that was like two
pixels it's okay I got it I got it I got
I know what to
do beautiful beautiful form in a 10 out
of
there's a one up over
[Music]
there she's going for the one up she's
going for it not that we need
it oh he not now
but the
[Music]
one oh no if I revive you here we're
you're stuck oh you revive on your own
eventually oh you just pop your own
bubble how do you get it maybe you have
to do like
the I don't get what the point of this
is y it's over it's over
over I feel like we can just get the
gift while
[Music]
dying while dying I mean I guess there's
surely a way to not die but I'll try
maybe you can do like can is it possible
to do like a diagonal
jump got the key no prise was the gift
okay he looks so happy in the bubble why
do he even pop his bubble he looks so
happy again please couldn't grab it
yet okay now there's no need to worry
about the gift so I just going to get
the silver key you can do it now I
believe yeah yeah look at her beautiful
as always
graceful I got the key like your how are
we supposed to not die like go the red
box there there must be some way oh
maybe
ah oh the enemy yeah you throw in there
and you step on him always got to think
if there's something you can
use to throw around oh
oh oh nice oh I almost died what oh how
did you get oh no let me in let me in
let me
in this time if you press the yellow one
I'm sure something nice will
happen oo oh yellow gift yellow gift J
oh he hands down your
side oh no I want to
go did you just say re I said
that's can you
can oh for you for you for
[Music]
me clap clap with the Pro Controller
beautiful beautiful
b e a beautiful b e a b e i
beautiful next
please man we're taking our sweet time
with this yeah I have to uh wrap it up
after the Donkey Kong okay okay I mean
if we have time tomorrow we can maybe
play but tomorrow tomorrow here we
go
wait
[Music]
oh where's the red button is on the
right if you if there's a is where's the
blue button here go stand on the red and
then drop onto the silver key and I I I
press
these yes land safely where
theop I shall now if you get jump on
that and then you save and you can get
the red
gift
good yes yes and now what's activated is
this still enclosed okay then we need a
blue button activation from your side
please on the red side you this be
awaiting your action and your
command uh uh uh uh
it was I think on the it was over there
oh
okay see
said
[Music]
he oh no you can already press
it oh never
[Music]
mind okay chill we're very chill yeah
the music is very relaxing
too okay maybe wait you're you can press
it
now what is this jump press it so I can
reach it cuz the red is kind of
blocking thank so
far the camera it's okay I'll do it
trust
jck now you got to press red
again h h h h no chill
chill yay
y time oh wasn't so bad wasn't so bad I
feel our brain cells recovered from the
PTSD and the
trauma I don't
think I'm okay we got to put this red
what we surely need this boy for the
gift yeah this is going to be hard ow a
slippery slope is what it is
noina you are as beautiful as the day I
lost
you it's okay he's also having troubles
walking here oh
[Music]
nice
but can you send one of those down maybe
can I do you think I can make this jump
without no never mind actually should be
possible
okay oh nice No you little
[\h__\h] all right nice get back here he's
stuck there forever for the rest of his
life oh
nice iwait your assistance here where's
the yellow one I wonder probably up
here aha mhm that one's
easy
m m
M okay you you go get the gift and then
we
can just trying to do skillful
platforming
okay that was like right as I got the
kid Mario stubbed his toe and died so
sad
why you died so sad Alexa play St your
to is really like death
really one more one more and and toy
collection remember the hand handstand
headstand handstand hand handstand can
you do a handstand not right now can you
do a
handstand I can't do either where does
this take
us
M oh okay wait
[Music]
what okay is the trampoline going to be
necessary somewhere yeah I'm guessing so
ah maybe I throw it for the blue box
when it appears or like I go with it
what that's going to be so hard maybe
you send the trampoline to the other
side yeah that could possibly be yeah
now it's it is here and then you can
take the the one into in like take it
into the
box or or you canate
this this is good I take gray key silver
key
and maybe you can send the key oh you go
okay okay I open the door and I think
now I can go back to the and you can
probably send the key over to me
if you pick it up there and then send
it
yeah
yeah wait wait wait we're missing a gift
though right it's up there up there
that's what I said
um okay okay I'll press this right mm oh
no no bring the bring the trampoline and
then bring it over this
way and then you can get
the genius easy hey I really think you
know we got
smarter I'm a
baby
[Music]
baby do you know it no oh it's
loer oh there's
spikes I don't like the
spiky where the hell are
you okay I'm with you I'm with you
okay got the yellow gift where's the
blue gift oh we need the blue
button no ah I pressed
it
[Music]
okay wait but how do I get there oh you
you got to go
fromwhere here I guess
[Music]
so get off there get off
okay where's the other blue box to jump
over that is it down
below please revive the
[Music]
WWA oh oh wonder if it's down below yeah
it's probably like somewhere oh it's
over there okay okay you just got to go
back okay you you you stay you stay
okay
we did
it we did
it beautiful I think we we like we found
our flow our workflow
yeah good team good team thank you guys
thank you didn't die oh no die no death
on the six one six out six or it's any
Mario cap time to bring the children
home capture the moment no capture the
Mario capture the more
moment
toy don't toy with me okay
kfp let's observe we probably need a few
Tri for this
one there goes
one should we restart oh no we'll
probably die anyway from the time let's
just look at
everything
[Music]
yeah they oh yeah they can't they can do
the jump they can do this jump though I
think I know but they can't climb the
the ladder
yeah can they damn it no yeah but they
can they jump on the bouncy
platform is that a thing if they can
they were able to jump on the burger
bouncy
the Patty
bounces oh no
oh ah here I'll make it blue for you
then you can get the the O maybe okay
okay oh but what about the the platform
the platform now needs
to yeah they need the platform on that
level can we get it there come
on
maybe maybe if I send it to no but then
[Music]
we'll find a way if there's a will
there's a way is there a way
here yeah I feel like there
is can you activate the red button when
I'm on the ice
Spike now it's on that level so I feel
like from right side we can bring it
maybe oh yeah they can jump maybe not no
no I think they can jump and get and
then get the tea okay
okay get the
I how can we get up
there uh maybe
maybe the the the it should probably be
down here first and then we bring it up
yeah H
hoies
okay okay and then I threw it up now
that they're there
or if we place it where the I just this
okay nice well oh and then and
then I do this oh but you can go down
and pass through on the bottom stay at
the top amazing okay okay we
got
going nice so in sync okay I ooh
okay I bring them
up on guys me too to oh I guess I have
to go up never mind oh
yeah nice all right all right all
right okay
[Music]
trampoline necessary on
the right right
oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah amazing Ena you're doing
amazing and oh wait you can't bring it
up there so easily I just like you just
throw it when you
jump a few more a few
more okay okay where's the last
letter oh they're down there okay how
do
I think can you come up here just leave
and then go to the right and then to the
left you slide and then yeah oh okay now
I just need the key
hi don't worry don't worry
don't you're putting the kids in danger
[Music]
okay why they I get the key I get it
there we go not the kids here I'll
prepare the spikes oh wait they can't ah
they can't do that jump it's ah from the
Ice Bike they can do the jump okay okay
I don't think they can get on the ice
bike not the kids so many unnecessary oh
do we need to bring the the trampoline
maybe no no like it's uh like from here
they can do that J like here I don't
think they can get on the ice bikes
oh try oh they can okay the three of
them three you know in the last Donkey
Kong fight we lost like four or five
lives I don't know if three lives will
be enough well we'll give it a try we'll
give it a
try desk don't worry her desk is very
sturdy I'm just kindly slapping
it all right all
right you got this
we got this that's a lot of ice
blocks
okay oh
donkey donkey CH what are we doing oh
oh if it being slippery this this this
feels classy oh oh no oh nice oh my God
oh my God
okay one no two more left okay going to
throw bad Barrel bad Barrel where is the
good Barrel yeah give us the good
barrels
[Music]
tle
no just distracted that's good just Sur
distraction but don't lose the last
[Applause]
life yeah good Barrel good
Barrel
[Music]
I had to lose at least one life it's
okay it's
okay chance with free lives again or oh
always going to be free lives okay
that's fine fine to do it's fine this is
fine keep moving keep
moving this is
fine normal Barrel nice nice oh no he
parried it y y
y
uh-oh oh
[Music]
interesting yeah you go you can do it
yeah oh no oh
no uh-oh coming the wrong position okay
okay okay all right we got this we got
this thir try time is the charm
Let's Get It Started donkey CR Let's Get
It
Started normal Barrel normal
Barrel nice first Barrel is easy when he
doesn't block it with the other one oh
he was like damn
it no no why why was the first one so
good oh bar you want to get
it jump get me out of there get me out
of
there careful bad Barrel bad Barrel bad
also bad
barrel and he's going to send a good
Barrel here isn't he
[Applause]
yeah that snow is hard mhm especially
when you're on the top level you have no
chance to get out of okay get out of
there
Barrel good barel good Barrel right
he always does the same thing oh it's
different no no no no I think this is
the same as
before bad Barrel now good
Barrel yes
yes snow i s coming no
no my
invincibility
tle oh no the T oh no get me out of
here I'm awaiting the good Barrel okay
good
Barrel nice all right two bad barrels at
the
top oh no oh
no bad barrel and good Barrel in the
middle but is it the same the snow
seemed kind of sudden and the snow is
random yeah the Snows random uhoh oh no
one live I don't know I don't know
[Music]
about okay okay okay this time this time
this is the one oh nice back flip thanks
bad
barel bad Barrel bad Barrel what you
going to do what you going to do snow
maybe snow okay then he slaps
immediately after the slap is when the
snow
comes sorry next time next time I swear
I swear I
swear but I I I don't know how we didn't
did you notice that the snow comes after
the slap I just notic now oh really yeah
oh right up the the
slap
okay the
pattern
okay uhoh uhoh okay yeah all right all
right nice nice two and then good Barrel
yeah get it get
it
oh it's okay sow sow
sow bad
Barrel oh no oh good Barrel
please oh there it is it's for you uh-oh
oh oh
it's okay get him get
[Applause]
him
okay oh oh no oh
no oh
snow good
Boh a is going to break it no it's okay
we still got two lives I think this is a
pretty good run Cal I want to jump over
it which does work sometimes keep
momentum oh hi
[Music]
no okay oh snow snow
and okay one V
one what is is going to be what is it
going to be oh no oh
no I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
jump I jumped around too much but that
was actually that was good that was good
General we did really well we're we're
having a better overview over the
situation is that a bad one cuz he only
good one oh it's a good
one nice okay noow uhoh hi hi
[Music]
hi me up to
Silver uhoh not the no at least I got to
hit okay nice
nice
uhoh oh thank you Frank youo you helped
me out of that
[Music]
situation know he would do that I got to
cross to him so many times so rude but I
guess it's because at least it's just
time
uhoh
[Music]
oh would have been so beautiful what
there's so many at the same
time that cheap okay okay it's fine it's
fine we got this we're getting smarter
and he's getting smarter but he just
multiplies by three times the brain cell
while we multiply only
two
nice
[Music]
okay oh he's going to
slap your slaps mean nothing to
me good
Barrel uhoh
noow it's okay in
oh good Barrel coming at the
top how did I not get
H risk it for the
biscuit what do you want oh no oh no and
now good Barrel slap and the good Barrel
uh-oh I was stuck it's okay come bring
me the good bar it's going to be bad oh
no oh no
calm now maybe uhoh no
no
calm this time this time it's always
this
time okay it's going to be good
there okay oh
okay
it's not a good run not a good run oh
hey
okay maybe the bad start means that it
will have a good
ending not we already always have good
start got the bad ending okay okay all
right all
right oh
no what oh
what this one this one
this
one he is
good he's
monkey he knows how to do the monkey
business
uhoh I not being ATT okay you can slide
them too
H we twoo good or two bad and a good
mm your
turn it's going to slap
W yeah she did that guys she did
it uhoh uhoh oh no I'm scared oh okay
hey hey y woo woo free lives and he only
got one in why are you why are you
always on the hand why are you trying to
do it's my lucky
charm all right cuz I guess the snow
doesn't hit you when you're when you're
on the handset does the snow not hit
don't know maybe that's actually okay oh
God no what am I supposed to do no no
it's okay come wa we can't mess it up
now we can't we can't we
[Music]
can't focus and
Dodge what does the handstand
mean
oh I leave it to you en know the my life
is in your hands oh no oh it it saved
you though it saved you sa
okay no no no choice no
chance this time TR there were no
previous times guys this is the first
time that we're attempting
this can the still not hit us when we're
hands
down I have a feeling that might be a
thing you you can try if you want to
okay you little [\h__\h] Donkey Kong
oh oh we know now that's the
trick I got it I got it but he's going
to slap but I don't
care ni two lives
left oh
careful you know your platforming skills
Y
uhoh no it's okay it's okay C
me that was not the sorrowful punch that
was the what was
it damn it damn
it oh
snow
oh you want to do it
okay one
more
uhoh I don't remember how so I can't do
it so fast I need to f when I do it oh
there it
is the con
handstand this is going to be it it's
got to be it okay okay no no no no no no
no it's okay is it
okay night yeah this is going to hit us
there was so much snow there too it
would have been fun if I was handstand
but I think we bounc on each other it's
okay okay handstand is good m
it's like
down down in a big
jump hi first one is
anti so
hungry that was my fault for Mama's food
same she made it with
[Music]
love
woohoo risky
risky that's that's for you maybe uhoh
it's going to break oh I still got oh I
got Yo I saved the barel it's okay it's
okay holy time okay it's going to be
two oh thank you for blocking I just
stand on the you that's also oh a
solution what's it going to be monkey
[Music]
kong uhoh it's okay it's
okay
uhhuh down there
uh-oh I thought it was going to do it's
yeah it seems like it but you can't
trust it it's never safe okay and then
got to be safe one it's going to
be okay I guess we can just let it go
and then it'll just SL
mhm it's okay it's okay
Cal nice hey
uhoh it's too
slipper okay good Barrel who's a good
Barrel you a good
Barrel what you
want I was just watching
you all right all right all all okay
okay all right this time this time guys
this time don't worry about it no no
don't wor oh so hungry the hunger the
hunger
games nice okay okay
come just got to stay where en is she'll
block the snow for
[Music]
me
uhoh yeah okay that's how you do it Ena
shows you
guys teach
him fell down it was too
slippery just stay still if you can't
I I want the barrel oh got it oh God got
okay
come sorry guys sorry guys for the
peak it's my Peak okay this is my
[Music]
Peak I'm peeking this is Peak wild
season I was watching don't watch
me I know I'm beautiful but stop
watching me you're jumping around so
much it's my technique to confuse Donkey
Kong but it shouldn't confuse
you
okay two top
ones the middle one yeah oh
hey this is going to
slap
[Applause]
he that's a bad one uhoh I always jump
over that
one good Barrel I'll that to
you wait I can do that on the
bar it's okay it saved you it saved you
your Lifeline has been used you only
have your 50/50 and audience Joker
left
careful this is yours this is your time
it's your time to shine yeah yeah he's
got The High Ground
come down here oh yeah go that works too
that works too making come down to you
and he changes his mind and goes back up
like it we like it donkey we're down
here don't call him down here he doesn't
know he he he takes The High Ground
again all right all right uhoh careful
that is dangerous but no life loss no
life loss give me a better one
donkey that is
some unfair tricks you play on a uhoh
it's no time
no just one for you got this Kiara I got
this this calls for a
celebration it feels
like but it's not the end of the game we
can have dinner but that really feels
like a celebration we did it I'll let my
know she can start heading
over 50
membership thank you you you're
celebrating thank you Michael you crazy
lad thank you guys thank you guys this
we finished world six now so we got like
two left and I think some end game we
got to do it tomorrow then okay on Ena
Channel probably again I mean we already
have Stu up to your Chann oh I guess it
doesn't matter
I yay thank you guys sorry guys we
couldn't finish it I really far we could
but it's
okay tomorrow more spram the better yeah
yeah exactly I think that's what they
think as well exactly oh we're going to
have some yummy mam this food yeah
exciting she took her time to I actually
I uh I think yeah I kind of like hoped
that she would cook something with her
beautiful
hands she love she would have loved to
cook for you either way I think she was
just unsure if you wanted to of course I
want mama needs food mommy always Cooks
best you know okay well we'll go enjoy
the food she'll be here in a bit so hope
you guys have a wonderful rest of the
morning afternoon wait is it already
finished or is she showing us how to
make it is she show cuz she she wanted
to show you but then like she was like
it's probably simpler we're starving so
I guess it works out I can watch a
YouTube tutorial yeah I mean if you ask
her she probably tell
you thank have a wonderful rest of
morning after evening yes we'll see you
guys tomorrow we deci tomorrow tomorrow
I mean tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow all
right okay we'll keep you guys posted on
what
time yeah okay thank you thank you for
watching have a nice day be productive
or
else by
bye meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
[Music]
meow