[Music]
so
do
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello
welcome back to the ghost game
it's been a while it when was the last
time we played this
uh last year is that what i did like
over a year ago she won't stop walking
oh how long am i still controlling
myself
yes you are because
no yes you are see oh yeah okay okay
for some reason i thought it was orange
no i'm the the pinkish goose and raina
is the orange goose
please introduce yourself to the stream
hello
my name
is
rainey
[Music]
wow
god damn it it's so hard
why am i playing
what what happened with the controls man
i can't like properly do things it's so
difficult
that's why i don't know i don't know why
you're using the rusty keyboard
it won't it won't grab on to this
stupid stupid goose maybe elena you have
to do everything
wait how do you do that
in the controller it's circle yeah i
think it's c
for
me
see you're doing it yeah like you have
to grab it by the handle
i mean is it really that be a little
more precise really that precise oh i
turned it over
and be precise come on
face it be precise i was super precise
just now
face this and
press
oh
hey dude we're testing out things
don't don't don't don't don't be in the
way of us i think now
what i feel like i had it now if the
game kind of it was weird sorry for the
delay guys the thing is
oh i'll be in the box
maybe that was a secret goal
oh he won't touch it anymore now that
i'm in the box
hey
can you can you can you bring it inside
i can move i can move in the back
oh you're tipping
[Laughter]
it closes on top of you
so cute
[Music]
oh no yes
maybe he could did you go up out on
purpose because maybe he could have put
you in the truck and sent you to austria
oh no i didn't go out on purpose she
yeah uh he came out or
yeah sad okay maybe i need to distract
her and then
um
i don't know i'm actually just still
trying to figure out the controls it's
different from a long time and also also
she had to
because we're playing remote control she
had to
uh
allow me she had to do the setting so
that she allows me to use the keyboard
it's like there's a child lock in this
game right now is weird
yeah remotely didn't used to have that i
don't think i mean now it's good that
they have the child lock i just didn't
know that you have to enable that first
oh you're certain dominance behind me
it's a hot day so she's giving me some
air i really can't touch right now
come on really i don't know how to do it
game volume i can't raise it it's
actually top volume now
it's just quiet you know there's no
music right now it's just a the flash
yeah there's no music the tap taps of
the feet
tapped up
really slightly um
[Music]
maybe i just don't have any power in my
beaker
[Music]
what does she know about the package she
doesn't know right i'm in there
oh
does she know oh
she's bringing it in
pull her pull her forward forward
that's probably a goal that must be a
goal
so i'm gonna try to check yes i'm gonna
try to check in and check out the oh oh
maybe you have to help me to get in
somehow later
ah surprise
good job
good job yeah and then she'll she'll
gonna she'll take the thingy out
and while she's away i'll do the same
okay
yeah maybe yeah i guess i'll have to go
into the box too
yeah wait until she's like not looking
okay
game is muted game is not muted but just
quiet
[Music]
it's like maximum volume on windows
um
like you yourself also can't hear much i
hear it decently
quietly but you know
let me
think
do a thing oh shoot
oh no don't shoot those guys don't you
hear this
i think you even heard it double
there how do i run i don't remember how
to run oh my god that's really loud
no wait a second now you're double now
you're double your sound is doubled
how about um yes okay now
now
uh
now you guys don't hear it anymore
because there is no sound again
wait
no no why did you go out
because i forgot how to run when i got
chased
okay you wanna get in the box i want to
what
basically oh when you see the
the
on the box you press circle
circle don't have circle what button
could that be on the keyboard
circle
there we go what was that i think that
was that
is that okay
okay then you wait for the lady yes
there is no game sound right now chat
see hear that now there's some sound
there was like one piano sound
do you hear this hear this chat
yeah
they must have heard that
there you go it's just generally a quiet
game all right
yeah we can make our own sounds like
this
exactly and let me hear your voice sound
test
also i'll balance it out a bit more here
make the picture okay
can you say something
uh uh hello hello i'm quack quack
okay one more time oh dang
now it's better
hello
i think i need to wait balanced it
enough
[Music]
okay i'm in now you need to get in
yes i need to get in there why am i
where am i
nah you can't get in like that i'm
pretty sure
where are you yeah i think i need to get
in like the same method as you yeah
ah oh she's bringing the empty box
wait did she cook me into some soup
i think she killed me yeah she made me
into some soup
oh my gosh yeah just be careful not to
be seen
wait oh shoot i can't go okay farther
because i see myself
i can't go further hmm can you go to the
right to the box
very weird difficult
is it because i'm so far away
i think so
i don't even know what i don't even see
myself
i think we have the same camera view
like i just see you walking around in
the corner
i can't go huh
i need to get closer where am i though
i'm not am i in that box though
i can't come down i'm trying to
[Music]
how do you honk
i wonder
square i i don't know how it is oh
oh
that's perspective oh that's where you
want
come on
[Music]
oh thank you for opening sir thank you
so much you opened the door after i
collected him
all right i'm coming be careful because
there's first there's people uh upstairs
oh i feel like the people in the garden
are fine hello
hello i just wanna i just wanna see my
friend reina
hard to move for some reason can i not
walk by here i can't okay yeah because
it's like the camera's like we're too
far apart from each other
[Music]
[Laughter]
what
ah so you after you get in you distract
him and then i go in
but is that not what we just did
um
we couldn't run he chased us out
successfully tried running in the other
direction but it wouldn't let me
all right when you run you have to hold
something uh over here it's cross x
oh yeah right that's not running faster
okay oh what was that oh
that's honking
that was getting pink
how to run this is a certain
dominance why is the keyboard can i
maybe maybe i can see the settings here
um sure uh
i said
what the
okay okay i'm not i'm not pressing
anything so it's yours it's i'm playing
two right
yeah i have to hold something here run
let's say
r
uh
what i saw no no no hold and toggle ah
it doesn't tell me the buttons though
i can look at a face oh wait here adjust
keyboard and mouse there we go
ram is shift you know i'll change it
i'll change it to run
our
grab is that yeah i knew i knew that i
i think i knew that
no way that was crouching the whole time
okay no that's fun
grab that
and
one mouse button
i'll do g for grabbing r for running g
for grabbing c for crouching
flap zumen's amount
okay
okay that's easy to remember r for
grabbing
no africa g for grabbing
let's see
did it not safe
yeah i don't know but i can run
oh oh
no it did save the running
the
[Music]
well so i'll go away no she will put you
hopefully no she saw me she saw me ow
can you distract her while i try to put
her in a football party box
maybe later when she she'll probably
walk away after putting the box down
again
i guess so
right mouse it doesn't do anything when
i press the mouse buttons
kind of the controls are kind of
oh wait ah
now
ah only okay
let's infiltrate
let's go ladies and gentlemen thank you
somewhere else
come with me no oh my gosh a vacation we
don't have to be part of the system we
can take a different path never mind
there's no path here there's no path
okay i thought you were going to take me
though that was your car the blue car
i can steal it for you
steal it no buy it anyway i'll leave you
here let's hope the lady takes you
oh
come
on cute man does it not fit two geese
oh what there's two boxes
what the okay
i'm dying
oh sorry
i
what what's in that box that's
trying to get it
it's closed on both sides i think or is
it
how do i turn it or is it flipped i
think like you can flip it or something
i don't have that talent anymore but
it's okay because you infiltrated the
system perfectly fine
i will
now try to make my way in there
how to i see now i can't move any
further we need to try to change the
camera to you again maybe
yeah when i wonder oh my god she's back
yeah hey
am i dead
no you're somewhere there you're
somewhere there
did it automatically change last time
i i feel like i pressed something at the
same time oh there we go
did you press something i didn't press
anything though
i honked
honk ah when you honk
ah
okay so if i hung
the camera changes to me okay
oh
she's taking that box in too wait
no don't take it
give me the box
can i be in the second box maybe we just
really both have to go in through the
boxes
yeah maybe but now she already put it in
there all right i'll try i'll try to
find the other box
but i can't go so far
okay you do something
okay oh my gosh i can't run
i can't run
[Music]
oh here good job now you're invisible
[Laughter]
you're practically invisible now
okay
but i can't move um
yeah we never played past this point so
i also i also don't know what to do
okay i hope the lady when she walks back
i hope she doesn't see me yeah wait oh
she's there
don't move don't move she's walking
she's like right next to you
on the left yes oh my god
100.
okay i'm gonna go to like these place
people oh so you can't move
wait a second
[Music]
i'm gonna change some settings for my
stream right now
[Music]
okay i'm hiding here right now um
i'm sorry but i see a lot of um
rude comments guys so i'm gonna turn on
the subscriber mode
so if you want to be rude you have to
subscribe okay
so subscribe
okay
next so you're in there hopefully safe i
will go into the box now
and
if i can get closer to the box though um
i can get closer to the box no i can't
go past this
[Music]
oh i can't try to distract
wait wait wait okay i'll try to distract
you no stop but no she'll just
kick you out again
does someone know how to
what the right way of doing this is
no no no no no you're getting getting
get
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't want you to die oh
i can hide here
what hi
don't don't let him kick you out i'm
wait i'll try to can i i'll try can you
honk from there
[Music]
he doesn't really care about that
um please copy donning me at the wall
i'll try to attack him
see what's crashing
i'm stuck i'm not sure about the buttons
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's like a
survival game now
i know
no you're not gonna make food out of me
no no no no no no okay okay okay okay
we're doing good we're doing good we're
gonna die
we're done
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
is there like where's the list how do
you see the list again
i don't really remember there should
they used to be a list
i love this new outlast
hmm you're so cute
hi
cute
oh shoot
the lady they're everywhere oh oh let's
go here
oh she's okay she's okay how can we like
lock the door so she doesn't get back oh
maybe maybe maybe but maybe we will it
doesn't we will need to go there right
it doesn't have a locker maybe
freedom
freedom for the birds maybe yeah maybe
we were never supposed to do anything in
the pub maybe this is where we were
supposed to go all along
wait
oh
smash it
how do we smash it oh
[Laughter]
oh what's this oh it's just a
door
okay hmm
there should be like a goal like what to
do or something but
um
you guys know what the button is just uh
press tab
there we go
break the dartboard get the toy boat
make the old man fall on his bum
set the table knife and fork and plate
oh yeah we found the peppers and candles
and be awarded oh that's the table
and steal a pink glass i'll drop it and
drop it in the kennel canal a pink glass
oh god there's a lot of goals ooh
we put this right here we put the plate
here this is the table you think so this
is considered a table
i think so because there's nothing else
okay
there's nothing else that can be
considered a table i don't think
well maybe we have to set it inside the
the pub
oh maybe i don't know either
what else is here uh this isn't on the
table oh can you come in
[Music]
container i don't know what it is
all right i think we do have to do stuff
in the pub
maybe oh yeah i guess yeah we have to
cool
she's okay i think she's okay so we
steal items from the pub and then set
the table here i guess so we always have
to take the stealther out here
be careful
be careful okay don't be made into a
stuffed goose we don't there i see a
fork there does it say what uh knife
yeah plate is done okay yeah see the
plate is crossed out the fork i saw on
the floor over there
pepper candle nice fork pepper candle
okay let's go
pick up okay
what's the other thing
knife
we awarded a flower
i shall avoid you a flower
i love flowers what's your favorite
flower elena
[Music]
oh yeah you can distract maybe
oh yeah
do you have the force no i couldn't she
was she was already back too fast
i'll distract i'll distract you take the
fork take the out yeah
okay okay follow me
it's so hard
[Music]
uh not if i can stop her
no no no no no no no no
no maybe we need to retreat a little bit
cause she's blocking the way i can't
pass
excuse me lady drop it drop it like it
talks
drop it drop it drop it
[Music]
i think
yeah we'll just let her put it back
again
and then
we hide we dug under the table we're
calling it now before it was under the
table
oh there's more though there's a fork
and knife over here too
oh there's like a napkin there
i didn't need a napkin as far as i know
well not this okay we we can duck under
here
i can't take these forks and knives
apparently
[Music]
we don't need a napkin
ah okay then
[Laughter]
you're so proper you want to eat with a
napkin
so you don't get your your pretty mouth
dirty
she's too scared of me to touch
[Music]
good hell yeah it already considers it
set you can just leave it there
i guess so
all right
all right what's the next one i know
we're talking yes let's try to get a
knife or uh
a pepper okay a knife
okay knife pepper and candle i think you
can duck under the
oh yeah here
oh no need to i distract no i'm so brave
try to get the knife then knife
knife
knife for life oh she's
okay i'll make i'll make way
um
she threatened you with the knife did
you see that
yeah i did oh my god
oh
that's violence against animals
[Music]
you're such a good goose right now
you are a good guru
why
[Music]
what's your problem
why she keep dropping the knife like
that
she's scared she's scared she she
threatened us but she can't do with
it
a nice one but we don't need that one do
we need like a glass no
unfortunately i'll drop it in the canal
[Music]
there's a candle
okay
no no no no no no no no no no no shoot
all right
yes okay
[Music]
[Applause]
why is the lady always there when we
don't need her
where did the knife go i don't see it
anymore ah she's she was holding it
there we go
this is how you make 40 minutes of
gameplay into two hours of gameplay
[Music]
once the man is like away okay
[Laughter]
oh no it's still there you can go
[Music]
yay
beautiful beautiful setting of the table
elena
um thank you so is it pink thank you
it's a it's not wait a pepper pepper do
they mean
pepperoni grinder or
i think so like a pepper oh there's
there
sorry the quality is kind of uh low
because of remote play guys sorry i it's
on my side too it's a bit pixelated
ah nanny i don't have anything
let me in okay oh you want the napkin
yeah go ahead we don't need the napkin
take it take it
and that lady oh my god she's she's
bringing so many of these boxes over
hard-working lady though
okay now we can go
birds on the move birds on the move okay
i'll be uh ready here to distract any
time
okay
i'll
oh she's just chewing me out she doesn't
know it's not the pepper yet she doesn't
know she doesn't know about it and let's
let her go back oh now she figures it
out but she didn't see you yet
yeah she doesn't see me
yeah
i'll let her go a little bit further i
guess
yeah yeah it's okay um i can just like
bring let's bring it back one one at a
time
oh really
that table right now
[Music]
go clean the different table
there we go let's go
yeah
we're almost ready for our romantic
candlelight dinner oh my goodness
that's impressive that's okay let me at
least get the last thing i didn't bring
a single thing over i'm so bad at night
it's okay it's teamwork i'll i'll bring
the candle this time um okay but i don't
did you see a candle there maybe it's
outside here yep it's here it handles
like
inside but on the right side
it's here oh
the candle is like here
you see i want to take
oh you want to take your hair i'll drop
it and you can take it under the
thank you you can take it oh you can
duck and then you can take it crouch
okay good
spicy
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
spicy now we can have some romantic
dinner
remember where's the food spaghetti you
know slurp it so then when
you know like you know what i picked up
from you because like you you you always
use that you know the single tier emoji
oh i don't use that sometimes a lot you
mean the ones yeah
that's one thing i picked up from you oh
it is very useful but they don't have it
uh
on every device i've noticed so
sometimes i can't oh really
oh
my emoji wait let me see the objective
oh yeah
be awarded a flower make the old man
fall break the dartboard where's the
dartboard
hmm you see
do you want to go to the garden where
it's like safer yes
well there's a harmonica wait do we get
a flower maybe if we put these
maybe
why don't we make this old guy fall
oh wait he's oh
maybe i need to honk when he's like
about two three yes oh yes
oh oh something like that
yeah
[Music]
or when he picks it up oh no when he
almost like throws
[Music]
i can play the harmonica oh oh i know i
know what to do
okay
when he
so when he's about to throw i'm gonna
like sleep no more god all right that
could work all right all right
oh he knows he knows i have to like take
it from
oh nice
hunk
wait wait
oh no oh buddy did surprise him
bamboozle
thank you there's music in my ears what
is someone's waiting there for us
uh
maybe these women will give us the
flower if we do something nice
hello
hello mom
give a flower
flower please
maybe if we give her a give them a
harmonica they will give us the flower
yeah
we can play some music for them
uh-huh like oh my gosh serenade them
wait mama
oh oh
you like that when they asked
[Music]
oh they're so cute they like us
give me more flowers give me more more
they're appreciators of pablo nachi
bird action
they appreciate it
cultured ladies
yeah show them those wings let's go
spicy
oh they don't have any more water and
not water flour no
we did that goal nice
okay maybe let's make this dude
oh he's sleeping
can we like ah take the take the stool
from behind oh that was close maybe
but but when he sleeps maybe
he makes nice music why do we have to
gang up on him
oh there's the dartboard oh
you saw that boy
yo he has all kinds of fun stuff here
and we wanted to break
how are we gonna do that break the
[Music]
[Laughter]
how do we get it to break
what's that remember what's that thing i
dragged in the back room
i wonder what that's for oh
maybe it's just a random item but
take it take it
[Music]
i'm sure i'm unsure
so rude
i want to stand on the stool and then
take the dark stand on this one
okay i'll distract him i'll distract him
i don't know probably doesn't work
yeah though i don't know how to get on
the stool i i haven't have problems to
get on top of this thing here
is that even
does that even work
oh
wait new one well he's doing this thing
but then you have to keep him distracted
maybe
okay okay
usually it's sing it's okay to do it
with single player so i wonder what i
what we have to do
true
true normally everything is doable in
single player
yeah you make him like stuff like that
you're s you suck at this game
you suck at this game yeah pick up pick
up these things yeah don't don't ignore
the stool ignore the stool
just look at me look how i can play the
game
i can't flip it over
right it stays like that so
ah
i can't hold him back any longer
yeah that's fine i don't know hmm how do
you do it
how do you make the guy
now he's he's pretty occupied with the
game again
where's the harmonica
look it on top
i'll not break this
i can't rent it from there right we
can't reach it
how do you look up like that um
mine always looks down
what do you mean
the the face how do you make him ah oh
there we go
you know but our
our necks are a little bit too short for
that
yeah okay okay okay i
i think
i want to try
uh
[Music]
when he sleeps again
remove the stool to make him fall over i
think that's that could work but then
for the for the darts i don't know how
to do that one
um okay
let's let him play for a while maybe we
can try something else instead steal a
pint glass and drop it in the canal we
can try that one what's the canal
oh there there is this it is yeah
maybe
i don't know
when i think of a canal and think of
something bigger than that but we can
try that
me too but i don't see anything else
oh gotta try
so one of those glasses yeah well she's
very occupied right now
probably easily runs
yeah
that's it that's it
put it here a drop
drop it
what we're broken oh wait no the canal
we have to open the
top because i think it just gave me a
sign that it's that you can open it here
wait no that wasn't it
that was something else i thought that
was a canal cover
is that
can we go for here no
i think that's the exit
i i think we have to bring this like
outside for some reason because i don't
know i don't know what this is actually
what is this
lady is here
[Music]
lady doesn't care anymore even though
she sees us all the time she just wants
to get those boxes in she's busy
gotta get some stuff done oh i got it
stuck
hi grandpa do you know what this is
no idea lady
also you're distracting me very much
let me play my dart game alone for
heaven what is
this what is this
i think
it's just it's just
nothing
oh
he's playing the harmonica now maybe
after that he'll chill cause like he
switched between
playing the harmonica and then falling
asleep
so
i got too close
let's wait
[Music]
no sleep
i thought you'd sleep after that go
sleep old man you need a break
life's hard
chillax
[Music]
what if i bring the harmonica like to
the safe room
he can't play it anymore so i guess
he'll
he'll sleep instead
yeah
okay
[Music]
he did he did that before though and i
did see him napping before
what that's at him let's let him place
the stool again
let's let him get down place the stool
again
actually
[Music]
okay he'll place it there see the heel
gun he's gonna oh yeah
no don't play the stupid dots back hurts
so play darts no back hurts so sit down
okay wait the chat says we have to try
to steal it before he sits down like
when when the moment went oh like he's
just like about to sit you're like
yeah
okay so we we're on that'll take a while
playing stupid darts
can you play darts
cause i suck at them persona yeah
oh did you know that we can play persona
now dana
oh
really you didn't know
we can play some personal games now
really yeah let's check i know cause
like some yeah i saw somebody play but
i don't know
no chad i already told you didn't i
wasn't there like some huh
there was something about that chocolate
no i don't really know the details but
we can play personal four persona four
personal persona four golden somebody
already played it and personally
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's not leaking it's just it's not
leaking it's not secret information we
can play it there you go
[Music]
okay um ah there you go he said he still
he stood up to fix that nice
damn it too early
little bit too early
[Music]
okay
no now he plays the stupid game again
you want me to do it this time
yeah you can try
be ready okay
don't mind me don't mind me sir i'm not
i'm i'm a good girl i'm a good goose
i'm a
[Laughter]
oh no you broke his back lena
now you gotta fix his bag poor guy
he needs to go to the i don't know
the back center
hey like
that's that's a tough one
the thought is a tough one
maybe we can find some inspiration
when we run around we just go through
the diner
she's there
and there's a solution she just
she just chases us away though oh
careful no
i'm gonna go inside and look for you
know
some museums for wine show
me too me too me too
what's the where's the canal what's the
canal i have no idea
oh
okay we're too far now
i didn't see any canal
yeah the only body of water i see is
like that thing over there
maybe we have to go back
wait wait wait wait
no way wait uh can you go a little bit
um
oh sorry yeah uh wait
what
wait i have to wait for her
i'll pass please lady
thank you
okay oh she's there
ah
outside there's chasing me away
it's okay it's okay outside the pub
outside outside no geese allowed
why not so discriminating
outside the pub
is that a wall or is that ground
huh right
stealth ghost mode activates traffic
yeah here left
oh he left
nice stealth
over here okay we don't
never went here
oh there's the boat
what's with the boat
get the toy boat uh we need to make it
float maybe and then we can take it when
it's higher
yeah it's coming oh we made it overflow
come here come here yes distract
distract
oh yes there it goes
[Music]
i don't think she cares i don't think
she can pick you up if you're under the
table
[Music]
can we even put the toy boat she's
probably gonna she's probably gonna
turn off the water uh oh it's already
accomplished so yeah it doesn't matter
like we don't even need to put it
anywhere specific yeah
yeah i'm gonna put it here make it swim
there now
for it it's happy boat is happy boat
wants to float
oh sorry lady so the last one no
is is this glass the one like at the
edge of the you know there's like a big
one i don't know
big big one
oh that might be big big glass like um
oh sorry
i don't want nothing this one no that's
too tall for even me
yeah
i don't think that's it can we soft lock
ourselves by breaking too many glasses
somewhere else and then we wouldn't have
any glasses left i wonder
oh i don't think that's possible i hope
so
there's still one more glass here pink
glass is a beer glass right
yeah
[Music]
this one right
was that different the one we tried
first
the one that we accidentally broke you
know
accidentally
oh
moment of truth
where's the canal
that was not it that's not it
i should have to keep on pushing that
okay by pushing that instead of shift
[Music]
sorry i can't read super chats today but
happy birthday congratulations
can we go through the door uh behind the
pub oops sorry we can try to check
oh
i'm gonna go fast oh she's she's right
there
stand
hi
she can't get us if you're under here
dang yes
how are we so blind that we didn't see a
canal
yeah maybe
maybe it was
[Music]
in the beginning but this feels like
it's weird it is an asl moment
what is it
[Music]
oh me chase away with a lady
okay
how about i scout
uh if in the beginning area there was
actually something
i go scouting even if they kick me out
it's
okay okay
um gosh running with this goose is so
difficult
i'm gonna go yeah yes sir i don't mind
i'm living on my own you can't kick me
out when i'm living on my
own i can't see
so wait isn't there a canal here
oh
oh my god what is this
that is a canal
we're gonna drop it here
the glass
wait what is this
is this how to break the dark board oh
maybe
what's this
is that a
nice tool box
oh shoot
he's happy forever together
i guess we're just gonna you know leave
here
we don't need to finish everything we're
just gonna you know go our own way
we're so beautiful
[Music]
chilling enjoying the nice weather
where are we
is this a new area where there would be
more tasks this is the first area ah
huh this is the first area remember
how it's connected
it's connected
wow
okay let's go bring that uh glass over
here
i'm so fast
we can go this way too what's this way
okay that's where it ends
what
oh get up there
get up there what is this
oh i can't open this door but there's
some extra stuff oh
[Music]
okay yes i'm a drunkard because my beak
is stuck in the bottle and you're my
baby how do we go back up ideal family
uh
we yeah we just there was some normal
land over there that we can go back up
i think i saw i guess we have to walk
all the way around
oh maybe
ah your hook still sounds kind of normal
mine is like a bottle a bottle hunk
uh a bottled up hunk
oh we can't go here spicy keys
[Music]
let's give them a traumatic traumatic
deja vu moment oh
picnic game
oh
the kids are back you thought you would
never see us again but we're back
how um does this lead us anywhere listen
to the beginning
on it
we need to
somehow we missed a really obvious uh
wait what about here
oh damn it
ah should we have like
uh unlocked the no go go now go now
[Music]
we'll go that way we're doing it a
second time
oh we don't jump into the river anymore
before we break the dart
oh that's gonna only be open from the
other side damn it
oh dang it
okay the glues are loose
the goose are loose
oh i guess we'll call this okay
yeah let's just
go by the way thank you for um
thank you for being twice in my birthday
stream
[Music]
yeah no problem
did you know were you surprised i was i
was very surprised you kind of changed
your looks
you looked yeah so pink and blue at the
same time
yeah i mean you know i have my i have
this shape i have my penis shape and did
you know i also have yeah that was your
personal shame yeah
yep
pretty impressive
yeah you look so different i almost
didn't recognize you if it didn't
clearly say in comic sense pavilion holy
life indonesia
what's this place have you been here
before
yeah this is like the pool
oh
oh barely remember this place
the one with the walkie-talkie remember
ah walkie-talkies
[Music]
do you remember they all they all hate
us they all close the gates
yes justice for birds
no discrimination for the birds good job
good job
that will teach you a lesson
yes
okay okay okay oh there's a well here a
basket what was that
it's like a coin a wishing well i'm
gonna put let's make that yeah
an extra
i can't throw it further wait i can oh
i wish for
reina
to be
healthy and happy for her whole
life our dreams come true
is there another question
extension
[Music]
are we going the right way
um
maybe look at this wobble huh
oh we can open this is a shortcut for
later if you want to run around
i have a rainbow oh let me put it on you
let me put the ribbon on you
can you put it on me
i guess not
it would look so pretty though it's a
blue ribbon
wait just let me try to put it
yeah
it looks like you want to eat the ribbon
accessorize the goose
yeah okay that just leaves me with the
river yeah i think yeah that's yeah that
was just a shortcut
it's good that we're opening all this
okay there we go
now we're back the goose are back just
went on a little bit of a uh a walk
geese need to walk sometimes
get their sports game going but
how do we break the dart again
yeah i still don't know that
i still don't know maybe if we get into
the car and then just drive like a
maniac and destroy everything
we could worth a try worth a try
okay i'm gonna get in the box
will she take
the present
will she take it
hmm heavy kind of happy yeah what
happened
nice
[Music]
you distract him and then i ran inside
there we go nice good jump
and i'll distract him
yes yes yes let's go now we warmed up
we're way better at this now i mean all
good
oh good oh good she doesn't see she
doesn't care about us she cares about
the box
okay we're back so let's figure this out
who
darts
maybe he will break it if we honk when
he froze it somehow
oh maybe
oh
maybe it's that easy
do it what's that what's wrong
one two
damn it he dropped it but he doesn't
break it
can i take it when he
where did it go i did land on there damn
it
[Music]
do we want to drop this in the canal
first
ah but then you have to go back in maybe
we should do that one last
but remember that thing we saw like the
toolbox
i dropped it in the water
oh
i don't think they would make us use
something that's so far away
because usually everything you need is
in the area
i guess so
ah
apparently it's correct we have to just
uh honk at him when he throws the dart
but it's a very specific timing
shut the weight okay then
okay
when you froze it
one huh
too early
later really
i feel like it was a perfect
sorry it's so insane though
[Music]
he has such a red nose
no trying to mount him
oh he's
oh he wants to harmonical where did the
harmonica go did you take it oh yeah
you're putting it somewhere else on you
okay we'll keep on doing it i'm gonna
i'm
i'm gonna take this away so he can't
play anything else but
oh
starts
now
five four three two one play darts
[Music]
oh
uh you you went me
your mouse yeah
we're back we're back in the game
what if
will he play darts if i stand here
right in front of the dartboard
maybe
come back sir come back sir
play darts please
ah let's just let him finish like this
action and then he'll he'll he'll play
darts oh my god lena just takes away
everything this old man has he has
nothing left his daughter died his wife
died and you take the last few things
that he has to enjoy his day
i don't know
i think it's to make him play darts
maybe maybe okay
to make him play darts
if he doesn't even have the chance to
sit on if he doesn't even have the rings
to play whatever this is then he'll have
no choice but to play darts oh my god
damn no chair i wonder where that went
okay i'll help you
thank you
[Music]
oh no
i'll help you
where is he going
he never went up there before
[Music]
he's looking for them up there oh no
he's is he gonna look for them forever i
think it's the ai
he's he's become so lonely that
he he because he became restless he
doesn't even have anything to play
oh my god darts old man
oh thanks for opening the door lady
thank you lady
did it
nice
but i think he's gonna look for it
forever no
is he ever gonna stop looking for it
really
maybe not it's over here sir
oh
oh he actually comes over here oh oh no
uh
then i'll put the harmonica in here
ah he gets the harmonica chair though
everyone's holding everything in here
oh my god
yeah he doesn't have anything else to
play for them
exactly
oh he has no more left
except the harmonica i'm gonna take that
too aren't ya
thank you
but he doesn't it he wants stuff
is he gonna look for this forever okay
maybe let's go
did we break him
we broke him finally
he's just hopeless now okay i think we
we should bring him back his stuff
hey look it's christmas you can have
your things back
hey the christmas skis well nice
marshmallow
nothing truffle truffle i almost
damn it
i'm about as bad as he is at this game
yeah but he's playing again
what is this
i still have no idea what this is oh
let's see
what's the main goal again
oh break the dart board and the pink
glass and now we're done
i don't know how to break the
blessing
[Music]
did we bring everything back he seems to
be playing normally again there's still
some rings over here no we don't need to
we don't need to bring
okay let's wait until he plays diets
again
okay oh he's back oh he's back
[Music]
oh no it's not up there sir it's in the
secret rain stash
oops i'm not even bringing it what is it
which one is it no
what
did you see that i was looking at the
bottom did he just take it out of the
floor yeah he took it out of like he he
just
glee oh he's a hacker
he's a hat girl man
i wish you could have seen it from my
side oh my gosh oh my i will re-watch
that moment
what is this wizardy
well okay now he can chill a little bit
i'll give you a break old man while i
drink yeah i'll give you a break
[Applause]
so reina
uh-huh
um
so weather's kind of hot lately yeah
why are you eating milkshakes for dinner
elena
because i'm
oh speaking of it i need to finish it
yeah because i'm
i don't know because i'm living a
healthier life
very healthy and before the stream she
was like ah got my milkshake for dinner
she said i will eat my milkshake for
dinner now and i'm like what what do you
mean did i misunderstand that i miss
here
eating a milkshake for dinner there's so
many things wrong in this sentence
it's like a
it's like a you know it's like a protein
shake but it's not a protein shake but
it's like tasty because it's vanilla
because it's no protein it's just sugar
no yes no
i don't like milkshakes too though so
it's okay but you should eat something
proper afterwards are you going to eat
something proper afterwards young lady
[Music]
oh i hear the gulping
i'm gulping my dinner gulp gulp gulp
how long is he gonna play the freaking
i know
okay i'm done with my dinner um i ate
vegetables earlier
oh that's i ate some spinach so i'll be
strong
vegetables he wants
[Music]
[Applause]
stream harmonica
play the darts
yeah you can't play harmonica so play
darcy said
what is he bugged now or what
you know he missed the harmonica so much
now he won't stop playing
yeah i think we should i think we should
wait if we interrupt if we keep
interrupting him he will keep playing
yeah but we waited so long
i don't think he ever played the
harmonica this long before
where are the darts the darts are here
oh there we go finally dude finally go
okay
okay darth starts time play darts
staring at you menacingly
[Music]
sorry
just wondering if that if that does
something okay so what's the timing
yeah i feel like our timing was perfect
like how is he gonna break it
yeah
there we go let's go
so that was the same timing as we did
before
new life a new thing drop a bucket on
the burly man's head
what's the burly man this dude
drop a bucket on his head
oh
is this a bucket is this a bucket or is
this a bucket is this oh no she's
looking at you with that thing you're so
so obsessed with this thing
i think this is a bucket burnley is a
strong guy okay where is the strong guy
maybe the opening guy yeah
i do want some revenge on him
okay we're done with the old guy we can
stop uh
ganging up on him
yeah finally uh okay let's find a bucket
you
is that
i think this is a bucket
this is the only bucket looking thing i
found so far
okay i don't know i'll check i'll check
somewhere else ah lady
a baby oh what
did she really just take that away from
you
yeah she did how dare she i'll bet now i
can go inside how do i drop it on his
head
me
bucket
bucket yeah
it up from here
from the porch maybe from where you were
to snow
i can't walk properly
whoa
the beer let's go
[Music]
oh maybe we have to lure him somewhere
uh to a good position to drop something
on him was there a bucket here oh
there's another one
oh
okay
sorry
but now we know how to do it she'll do
she'll um she'll bring it back properly
probably should probably place it back
there
or
[Music]
but when that when will the guy ever
come there it's like in the very back oh
okay she put it back
but that's not the burly guy and then
the box the box the box the box we have
to push aside so he will stand on top of
it
he might not even have to stand on it
oopsie
i don't think i was able to push the box
before oh really you know i tried but
couldn't move it but how do we get the
dudes to come here
like he will
oh for what reason would he come here
if we steal something from him
he never followed us that far but okay
let's try
knife let's try that but then one person
has to wait up there to push the bucket
down and one person has to lure him
there yeah doesn't make sense because
this game is supposed to be single
player yeah so
true
hmm
shoot i got chased out oh no oh no oh
okay thanks thanks thanks
hi
he's not really strong looking either
is he wait maybe maybe this this person
with the boxes maybe that is actually
the burly guy
let's try to drop it on her oh no no i'm
just looking for a flower if they gave
it to impossible
is it even possible i don't know
um
by accident
okay
she'll put it back the burly man's head
early men's head
it's definitely him
wasn't that a lady though
yeah
it's right on top it's right on top of
that yellow box
[Music]
it doesn't land on them though so it's
someone else yeah
maybe
[Music]
you're not the right person wait why is
she going up here
i don't know go ahead lady what uh
what's your business what may your
business be up here
maybe now that way so far some of the
npc's routes will change
how they walk maybe
because did she ever walk that way
no maybe no
oh sorry sorry
she took the shield wait why is the
shield here now
oh there you go yes follow me oh
how do i make him open this all right i
go oh yes yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
goose chase let's go
here i am here sir follow me sir
follow me follow me
is he coming
is he coming wait wait we were on the
right path though oh yes yes yes yes
[Music]
but someone has to push the bucket
one of us has to go up are you do you
want to go up or should i one one person
can just wait up there i suppose
okay and then
we switch the camera to the other person
one waits for the bucket to drop
oh he's following you nice nice nice
okay
wait
it falls over so easily
where is he now can you honk
does it switch to your camera no way too
close
he's here he's here
i think he
it's outlast outlast
it's freaking out last they're all
they're all chasing us
i think since it's a single player i
think it wouldn't make sense if the
trick needed two people oh i think we
just have to like lead him to the
yeah to the whatever space okay okay
okay
oh okay okay i'll uh
he's does he still if i walk over here
and honk here will he come over
yes yes yes maybe maybe yes yes
where's the bucket she's putting the
bucket up yes good timing good timing
now walk away lady
you can't you can't hurt me here
[Music]
no
no what if the goal is a goal that only
is added in multiplayer though
oh that's sort of thing because it's a
goal to like finally end the game
maybe
again can you honk at him
so far damn it
where am i
good honking will do
okay nice
oh my gosh it's so um
oh no no more no more space oh oh
come here
yeah okay inside
it's just an optional task yeah but
still we want to do it
we want to do it
okay i don't think it's the optional
task i think it's the thing you have to
do to clear
yeah
i think it's the one you have to do to
clear the stage okay
wait the box is open now
oh
i put that somewhere there
chad is saying tomatoes
i think what is this i'm putting it
yeah yeah okay okay tomatoes tomatoes
tomatoes tomatoes
do you like tomatoes i love tomatoes
okay i put all the tomato outside
no
maybe only maybe the guy cares about the
tomatoes and he tries to put it in the
box hey hey go go go come on chase me
chase me
chase me now oh camera
my control dies
okay yeah yeah go go go go go go keep
going keep going keep going oh shoot
[Laughter]
[Music]
i saw no other option
okay
give it a sec give me a sec
it's so crowded here though
that's so crowded
oh dang
[Music]
it's hard sorry um i'm too far away
yeah like the thing is like if i'm too
far away like her controller will also
get messed up yeah
and when he chases us oh okay okay okay
follow us follow us follow us please
hello come here come here
come here
yeah okay they're gonna check and
they're good they're gonna like do the
watermelon
no but i want a tomato
what will happen if they fix the tomato
does it do we have time okay
yeah we're gonna fix the tomato and
maybe we can drop drop the thing when
oh
i'm trying to follow oh oh oh he's
looking at the pepper grinder
[Music]
oh yes
there's blood on him
ah
we made ketchup
high quality butt pressed ketchup
organically pressed yeah
oh that's how we did that the only thing
we have to do is sew the pink glass and
drop it in the canal
okay let's do this guy we're done with
him do you remember when you left the
glass
yeah like the water okay the water where
we kept the toy boat okay
sorry sorry i'm trying to run away from
this guy
come here
don't touch related don't touch
okay i it distract him
maybe i'll try to get the glass done
[Music]
i choose you oopsie i chose you now
okay
oh it's too far yeah it is too far
okay let's honk
hong kong okay
[Laughter]
she took it away
is it now under the pub again yeah it's
in the restaurant
okay okay i'm hiding
let's hide so he just goes the freak
away
okay he won't even go up there nice
okay let's just stop that she'll go for
a moment
i if i go up now he'll he'll chase me
probably again oh okay okay okay let's
wait for him to
oh he does come up here
don't
don't let him find you
he will abduct you
yeah
why is he looking for the glass the
glass was up there anyway it's he's
looking under the bucket
oh that's a bucket i thought that was a
glass
all right
nice lady i'm waiting for this lady to
um um do something else
yeah what's she is there's a bucket
is this a bucket
what is your bucket oh he's busy with
tomatoes nice it's busy with the
tomatoes
okay okay okay okay oh come on i can't
move okay let's go now i can move
okay
are we going on the super stealthy are
we going uh uh the canal was over there
yeah i know
um okay um
wait wait for the landing to yeah
wait for the lady to pass
and
what are you gonna watch
we're gonna wipe that table
yeah
go
okay
let's go okay okay
run run canal time
goes run
run run run run to the canal
finally that was so so much pain in the
butt
there was a platform there to drop it
here
oh sorry
yeah hitting my butt
yay is it over
the game doesn't tell us anything new
the game yeah the game the game uh gave
us an achievement gave me an achievement
so maybe that is it for the game
what what does the achievement say
finito the pub
oh
there's a new path oh
did a new door open well i think it's it
should still be no no that's us
like this is us
the one that the path that we took
remember
yeah but someone said that there's a new
path
oh
is there a new path okay
i don't think there's any more content
though
okay then uh i mean maybe we could just
go to the pub
oh okay i can go to the pub and like
check the back door maybe
[Music]
go go go go go do we have to uh do we
have to do the whole thing again with
the
oh my god are you serious is it box time
it's box time baby
okay the game has an actual ending oh
interesting okay i wanted to see the
actual ending oh god are they busy with
the
is the lady busy
is she is the lady even gonna like is
she gonna come
nice
nina how are you doing dad
does she realize no i don't think so
there we go
okay
there you go
oh
wait that was so easy i could just
distract it with the design by moving
the sign
all right it was sweet all
[Music]
let's go we turned on easy mode
where's the new path
i want to bring tomato
wait is it here
probably the back door is here oh it's
there okay
oh don't you want to bring a tomato with
you
oh we'll share we'll share but i can't
open this one
oh
check these sick moves out
oh jump
oh my god
wow
[Music]
a beautiful beautiful area all for us
a key
a padlock
where do we
find the key
oh maybe in the water yeah let's look
oh nice go for this nice swim
zoom
[Music]
nanu
there must be a key at the end of this
this is like the credits you look at the
whole game again
by walking through
we're giants oh that's cute
it's over humans birds are taking over
just like in australia there's a crouch
oh and now this is the model
oh
this is the model oh what we're looking
at
this
a castle for us
for us to live in
we can break it
what
we are we're terrible terrible people we
can break it on this side too
oh
what's that oh my god oh
follow me later
it's like romeo and juliet don't die
where are you i just want to say i love
you
oh my god
[Applause]
a vowel
and take it all the way back and take it
all the way back home take the bell back
home he's like a marriage bell
[Music]
[Applause]
the beginning
our home
where is our home
i don't know this whole area is our home
maybe like just not the model yeah okay
okay
oh oh look
i have this flower
it's flower for our marriage
look at this
so nice
congratulations
[Music]
that way oh oh
you're so smart
okay it is my job
to lead this family on this way of two
birds
i think here
not here maybe this is like this is the
padlock i want to go that way okay this
is not back home
can i not open it down with the bell
i don't want to open it
can't
open home is maybe the very beginning of
the game huh
down maybe down no
ah
no
no bring it all the way back home
that's very um
confusing uh confusingly phrased
where is home
freely in the wild there is no home for
us
[Music]
um you wanna go back
you wanna go back
i
[Music]
don't worry guys
congratulate us or we're gonna
we're gonna destroy
[Music]
i'll follow you soon
can you follow me i'm scared
okay
i'll
okay maybe he will
maybe he will walk and
hmm
i guess this is the challenge bringing
it all the way back through all these
people again
yeah i guess so
what is that just all he's gonna do
oh yeah maybe move that so he'll he'll
take it also
will he will he be interested in no
huh
okay wait let me just honk here okay
yes yes
[Music]
he doesn't care about the bell does he
territory give us the bell it's our
wedding bell
lady
[Applause]
lady i thought you were nice lady
oh yes go go go into the water kiama
[Music]
all these people
nice nice i'll go in the water i'll go
in the water nice nice nice
[Music]
they can't go any further nice
yeah do you wanna do you wanna bring the
flower or okay it's okay the flower does
did its job okay yeah but it's okay
flower in your heart okay
i made it
hallelujah
okay they closed even the well
why it's so sad anti-goose
so rude what about this one oh i get so
bad locked
oh that's what they did they put
padlocks on all the
to force us to go
back we can't run if we run
yeah if we run we alert the people all
the people
we want i thought we wanted to alert
them
uh sure i guess not okay
oh
where is home
[Music]
pull the pull the uh yellow thing okay
i can't it doesn't let me
oh sh
statue
no i don't even know this place i don't
remember it anymore so i don't know
where the exit is
uh
oh
this okay really difficult the ending is
really difficult
run run run run run as fast as you can
where is oh yes whoa
reina you're
you're that's the reason that's the
reason why i love you so much
[Music]
i don't think this is the exit
is this the exit it's one exit but uh
at least my breathing room
this doesn't lead anymore okay at least
this is like a safe place let's try to
scout and exit yeah okay
[Music]
yeah pull it out yeah let's make them
busy
[Music]
yes that's how we exit i remember
oh yeah okay okay
let's keep them busy what is this sign
it's cute actually
okay
[Music]
and i'll bring it wait don't come here
don't come yet i want to distract her
because she's fixing the sign
uh-huh okay i think you can come
it's a fish okay okay
oh shoot don't run
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
oh can you go for one
yes she can't touch you anymore
justice for the birds let's go for the
birds
all right all right wait you wait here
wait here with the okay okay okay
teamwork teamwork teamwork let's go
ah this is uh
[Music]
oh that's full boarded up
maybe if i take some of this stuff
[Music]
and danny wants to no no no
only him
[Music]
camera can't catch up with us there we
go let's go
where the you were i thought it was
you
[Laughter]
[Music]
happy wedding anniversary number one
happy
wedding
all right we did the honeymoon before
the wedding
yeah
it's all right likes the order doesn't
always matter
what are these signs now we're just like
a zucchini
no exactly that's what i was like i have
no zucchini
gee i wonder
okay let's just go run straight through
so proud
[Music]
so dramatic oh my god the music
yes
no no run
go go
[Music]
this is the problem when you don't have
thumbs up
freedom
[Music]
a front door
oh wait here now we could run
oh oh that's easy that was easy that was
easy
let's go
[Music]
wait i think that's not that's not
can we go there
is this home i don't remember this place
this is where we
ah
this is where we started
is it it is right it's home
maybe it's not home
this is where we started
oh no no no no no
oh yeah
[Music]
speaking of ducks is this where we
started
how's our home oh
a bit further a bit further oh there's a
path
oh my goodness we are hoarders after all
[Music]
no wonder they hate us so much surprise
more more bells oh
how many times have they built me
oh
now they go on
in their lives some geese as the keys
that's the geese
[Music]
finally yeah
i never saw this how long did it take us
to finish this too long
[Music]
i was told it was like 40 minutes of uh
um
content but we spent two hours
i think it's like
i think
i know what you're doing yeah and also i
had some
control problems so true
and co-op has its own you know perks
[Music]
yeah
it's just the controls it's the controls
and the ping and obviously the ping
because we played for remote control you
know yeah
wow
[Music]
yeah
thank you very much
oh you're welcome house house with a
lovely
oh yeah basically extra stuff if you
want to do it
yes we're now officially married ah gasp
gasp let gasp
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
such a good swimmer
what are we gonna call our goose babies
um
i don't know any ideas
[Music]
oh that's perfect everything lines up so
nicely in the hollow toady household
yeah
everything hey wanna grab some drinks
[Music]
don't drink the pond water in reality
it's not good for you guys it's only
good for birds oh well you guys are
chickens i guess um it's probably fine
i'm a bird it's fine for me yeah
so guys
do you
remember
are you
properly streaming
animal everyday are you
i put up the thumbnail on the on the
screen
oh okay okay days ago we uploaded on my
channel and uh cover an english cover of
animal so i hope you're listening to it
please listen to it every day five times
at least
to make the honk gods happy
so please listen to anime yeah hong kong
hong kong
honk to listen to animals
yay
[Applause]
thank you
for streaming with me and for finishing
the game with me and for doing animal
with me wow
so we should do something else oh my god
yeah yeah yeah i have a lot of fun we're
gonna plan a cool uh a
song cover on leina's channel right yes
yes so please do look forward to it
i'm looking forward to it i want to sing
more we'll playing it yeah yeah
thank you guys for watching thank you
for watching
i hope you guys enjoyed it sorry for the
scuff in the beginning oh it turned out
to be fine later on so
no um hard feelings guys
yes
yeah
yeah let's go do some
private time stuff behind the curtains
[Laughter]
so soon
yeah but we can't play healthy we can't
let them see you no it's embarrassing
yeah
spicy i hope everybody else has a spicy
evening too
have a spicy day everybody
enjoy enjoy
[Music]
[Laughter]
and uh we in german we say
it's liberty
[Music]
lena teach me indonesian soon okay
okay yeah of course okay let's go
uh but i also want to say uh today is
sunday um but i think guys i'm taking
tomorrow off
uh and then schedule will probably come
out
later on monday
we will see please wait please be
patient okay thank you everybody
anything you want to say dana at the end
stream animals
[Applause]
and subscribe to naina channel do it do
it do it do it do it do it do it
she's a great streamer and and she's uh
she she's she's lovely she's cute she's
funny she's spicy what are you waiting
for let's go
[Music]
bye
so
[Music]
you