first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
the great Wanderer
[Music]
till I'm reaching out to you
retrospective
[Music]
don't tell me why
are you
sleep talking breath
[Music]
[Applause]
hinatori
[Music]
heart Challenger
Sparks
[Applause]
[Music]
favorite night
smells like me
thank you
[Music]
do you
know Play It Again
[Music]
please
first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
a great Wanderer
[Music]
retrospective
[Applause]
hello
oh my God welcome to my karaoke stream
where I can you even call it karaoke
when it's my own songs and it's a
release party
yay we're having a party oh my god let's
go we're having a party because my album
release that's good look at this hey hey
in case you missed it wait let me put
some bgm on while we're doing oh Evan I
have a good idea from PGM
one second
all right
Sparks midnight version remix
Oh What A vibe what a bob
do you mind I was just streaming your
album I'm busy streaming your album can
you dance
um
yeah how you doing
this is gonna be awesome this is gonna
be fun I'm gonna be singing all my old
songs and all my new songs and so all of
my songs
and maybe you'll get a little sneak peek
to the
mysterious remix that you get if you buy
the physical version of my album that's
right that's right there is a physical
version uh now right now you can already
listen to the digital version on Spotify
and Amazon music and apple music and
iTunes
Etc
um but if you pre-order the physical
version link is in the description then
there will be an extra track that is
currently in the making and yesterday I
received the draft it's gonna be is he
is written as Sparks dark remix number
11.
um but it's actually a metal remix
right now we're listening to a Lo-Fi
remix of Sparks but can you imagine
Sparks as a metal remix you want to hear
that don't joke
oh and right before
um here one second
right before this stream I uh just
released a teaser do you want to see it
again here let's let's watch it really
quickly
might be loud in the first second
I'll turn it down
oh no it's fine oh too big
[Music]
yes so
tomorrow
the MV is releasing at this same time uh
minus 40 minutes
at 5 PM my time will be the release of
the music video the full music video yay
yay for pineapple yes yes yes yes there
will be
um some kind of a music video for all of
the songs
on the album
um but some are more
[Music]
um
some in some of them I put a higher
budget done into others
Musical videos
[Music]
okay
um you know I will I will hold you on
your tippy toes and start with songs
that I released already
and also I was thinking for the new
songs we can look at the lyrics together
while I'm singing them
um because I'm not sure are there even
any official lyrics out there already on
not official but like even unofficial
because I was looking one or two songs
up and I couldn't find them maybe we
just look at my own together
there's someone genius oh okay okay who
who puts those on there
whose job is that
I'm curious
but we probably don't know
okay but you know totally lyrics You
Should Know by Heart by now so I'm not
showing those
actually the sixth song of the album
let me know if there's any audio issues
or delays so there shouldn't be but
um let's go
[Music]
I haven't sung this in a while
thank you
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
[Music]
foreign
yeah
[Music]
I've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
if I go wrong what awaits me
could you tell me please
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
mean
[Music]
luminance
Valentino
my first ever
original song
many many
memories are intertwined with this one
and it's still such a classic I'm really
happy like how this song has you know
people remember it people know it people
like it people cherish it as much as I
do yeah and and because it was you know
my first OG song but also the the song I
performed as my first ever 3D
performance in the third Festival
it's like oh
so man so many memories Thanks for the
Memories even though they were pretty
great yeah
yeah
I've always loved it for its epicness
and you know go to son who wrote this
song has made uh two appearances in in
the new songs too uh so the hinotoni
Creator
created uh also worked on
um love rush and retrospective that many
many guys and peoples and girls love
very much yeah yeah and he's working on
the Sparks dark remix yeah
it's fun to sing and I'm like so used to
singing it and I still
um stumbled over lyrics twice did you
hear it
the lyrics you know I'm just really used
to singing it you know it doesn't matter
what the lyrics are but I'm just really
used to singing it and I was kind of
hyped up so because of the hype I
stumbled over it
I saw in the comments saying no delays
so everything's cool or bad
well then
ah we shall continue with
my second original song If you look on
the right side it's heart Challenger
number seven of the album mm-hmm
let me just bring out the lyrics
[Music]
hot Challenger lyrics this song
if you remember was
kind of
um for Cali
ah this song
yeah
and then she ignored its existence for
the longest time funny funny funny
yeah
yeah yeah
and bring out your towels if you have
one around to swing it during the chorus
in a circular motion above your head
like a like a helicopter okay you know
what to do if you've been to dukumi a
quinoa concert for example all right
bring out those towels bring out those
towels let's go
um
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
please
oh hey
wow
yes
[Music]
that is
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
I need to tell you that I love you
through and through
[Music]
there's no one else in this world that I
would trade for you
well it's okay
[Music]
thank you again
go
wow
hey
[Music]
I cut it off there because I don't want
it to play the next song
[Laughter]
[Applause]
the Bliss heart Challenger oh all the
memories
[Music]
this is like you know I know many people
uh
because it's really cutesy but like I
really for myself
wanted to have a song like this because
I love cutesy songs you know
you know it was so fun
with trumpets is heart Challenger so
much and remember the memes the trumpet
memes when the heart Challenger came out
[Laughter]
um good stuff
a trumpets we love the trumpets
and yeah there was this whole thing oh
yeah the the jokes about the name of
heart Challenger uh love conqueror what
love conqueror
what else was there the other day I
heard a really negative one love
Destroyer or so
hard Clapper
hard container
hard monitor
cardiac contender
oh my God
this is so funny ah yeah back at the
time because of the music video I I had
all these cute illustrations that I was
hi nerissa I was changing my profile
picture to with these cute hairstyles
remember
yeah the music video actually like after
hinoki did so well I thought okay let's
put a lot of budget into the music video
um and so there's a lot of like 3D
elements in the music video so I really
really love the music video there's so
much
so much work put into that that one also
because Mama Loni
um back then she was like Unstoppable
and you know she would draw so much so
much for this like oh my God
she took so much time out of her days
to give me as many illustrations as
possible for this um music video
normally normally it doesn't go quite
like that like
yeah but she was so sweet so helpful and
with her help I was able to create them
the kill test most ideal best cutesy
music video ever and I still love it so
much yeah
and it has this whole story that I came
up with too yeah with Wawa first like
noticing oh it's time Valentine's Day is
coming up and then
and um uh like getting like writing
lyrics and writing a letter and then
preparing some sweets chocolate CR like
in the baking at home and then trying
out different hairstyles and then
getting ready and then meeting her Kalia
pomori the lady who's evading me at the
time and yeah giving her the chocolates
and you see the scene where the hands
are both on the screen and then
everybody was like oh that's Kelly's
hands oh oh that's what everybody
realized oh
[Music]
memories man
when I was at her place went off collab
and I'm like oh did you listen to my new
song
yeah
but Kelly Kelly has been up to date with
my current musical Adventures even
though they're not
um dedicated to her but
laughs
those
um oblivious days are over
I even sent her the Sparks remix
um and she said I quote
may I quote
said bro this is something I'd Loop
unironically slaps
mm-hmm
yeah I was going crazy over it bro I am
dude now I'm bro
anyway it's okay yeah yeah it's okay
shouldn't say dog no
okay next to my third original song
what was it what was my third original
song tell me tell me what was it
um
because I don't know at all no no I have
no idea
[Music]
oh it's playing right now but the wrong
version
spocks
spies let's go
it's been a while
oh yeah
are we the Sparks outfit's still cute
hi hi
lying down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do hard to tell what's wrong
what's right yes or no don't know don't
know what to do oh the storm hits hard
and you're losing the way just take a
chance and dance in the rain cause you
got the key if you didn't forget it at
home don't forget don't forget what I
said and get out of your head life is
only what you make it you're gonna be
okay
go ahead and do it do it
everybody
because
[Music]
it's going so fast
get out of your head life is only what
you make it you're gonna be okay
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
[Music]
even when the flames
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way so don't be afraid
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
fire today
[Music]
thank you
man
Sparks is just like
wow I think I think Sparks
um kind of like gave me this push
and elevated my
but you call it music career
um
and it I think it helped uh make people
pay attention to my music a bit more
yeah yeah it sparked my music career a
little bit and it was the start of me
singing English songs because like up
until then I felt more comfortable
singing Japanese songs but I thought
well
[Music]
I should give it a try hmm
and Kira gave me the confidence
really with
some really fun lyrics a fun song and a
good mix of my vocals
yeah so I have so much to thank
uh took Kita cool since then has been
such a supportive music Creator to me
and yeah I I I don't know we've had
Sparks uh I feel like
I would have would have
still been creating like various J poppy
songs which is fine too
um but it made me experiment a bit more
here and there
and it it also just did so well which
helped me for future music uh production
and yeah yeah I'm just so happy that
Sparks did so well it meant a lot to me
um
ah opened my horizons a little bit Yeah
Yeah
um
[Music]
light a spark in kiwawa's music career
um
yeah so big thanks Kira
don't know if you're listening but yeah
and spikes I performed spikes in the
fourth Fest Fourth Fest no not forfeit
yeah
right in four effects I performed do you
the third first I performed hirotori
young concert I perform Sparks yeah
yeah because I thought man you know this
the song isn't so new anymore but I
think it deserves to have its Spotlight
in front of a big audience hmm
right
yeah
I love I love all my songs and they all
mean a lot to me and they all have like
special
special memories
um but yeah Sparks really popped off and
I'll be forever grateful for that um
yeah
all right after Sparks
which baby was born next it was
FIFA naito
favorite night so with fever night I
really experimented hard
because oh this was because uh uh
hinotoni had its one year anniversary
and for the one year anniversary I had
free remixes made
and one of them was a synthwave remix by
astrophysics who I only knew from you
know some of uh their other works and I
was like I kind of want to hear him do a
remix of and then that turned out so
good that I was and you guys really
loved it so I was like hmm people really
like synthwave maybe I should try making
a something with astrophysics a mix of
synthwave with like retro Vibes that uh
I'm um there's like a couple of songs
that I heard before that were kind of
like that and I
um wanted something like that and uh
yeah I together with astrophysics we
created
um something that to me is honestly a
huge pop and such a Vibe and nighttime
car rides if I had a car would be
blasting this
let's see where's my
where's my lyrics oh
okay here it is
fourth original song favorite nine and
hi hi oh yeah muscle cars let's go
I love the choreo to this too
I'm tired of the same song every day
like it's on repeat I need a risky
breakdown oh honey the night is calling
don't need a steady simple Melody can
you make it all original
take me away like it's just the two of
us
do you feel the music baby
meet me underneath the strong light come
alive move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight give me
that please get me dancing
[Applause]
soundtrack
is this a muscle car
so good
lately I'm dancing alone
so robotics so emotionless but then I
see you ooh a crust a dance floor so now
honey follow me I need a feeling
I'll do something to keep me up all
night
Don't Look Away now it's just the two of
us I'm ready until you feel the music
baby
underneath
[Music]
I don't need no drinks tonight give me
that please get me dancing feel it
rashes
[Music]
I don't need no drinks tonight give me
that please get me dancing
[Applause]
baby can we dance until the day like
crazy about the sound I'm making with
you
wow
[Music]
spilled some water yay
yay wow oh some of the parts of the song
because of
certain lines Keys uh are a bit hard for
me to sing
but I still love it so much such a Vibe
and the instrumentals oh my God
instrumentals
oh my God
yeah
my favorites I thought really oh I'm so
happy to hear that
It's A Hard song I would say but God is
good yeah cause like certain lines
they're like kind of monotone like baby
baby it's it's kind of hard for me to
sing and uh
uh give me that beat get me dancing I
Don't Need No drinks online give me that
please get me dancing for some reason
some parts like are a bit difficult for
me to sing but they don't quite match my
voice probably like I don't know what it
is
yeah but I also really love the wrap
because the rhythm of the rap is so much
fun to me yeah the speech the Temple of
it
um
the Corey of fibonaccess ran through my
head oh I had a swaying and the hip the
hip sways yeah it's so fun I love
dancing fever night I wanna
I wanna say I want to sing and dance it
again I wanna sing and dance all of my
songs actually yeah because my first
five all have a choreo
um because I had time to one by one make
choreos to it
and then pineapple has a choreo already
and now I'm working on the sleep talking
choreo
and I'm thinking lovers could get a
choreo and the great Wanderer too and
for retrospective in my mind if I ever
perform it somehow in 3D I don't think
it needs a choreo really I want to
perform that with like a guitar prop in
my hands I I was like low-key already
we're very high key already imagining it
in my brain
today when I was blasting the album on
my TV it sounds very different you guys
gotta try it in case you haven't yet but
hearing it from different outputs sound
makes it sound very different like I
listened to it on my headphones and also
on TVs big TV speakers
very different Acoustics and both are
really really nice if you listen to it
on headphones I I need you to listen to
it in really really high volume
you need to blast that [\h__\h] go big or go
home okay
um
yeah yeah the it just picks up different
things it enhances different things
I know
[Applause]
it's like a different way of enjoying
the songs I feel like especially the
great Wanderer you have to listen to it
in a car or somewhere that like you can
you know turn up the bass
[Laughter]
the great Wanderer
yeah oh
man music is
music is porn basically
music is
porn
wouldn't you agree
let's be honest let's be honest okay
okay I don't have do you lyrics on my
folder for some reason do you lyrics
when you have to look up your own lyrics
but honestly I think it's so cool like I
said this the other day but it's so like
surreal to be able to look up my
original songs lyrics and they're just
there on several uh
you guys gotta keep up we're already on
the next topic don't stop panicking yeah
uh the scene on several in lyric
websites it's so cool
oh man
it's so real so so real and so real
I got it and this oh my God it even I
don't even have to go on the website
it's just there
I love it when when Google just puts it
there you know what I mean in the search
and the first like right right above all
the links it just puts it right there on
top so I don't have to go to all these
ads
banned websites [\h__\h] those
um
okay I'm gonna chill
we're all ready I do you my fifth
original song that came out last year
already quite a while ago huh almost one
year anniversary of do you
um release 2022 and after doing
I haven't released a single in a while
because after a little bit I started
working on an album I thought okay okay
I will focus on an album now
um
until do you it was like quite maybe two
songs per or two two and a half songs
per year
I guess more or less you know Tony was
still 20 20 right he not told me it was
20 20. and then
heart Challenger was early 2021
Sparks was summer 20 no yeah summer 2021
then sometime past
and spring 2022 was fever 9.
and summer 2022 was do you
yeah so kind of two songs per year and
and the first year was in the full year
so 2020 2020 was Justin
um damn so it was a good Pace but then I
paste it down
because I I needed to plan the album
um
foreign
okay let's go guys
[Music]
this is not even instrumental
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
this wasn't the instrumental where's my
that's just the normal
for sure that's the one
I don't want to stop it yet playing
Russian roulette yeah boys
[Music]
and you let me go
love hate all the same if you know play
the game
no I can fight the feeling and I won't
try all the same if you don't know play
the game baby you'll decide if you want
me to shout it out right now
[Music]
don't ever let yourself falling you got
it cause life's just like a toxin the
way pain is so common your problem I can
solve it I'm just a full in love know
that there's more than a crash so you
can't save me I'm in too deep and I love
the rush yeah I just can't resist you
your eyes are like a spell that I can
break through and let you scare me but I
don't know baby
eating yellow fresh right I was gonna
say
love hey it's all the same if you know
play the game
[Music]
all the same if you know play it again
baby you'll decide if you want me then
shout it out right now
the game I can't complain
[Music]
s
[Applause]
got me Breathless
[Music]
I can't complain
do you do you say you lose
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
oh
this song
this song is so difficult
it was it was like oh my God recording
it was so difficult because it has so
many backup vocals um
you know this also comes from the Kira
team and
spikes was like
still
okay in terms of backup vocals and
harmonies but do you
has so many and a lot of them a lot of
the lyrics are also overlapping so it's
not I say this again and again before
but it's not really mean to be sung
Alone by one person
is
it just took me so much time to record
this in the first place but it was fun
and it just when it all comes together
it's just so
um
I just oh
it just feels so
well produced you know what I mean
it just feels like such a high quality
production thanks to that um
thank you
and do you
after Sparks you know Sparks was not
quite K-pop just yet and I wanted to go
in there I wanted to do K-pop Style
music which in the end is just
more or less trying to uh imitate
western music pop music
but yeah I like that in between you know
um
and we went all in with doing yeah both
for the MV and and the song
I love the music video so much because
we played around with you know I could
only use my one 3D outfit my default and
I thought it wouldn't fit so I'm really
proud with what I came up with you know
especially because like the two kiadas
that are opposite monotone color is more
or less dancing with each other
interacting with each other are like
elevating the music video
because you know two is better than one
and makes it more interesting and it
works with the whole Aesthetics and also
it works because the song already has so
many overlapping lyrics
and ah I just oh my God there's so many
things that just worked out so well
right
um
foreign
color versions I wish I could like just
put them on but it was kind of like a
Envy only thing because we had to edit
the model and I can't just like simply
do that
um for streaming use
um the fan is still yeah oh just
actually let me show you here here's
some fan art appreciation
um even though do you is already a while
ago and it sparked a lot of fan art
just the other day
gums ful made this thing perfect perfect
those two key Wawas
yeah
it's so cute I love the art style
white and black chihuahua which one do
you guys prefer which one you like more
hmm
if you had to pick one
husky
o
orange Kiara why not both black Blanco
Blanco Bianco
one above both orange
origin between these though
yellow ostrich
stop
I was never yellow before I'm just
Orange
sorry Insider meme for daily kfp
Watchers only
yeah guys we have breached the new songs
oh my god I've had uh karaoke versions
prepared you know they're just they're
different from instrumentals because
they have like some backup vocals and
harmonies in there
just for my usage
but it's nice to listen to those two
because you can hear that you can hear
the
um Harmony is so beautifully
okay so we'll start with the one that's
releasing a music video tomorrow but
also we're gonna be looking at the
looks I think uh if you want guys
[Music]
the official lyrics
horse key
mascara
so do you
um
do you prepared me for pineapple and
sleep talking because they also had a
[\h__\h] ton of backup vocals and stuff
uh quite
um
lengthy to record that stuff but also
very very beautiful at the end to put it
all together so I really really love it
[Music]
um
it's this one
here I have prepared
the lyrics for you guys
so you can look with me Yahoo
and then if you want you can transcribe
it
if you're if you want these are the
official ones
am I ready am I ready I'm a bit nervous
about singing all these new songs
because uh especially for retrospective
I noticed
it's difficult
singing it live
pineapples is fun so I'm gonna have fun
let's go pineapple hey
that love is just like a dream
feel like a mountain from the hit love
it feels so sorry
oh yeah oh just like that you know just
how it goes
don't ever stop on you already know
you're just so sweet my baby
yeah
I've got no worries
[Music]
I wanna try it
one two one two three
[Music]
Don't Think Twice
wanna try it now
[Music]
one two one two three
I'm going one two one two three
[Music]
oh bye
love is so so much
you know after sleep talking
pineapple was the second song to be done
um right you know first of all the
instrumentals and then also the mix and
everything so those two songs were done
so early
um which is also kind of the reason why
I decided to plan ahead to
um you know go with those as my biggest
promoted songs personally I know
everybody has like different likes
but I also had to start somewhere I had
to make choreo pineapple was there and
ready and I love them I just had those
ready like months ago while for example
the great Wanderer
was finished
uh maybe two weeks ago oh like with the
mix
and retrospective and love brush also
very very recently yeah
and I was quite stressed out about those
three songs because everything oh yeah
I ended up being very last minute I
honestly would have liked to have a bit
more time
for all three of those I feel like I
could have
um still I'm out with the great wonder
I'm honestly like really happy
um because Johnny even though this
wasn't planned but Johnny ended up
mixing it
uh in in like one day
uh like you just like put all of this
effort into it because I asked for his
help because we were on a deadline and I
needed this to be nailed immediately and
I really trust Johnny's mixing
um yeah yeah he just chill you know this
takes a it's quite the process you know
he tuned and mixed it in one day
and
they even recorded some extra backup
vocals together because Johnny and Moni
were like together at the time when I
was struggling with this
yeah and
uh for
for
love rush and retrospective
um yeah I I I wish I had more time for
those to be very honest with you
but
my time was cut short
it had to had to be done but honestly
that's why I was a bit worried about you
guys hearing a bug you guys really seem
to like it so I'm really relieved
um
I do personally think it could be even
better
in terms of like mix vocal mix
but
you guys like it so I'm happy yeah on
the other side pineapple and sleep
talking where the instrumentals were
done so early so I could record really
early and we had lots of time to mix but
even that was done month the months ago
like three four months ago
I was sitting on those two songs Forever
mm-hmm
I can see that since you know the behind
the scenes but to us it sounds great
thank you
let's move on to love Rush
um pineapple was like you know made to
be a summer box love Rush was made to be
um a kind of a sequel English sequel to
Heart Challenger and
um it's kind of inspired by that Dragon
made opening singers songs fana
so in case you heard those before maybe
you can feel those vibes yeah let's um
bring out the lyrics
[Music]
to look really cute on grave paper
let's go
ninjas
hard to read well it's so easy for me to
read also it looks stylish so
let's go
[Music]
I don't know how to make it lighter
dark clothes
[Music]
it's been a while since we started don't
surfing would have felt fine now a
certain feeling sinking in but yet we
we're growing stronger as time goes on
and I can think of ever ever letting go
wait
sorry can I check one thing
I actually had um
I had some some updates made to the
I don't know if I just want to make 100
sure that this is the right one oh yeah
I think so
probably
just double checking is this the new one
oh yeah it is okay nevermind
sorry
all good
reach down
[Music]
been a while since we started down to
think what I felt fine now a certain
feeling sinking in but yet we we're
growing stronger as time goes on and I
can think of ever ever letting go every
night I dream of feeling smile got you
tied up in my heart I remember it's a
worth the while till now from the start
beside you I'm free and I'm home finally
we're alive
[Music]
fade away
and you see me
[Music]
every moment I'm waiting patiently for
new surprise A Perfect Memory will keep
it's always making us Bolder though
we're getting older these times
every night I dream of you and smile got
you tied up in my heart I remember
[Music]
Fly Away
without you I'd be undone you gave me
what I dream of you're my love rush I
can't give up
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
every every day
[Applause]
[Music]
right here won't fade away I'm
don't say goodbye even in the dark times
[Music]
foreign
yeah lots of beautiful piano and other
beautiful emotional instruments here
um so I'm like so happy with the
instrumentals and also the Melodies and
yeah the lyrics turned out so cute
basically I asked Moni to write lyrics
that
um are a love letter A thank you from me
to you guys
and for you know the support you've
given me so far and yeah hoping for this
journey to continue and yeah just me
saying thank you showing my gratitude
it's a thank you I say love letter but
you know it's it's sure you can say love
letter but it's you know a thank you to
you guys
hmm for supporting me even in the dark
times you know even when when it doesn't
seem so bright sometimes yeah and I I
really love the lyrics man
it's just so real and so perfect
um
that's why I kind of wanted to show you
the lyrics too so you can really feel it
and immerse yourself in the lyrics while
I'm singing them
um
[Music]
I'm making us Bolder though we're
getting older I love those rhymes
I love that part too I love the
harmonies of the bridge no no
yeah the lyrics are perfect
it's such a cute song
um
thank you guys thank you I'm so happy
you like it next it comes like probably
a big favorite
a big crowd favorite
foreign
[Music]
have some things to say about this one
but I'll say it after I sing it
tgw people are yeah abbreviating it with
tgw it's like confusing me I'm like well
I need a second to register what you
guys are talking about when you write
tgw
TGF TGF no ttw tgw the great Wonderwall
foreign
I think you know
it came together
so preferably
so yeah let's sing it
for the first time live
oh wait let me start that louder
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
did I lose my way I can see the day when
I can reach you again
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
fall back
to you
[Music]
it will lead me back till you see me
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
I almost want to sing it again because
it's so epic
yeah
yeah okay that was The Wanderer the
great Wanderer um
uh kind of an idiom Simple Song
love this song Best Song oh my God oh my
God hard song for life actually no like
I struggle more with others this is fun
um it's like in a really comfortable key
for me too
um and like
you know the the verses are song kind of
calmly
until the pre-chorus so only the verses
are kind of calm so it's like if I would
chill
um
I saw someone asking where's the Simi
yeah that was kind of supposed to be in
there but I guess it kind of got cut
it was supposed to be I think I ended up
not working
no I did record it but it was cut I also
think it's better without though
um I think it was a bit unnecessary it
goes like
okay
[Music]
you know what I mean
it's like a little little scream
I don't know if they forgot it um I
think it's fine without but I guess now
it's not there so I should
get rid of that
doesn't hit as hard with it right I
think I think so too it was better to
give it some space and get rid of the
um it's a little silly yeah yeah finger
spinner was out
I recorded it though I think I remember
yeah so in case you haven't noticed the
song is about you know being lonely
about being isolated and especially this
one this one's a little bit like
immersed and lore and serious about how
a YouTuber would feel if
if bituber
if YouTuber really stuck in their own
Dimension
um but even without that thought uh I
still there's definitely a lot of
moments where within whole life I felt
quite lonely and isolated and this song
is kind of about
partially that feeling but also a little
bit uh dramatizing the whole oh V2 bar
I'm I'm in on the internet and I'm 2D
I'm virtual I'm not real I can't touch
you oh my God lonely
so it has like two sides to it the the
dramatized exaggerated like you know
what if but also the realistic
kiwama feelings of loneliness
is now
yeah and I think a lot of people can
also relate to this
um
yeah yeah it's really really
Beautiful lyrics I think
put onto a really epic sounding track
um it's actually
for the track itself
I originally the producer of this is
Martin I asked him to create something I
think I gave the instruction to create
something epic but I didn't really know
exactly what
and at first actually the first draft I
got
was something completely different
completely different genre more like uh
ordaines which song was that something
like cutesy anime opening-ish
maybe it was even her first song
um something like that
I was like that's really cute I really
like it but it's not what I need because
I feel like this is already covered by
maybe love rush or so yeah gate open
start it has like gate open start Vibes
which I really like too but I was like
No I
I don't think I need this in my album
not for the new songs I want something
else but I can't I don't know what so I
said can you try again and then later he
came back with the demo for this
um and then I was like hmm
this is also
maybe not quite what I envisioned but
it's very interesting it's very
different
so I guess I'll take it but I was first
not quite sure about it yet and I think
the singing melody was partially also
still very different from what it is now
and money actually ended up creating a
little bit of a different Melody for
some parts
um because I thought
some parts could sound better with a
different singing Melody could flow
better so a lot of changes have been
made to the song
um
and yeah in the end like now I'm very
confident about it
it took a while to get there
uh I was quite picky
with like also the mix uh you know this
is the one that was made in one day
cyberpunk Vibes thank you great call
thank you I think so too
and yeah this feels incredibly polished
yeah I'm glad uh it turned out the way
you did it was kind of unexpected like
the first time I heard it I was I was
still like it was hard to imagine what
it would be like in the end
but I'm so so happy with how it did turn
out in the end
[Music]
yeah you guys really love it so that
makes me really happy it's so epic oh my
God like it wasn't even created by my
Kira Johnny Money Team it was produced
created mostly by Martin but they were
after they mixed it they were like so so
much vibing to it they became big fans
of the song Too
twerking to it endlessly
yeah that's the great Wanderer I'm
looking forward to singing it many times
in the future because it's a really
chill song maybe I'll sing it again at
the end of the karaoke
yeah ah
ah please please anybody who has a car
listen to this in your car at night
um
and it's one of the more emotional songs
too
so it has
um
quite the deep meaning and connection to
me
yes oh
next another I mean every song is
somebody's favorite which I'm so happy
about I really didn't expect that
honestly
let's go to the next one
next is retrospective I don't read that
those are some notes wait what was that
actually
oh yeah yeah you're gonna screencap that
and you're gonna read free with
it's it's some notes
um money wrote
oh look it's embarrassing
and what did that say
s
hey do you want to read it this is uh
you know because money wrote It's kind
of outdated some things are not filled
in okay here let's go uh oh it's even
cut off you couldn't even read the whole
thing without my help
oh God yeah okay this is the explanation
to the song I guess too uh retrospective
since the singer can be seen as talking
to themselves in this song with lines
about being unable to do things that
undo things regrets and feelings of the
future self-doubt all tied into one you
in the song is actually referring to the
singer themselves me it's almost as if
the singer is talking to themselves
asking for reassurance from a person who
will never give it to them
AKA themselves they will never receive
reassurance from themselves because they
don't believe in The Sims either oh [\h__\h]
yeah
um oh that was sad
yeah this song is
yeah let's let's go let's have fun
this one's so hard for me to sing so
please forgive me
um
I'll probably not be able to nail it
thank you the lyrics I think and also I
guess the genre are a big reason many of
you guys like it so much you all are as
sad and depressed as me I can I
go I see you
let's twerk sadly together to the song
shall we
[Applause]
oh baby I'm looking at what remains I
couldn't tell you the same I guess
that's a life
if you couldn't tell bye now I'm
hopelessly waiting begging all night to
break through stuck in an endless
[Music]
[Applause]
that's the best
[Music]
every night
[Applause]
[Music]
concern is filling up your lies once
again now I'm over broken out save me if
I can let it go
inside
it keeps sitting away at me every day
asking why
[Music]
I can't redo the past and present calls
me the truth
[Music]
hooked up
and I try to change me but my mind can't
just erase me any more than I have
already
done and looking back and ready to admit
that it was on me
[Music]
the thou puts out my love
I I can't be sure of who I am or when
I'm alive
[Music]
you
know
[Music]
I missed that one oopsie
where was that
yeah yeah some parts were a little bit
raw meh but I
yeah the chorus is like really like I
like belting it but there's like this
like sudden key change that's why I I
don't know if you noticed but I had this
line
and yeah you know this line the lower
lines I had them added to the karaoke
version
yeah
oh you know what I think
no never mind that wasn't the song
what's that I don't think so
but
do you want to hear the the beautiful
harmonies you can hear them a bit here
[Music]
love you
that's the harmonies
[Music]
I think there's another Harmony
somewhere down there but this is the one
I remember
you guys like this one so much huh the
funny thing is it was supposed to be
kind of like a Paramore
ink and coat uh song but
this song
had a hundred percent different
uh Melody singing Melody when I first
got it and I was like because you know
gojo-san made it and I love the songs
kojisans makes and he's like really good
with instrumentals but when I listen to
the to the guide Melody I thought this
feels like kind of like typically
Japanese production
and since I'm gonna sing an English over
it I thought
I think I think the singing Melody
should be very different hmm
but I was kind of like what do I do I I
personally don't trust myself with
making um
making a singing Melody on my own it's
very difficult so I discussed with Moni
I sent her the song and I said you know
I really love the instrumentals but I'm
not sure about the guide Melody and
she helped me uh with Johnny create a
completely overhauled new singing Melody
that flows better with English lyrics
and because of that it's suddenly got
this dramatic Evanescence Vibe I don't
know if you can hear it but to me now it
sounds like Evanescence
yeah it was very different before but
anyway I don't even remember it anymore
oh thank you was that Marissa
that was my first thought let's go
I think it really needed that and thanks
to that I'm I I was so happy with it I
was like surprised like oh this is this
is Evanescence but you know what cool
not what I was going for but pretty
similar and I love it no can't wake up
it is honestly
so well to put that in there penguin
my
life
can't wake up
wake me up
save me I don't know but
I can't wake up I can't read to wake me
up the past and present tells me the
truth saved me the talent me calls me to
truth it's like to save me
can't hear it now let's go mess up
incoming oh my God I want to hear that
um
[Laughter]
yeah
future remix with Kelly oh oh didn't she
say this was her favorite anyway
I would like to hear her emotional edgy
dramatic remix and not remix rap to this
oh
wait next time I have an off collab with
her let's see what we can do
[Music]
yo let's go that sounds like fun
all right all right all right so yeah
this this song had a lot of flag let's
say plastic surgery done
but it was so worth it it paid off for
sure
all right
y
there's another one
which if you remember from the stories I
told you
it was not written for me but I was
shown it to me as demo tape just as an
example of what they could make
um and and then I was like
I want this though I want this this is
this I need this in my life I need this
to be mine and I was like no it's mine
it's F mine now yep
[Music]
[Laughter]
and this is the one I showed to laplus
and at after hour after because I
thought it was quite similar to do you
in terms of Vibes but it's a bit more
mature
so enjoy
uh where is it which one is it
it's been a long day
will it call me you got me sleep talking
sleep talking
talk to me bye I'm laid up already hit
midnight
ah convince myself I'm doing all right
but you know taking one step taking one
back when you text me saying no way
ain't no fair no fair no fair your eyes
they telling me come here now I can't
wear your body got me talking breath
unless you got me one thing oh baby
don't you know oh got me I'm hooked
and you and I just can't forget but you
got me stressed I'm just running in
[Music]
talking always
hey mister you got me all day I'm sleepy
in my dreams I just hear your voice I
ain't got a choice like that baby you
might never know hey don't you leave me
alone I'm waiting head on the phone so
baby you're just gonna make a call and
I'll know if you really all in it give
it to me now boy your body ain't got me
talking breath but you got me wanting oh
baby don't you know got me I'm hooked to
go I'm breathing you and I just can't
forget but you got me stressed I'm just
running in
[Music]
in my dreams
sleep talking in the night yes
[Music]
you're gonna make me sleep talk every
day hello
[Music]
don't pretend
hello
baby who are you talking to
oh it's the moment I can't escape I'm
breathless I I can't deny oh it's you
who made me this
[Music]
in my dreams
sleep talking in the night asleep
talking oh that's right yeah
[Music]
hey
ah I want to sing a song like a million
times man uh I just love it so much I
just love it first listen sleep tucking
I'm gonna get better at singing all
these songs live again and again
and then I'll mail them one day but I
think you'll notice probably that this
song also has like true look it's it's
tough singing it alone
but it's so fun I love the flow actually
I have a little treat for you guys
I want you to listen to something I'm
sure my team doesn't mind but you know
me and my team I call them Chihuahuas
Angels which is a Kira Moni and Johnny
my producers and lyric writers uh who
create who worked on like almost all of
this
um and we've been like you know
celebrating and vibing and they're like
my hype my hype girls and boys and I
love them I love them they're so fun and
and they hype me up and it's so
supportive and sweet and and they they
sent me something because they're also
so proud of the things we create
together so listen to this beautiful
acapella uh version where you can hear
all the beautiful harmonies and so on
together okay you want this I know you
want this
it's been a long day
will he call me yes your God may sleep
ducking Falcon sleep
[Music]
convince myself
talking in my dreams of sleep tucking
all these nights
[Applause]
that you got me all day I'm sleeping
yeah just like that baby you might never
know hey don't you leave me alone
[Music]
oh baby
you can make me sleep talk every day
[Music]
Just One Look dance so don't pretend
hello
baby who are you talking to oh it's the
moment I can escape
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
every day
I'm gonna cry because it's so amazing
right this makes you guys appreciate the
mix and the amount of like harmonies and
all that and back of vocals even more
right but you guys been saying in the
chat and I didn't even think about this
this is perfect for everybody who wants
to make a remix for it maybe I'll upload
it separately to motivate people
isn't that so beautiful right like this
is why I really really like trust them
this team of mine why was Angels they
are just so powerful yeah this is why I
say that I think the production value is
crazy Next Level isn't it so beautiful
did you hear all those sleep
sleep sleep
I think I recorded like three or four
different harmonies for just the sleep
play Parts
um
yeah there's so many at the house you
know so many oh my God there's so many
oh you're so beautiful even without any
real bead it was incredible right
yeah
it's just a gorgeous
um
I I asked him how how the [\h__\h] do you
even come up with so many like beautiful
harmonies and [\h__\h] you know they give me
the guides and I just recorded I'm not
I'm not the one who's coming up with
this
yeah it's Flawless may I throw you a
rules for that please go ahead it will
die within 24 hours
you like a one woman capable oh my God I
saw it in the Tweet yesterday uh or a
tweet or somewhere I think it was a
tweet and I was like that's
sung in a group of at least three people
and and yet I sing it along alone so I'm
like uh one woman K-pop group yes
oh my God I I want to sing all these
songs again and again and again oh man
it's just oh so good
isn't it so good hmm oh man
good stuff
it's so beautiful
ankle ankle and I do have one special
thing for you I'm I'm just doing this on
a whim because it flew me away yesterday
do you see here on the track list Sparks
dark remix number 11 CD exclusive track
now it's not done yet but I'm sure some
of you guys wanna maybe get an idea
maybe this will inspire you in case you
haven't is there anybody here who hasn't
bought a pre uh yoyakud
um reserved the the physical version in
that case let me have you listen to the
Sparks dark remix for five seconds or
maybe eight seconds or so and then and
then you'll know what's your info we're
still working on this this is a work in
progress but I thought it's absolutely a
shame
well it fits because I
think bonus track huh we can have a
bonus track how about a remix which song
well Hino totally already got so many
remixes
I feel like Spark's such a classic but
people love so much maybe for Sparks but
what kind of remix uh well you know
part of me was maybe just joking but I
thought
let's go in a very very very different
direction of what the song originally is
and to a metal remix in baby mad style
uh and I wasn't sure at all if it was
gonna sound good if it was gonna work
out but
wait let me let me find the the best
section to make you listen to
uh
that's so [\h__\h] good this is not
finished yet but wait
wait this this part maybe
um
you get like five seconds or so
uh what
oh yeah oh this is good
oh
wait wait wait wait
I will not spoil too much
um three two one
[Music]
isn't that insane
yeah
I was like what how is this how is this
fitting how this is actually working
how's that actually work with such a
cute
EDM song Whoa whoa
that's not finished but I'm thinking you
just heard that part right
um I'm thinking of adding
trying to add screamo like
[Music]
don't stop
away but I just need to learn how to do
screamo first oh stop don't stop I don't
know how but at those parts I want to
add screamo
how is it in the screamer
oh maybe like that
[Music]
no I'm I'm gonna work on it
mimic a motorcycle
um
don't stop don't stop like that
this is
yeah just a little draft for you guys to
hear I hope I won't get bonked for
letting you listen to the draft but I
think it's fine
yeah oh right there's uh uh in whole
star system one who's really good of
screamo hmm
yeah
but I want to do it I don't want to
commission someone else to do it I want
to do it but maybe I can ask for advice
I'm gonna do it don't stop Don't Stop
Don't Stop Don't Stop just go your own
way
I'll probably need like a day off uh
after I record that
but yeah I was freaking surprised by
this so I was thinking maybe in the
future if I ever bring out an AP or so
or an album again then
you know I still want to bring in some
variety some things I haven't tried
before and one of those things would
probably be a metal song
yeah yeah for this though I'm still like
you know you know how Google is making
this and you know how he always um
brings in the super dope guitar like he
has a guitar guy
Who records a real guitar guitar for uh
like Hino Tony
and retrospective Etc
um and so I was asking
do you perhaps
are you perhaps able of adding shamisen
to this I don't know if it will fit
I don't know if it will really be in
there in the end but his guitar guy can
also play shamisen apparently
which is like a
Japanese a guitar no nothing but
Japanese traditional guitar thingy and I
really love the sound of shamisan and
with that we'll get a bit closer to
Babymetal
so we're trying we're gonna try it yeah
we'll see we'll see we'll see
foreign
so much potential right
okay you guys want to hear uh
uncle right
and let's sing the great Wanderer
I think that is the most requested
[Music]
but you gotta promise me to turn up the
volume
and blast it in your stereo
or in your headphones
Encore Encore whole life e and core
hey
the great Wanderer
I screamed a little bit though
oh
let me drink an extra amount of water
okay
I want people to sing this
uh I want people to sing all out all
these new songs please I'm gonna send
all the karaoke versions to the hollow
Library members
and hope that's at least the en members
may be sing it and maybe it members
I want to hear Muna sing sleep talking
and I want to hear
um
good at saying pineapple I don't want to
hear
uh
ah I want to hear retrospective sung by
narissa
I want to hear
love Rush sung by
and I want to hear the great Wanderer
sung by
um
you know
maybe or Elena or anybody really
let's go
[Music]
passing by familiar Rose
the reason why
who I am you couldn't know
stuck in the ruins
[Music]
I'm in the absence
[Applause]
[Music]
before my eyes
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
of us
[Music]
before
you see me
[Music]
oh
no
t g w t g w
retro anchor
retrospective
[Music]
again I'm gonna try again it might not
get better though
[Laughter]
oh my God Echo
let's turn the echo off
basically you want an encore for
everything huh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't
I can't reduce
[Music]
foreign
calls me to truth
[Music]
wavering eyes
the thou puts out my love
can't show
of who I am
[Music]
don't tell me
to you
[Music]
okay okay okay
that was way better than the first time
I sang it
let's go yeah you know getting more
comfortable with singing at life
hey
thank you thank you you know I really
love this part because
like it suddenly overlaps like five
different harmonies
I sang alive
and alive and yeah so many different
harmonies I love it oh my God chat is
that again why yeah why why why why chat
wake up wake me up okay wake up
I can't live like me oh
hello
my
God oh yes
yes guys guys
[Music]
um are you sleeping
I maybe you should be asleep talking I
don't know
come back to me
I'm lonely
lonely I'm so lonely I have no body
I'm on my own
oh no that's basically the tgw lyrics
hi and welcome back
okay okay okay okay this has been fun
I'll do one more encoder and that will
be pineapple because that's the first
one I sang and it's gonna have an Envy
tonight
it's an exciting MV
so let's sing pineapple and then I'll
read some super chats for maximum an
hour maybe because I gotta get up really
early tomorrow for balder is good I have
the
waking up early rotation
oh
turn this time
um six a.m let's go
uh uh okay
pineapple
Papa pineapple pineapple pineapple is
no no I will be reading super chats but
um
for pineapple after I sing it now you're
not allowed to sing it to listen to it
anymore until the Envy comes out so that
you don't get you know
you know you you you should take a break
because I mean honestly I've listened to
pineapple so many times and I'm still
not sick of it but I think it's better
if you if you don't listen to it anymore
until MB just listen to your other songs
[Laughter]
get sick of it yet okay I mean I don't
think you can but you know
anyway
last all right
please everybody listen to my album on
Spotify Amazon music Apple music
Etc and maybe pre-order if you wanted
Sparks dark remix or just the physical
version in general to to
commemorate this occasion in links are
in the description
[Music]
it might actually arrive already in like
October or so so please support my album
my first ever albums
let's go
well everyone says that love is just
like a dream
feel like a mountain from the Heat
feels so Serene oh yeah oh just like
that you notice how it goes
don't ever stop on you already know
you're here
[Music]
I don't got no worries
[Applause]
[Music]
to me is
one two one two three
[Music]
Don't Think Twice
I'm calling one two
one two
three
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
back
one two one two three
[Music]
oh hey
yeah
thank you so much for listening guys I'm
so happy I'm so happy happy
my new first album point of view is
currently available to stream on many
streaming platforms if you want to show
support
please go and do it yeah
please listen to it lots lots lots lots
lots lots lots lots
and then tomorrow when the MB drops I
hope you guys can watch it many many
many many times
no not not related but makes me think of
matsura ayat too
yeah yeah
cause that's her nickname
[Music]
foreign
I need to go idle meeting
and then we read some chat
yeah
[Music]
oh my God
I'm so addicting I can't why did it
oh I will go to idle meeting and I'll be
right back okay and you guys just listen
to
um
and enjoy this one
while I'm while I'm away I'll be here
again
[Music]
foreign
let go
hear your voice
harmonies
[Music]
by heart
do you see me
[Music]
what's up
fake Chihuahua fan
oh
yeah okay
[Music]
no more singing aloud I'm going to read
super chats no matter what
a little bit only a little bit probably
not
um enough but a little bit I'll attempt
I'll tempted
[Music]
oh
wow
okay for my own Safety and Security
I should be playing something like this
instead
because there's no end to this otherwise
oh my God
[Music]
This is distracting too but you know
one question guys
[Music]
oh do you think it's necessary to have
four different builders get povs I don't
know man because it's 6 a.m for me and
kind of low-key thinking like
maybe not this time
no no
no oh my God it's like I don't know I
don't know if I'm sure I don't know how
dead I'll be
but
I don't know like last ideally we want
to fix what happened last time I'm going
to stay together a bit more
um
yeah
so then it should be even less necessary
but yeah
and I don't know
difficult
foreign
[Music]
do I ever know what I want to do
don't
[Music]
oh
oh oh that piano
[Music]
it's like taking a little bit different
kind of a rhythm I like it
[Music]
haven't listened to this remix in a
while
[Music]
and tell me where it needs to continue
reading I don't know help help
what can I do music is just so good I
told you music is porn
father's gained I have the the group one
yes the group one okay okay okay
[Music]
um
Super Chat reading or a bit
[Music]
okay
hey
[Music]
oh wow oh that part is so
gentle
oh
that's so gentle
it's like it's like
[Music]
like I'm falling into a big comfy bed in
in silk
uh bedspreads
whoa
I don't remember this remix it's not
done by like or commissioned or anything
by me but interestingly it's uh on my
you know on my topic like all the
generated by YouTube topic thingy
it's um the Sparks midnight version
remix
one of those
yeah yeah okay okay
[Laughter]
my plan is to sleep early today but
before that I have to cook so I can't
wait too long
but we'll get we'll get some stuff done
okay just a little bit just a little bit
okay here we go I'm reading these super
chats okay okay okay okay okay okay
good luck with that at this page all
right all right stop making fun of me
I'll go super speed you won't even be
able to hear it
just another case
announcement announcement although you
crashed me but it is still my honor that
have served forever dance is really an
earworm oh because of the freaking
helicopter yeah
um
it was not a helicopter I was Bamboozled
I was set up by the holograph team
to look stupid
they set me up
they put in the script
uh hey I bought this helicopter uh
online the other day and what do they
show a [\h__\h] glider or something like
that
what
unbelievable they want to make me look
stupid man
um
oh
yeah
also said it so I'm not the only one we
were both set up
um
hey you think it's maybe the joke is
that we don't know what it is
I don't know I don't know but yeah it's
it was like something that makes you
question what was just being said wait
did you just say helicopter what's going
on
am I being gaslit
did you voice the chicken no I didn't no
action
foreign
[Music]
it's not a helicopter
it is
what is it
I don't know
some glider I'm not
I think it's the thing that also shows
up in in that movie that I watched blue
Thermo
they it's basically a thing that can't
fly on its own
[Music]
it's a female can't fly on its own
because it has to be in the end in that
movie I learned about it yeah
um
you need you need another like airplane
thingy that like pulls it and then
they're connected with uh with some kind
of rope and then they can let go and
then the plane can fly on its own for
quite some time
um
either like that or there's also like
machines
that you know for when you want to just
practice gliding
they can like push push you up in the
air
I've learned all of that in that anime
movie Blue thermal was really nice
launch you yes yes
no
[Music]
yeah Skye thank you and your profile
pictures is that glider now too I love
it cute space wonderful thanks for the
pink ing yesterday was my third birthday
with you in KFC oh
we buy this is no looking forward to
another year with my one and only last
OSI and one and only and last oh [\h__\h]
I'm the last one standing what happened
with the others
this last because no one could ever tap
you for me so you'll stay my Oshi
forever
oh thank you so much and congratulations
on your birthday
yay
I'm happy for you I know it's stressful
to get older I feel it very much too but
uh the we get older we're growing what
was it
um
um here
[Music]
uh
uh we're growing stronger as time goes
on and and though we're getting older
these times will live forever on and on
yeah yeah yeah no I'm just uh quoting My
Own lyrics now love Rush lyrics hey
so let's grow old together kfp don't
leave me you're stuck with me okay I
love you happy Birthday
growing Boulder no growing older it's
making us Bolder though we're getting
older okay
[Music]
was uh followed up by even more oh my
God oh my God oh my God that in total is
I think at least the red super chat
actually let me give you a choo choo
ah
it didn't even look like that was uh
continuing but it does continue to me
you're just the cutest most relatable
most enjoyable internet person I'm an
internet person out there and you just
uh you inspire me and motivate me to do
things again and I try things I never
did before you also quite literally
saved my life from going to a lonely
hopeless uh miserable existence
[Music]
AKA
tgw and retrospective I was at a little
point when you debuted unhappy and not
able to help myself without you I
wouldn't have had the strength to turn
my life around you gave my cold lonely
dark World War oh you must love
retrospective than tgw
songs
life and light as the son of my world
that you became
[Music]
space wonderful are you here I know what
you do
yeah thank you so much for that my name
I want to do stuff for you and carefree
that's why I started drawing again doing
MMD and other stuff yo let's go I'm I'm
excited to see your journey
I love you so much Kiana I will always
be a loyal fan to you no matter what
sorry for relying so much on you no
no
um
I'm happy
you're like feeling
helped and inspired by me
well as if you can congratulate me now
and also I want you to eat me please
congratulations on being fried too
wait four months break
you were gone for four months so long
[Music]
four four months
oh
[Music]
so long well it didn't feel that long
and you look very delicious
uh chicken wings or chicken nuggets I
prefer chicken nuggets
[Music]
okay my glasses well don't ever go again
unless you really have to Let's but I
would appreciate if you would stay
stay now sit sit down you're stuck in
the bucket you're not supposed to be
able to walk anyway you're supposed to
be
in the bucket stuck if anyone moves you
is me or a customer or so but you're not
supposed to be able to move on your own
okay
[Music]
thank you so much for the sweet message
and I wish you all the best with uh the
things that you're starting up again
I would love to sing it all and I hope
that you know you may be able to relate
to those darker songs in my album but I
hope that nowadays you feel more like
the brightest songs in my album
like pineapple and love Rush
mm-hmm
that's how I feel thank you sir
tickets soon
thank you for the pinky I saw you just
sending one just now too
you are you are
she I got you spending oh spending all
your money money
shush I'm sneaking you're not sneaky at
all
I noticed you all the time if you want
to be sneak I don't know what you want
to be sneaky for but if you want to be
sneaky you're gonna be more sneaky than
that
why are you trying to be sneaky because
um you were late
hey could you still be more question I'm
corn
dude you better just watch Devon you
should just watch the bot I already did
an encore of retrospective I always sang
it twice
spending all my money money
spending it on my chicken honey honey
times the charms
no I need I can't I can't I can't waste
time I have to somehow force myself to
sleep maybe
at the latest at midnight I don't know
how I'm gonna do that
[Music]
impossible I'll be tired I'll be very
tired but the good thing is like
um since it's kind of a shitty time
starting time for narissa
uh and also I think Kelly maybe has some
stuff to do after we're not streaming
more than three hours
so I'll survive
I'll survive I'll survive
I'll survive
hey
[Music]
I'll be fine but that's why I'm saying
like I think I might not stream my POV
because I'm not I'm just I think I'm
just gonna focus on being there
and because when I have a stream on you
know streamer brain wants to be
entertaining
and there's more to take care of so
but I'll I'll make sure to stick with uh
someone who has a POV up which is
probably all the rest of them
a stream
oh pretty and I say stream POV and I
don't even pull up my own POV oh [\h__\h] oh
no yeah because you gotta stream a
different POV
you should be busy streaming a different
POV oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
actually just yesterday I was thinking
about how I I can do a lot of puns with
POV whenever I say oh yeah so this in
this collab uh uh I have a POV so stream
my POV my album uh I don't know I don't
know there's definitely potential there
but yeah I'll try to stick with them and
so that you can see what I'm doing and
I'll tell them too
um actually I was thinking
to suggest
I don't know how exactly we would do
this or like how I suggest it but
um
I understand that you know there's so
much to look at but
uh narissa and me especially agreed on
this when we were talking about it
um it's difficult to react
when everybody's doing something else
you know in a group of four if everybody
watches a different cut scene or walks
around somewhere else and talks to a
different NPC everybody is like
overlapping and that's why like I
struggled a lot for example in the city
um exploration because I felt awkward
you know I felt also like
like sorry to at the other pov's viewers
because if I if I comment too much of
what I'm seeing they're gonna be like
what what is she talking about stop
screaming like we're looking at
something else you know I just I just
don't think that works so much
so
um I was gonna suggest that if there is
something big to explore like that like
a city we should choose one of us
to kind of
just more or less decide what we're
looking at and everybody looks at the
same thing you know what I mean
so let's say we're going into the goblin
Temple
[Music]
um and we say Okay Marissa we'll follow
what you do and then in the next
whatever it is city will will follow
what Cali wants to see you know
everybody just looks at what they're
looking at is that is that a good
suggestion
that would help so much to like react to
what's going on without feeling awkward
and interruptive
hmm
okay okay sounds good right I think so
too
rotating it has potential
rotating yeah rotating the guide yeah I
think would be good
I think it will also be more fun because
we're a group of course everybody wants
to do their own thing sometimes but um I
think it makes more sense to as a group
react to things together
and and experience it together yeah
yeah
or not maybe not even like okay one
person for the whole Goblin Temple but
just like taking turns and hey let's
look at this together and then after
that okay but can we look at this
together but somebody will have to like
initiate that you know so
yeah
we'll just have to communicate that I'll
tell I'll tell them that maybe that
would be a good plan
okay
strikes again anyway Nathan cotton was
saying in his pinky sorry I can't make
the life work gets in the way what which
life was this either the balder skates
room
um but I'm looking forward to watching
the archive of you before going through
the character creation the best part of
any other nah we did it beforehand
though mostly hope you had fun making
your character Wawa I'll try to catch
gameplay later
[Music]
I've had I've been having so much fun
with BG free yeah
after creation was fun too uh we were
saying though would be nice if they had
sliders
um for like also facial features
they didn't have so many options for
facial features
like very set in stone faces
that's one criticism I have I have they
all look quite nice and especially the
hairstyles
there's so many hairstyles and like you
also have a lot of hair colors that you
can choose from so that's cool
[Music]
I didn't because of the face motion
capture oh yeah I heard I heard of that
hmm
[Music]
I heard of that I am
okay though I think still that
yeah
character creation is pretty good
um a few more voice variations would be
good too but I guess they have to um
record a lot of dialogue so
understandable
[Music]
um
I wish my laptop could run it but it's
way too old oh no maybe
isn't that awesome
wait you can play controller right but
doesn't mean you're also on a console
but you probably don't have one either
huh
that's too bad
that's too bad maybe you can run
Baldur's cave one on your laptop
[Music]
oh some mothers had a new thing oh
really
faces
IPC is a toaster funny
anyway uh yeah so Nathan costumes
perfect we were just on the topic um I
hope you guys don't mind if tomorrow I
don't stream my POV next time if it's at
a better time for me I'll do it though
I'll I'll stream it
and but yeah okay I hope you caught up
by now
thank you Nathan you're the best
all good all good okay okay
[Music]
go to one of the other povs
G is that something like a rainbow
pretty close to a rainbow oh my God
thank you returning clientele
what does that mean clientele clients
clientele returning client help what is
that where's that new
[Music]
names meaning
I know I know it means customer I know
it means customer but why why returning
where you did you leave me
I did feel like maybe you're not around
as much anymore
um
but but I don't know if that's what you
mean
just a fancy way I said I know I know I
know clientele I like the pun in there
again
[Music]
foreign
but where did you return from
oh I guess you could also take it as
regular
[Music]
who could have imagined that the
horotoni girls would make such a
phenomenal
song just for me
you know I really thought Timothy you're
not here now but I really thought that
you especially how you are that of
course you are that you especially would
love this song I I thought a little bit
about you because of all the puns but
you don't even probably you don't even
understand all the puns in there because
some of them are Japanese
I know he was behind it no he wasn't
behind it but
I'm sure he would have written the
lyrics exactly like that
I got most of them
in Indonesian too I think so a little
bit yeah
it was like mostly English
then a little a little bit more Japanese
and a little bit of an Indonesian
um actually
um if there will be more tony songs in
the future I was told that
um there will always be like a mix of
languages
songs and
um there might be times where the focus
is more in Japanese or maybe even on
Indonesian
but it will always be mixed
[Music]
yeah cool right the Envy eggs crazy the
lyrics impeccable you stole that one
the singing cracks you chicks blew me
away then you always right now new
number one favorite hole hold on of
course in this
my love for the 120 dance made me almost
forget the new lore you dropped having
to use a special gravy to absorb heat so
your hair doesn't spontaneously combust
is a bit awkward no it's not it's just
bird things man why are you unable to
control your fire internal temperature
body heat is it because you're stuck in
him can you stop asking so many
questions
is this a scheme to make yourself appear
weaker to confuse your enemies shouldn't
you be immune to fire so curious
I'm also looking forward to when I'm
telling you in the future I hope key
alter has fun with bg3 the game is very
entertaining I think uh you you I follow
me please to this other room
did I do I still have to I might not
even have a I think I sorted out some
things I don't use so much anymore so I
don't even have the usual room anymore
are you happy now guys you keep you keep
on saying uh can you ever clean out your
obs
and then but now there's a time where I
would need it I would need the usual
room for once and I don't have it
in
you lost I could put it back in there
but no it doesn't mean you're free that
doesn't mean you're free you're still in
there you're just like stuck in it
because I can't open it anymore
no no no you're stuck everybody's who
everybody who is in there is stuck
anyway Trevor Jean be careful about the
questions that you're asking because
you're asking a little bit too many
questions
my I've got my eyes on you I must
silence you if you ask anything else
it's really dangerous
I would already put you into the usual
room now but
there's maintenance happening I guess
am I going to get an answer no because
I totally have one but why would I share
it with you
huh
it's control
your own body heat or your feelings you
know those are intertwined for me
maybe that's the answer maybe my body
heat or whatever internal temperature is
connected with my feelings and one
cannot always control their feelings um
can we huh
[Music]
no not crack no I'm just trying to my my
right shoulder is extremely stiff right
now I'm trying to massage it but it's
just
oh man you guys need to be quiet or else
thank you travel G mwah
let's forget about the other thing I
just want to say thank you for enjoying
100 20 song
ah
ah even the even our MC was um puns
actually
um we tried to do it partially in
English but uh the prompts were still
like in Indonesian and Japanese so you
may have not really understood but
um
yeah it was basically we should guess
what's what's being mimicked and then
it's it ends it always would end in Tori
which is bird
and the first one was niba Tori chicken
but the second one was Yakitori which is
Yakitori which is a grilled chicken on a
on a not Spike on you know the thing the
sick
um
which is
not even a life Bird anymore that's just
food and it's kind of threatening to put
that in there uh a skillet yeah yeah
Satay I am I am I am I am
ah
the funny thing is in the in the
rehearsal
um they put a different prompt
instead of
Yakitori and Elena was just it was
obviously in in Indonesian but she was
just not getting it she was like hey hey
I don't know I don't know hey I don't
know I don't know this is no I can't do
this okay I don't understand I don't
know what does this mean yeah she's like
panicking
because we were rehearsing we were
trying to do it in the right amount of
time
and she's
yeah
but I don't know
but I'm like what's your problem it's
it's
truly in your language but it was like a
really long like
honestly it was a sentence in Indonesian
and we couldn't understand we didn't
know what was the issue and then she
then we cut
the rehearsal and she goes out to talk
to her manager to have her manager
explain it to her and even then she was
like I don't
okay
and then we had to change it and then in
the end I understood it though
um
apparently the answer was I think
Sumotori
uh
and and that's I think just the
small wrestling oh sorry it's so funny
it was another pun that's kind of like
unrelated to birds it just ends in 20.
[Music]
foreign
but apparently what they threw at her a
small Tony no no no
what they throw at her is just a quiet
confusing Indonesian way of creating the
pun I guess I don't know
I don't know but she was so confused by
it and then and then once I found out I
was like hey what was the problem you
could have just you know made a Sumo
pose but I wouldn't even have been able
to guess that because but then I would
just get Sumo I didn't even know about
the word Sumotori
uh-huh
well that was cut and replaced by
Yakitori
[Music]
foreign
MC it was even more time pressure
because like in you know the plan was to
do like maybe two three or four maybe
around three ideally around three rounds
of our game but we only get one
speaking of Summer and then we took the
pose and you know the goal was to have
the same poses pickled up
none of us had it even though we were
already going quite fast that was
already the end of our time and we
couldn't even do a second round
[Music]
when I was like
so sudden it was so fast it was kind of
unnecessary let's be honest but okay
oh yeah I went for gulabia you know what
that is it's like Japanese uh
hmm
harmless
uh kind of harmless
but uh sexy
yeah yeah pin-up kind of like pin up
yeah
there's a lot of
in Japan it's an idol that just
puts out a lot of grab grav viewer
content like photo books and videos and
so on
uh and I thought speaking of Summer
crazier I don't know why because because
of sexy poses I don't know I don't know
and because they most of the time they
wear swimsuits uh so
it's crazy
huh
anyway yeah that was my thought process
thank you
[Music]
I absolutely love holotori dance so much
I literally can't stop listening to it
since Premiere it's so catchy I'm so
happy hopefully finally have an original
song volatility is the best similarity
Dance Forever yeah and I didn't even
have to pay for it let's go
[Music]
um
yeah our first original song Thank God
management is behind it uh because yeah
they put they put some work into it it's
shorts but it's well produced I like it
looking forward to uh almost to one for
oh [\h__\h] it's growing so fast
I'm looking forward to what kind of
songs we'll be making in the future but
when Tony dance is a pop and I'm glad to
see you guys dancing at 2 on social
media thank you thank you thank you
thank you I'm known for enjoying it and
for listening to it as well Jeff style
thanks for the pinky sticker thank you
thank you thank you
evil doctor catfish dinosaur cello
dancer Prince of Denmark Junction
for the pinky
sending this during a break at work one
year ago I bought a membership for my
birthday and I've never regretted it
although I haven't been able to be in a
member stream live oh
could I have a birthday song during
Super Chat reading when you get to it
[Music]
all right all right all right
you're gonna you're gonna get like a
acapella one though
happy birthday to you
and even though I don't know
when was your birthday happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday in your
shoes
happy birthday however mysterious many
years old you are now congratulations I
don't even know when your birthday was
and how old you got
a song
Happy Birthday to you happy Birthday and
your shoe happy birthday and your
parents too
wow
[Music]
beautiful
um Mariah Carey
Beyonce's style belting
[Music]
day
[Laughter]
I'm just messing around
can I have one too ah
line up
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday space wonderful
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
okay
what about these shoes I guess happy
birthday to your shoes too
yeah I guess
[Music]
I'm like your glass broke
let's
go
thank you Prince of Denmark for still
being in the membership even though you
can barely go to them live
um I'm I'm sad you can't be alive but
I'm happy you're still you know checking
it out we have a member stream tomorrow
maybe you can catch that one if not no
pressure thank you for the support Jesus
I saw you sending Super Chat yesterday
too
Advent huh that's okay you you do what
you want to do but I saw you I saw you
Gregory Ralph thank you soon restful for
one dance
thanks for the pinky another one oh you
are
spending
too much money
[Music]
caught in 4k I don't know if it was 4K
but I'm very bad with money maybe you
should give me your bank account details
and I will take care of your money
instead
no please don't trust me with it I'm not
good with money either
[Music]
in terms of playing a ranger is a woman
after my own heart hope you like it huh
I'm Cupid basically
I could I could role play as Cupid that
would be funny if that was possible
a bit inspired by me watching charms
these days in the last season the cupid
shows up and uh Phoebe is quite
quite enticed by cute bird
surprise surprise cupid is a Chad and
knows how to make you fall in love with
him
oh yeah that was silly oh you you know
it oh my God
it's cute though of course Coop knows
the right words and all that yeah that's
what they call him but in Cuban they're
not baby Cube yeah yeah it was a big
chat Cupid
I vaguely remember that episode it's so
weird to me I I feel like I've seen
every season before on TV but this last
season
I might have only seen like two episodes
or so
but it's nice because it's like
basically completely new content I
appreciate it
is that a tantric no
no
no no no no
but you know I always try to give
somebody a tangent if they send a pinky
or a red one kind of like a like a thank
you here's a tangent to go enjoy
um it's like they ordered you know like
uh like um Burger set meal
and this is me giving them that you know
I feel like I have to
provide them with some tangents to go
yeah as a thank you
that's why I always try to
bring something out of whatever message
they send and when they don't send a
message I'm like what the [\h__\h] do I do
with this how am I supposed to create a
tangent out of nothing
no anyway thank you Phil weasel Douglas
and Rain are dankish and priest of
goddess thank you
[Music]
that's why there's a long queue yeah
longest queue ever
excellent service right
I agree I love my service
acceptable casualties
[Music]
Stephen einter Duncan
simply here now we have this problem
simply sent a red super chat but only
with a heart emoji
simply what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
no no words needed I guess just love
love love
hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot hot
hot hot hot
hot
[Music]
I'm a man of few words
but of much love right and big heart
heart
heart heart heart heart heart heart
heart heart
and big pockets
[Music]
heart heart heart
filtered
why would you stop her from doing that
that it's the best stuff
filtered anyway
[Music]
that sounded realistic game
uh
[Music]
Joby one thousands soon
I'm back from my trip I went to smash
tournaments I can say that I did pretty
bad but I had a lot of fun anyways I'll
do better next one miss some stuff but I
love Hello
thank you oh smash elements sometimes I
see those happening at like conventions
but I guess yours was maybe a bit more
serious I don't know but man it's
measurements
maybe one day I should try participating
[Music]
and I will I will
I will definitely lose but
no no I shouldn't try no no too much
effort I don't have time
[Music]
whole life smash tournaments still
realistic but against other people
nah
I like the game though but
uh I don't think I could get too
competitive I just want to casually play
it for fun you know
come on
[Music]
I hope you had fun there next time
you're gonna get him next time you're
gonna get
at least placement number three
who would you mean I don't know when I
was like younger like really really
young when smash was on the GameCube
um I I think I was always playing like
Chic you know which was Zelda basically
she can Zelda together because I thought
it was kind of like
um versatile and I like girls you know I
always liked girl cute girls characters
didn't want to play any of the like not
so aesthetically pleasing
spoilers I mean in in Smash they're the
same person basically you can transform
so come on I don't know I honestly don't
know I don't think I
in which game does cheek show up because
I don't think I ever played it so I'm
unsure myself
[Music]
Ocarina of Time
now I played and watched Ocarina of Time
[Music]
but I'm
Zella is not Chic I don't remember her
turning into chic
but because of your reaction now I'm
guessing she did
[Music]
it is
oh my God
[Music]
I would have been honestly so surprised
if I played Ocarina of Time sometime
this year or next year
[Music]
yeah
I mean there's definitely watched
or played it before
but I I I I don't remember that part
oh man
I don't know I blocked that part out I
think and if I ever played it on my own
I when I was younger I never got that
far I think
and Nev I would have never gotten that
far because I never finished games when
I was younger
um
[Music]
where's a little bit can we move on why
why
do you not like talking about Zelda
[Music]
why
tangent going oh my God are you timing
my tangents
[Music]
don't don't time my tensions
foreign
[Music]
I need to open up the usual room again
see now I feel like
insecure about it hi
[Music]
guys
I love how you guys are adding that in
now
I messed up so badly
oh my God
somebody make it clean
where was I
am celebrities happy
happy birthday
congratulations
thank you
thank you soon
[Music]
I
I think I still have the audible
subscription
um Evan's L banks with a pinky no need
to read I just want to say I'm really
proud of you of all you're doing lately
nice job I guess
that's like even more fitting now than
it was during Baldur's page
thank you what why are you okay
what did I say oh because of audible I
really forgot
ah
eight foot drop oh yeah
oh oh I need uh oh oh I think he oh yeah
he's gonna do retrospective at least
we gotta here no no he surely didn't do
it yet
um but he's gotta do but the problem is
like it's by people sending you to
blings right I guess no I guess they
could send the YouTube topic
that that should work I guess it doesn't
have a music video though unfortunately
foreign
[Music]
he'll probably still make something cool
out of it but definitely want to hear
retrospective
[Music]
oh that's gonna be noise
yes a week ago what whole song you would
like to listen to so there's good timing
and why does doesn't it just like happen
spontaneously on his stream anyway
[Music]
mm-hmm
but he was also surprised that it was so
short he was like about to drum a bit
more
and he's like oh oh it's over
[Music]
it is kind of surprising yeah
anyway thank you Evans
[Music]
I'll speed through these ones I'll speed
for them
no no no no I have to make progress
ion Elvis oh it's been a while Elvis hey
thank you yo what are those dance moves
thank you Elvis opening for the red
super chat
do you like the new album huh do you
like it do you like it do you like it do
you like it do you like it
let me know what's your Bop on this
album when you hear me asking you do you
do you do you do you
like my new album
oh yeah it makes sense
oh my God oh my God genius I was gonna
say Michael Jackson but I guess it could
be Elvis
bring your Elvis
[Music]
Junction
oh that's so cool I want to try dark
urge but it's too late now Caleb Caleb
wise thank you green welder I've also
haven't seen you
so much
connection friend
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat it's
funny you should mention taking a break
after six years
wait I've been in whole life for six
years
huh
[Music]
I'm actually taking my first vacation
six years right now
must have been a typo must have been a
typo
[Music]
oh
it's also my 34th birthday today I
didn't tell you the last couple years
but I felt like I should do I should for
my third birthday with KFC anyway have
fun how dare
me about it the first two times
well
red Super Chat
birthday you know what that means
[Music]
happy birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoes happy birthday
in your pants to have
happy birthday to you
you are Queen Wilder
and you are my chicken
the possibly only one from Canada
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday
[Music]
to you
34 years yeah
you're just getting better
cherish everything yeah
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you apparently that
was wrong there's a few more Canadians
[Music]
in case you're free
on the next weekend
[Music]
happy birthday Toronto is in Canada
right
right what I'm not wrong right
I'm pretty sure it's in Canada
personal invite yeah
yeah see okay I knew it I knew it I knew
it I knew it anyway
so otherwise he would have been like
what the [\h__\h] Toronto is not in Canada
what are you talking about
well it is I'm a genius
yeah but I I I I know there's like a
handful of Canadian wobble viewers
there's just really not that many
um I know I uh I don't know why but you
know I'm happy for every single one of
you and I hope to see every single one
of you of the run into one because you
know the fact that I only have so few of
you I can count you with my two hands
therefore I will be doing an attendance
check of all Canadians
on this weekend
in Toronto
I have all your names on my list
[Laughter]
I'll be doing an attendance check so you
better be down
see you there
don't you wanna hear in a big oh
imagine the acoustics
of the great Wanderer
in a big convention room I wonder how
that's gonna be I'm thinking to do great
Wanderer and maybe a pineapple or so
probably
oh don't you want to hear that um
but I have no idea how the Acoustics are
there what kind of room we're gonna be
in
let's see we'll see
thank you going well
I'll see you at that convention right
right right right right right
[Music]
what did you know morally immoral
Mario's entire family
[Music]
thanks for all the the blue flush chats
did I go adult meeting during this or
what
uh skip those though like in the good
old days running this channel thank you
wrote something oh a humble offering to
appease the YouTube Gods please let Wawa
stream in peace thank you oh was was
YouTube being [\h__\h] again I've been
having so many issues and always had the
worst times surprisingly today
there were no issues for once right
except for the chat dying but the stream
didn't die right
it better not die on me during this
is what I was thinking the whole time
[Music]
um
no stream Dance No thank God it's been a
really weird
but I don't know
I don't know I don't know why
like there was like one time the other
day where my OBS died but my internet
stable though and most of the time it's
YouTube That's disconnecting not obs
so that must be on YouTube and I don't
know what their problem is it's been
happening too much and chat has just
been
dying in this past one month or so
way more than ever before right
what are they doing what are they doing
what are they doing YouTube
like during a stream it happens like if
it's a three hour stream it happens like
six times or so
almost two months and what are they
doing
maybe I should bring it up
to YouTube directly knock knock YouTube
what the [\h__\h] is going on
[Music]
sort out your chat issues
maybe Implement hyper chat I don't know
but even hyper chat can fix you unless
you do something on your side
[Music]
for the shadow bunky
[Applause]
[Music]
no not again
yes hire my Harvard student yes
I don't know if he's looking for a job
but
I mean working on YouTube
this is definitely something cool to
write on your
uh
resume
yeah thank you please
set certainly Duncan president
that reminds me of a black eyed peace
song
I think it was black abuse I am a CP
production matter runt Junction
certainly thank you
Nathan
Nathan are you sending a pinky in every
stream at least one if not two
I think that's what's been going on are
you okay do we have to have an
intervention
um
it's okay though thank you so much I I I
I I you know I I say this thing these
things you know to
you know
I'm jerking you know you must have
control you must know what you're doing
and I really appreciate the support
I really appreciate it thank you
I can't imagine getting nine at this
getting 90 M's although wait what was
that at 9 90 and what although I guess
it would look something like um
currently I have free and free DMS not
for him free DMS at least free
is what's popping up there's probably
more
free free mentions at least not free of
charge I mean any of them are free of
charge of course
[Music]
free
I don't know Nathan what compelled you
to send this Super Chat
[Music]
I don't know what it was
but
I don't know if it was necessary but it
was funny
it was such a stretched out it was such
a
you were the only one who thought of
that
nobody else was listening to me saying I
have nine DMS and thought 90 M's
just you
you heard it too nah you found it don't
[\h__\h] me why I was just saying a
normal thing
[Music]
[Laughter]
why
Gregory wrote thank you thank you
foreign
really great seeing you enjoy it so much
and seeing more of the actual story hope
you have even more fun at the next BG
collab thank you yeah that's uh in
nine hours I think
[Music]
oh my God help
help
God I'm done with super chats for now
almost thank you
I am enjoying it a lot
I feel kind of very conflicted about
doing a solo and the collab stream at
the same time
yeah but
I don't I'm just I decided to not think
about it
and just just do it just do it
[Music]
they're both very different anyway so
far
very very different from what you see
what I do know that yeah
I mean don't let your memes be dreams
no pots we'll let Gates be just be Gates
[Music]
it's a good stream to fill on the slot
if you want to come back to the soul
save every now and yeah it's not like I
really need to fill up my schedule
wait what day is it today
is it Wednesday
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
laughs
okay okay
[Laughter]
no I paid my bills today yo don't even
get me started what the [\h__\h] man
basically the same thing is happening
again uh but with a different package
apparently I don't even know which
package it is this time I paid those
stupid bills
from DHL last time even though it was
too high and it was unreasonable
and I never received anything in the
first place
besides the already
like like the one
the one warning from the law firm that
had like a [\h__\h] ton of late fees on it
already when I never received anything
in the first place pissed me off so much
and did some communication with them if
you remember but nothing came out of it
um besides
yeah pay it pay up [\h__\h] and now
think I'm I got a letter
from same law firm again about DHL
apparently
[Music]
asking me to pay up this time it's not
as expensive
maybe only because
I don't even know what it's for again
don't know what it's for
um but it also said I find it very
[\h__\h] rude but the letter said
something like uh
you have once again missed to pay up uh
if you don't pay within tomorrow
that's not even realistic like when you
send a letter how do you know it's even
gonna what huh if you don't pay the like
the rate
in case I'm doing it by rate apparently
because it says it said you failed to
pay until now and you failed to follow
up on our offer to pay on rates so pay
by to you guys say
it's the last time oh
it wasn't a scam it's just them
I don't know extorting me
um but yeah it says you you failed to
follow up on the follow you know follow
up on the payment
that we offered you last time to do it
on rates so if you don't pay this rate
uh within tomorrow then we are forced to
blah blah blah blah blah you know
uh but I just paid the whole thing
and now uh today and I'm like
[\h__\h] them
I'm still gonna I don't wanna get in
trouble and I don't wanna get more late
fees so I just hate it but I'm gonna
still write to them and ask them what
the [\h__\h] I'm even thinking about like
using my power because I'm so sick and
tired of them uh and tweeting at them on
Twitter
[Music]
rudely you know like those Karen's like
excuse me yeah
I will never
eat and again
you know my brother was like [\h__\h] them
you can't do this twice to me I gave him
once
why are you doing this to me again what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with their system like
not my fault that they failed to charge
me upon delivery for whatever it is that
they delivered
and then
out of nowhere I don't even get DHL
reminders to pair something no out of
nowhere I get a law firm reminder which
implies that something was supposed to
arrive before but I swear to God
nothing is arriving where are they
sending it to I don't understand
it is outrageous did they actually send
you something I don't know what but last
time it was about the Dana package
apparently
they did like
I called them and then they told me to
send an email to give them the letter
uh and they investigated and apparently
it was the Delano package and now I
don't know what it is
[Music]
I think
um the Pokemon merchandise that I got
like three days ago or so
uh
uh what did I just open it three days
ago and I got it a while before
no no no I think it's pretty fresh
um but that one was I think DHL it could
have been that but
yeah again I what I don't understand I'm
so mad
sorry man
anyway I told
uh General if they maybe send things to
me again don't use DHL because [\h__\h] them
I don't want to deal with DHL anymore if
there's any other option you can choose
please choose a different option
I I don't want to be like scammed and
extorted and buy them again
I mean the first time was Elena this
time I think it because I I can't think
of anything else I think it must be
something that
this what if the
what if it's the
what if it's the postcards I was
wondering if they sent me the postcards
are they gonna charge me something for
it the ones I have to sign
I I will ask I will inquire what it is
I if it's the postcards I'm gonna be so
pissed because I was actually kind of
thinking like
[Music]
what's gonna happen with these postcards
it's a huge package it's really heavy
got a [\h__\h] ton of postcards but how
would they know what the value is of the
process because in the end the postcards
are kind of like free of charge anyway
for like
um
uh you know the bonus my birthday
merchandise bonus that I have to sign
and then send back to Japan for them to
send it to you guys
apparently doesn't matter what it does
yeah but still
if it's that I'm so [\h__\h] dumb I'm so
sorry I don't even I I don't even have
any influence on that and then if they
would just charge me up front when it's
when it arrives I don't know what what
they are doing
normally they should charge you up front
normally the receiver wouldn't owe any
money that's some sketched right but
apparently it's a scam I don't know or
the whole length concept is just scam
but they that's what they do so they get
away with it I don't know
whatever it makes me upset and nothing I
can do about it anyway so you know
can you reimburse it if it is connected
to that I will send cover the bill
yeah
I am
I think I will write that tweet I
actually already wrote it but Twitter
didn't send it
[Music]
they got lucky this time I wrote like
how come this is the second time in this
year that you guys are before sending me
anything else prior you just sending me
straight up a a letter from a lawyer Law
Firm threatening me with uh this morning
uh and and late fees even though I never
received anything in the first place
why did this happen twice in this year
already
why
[Music]
a month in the future
and
even then they're just gonna reply with
it
oh we are so sorry please send us more
details on this email address
now I'll I'll I'll try to I I I would
love to use my power like that but I'll
uh
I'll try to sort it out privately first
[Music]
I want to destroy them yes
yes it's the same as last time
basically same letter as last time just
a different amount of money
[Music]
um
anyway gonna cook now and hopefully
sleep relatively early
um I'll see you at the member stream and
Baldur's Gate on somebody else's Channel
okie dokie
and
pineapple Envy
tomorrow
uh
wait
[Music]
tomorrow 5 PM sing EST
[\h__\h] cute
I'm on a pineapple floaty
hey
today depending on your time zone is
music video
[Music]
you may want to reach out to Austria's
equivalent of the uh yeah I probably
should do that
yeah
who's consult with a lawyer um excuse me
where's typhen my legal what does Typhon
say about this it's typhoon here
[Music]
would be interesting typhoon are you in
the chat
just this is all I want to know before I
go
legal
Kevin says get a lawyer well I have you
now we have something in in Austria
that's like yeah this like consumer
protection whatever where you can go for
free and consult [\h__\h] I've never gone
there before but you can consult them
for a lot of stuff you know
[Music]
but yeah I don't know I'm busy and you
know I always feel like kind of lost of
these kind of things because I just feel
so overwhelmed with everything
contact consumer protection that would
be what I'd advise someone to do first
it's so cool to have a lawyer in here
I totally get you there thank you it's
like adult stuff you know I just can't
so I just can't that's how they get you
though they make everything so difficult
and complicated
and I really tried last time I had a
whole back and forth with them
with DHL
you know
but it didn't lead me to anything to
anywhere
um
because I told them you know I never
received anything and they're like
well
I'll just never use DHL again [\h__\h] them
but what can I do if people sent me [\h__\h]
[Music]
I was once made to pay my internet
provider for a while that broke because
they didn't cover it properly oh
[Music]
you need to harass the law from veterans
but again it's like so much effort man
to like care about this [\h__\h] because I
got other [\h__\h] to do too right so and
I'm all alone like man
no
[Music]
gave us the edges we'll do it I wish you
could take over
I just don't understand like if they
would just
if I would just receive like a DHL
letter in the first place like fine
but the law firm letter in the first
like out of nowhere that's just that's
just a lot what's going on
anyone
did you call the number on the ladder or
on their website uh well let me try that
remember uh what did I do I
I sent the first of all I called DHL and
I was advised because they I asked if
the law firm is legit if they really go
and use this Law Firm if this whole
thing is legit receiving a letter like
this and he was like yeah
um we used several law firms like when
it gets to that point where they don't
receive the charges that they the fees
that they charge then they send it over
to these like couple of law firms that
that handle it afterwards
um but he wasn't sure the guy on the
phone wasn't sure if this was one of
them so he told me to write them an
email so he gave me an email from the
bookkeeping Department yeah they're like
debt collectors collect collectors yeah
so I sent the letter scanned in to the
email that he gave me and they were they
investigated it and they told me yeah
this is we work with them this is legit
um and I'm like okay but I never
I don't even know what this is for and I
never received anything they were like
wow this is what it's for
done
attracting them officer no the the the
law firm letter doesn't say anything it
doesn't give you a tracking number
it doesn't imply anything what it would
be for which is so confusing
but now I have the email address I'll
just write to them again
but yeah no
this yeah that's the case consumer
protection is 100 your best bet
you typing
uh
I guess that kind of exists everywhere
huh
[Music]
It's Made for This
okay
I paid for it already yeah but they
better pay me back
I just paid for now because they're
literally threatening me
like
it says like oh my God we're gonna we're
gonna what what are these words I don't
know the English words for this I'm
gonna we're gonna what's the word pound
in pounds
we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna sue
you you we're gonna take everything you
own [\h__\h] like that
oh
son but lawyers are [\h__\h]
skip boys
[Music]
so scary man
protect me
lawyers are lawyers are supposed to be
protecting and helping normal humans but
at the same time they're like our
biggest enemy when you're like against
them
remember when I was a weird skeletal
drum yeah yeah yeah you the way you just
forming that sentence confuses me but
you you mean you know because you did
jobs that you don't really like right
and now you're like more
you do you take the jobs you want or so
right
um
anyway I'm gonna go now and remember
that's not all other senses no it's not
a scam I'm telling you I already had it
investigated before by DHL
it's just they're just they're just
being scammy but it's it's legit
I'm telling you
it's the same thing second time this
year
I really talked to be a channel really
I'm not this is not all in my head
no it's for real for real
yeah I'll I'll if I find some time I
will try it
going to that consumer stuff
I think
[Music]
retrospin
I'm being scammed by [\h__\h] DHL I just
can't they keep on threatening me with
all this [\h__\h] I don't
I'm scared please help me
okay goodbye guys
hahaha
uh
have you talked to your mom about this
oh uh I think
[Music]
about the first one
I think I told her about it she may have
already forgotten it but I think I told
her about it when she was here
mm-hmm
OS
okay bye bye
I'm telling you
no it's not
[\h__\h] I'm being gaslighted I want to
believe you because and I I'm sure what
happened to you really happened
but I'm pretty sure
I mean
oh man
oh bye bye
[Music]
laughs
dream POV
[Music]