[Music]
do
oopsie cake
[Music]
i'm not muted anymore am i
and welcome everyone and congratulations
to heart challenger
for one month after release anniversary
yay light vote uncertain
i use light mode for most of the things
but actually like this is
uh i'm just using a different browser
than usual so nothing is
uh set to anything because uh
i have given up on saving everything
because uh
the apps that i have been recommended
don't work the way i want them to
so we're gonna do it this way i'm just
gonna you know scroll through and
hopefully not run into anything
dangerous
[Music]
so it's not only that it's also white
day
so i mean it was what let's just say it
still is white day
for the people who don't know are there
people who don't know what white day is
we talked about it yesterday on my
stream but
are there any people who don't know
i mean i've looked for the tag before
and it is fun
looks fine from what i've seen
[Laughter]
is one month after valentine's day and
it's like uh
they made it up in japan and afterwards
it
uh spread a little bit across asia
but basically on valentine's day in
japan
the girls make chocolate
on their own mostly mostly handmade
and then give it to the person that they
like
or they also give it to friends and so
on but like
the most important thing is giving it to
your class
and yeah they do that in school or
sometimes i guess
even not in school um
yeah meow i think so too and uh
yeah so then one month later they have
white day where the boys answer
i honestly have to say that's way too
[\h__\h] late i cannot wait
one month for an answer
sony
apparently that's what they do one month
later
the boys not so much make their own
chocolate but
they give them like actual not self-made
presents mostly then you give them like
jewelry to
jewelry or however the freak you
pronounce that
jewelry jewelry jewelry
sounds about right right
that's sunspot right i think yeah and
sometimes even laundry oh as we found
out yesterday
white lingerie
[Music]
um but yeah so that's white day for ya
but it's only really a thing in japan
and in some asian countries
so yeah anyway it's been one month since
we did
the heart challenge choco challenge and
i wanted to
back then i wanted to i did a stream
where i went for
a lot of them but there were way too
many submissions
so i was not able to get through them uh
and even today i have to say i mean i'm
only going through submissions that were
submitted in time okay i'm sorry
i saw some submissions that were
submitted afterwards
i saw you i acknowledge you but i'm
sorry
and i will not introduce because there's
like so freaking many
uh submissions
it's uh crazy like probably over yeah
exactly it's like 500 or so
yeah more i don't know so
we'll be going through that bro i don't
i probably won't give like a big
comment on every single submission uh
but but i'll i'll try
another token
who made a submission thank you very
much for participating in this
uh it's um a really cute thing i want to
do stuff like this more often
and thank you everyone for taking your
time i also want to say
hello 60 60fps
welcome back i've been waiting for you
wait it's yeah yeah it's really smooth
i think there should be no more
issues like we had in the past few days
because i now have a like a thing i have
a
ethernet cable connected to my phone
so now ems move smooth like a baby butt
like a baby's butt
so thank you for giving me that idea
and it's working really well i think
so i mean it's not not exactly
not exactly prime time here yet i
suppose but close enough
uh i think yeah i'll test it some more
let's see uh if minecraft works better
but i'm not sure if that was actually an
internet problem
but anyway
so relieved that's such a great um
solution
putting an ethernet cable into your
phone thank god that
such a thing exists yeah
okay so let's get started uh going
through the submissions shall we
shall we and as i said i can't give
two detailed comments about everything
because i want to get through it
hello kitty cat hello hello how are you
doing
baby mimi
are you ready to look at some chocolates
and hopefully not throw up
mine
let's see what we got okay so first of
all uh
for succulent i'm i'm scrolling
downwards by the way i think this is
probably where
yeah this must be judging from this this
must be where i started streaming so i'm
i'm sorry for everyone above we're going
down that way we're not going up
i'm sorry i'm pretty sure that's where i
started streaming somewhere there
so everyone afterwards i'm sorry
i think that's so yeah that's uh
oh it looks yummy it's a
it's a mousse but it's like uh it looks
like a like a chocolate milkshake
with a strawberry strawberries make
everything better also there's a cactus
uh in the background i like the cactus
and so this will be the pace uh how we
go for it unless there's something
really crazy we'll take some more time
i'm finished from what i was planning
but here's a matcha white chocolate and
dark chocolate brownie
oh ho do you guys like matza
um sorry this is not like the whole
picture uh but this is just how you will
see it
a little detail do you guys like matcha
[Music]
matcha this is a good combination matcha
and dark chocolate
and strawberry is i think a really good
combination
i personally um i like matcha
as as a tea and for sweets
i can eat it but i like it more
as a tea mata
now we have here muffins yummy yummy
muffins very
very simple very classic love muffins i
want some
thank you we got here my entry for
guinness cards
chocolate and raspberry raspberry
spheres raspberry mousse chocolate and
chocolate pies
damn son let's see
oh served on a freaking
tree had to think about it for a moment
what that was
oh my okay you can't see the whole thing
don't mind it but
damn well that's so i i feel some
some creative uh sense
and some creative other adults
what's other in english again
come on help me
ah you probably i guess you don't say
that in english do you that sounds weird
never heard that before
and in german we like to say someone has
like uh something something
vain like a talent yeah yeah
but okay i guess you probably don't say
that in english
but you know what i mean yeah he's kind
of artistic i like that and i love
raspberries i love raspberries so much
so we got here last minute entry for
hatchimals and chocolate chip foundation
these are cacao berry like tea what
but superior 38 milk chocolate bon bon
soup homemade orange comforter
wow homemade orange come over damn
yummy that looks good i like um
i've eaten like chocolate with like uh
orange filling and like orange stuff in
it
from i think it was lint
before and that's so yummy that's such a
good combination
having orange and chocolate together
so yummy one of the best
combinations i would say or like fruit
combinations with orange
with chocolate besides like you know
strawberry and that kind of stuff damn
so good noise
is what this person says what is that
this looks like a chocolate
cream pudding something like that not
sure
then this doesn't seem like there's a
chocolate soup oh wait
there's like what is that is that
brownies or okay you guys don't see it
uh
but the birds are hella cute what the
hell
yeah you don't need to see it but
there's like here there's that's
chocolate it's pretty dark
it's that that's so romantic though
will this appease you bird mother
takanawa kirsh black forest cake with
cream
chantilly gentilly
owl jokes aside i wish i had more time
but this is the best i can do with the
limits
schedule i love black horse cake
that looks really good yes
but i want it to be bigger that's so
small that's like one bite
looks like one bite i want more
but black first cake is really yummy one
of the best cakes out there
now we got some cookies uh
made some or orange again orange butter
cookies filled with chocolate con
ganache i'm glad it turned out pretty
decently oh
chocolate ganache what was it is it just
a chocolate cream inside
and the the cookies i like orange taste
oh yummy nice
lava cake with raspberry ice cream self
made too
ice cream self made i once learned in
school how to make ice cream yourself
but
i have never made it myself since then
although it it's kind of easy
it didn't turn out as bland but still
was that tasty why did it not turn out
as plant that looks yummy
wait i'm loading well
that looks pretty damn i mean i mean it
looks very tasty the presentation is
kind of
cheap but other than that
yeah yeah ice cream in school yeah i had
cooking cooking classes
yeah it was pretty normal to have
cooking classes
in our schools at least in junior high
school
don't know about uh
[Music]
what what comes after junior high school
senior high school what wait
what i forgot the english terms for it
it's pretty damn normal
christ oh that's just high school
oh that's just high school okay
i got a bit confused okay okay i got a
bit confused
but i i i didn't really like the cooking
classes because
we had to work in groups and i don't i
didn't like working in groups much
one reason number one why i didn't like
it and reason number two
i was uh annoying
men look signed
but we did cook some good things i guess
yeah
yeah yeah group projects
are
oh i suppose maybe this was still after
the deadline because of this sentence
kind of elaine says okay skip you all
just kidding we're already here okay but
i guess this was already too late
um but hey okay you get you just get a
glance okay
okay i glanced at the beautiful cupcakes
i already saw them
this is uh i saw this one when i was
saving the pictures but it didn't work
out
this is okay i can't show you the full
picture but what the [\h__\h] is
going on this is uh crazy
it's the shape of a g cleft with a
little burp on top
uh an old project okay no no no no i
need it yeah some people submitted like
old things
no you have to make something new i gave
you enough time to make something new
looks impressive though but no um
no
thank you thank you anyway
this once again someone combines orange
with chocolate
what a genius how did you do the
patterns
how did you do those are they are they
real
or is that photoshopped i'm not sure
are they real how did you do that
or
[Music]
and i went to make something for hot
challenger even if i'm not good at
baking hope you enjoy my cookie dough
pizza
wait pizza but but it's like made out of
the cookie dough
with chocolate on top and and
strawberries
i mean it looks like a cursed sweet
pizza
but it must be yummy because you say
it's cookie dough
it has white and milk chocolate chunk
chunk chunks in the base
that could be good i mean i would need
to try
and uh you can buy seeds
[Music]
interesting these look yummy so colorful
too
i made oreo travels for the first time
until we bought the orange one oof
they look good nice good job
10 out of 10 chocolate cupcakes with
powdered sugar made with all of my heart
for this event oh
oh with our little thingies there
i haven't made cupcakes in like a
million years i only made my microwave
cupcakes recently
ah i need to learn again how to make
cupcakes shouldn't be that hard anyone
can make cupcakes like
cupcakes and brownies is like something
that anyone seems to be able to make
oh we got here chocolate covered orange
strawberries
yeah i mean that's uh you didn't do much
but okay
it's yummy
hard zones i took one of these i don't
know but i made them they have chocolate
and i decorated them as nice as i could
so it can't sometimes you just got to
throw ingredients together and pretty
hot
i don't know is that like chocolate
brownies like in in round shape
i don't know i don't know
chocolate balls about like
made it made with rice flour flour which
i just found out doesn't rise
what rice
cocoa powder sugar vegan okay
[Music]
i mean they look yummy i guess
i don't know can't judge much now this
one is uh not actual food
it's a 3d i think it should be really
um i like that that's funny for the
covering up
oh my god it's really good
i'll give that a like oh i can't yeah
because i'm not logged in here
thank you 10 out of 10. even though it's
not food
but that reminds me of like you know the
when it's like christmas or when it's
like easter they sell these like easter
bunnies
are made out of chocolate and they sell
these uh
nikolaos here they sell nikolas
for christmas out of uh chocolate
the legs so we have here
a rocky road fudge brownies what is
rocky road uh
does that mean because it's like with
nuts oh
yummy kfb thank you that looks yummy i
want to try
and you made some brownies with your i
think that's brownies too
or no it's not isn't that like um
like what do you call that is that
brownies i don't think so isn't that
like the
it's like it has a different texture it
looks like it has a different texture
if that's just fudge okay
i guess so it looks yummy and we got
some a video
of this submission which is a chocolate
bread
yummy it looks well made
looks almost like a chocolate crab
but i suppose it's bread i even
have like oh the process of making bread
look wow
i wanna eat that looks yummy
thank you now we got uh sorry for the
late
super late intro entry i was basically
celebrating
doctor quit dark chicken dipped cookies
those look like the kind of cookies that
we make for
for like winter christmas season here
oh yummy good job thank you
tell me no what the hell is this
why
i mean i love corn and i love milka and
i love chocolate
but look at this one oh my god
wow wow it's so cute
oh chocolate cookie gram i did today
okay
you did that like in one day wow
thank you that's like the the cover art
for heart challenger and the logo too
jose jose ina come on you are so cute
thank you oh
there we go we got some uh danish
oatmeal balls with made with cocoa
oatmeal butter
sugar and coconut okay i don't like
coconut but other than that
that sounds really good to me coconut
fans will love this one
now we got um we got
the chocolate truffles
nice
i imagine it might be a bit more morty's
taste given the
pecan pie liqueur i added to this oh
there's alcohol in there
oh i see i see i see
interesting they all kill me they look
i don't i don't eat many truffles at all
i don't eat truffles ever but maybe i
should they sound fancy they look fancy
potential comments on 800k i made uh i
made millionaires
shortbread because i'm sure you'll also
be celebrating that muslim very soon
that looks very well done looks very
very beautiful
nice thank you
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] are you show your face in
the chat
show yourself
where are you i remember kiana saying
how handsome i might do chocolate
covered tarantulas or something for
valentines i decided to take the
initiative as a good careful employee
and do it myself
i didn't have any tarantulas so scorpion
will have to do instead
why would you do that why would you
why would you ah dear lord
uh
absolutely disgusting
are you are you from australia or
something
oh my god kazana
there she goes or he what
abby i'm sorry danger i'll show myself
to the usual room in class right now
uh-huh yeah you better show yourself for
the usual room i think you already know
where it is
10 out of 10 would eat would you guys
try that
would you guys be honest would you try
it
be honest be
honest
yeah we got the perfect emo for that
nine nine nine nine nine nine nine nine
nine nine nine nine nine strawberry yeah
yeah the strawberry yes yes
or just lick off the chocolate from the
scorpion
i pray i prefer to not even do that
nine out of ten
which is a n e i n not n i
n e
oh dear lord i think there's probably
more than that like
more more more cursed submissions like
that somewhere
now this is normal this looks good made
this chocolate and coffee
cake oh coffee huh i don't drink coffee
and i don't really like anything that
tastes like coffee
my brother would love that though what
is that
what is that is that a cake it's pretty
it looks pretty
big it's taking up the whole plate wow
you made a whole cake for this thank you
why is this why is this marked as
sensitive
during a quick reunion with my family in
between workshops in the middle of
nowhere
i submit hard challenges why is that
why is that why is that largest
sensitive
where is my window oh this one
let me check
that's not that's not sensitive
that's not sensitive
oh my god so sensitive what's sensitive
about that
oh my god twitter please
and chocolate cool out with cheese cream
on top yummy
they look good with the heights too
nice good job they look good yummy yummy
let me get some tacoma appreciation
content
yay for everyone who misses takamoni
content we have a
collab this week i mean it's not only me
and cali but
it's me callie gooda and inana we're
playing uno on my channel
thank you for that that's really cute
and this is that oh
that looks yummy
yes yes yeah chocolate cake yum yum yum
so simple but so good mmm
this looks like what i made
yeah you're welcome for that recipe
i'm making a bunch of my co-workers
following tantra's recipe ah
this is the test badge mine is a few
that i already ate aha
they taste good even though i have no
experience making desserts what's fun
yeah there you go see my recipe was
oh no i see something below that looks
really bad
i don't know my recipe was uh
easy to recreate and easy for beginners
so
10 out of 10. now this is this is not
what i mean
this is not what i mean um but let me
check real quick what that was
okay that's just normal brownies why is
it sensitive
brownies yummy good job they look yummy
but now
what
not
what a waste of a perfectly good egg
don't waste that egg no no
poor egg someone save the egg
[Applause]
that was a good crack wasn't it
oh the alert chocolate chunk brownies
and milk potential thank you i don't
like drinking milk like that um
that's not my thing but thank you for
the brownies cute drawing too
thank you this is my second time ever
making something on my own i'm already
proud of it it's made out of black
chocolate white chocolate almonds and
walnuts i didn't expect it to go this
well
hey they look so good
i think these look like my recipe
nice cute
good job oh you put them into a nice box
too
like that now that's
that's really cute that's um mostly like
what i originally imagined what people
would make when i when i started this
contest
like chocolates to give to someone
but okay i like all the other things too
except the scorpion and the egg
soup um
but i like that the other things too you
guys you guys got really uh
creative but mostly i was thinking of
stuff like that like pralines you know
but as anything's fine really the cakes
are awesome too oh
me and my sister made this lava cake
i mean it looks like a decent lava cake
good job noise oh my god yes
yes a sick ton of strawberries
on a chocolate cake oh yes
oh yeah oh wow that's a lot of chocolate
oh
i help you i hope you didn't give your
dog
you have that chocolate that's his eye
oh my god
oh my god dogs look so funny
[Laughter]
oh my god it looks so good i want
strawberries now
now here we got a kiana cosplayer
with a kitty cat
[Laughter]
what did she make um what's that uh
chocolate mousse with whipped cream and
raspberries yummy
10 out of 10. i mean that's just a full
set like a cute
cute girl cosplaying kiana with a
insanely beautiful cat and a freaking
chocolate mousse with raspberries
what else would i ever want oh the alert
that's
that's just 10 a million out of 10.
yeah thank you i just lost my voice for
a moment
now this is not really for my contest
seems like they made it for choco sensei
so i'm gonna skip that
and brownies yummy looking good
good job good job and we got something
sensitive again one second
i doubt i highly doubt that it's
sensitive well let me just
check it out oh yeah that that is not
that is not sensitive
look yummy it's kind of green
mint chocolate chip cheesecake
interesting
looks good yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
thank you guys for the super chats by
the way thank
thank you thank you
um this says send them to the usual room
and it has some brownies below
sorry guys you can't see the full
picture but i love it
send them to the usual room
and we got uh we got what
a cake it's a simple
simple she says full layered dark
chocolate and vanilla cake with
chocolate and vanilla buttercream icing
oh my god oh
it says the usual room on the cake oh my
god and since that
here it says peekaboo i see you oh my
god i look so angry
is that me oh my god
this is amazing
that's amazing i love it oh my god
oh my god that is
also one of the winners i would say look
at that [\h__\h] figure this is
terrifying that's not terrifying that's
beautiful
now we got um some not chocolate food as
well which i appreciate because
uh it's just so much chocolate and at
some point i'm gonna start feeling sick
uh we got some curry in heart form
but normally okay if you wouldn't add
chocolate there then you would have
failed the contest
is that donut self made it looks like
out of the store
but i i suppose itself mate thank you it
looks yummy
and we have some truffles why for kelly
it's supposed to be for me
we got bring on zero from uh brazil
yeah yeah yeah i know that i mean it
looks very simple
yeah i'm not sure i forgot what
that is isn't that just like chocolate
mixed with like caramel or something
like that
i'm not sure come to brazil yes yes
i've been there been there done that
stop asking me stop asking me to go
there
i will go there again eventually maybe i
did i didn't enjoy my time in brazil it
was fun
come to brazil now this um i saw this
before when i was scrolling through them
this looks so nice like i don't know the
colors
the color choice is so aesthetic
that blue with that brown
and then dark the dark chocolate brown
that's so aesthetic right they use some
food color
thank you now we have uh these closet
tears and sweat
oof i hope your sweat and your tears are
not inside of them
they look good though good job
these also look yummy valentine's sweet
i have made this here
yummy who did you make them for
hopefully for me
oh we got uh couldn't cook or bake
anything so i ended up making chocolate
biscuit sandwich on a bunch of nuts with
cocoa powder
[Music]
okay okay oh you tried
i guess you tried first attempt making a
mousse
my mom loved it you mean a mouse you
should try making a mouse
um just kidding but oh my god yummy dude
you got um the
bomb band that's nice outfit
of english what's that those berries
called in
in english again
blackberries yummy i love blackberries
that cake looks really oh i guess it's
not a cake it's a mousse
that looks really good thank you
herb chocolate cookies my entry for
girls valentine's juggling contest
oh my god i love those eyes
i love the eyes they look so crazy
i'm burped oh my god
the eyes look so crazy
product placement wait did you write
wait did she make a pee out of that oh
my gosh you did
eyes of fear
i love them
thank you sorry i can't watch a video
right now sorry
uh making chocolate stuff that already
exists in my room grated cocoa
ginger powder vanilla extract and
peppermint essence wow
i don't have that kind of stuff just
randomly in my home noise
yummy eight heart shaped truffles to
celebrate takatakara hitting 800k
subscribers
thank you thank you me and my grandma
made some valentine's day candy for our
family and i hope you would want to see
them too
oh so you don't make them didn't make it
for me okay
looking good though bad quality photo
trap my best what is that what does that
say okay
[Music]
yummy and what we got here
wait that's so skill that's like a whole
cake
with like strawberries and oh my god it
looks so well-made
[Music]
10-10 for that person now we got
chocolate brown and triple chocolate
cheesecake and taco many chocolates
ah that's so cute i wish you guys could
see the whole thing
check out the hashtag by the way okay so
this is the kind of stuff that we don't
want here
in my pho in my uh
and my hashtag thank you we're looking
at chocolates here okay
chocolates
[Music]
oh my god they also look so well made
look
oh okay you you barely see it but it
looks so good
ah wait the photo is even so well made
all right let me scroll a little bit
there we go
chocolate coconut tart i don't like
coconut but
it still looks really good
not really fine sicilians but haven't
figured out my own personal brownie
recipe
glory to kfp
you're all personal well would you like
to share that with me that looks really
good
wait what is that oh my god i thought
you know because they don't sell milk
in my country with in that kind of
thing so i i thought for a moment that
was like some kind of washing detergent
and that you're making
chocolate with like washing washing
machine detergent or yeah bleach or
something like that i was getting
worried for a moment but okay
you made hot chocolate nice
what is that that looks kind of worrying
to me okay it's a sword
okay good job
oh my god
that's sad isn't that the sketch that
inna made for me
in her beautiful swimsuit unfortunately
i raised the most design well
please send me the moulds oh my god
this person got molds with it give them
to me
please nice
what do you got here uh chocolate love
letter for my
cali what the [\h__\h] this is supposed to
be for me
looks good but whatever um
this is not for us i think
oh i can't this is something i can cook
this is one of the few things that i can
cook
chocolate el covered crepes
we call them in australia
yummy
thank you for inspiration for this
valentine's day presentation i made
chocolate travels and stuff
but you are okay with this okay so in
this case i forgive you because
you made it because of me but you gave
it to someone else
that's so cute like obviously you can't
i guess meet that person for real i
don't know maybe maybe
maybe you can i don't know but i see the
person behind the door
yummy that's so sweet that's just such a
sweet surprise
like like when you're when you can't
meet your loved ones before you bring
them some valentine's chocolate
to their door oh you are
a good i suppose you're a boyfriend so
you are a good boyfriend
nice respect
and now we got uh what we got
oh the same thing close to what i made
oh yeah that looks basically what i made
that looks like what i made
good job good job thank you for copying
my recipe
oh uh what we got
chocolate cupcakes are frosting oh
the quality of the picture looks like
you photographed a photo on your pc
with your phone like you you took a
photo of a picture on a monitor
i don't know um but nice one
uh next up oh those look good
yummy oh
nice advertisement nice promotion there
oh my chunks and chocolate covered
strawberries
oh yeah i need some okay um we have some
chocolate okay i'll be right back i'm
gonna get some chocolate one second
chocolate
okay
[Music]
i'm back and i got some chocolate i got
a jotto you guys know that one
g-i-o-t-t-o
that one is so yummy
so good so good
yummy yum yum
ha ha ha
um
hmm
all right
look at that smooth texture
i don't know what exactly that is what
you made that out of
um but it looks really good oh
now we got to my truffles nice
hmm
looking good oh my god
isn't it
i know what that is thank you that was
cute
um chocolate crab cake with peanut
butter cream and chocolate glaze
honey
and we got um monkey cake i'm looking at
an
easy solution huh you found the easy way
out didn't ya
for lug
what is that what is that you don't tell
me what it is but it looks good
what is that someone knows what it is
all right why why are people using my uh
my
hashtag for some weird things again okay
there we go we got another cosplayer
thank you for participating eating
eating kotori
i would never eat koto jitsan
thank you though thank you she did
another one with uh
the maid outfit cute
thank you
foreign
oh these look these look
well made oh what made by
austrian hens where is austria what kind
of country is that
and bill at chocolate villa
i don't know what the [\h__\h] australia is
where is that where is that supposed to
be
where is that even supposed to be is
that like
yeah near new zealand
is that where the koalas and the uh
dolphins and kangaroos are
my spin i've never heard of that country
before but
i'm from australia
why did you come out with this time
quick easy kettle
yeah the mug cake felt like i'm not
impressed but
but nice oh my god
oh your brother's birthday happy happy
super late birthday to your brother
that cake looks really good the the
glaze is also
really smooth and you got like a
inner chocolate cream layer nice
i think your brother must have been
really happy
these look cute
cute cute cute cute thank you
what is that chocolate penguins
that's supposed to be penguins
i guess i guess
i guess yet
yeah babes burp chocolate
cause you're the league of penguins oh
my god you must really love penguins
penguins are quite nice can we have a
penguin veto replacing
in her life not not
and penguin eh
i make normal cookies but i arranged to
cook with cocoa and chocolate because i
want to turn in this tag
i think this is a japanese mirror
oh where's she saw that does look good
what what is that what is that
this part made out of i wonder
in any case it looks good
cookie hmm
[Music]
oh my god that looks
really really good ah now we got some
really cute cookies
it's okay
i want to eat please
i don't want the video we don't need a
video
[Laughter]
i don't need a video
i don't what is the video from earlier
what what what's your video
ah i'm the one where i said i can't
watch videos right now
well thank god i didn't watch it
oh thank you
uh what we got here brownie was dark and
white chocolate
oh that's a lot of brownie mmm
i really need to learn how to make
brownies
that looks really good too oyster salt
we got i think another japanese beer
again
the one that made that insanely good
looking cake what happened to you
oh wow that's a lot of chocolate sugar
wow
brown is pretty simple try it i will i
will i will
oh
wait i will watch it because it's here
and i don't have to go anywhere else
again again
oh
[Music]
oh that's so soft oh
my god oh my god yes did you hear my
cactus now
yeah what is it
what is it you want chocolate you can't
eat chocolate i'm not good for
animals like you sorry
did you hear her
say hello baby wanna say hello
hello
say something say something
okay she normally doesn't really speak
much
except one is like about food then she
speaks a lot
in the morning when i wake up and i walk
around the apartment
and um go into the kitchen she's like
mom
uh brownie cake questionable frosting
quality
oh my god
okay um
indeed questionable wow
did you get like a phoenix mold what
what
you can put it on fire
i thought using a mold would be like
cheating but there was a lot of nuance i
wasn't prepared for and when i
think of phoenix i think fire so i lit a
couple on fire over a bowl
of love potion for love first yeah is it
because i told everyone that's my
favorite ice cream from um
uh 31 ice cream baskin robbins
wow who is that so cool
he was getting
wow i like that that's a good idea
damn what a fl he's just flexing
he's just
[Music]
damn now here we go that's uh art which
i normally would not accept but it looks
cute
got waffles and macarons and cupcakes
damn you're good at like food art
nice very cute
oh my god again
let me uh
okey-dokey here we are again
and normal cookies with raspberry jam
and dark chocolate
oh cookies
they're so round so cute
they look so thick
oh and really cute also i think i got
the same place mats
oh again someone made a mold
shape inside me on my marine's heart
symbol cracked on the edge while we're
removing it from the mold callus field
turned out pretty good and
oh we made others too here
oh it's cool yeah people are getting
really creative here
thank you
ah
you suck both of you
both of you
my god
usual room you know
it's mr fragment there's no one what is
that even
who's that
oh my god marvel cake from scratch
oh wait it looks so good
oh how do you make marble cake
it looks really good yummy
that's basically what i'm eating for
breakfast for the past three days
chocolate brownie with ice cream yummy
nice uh photography as well
good sense you got there and we got some
chalky hearts for your girlfriend well i
don't know i don't give a [\h__\h]
finnish marco brown is yummy why is it
finished though where's the difference
between finnish and
other countries brownies where's the
difference
tell me what is what's so special about
them
unfit oh because they're finished
because they're done
we got um panna cotta with grinded
hazelnut
an almond tofu with coconut flakes
yeah the tofu was so jiggly kelly's
mascara couldn't stand on it without
breaking
you could say it's too boring
nice and we got nutella chocolate crabs
noise i like to eat that very often
that's cute a little um you know who
that is
the cat yummy we got chocolate lava cake
oh
again someone with good photography
skill oh
that's so artistic cause like okay you
can't see the whole thing but he's like
cutting it
like oh my god that's like you are
flexing with photography you're trying
to get extra points of
good photos oh
and i love ninja job
wow these are these are pancakes they're
so dark
wow they look wow um
i have to say like if hershey's if that
hershey's
syrup tastes the way that hershey's
chocolate does
then i don't think this is good
but you guys
don't know what good chocolate tastes
like it seems
i've tried hershey's chocolate before
it's not
not good the syrup is better
oh i can see that i can see that it's
better as a syrup okay okay
okay then i'm gonna give this to super
syrup a try
what we got here first time making
chocolate i failed so many times and
finally complete my
strawberry serious chocolate oh
strawberry cereals yeah yummy
oh they look good it looks something a
little bit similar to what i did
what the hell um
what do you got here there's a cute ah
wait is that this yeah that's
the same person again as before with the
molds
yeah they're so cute oh my god i mean
there's some holes in
bubba which look kind of painful
cute oh my god
cute i want those mouths we should make
merchandise out of those molds
with those molds you could make those
keychains yourself save some money
but get the real thing
whoa belgium chocolate nice
that's what i like to see kiana can't be
nice
yes yes yes what do we have here oh you
meetings you
you again you try again okay
what is that rich chocolate what moose
cake
we've cashed you duck what okay
you're trying to be fancy here you're
trying to be fancy without wine and that
in the background
from southeastern australia honestly
australia australia makes
probably way better wine in australia
okay so next time get australian
wine okay
coal hazelnuts not so much
like this one is a really good taco
though i love with the spot chocolate
can um uh confirm very yummy
yes now we got what flew this
something you french
and my nutella filled french crabs were
made of clover
our great uncle alcohol
because i'm way too good at making
chocolate i'm also adding some bonus
cards to bribe my
weight into the stream
[Music]
oh yummy wait you gave the the thing
that i made to try to they don't look as
good as
the ones that what is that flag
i also like how you use that uh you guys
don't see it i hear you see it the
turnaround kfp chicken giving dakuma
some ocd triggers
you welcome dakuma
and me and my friend managed to poison
ourselves by pancake with a lot of
sweetness
sweetness from chocolate you poisoned
yourself with that
oh no the chicken at the top left you
don't see it but it's so cute
wait are there's like mini pancakes but
that reminds me like mini pancakes are
basically um an
australian dish called uh paisashmon
can recommend 10 out of 10. oh is that
supposed to be like
the orange is like supposed to be me and
the pink one is supposed to be cali
cute tacoma
[Music]
okay let's go for them a little bit
quicker
that's cute that's not chocolate so
you failed the mission but that is cute
we got some cookies
we got chocolate crab with raspberries
yes
let me open that uh
yummy yummy uh-huh
that's very romantic with it with
candlelight
it's not loading come on come on oh
that's uh what is that it's just
a lot of fruits with uh dark chocolate
and sea salt flakes
yeah interesting we got heart-shaped
brownies
we got that thing again
[Music]
the effort though oh it does look
i don't know about that but the sakata
looks uh pretty accurate i mean
yeah it looks pretty accurate
basically sakota is an australian um
famous cake it's a chocolate cake with
chocolate glazing
glaze chocolate covered in chocolate
grease
glaze and chocolate and inside there's
like this uh
okay you don't see it but you see it
here there's a really thin
layer in between with uh like um it's
supposed to be apricot jam
it's always supposed to be apricot jam
[Music]
um
chocolate oh nama chocolate
wait do people call that nama chocolate
in english too
i thought that was uh the nama is isn't
that that's japanese
you call
nude choco and what do you call that in
uh english
nama like not my chocolate
raw yeah it's supposed to be like raw
chocolate it means raw chocolate in
japanese
hey what would you call that in english
just you call it raw chocolate
never heard of it till now oh
interesting okay
ah cute moment of course it's for the
high chance of chocolate challenge here
are some
yurikuma arasi chocos i don't know what
that is
but i think it's some kind of like brand
or something i suppose
looking cute and we got some more molds
oh
oh okay
cute very very cute must be very
delicious thank you
some more brownies i can't be cake
ah wow
oh oh
that looks good too good job dominique
we got some chocolate chip cupcakes
yummy oh here's my okay this is where
the stream started so
oh no that's where i talk oh okay no
this is not where i started
this is me that's me now we got here
yes yes yes and we got the
chocolate turtles uh
okay yes they totally look like turtles
yes
thank you that's cute
read that a face ah
it's so cute
oh you made some molds too wow so many
people are making molds this is so easy
to make molds
how are you guys making them i guess
it's pretty easy huh
yeah oh yeah
i wonder what that tastes like
what is this is that
is that a cake that looks like a tart
stuck a chocolate tart
cake
and that's just oreos thrown together
nutella cake pops oh
okay i don't know what the shape is
supposed to be that's a heart but the
other is i'm not sure
let's try making kfp [\h__\h] ah oh
that's supposed to be kfp ah
uh yeah k
[Music]
f p
yeah i can see it with a lot of uh
fantasy
parsley with brownies and chocolate ice
cream thank you
oh oh hello there's me i can't give my
cake first time just for the for the
contest thank you
it goes like and then there's me
thank you that's very cute thank you it
looks yummy i like that
uh it's strawberries
[Music]
yummy i love strawberries strawberry
cakes and stuff like that oh yes give it
to me i can eat it all day
every day we got something really cute
here too
like a kiara doll with a with a um
kotori cake back then kotori didn't have
a name yet i think
still waiting for him to drive it i have
finished a girl yeah back then
he was still called a colonel
oh it's supposed to be like a oh i
thought about the top of it looks like
oh my god i love that idea
i love that idea and the doll looks so
cute it's either felt
or something like i guess wow
nice i'm real tender stole my name
it's okay it's okay kotori is even
better name oh
we got um art thank you
but we were looking for actual edible
food
thank you thank you some brownies mmm
and some cookies
now that i think i think we reached the
part like i remember like seeing that
before i wonder if i saved that before
oh that is a
that that looks like a big mess but
it's supposed to be uh chocolate lemon
bars i would like to give it a try
because i like uh
lemon tasting things
kind of be love can't be represented
brownies and chocolate chips and flax
meal what what's that flax meal what is
that wow
so much icing i love icing
and dark chocolate with walnut bits
mixed through banana chips on the top
and white chocolate drizzles on top nice
yeah yeah yeah sounds good to me
[Music]
i can't open it right now it seems oh
it's very slow there we go
yeah that looks good
wow proud i didn't make any poop
comparisons
not yet
thank you for the super chat i'll read
it again later
any excuse to make brownies thank you
everyone show us those emotes we're the
memory modes where are they
us those emotes
thank you oh you didn't make anything
and it's hershey's chocolate which must
be terrible
uh ooh
spring rolls chocolate cookies or snacks
maybe i said i suppose it just took like
some
some i don't know rolled snacks and
poured chocolate over it okay
some people are putting a lot of effort
into these
and some people are putting like no
effort into these or like barely any
effort which is okay
which is okay those are funny too um
[Music]
but i'm happy everyone participated hmm
that's basically what you detention what
the [\h__\h] i did
i put a lot of effort into mine okay i
even i even packaged it nicely for cali
what i made okay i
i put effort into the chocolate i made
as the first time i ever made chocolates
how dare you criticize me you're going
to the usual room
[Music]
the texture looks really good it's just
a chiffon cake but
it looks really really well made thank
you
and we got someone who made like the
same chocolates that i did nice
we got uh brownie tart pie
noise looking good we got another
mississippi mud pie chocolate ah
chocolate graham cracker crust yummy
with homemade chocolate brownie filling
top of a mix of homemade with
yummy open it open it
open it quick okay you guys can barely
see it but
yeah that looks good
yeah well
[Laughter]
thank you for participating
what's that okay you guys can't see it
oh what is that my uh chocolate covered
marshmallows okay
thank you then we got
brownies
happy valentine's day balloon so sweet
oh oh wait the k k heart scenes with
kelly
lips and candy loves kelly ah
is that just a bowl of whipped cream
or is that a brownie and then top of
whipped cream
okay this is why they start looking
familiar to me i wonder why i stopped
introducing them
but i i i i swept through a lot of them
very quickly on the previous stream as
well so i'm gonna try to go
through the rest as well that looks
really yummy
like the presentation obviously
and then this drink looks really good
and you guys can see it but there's like
this cake here
the rolled cake yummy
i love that that looks so good and it's
like in the snow
whoa good job with that
i love that and that's a work in
progress
and that is brownies nice thank you i've
yeah i've seen this before
have i shown this on string
uh a moose cake with sugar caramel
decoration
with chocolates the cream what what is
that
it looks interesting there's a lot going
on here
you don't remember i i definitely saved
them though
and we got another cake
yummy is that mint chocolate ice cream
though i don't like that one
thank you some peanut butter chocolate
crisps yummy
hearts of fire mexican cinnamon
chocolate
with crisp fries yeah sounds
interesting and we got oh
french dogs with hazelnut chocolates for
you are you talking about nutella
yummy no what
if this is a crime against a friend why
would it be i always eat french toast
with a [\h__\h] ton of nutella on top of it
that's the best way to eat it
what's that
homemade chocolate ice cream between two
homemade chocolate chip cookies
topped with that's like an ice cream
sandwich right those are so yummy
topped with marshmallow cream and lint
chocolate yeah hey that's creative
thank you that looks good and we got
some
nice looking hearts mold it
saying heart challenger thank you it
looks yummy too and these
these pancakes these crabs look so
beautiful
like look at them look at how even
the colors are i i never can't i never
managed to make mine look like that
but i make them a little bit different
like i always make uh
i don't make crepes i make palette
chinking that's something different
and they're not supposed to look that
perfect so that's okay
they look really good yeah
i think that's just a meme right
and
[Music]
um rice chocolate famous dessert in my
country that just looks like a
chocolate soup
i like the movement in that picture
though
and oh wait here's kelly's
wait wait look at that we got uh what we
have here wow
that's a lot of things oh yeah you made
so many things
thank you yummy and here we go we have
cali here
tari tanner yatsuda i ate them
and uh they were they were pretty good
she made them with
uh japanese chocolate but and i
generally prefer
overseas chocolate but this one was
really good
uh interesting how she
wrote cabbie and then ate
the eye obviously
ah but i was yummy i was so surprised
that kelly participated
[Music]
when i went to her place to watch shrek
that was fun too oh i miss callie i'm
miss kathy
oh i miss her
i miss her i dino
hmm well from here
on from here on i'm sure that i showed
them on stream but i just
swooshed through them so i'm gonna
swoosh for them again but a bit slower
thank you look at these things when
something stands out i'll stop like for
some of this tanyaki
yeah you made taiyaki do you guys know
what taiyaki is
in japan and there's this uh like fish
form like only the only the form is like
a fish but it doesn't taste like fish
yeah it's a it's made out of like normal
dough like
like waffledale oh and it's filled with
all kinds of things
yeah yeah yeah it's really yummy mostly
it's red bean but they fill it with all
kinds of things
it's really yummy they start they um
sell it at like uh like outside in like
smaller uh foods
well how what do you call that stalls
what do you call those kind of
places
food cells yeah yeah yeah yeah
sometimes i i got them at those food
stalls in japan
they don't taste like fish no no no no
no but they're really yummy they got
like
all kinds of fillings and they're like
fresh and hot mmm
oh i see skin skin
we got some cookies we got some
red velvet roast cupcakes mmm
hard brownies oh yummy yummy yummy wait
in front of a uh fireplace damn
you got a fireplace damn son i want a
fireplace too
nice what do we have here
it's all white chocolate i don't see it
show me ah
[Laughter]
cute very cute thank you oh that looks
good too
oh yummy chocolate souffle
oh you know what i love that reminds me
of a creme brulee i love creme brulee
i'm a huge fan of creme brulee
i haven't eaten a good one in a long
time
um pancho everywhere you go is a
fireplace
oh yummy yum everything looks so yummy
hey there's my stream in the background
goodnight
chocolate covered pocky homemade pocky
pretzels
for the most beautiful feelings in the
world oh with candles
oh and those are like my feathers oh you
guys don't see it but here that's
supposed to be like uh
my feathers cute
again well thank you again oh they look
pretty
what okay i guess so you didn't get that
from starbucks uh the
the drink inside the drink inside the
salad made right morning chocolate
coffee wow
those cookies they look like like the
soft kind of cookies i love that kind of
uh chocolate cookies like the softer
ones like i like the the not so soft
ones too but
don't these look like super soft i like
those too
you can literally see the softness here
why don't gift for you kiara thank you i
hear something sensitive
what could that be wow really
that's marked as sensitive
wow yummy that's huge though
what wow is that is that brownies
oh what do we have here what's that
made simple cranberry lime macaroons
with white chocolate cover
oh white chocolate i love white
chocolate you guys like white chocolate
i love white chocolate i love white
chocolate and milk chocolate and all
kinds of chocolate but dark chocolate is
not really my thing
why she saw oh cute
i like how some of you guys like always
put like some kind of
like detail like kotori or me there
thank you that's cute that looks really
pretty what the hell is that
why it got burnt oh no
no f
f for this buddy oh no
what is that chocolate chip m m cookies
these look yummy too they look very uh
simple
they don't they also look pretty soft
they could have maybe used a tiny bit
more time in the oven maybe
i don't know they look good though
and we got valentine's fudgy brownies oh
too much chocolate oh i like these
because they got raspberry jam inside
yummy
again that cake seen this before
and brownies brownies so many brownies
people really like brownies oh we got
some shortbread
lemon lemon shortbread right wait why
chocolate millionaires chop sure what is
what is that this is the second time i
hear about that what is that what is
that i wonder
oh don't worry don't worry rice don't
worry
it's very interesting
so many brownies yummy they look good
is a peanut clusters this is what you
call guinea chocolate i'm not sure about
that
oh no no yeah we've seen that oh my god
there's even a instructions on how to
make it
i don't need that i don't need
instructions on that
also there's something i need to skip
we've seen a [\h__\h] before i've showed
that on my stream before
so that's that that's just eminem's
guys it's just
eminem's lined up to say kfb
and we got these ones we have seen
before right you guys remember these
you guys remember this one this is
really cute turkish you're so adorable
they're so adorable i love these
yeah we have seen those right these look
so pretty too
remember this
like these remind me when me and kelly
were like um shopping together
for like uh souvenirs she bought like
some like
universe looking like chocolates like
that looked like some planets she got
really excited when she saw them
and those are kind of remind me of those
so pretty bam what what's happening here
oh no burnt brownies
oh how cute some bears some
cakes looking good what the hell no one
asked for that but okay
have i shown that on stream before have
i shown this one before
no one asked for this
but okay oh thank you too
so disappointed also that's not even
nutella what the hell is a fake nutella
ah something normal again thank god
oh sorry about that
not supposed to show stuff like that
here we go again got some brownies some
more brownies
what's that peanut butter chocolate bars
roasted cashews almonds coconuts oats
and peanuts
yummy i mean they don't gotta be honest
they don't look
good but what
what wait what you started speeding
after mine i remember that so if you see
mine you've gone too far
okay okay thank you thank you
uh yeah we really barely had any time
last time i was really on the time
pressure sorry about that guys
i know all of you guys put some effort
into it and took your time
and even though even the really low
effort ones i really appreciate so i
want to show them properly no matter if
it's 500 or 1000
cookies or chocolates i still want to go
through them so
thank you guys for participating and
those look good and this is a work in
progress
look at that cute doll can we sell that
as merchandise
you know how we uh have uh the the [\h__\h]
in the plushies
as merchandise now but i hope that we
can i thought it would be really cool if
we could have like
like us as plushies as well
yeah maybe some
someday we can have uh
plushies of ourselves yeah
now that's uh i love chocolate bananas
okay
but that's kind of making me nervous we
got some
phoenix shaped white cake yummy
a brownie cake between what am i reading
brownie cake with phoenix shaped white
chocolate
yummy and the cookies ah
there's a duck taco cookies i just want
to say i didn't read the name so i was
like oh these look like dankoma cookies
i didn't even read the name but yeah it
is dakoma cookies
look wait that's a
wow yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
ooh some truffles for yourself well then
i'm just kidding why she's so yummy
thank you
wow that looks very colorful
my mom and cousin helped me on this oh
oh wow wow
wow it's like a like a
ton of chocolate sweets put together
made into a cake
hmm it has teeth what the um
this one who has teeth
now we got uh myself apparently that's
made up of chocolate not sure how
it uh looks like a i don't know
it's hard to see what that is like made
out of
oh thank you we got some more chocolate
crepes
i love making these myself and again we
call them panda chicken like there's a
an australian dessert called panachinkin
which is basically crabs but just a
little bit
thicker and we roll them and we put some
like
jam or or nutella or something in there
it's basically crabs but just thicker
you know
and kind of easier to make i feel like
for crabs you need like the the the
right kind of
um uh
um how to say like a like a cr
like a crab uh thing to
you know what i mean and a right pad or
like a like a whole
crap crap making a thingy
if you know what i mean yeah it seems
kind of hard to make
crabs because they are supposed to be so
super thin
yeah like a crab station
yeah the hot plate yeah the hot plate
that's what i mean
oh my god guys oh my god you know what i
loved it
like craps and pancakes right but like
one thing
pisses me off like anime conventions and
stuff like that
they often have like like crepes right
like chocolate crabs with bananas inside
and all that
as like snack and i i always get so
hungry and i never really bring a lot of
food with me and even if i do
when i go to you know events like that i
i always think
always end up craving for the fresh food
right
but those crabs are always so so
so expensive they're so expensive
they sound like one tiny ass crap
for like eight dollars or something like
that
they they sell that in every anime
convention all over the world i think i
think they
everywhere like not even animal
conventions there's like all kinds of
like
conventions they sell craps
and they they're so expensive
but they're yummy so what can you do
these look good ah
oreo bun buns i thought it's like
crumbled like oreos inside
with uh white chocolate
oh i like the orange gives it a nice
color
thingy nice cute
oh chocolate cupcakes blue icing oh
you know chocolate can look much much
better if you add some color to it so
good job on that we got some
swiss chocolate ice cream no the
presentation is good other people a
way worse job
[Music]
you wanted
thank you a long time japanese viewer of
mine who is always here
always always thank you oh these look
good
i want to try those look at that text
texture that's like
nama chocolate and like the on top is
like like chocolate powder
it looks so soft
i gotta be honest this doesn't really
look good
chocolate ice cream in the shape of an
ice cube with meal milo powder
topping it doesn't really look good i
gotta tell ya i hope you enjoyed eating
that dough
thank you
i gotta be honest okay
i'm judging your chocolate
milo is delicious i don't even know what
that is
we know it's disgusting oh there we go
we have the different opinions
i think we have uh i think we have like
um
like something like milo in my country
too
but something it's something else yeah
kitten made a lot of cats
living up to their name i decided to
make blondies because my mom would
always make them and they're delicious
but just making them as is would be
boring so i upgraded them
nice thank you
blondies is that what you call like
brownies that are just like
[Music]
like like that
but vanilla brown oh
look at that that looks good that
strawberry damn look at that skill that
devotion
this looks good only she saw yeah
low effort really low effort but okay
um i like the tiny one
wait that's a that's a raspberry wow you
saw you got a lot of green on there you
could have trimmed
the green a little bit yeah i gotta
but okay i'm in a nice nice color touch
but low effort again
ah here's guys so this is where i
started like i stopped
stopped going for them slowly i suppose
garnish that's a little bit too much
garnish okay
by the way is there anyone here who like
at dinners
or like lunches where there's like a
little bit of a like a green garnish day
like it's like like a leaf of something
is there anyone who actually eats that
who eats that and who doesn't
like i never eat that i do
i will always eat it no no no yes yes no
yes
oh seems like 50 50.
seems pretty 50 50.
you're not supposed to yeah i mean i
mean if it's mint
then i think you're supposed to eat it
but sometimes
i got some nuts stuck um from the from
the choco okay
i'm not okay i'm not even i already know
what you guys are gonna say about me
saying that so i'm just gonna drink
drink my orange juice
oh my god my cheeks hurt
well anyway so i guess this is where we
stopped
like where we started like zooming right
the towel truffles what the cute kitty
cat
whoa so cute i don't care about towel
but i care about the cat the cat is much
more important
for people who don't watch the riser
streams that i do
for people who don't watch the attitude
riser streams the joke here is
that i've been playing this game after
the rise out one
and attend a rise at two where one of
the characters is
this boy called tal and i didn't use him
in my team in atheism one
and other artillerizer too he changed a
lot and looks much more handsome
so
he was hoping cause he seems to be a fan
of him he was hoping that i was gonna
use him but i still didn't give him a
chance so
he's very disappointed and he's always
talking about tao
sorry yes i still don't use him
i mean i used him for one round the
other day for one fight
that's good enough so yeah i guess
that's it
uh after that is just uh stuff that we
already went through yup yup yup yeah i
remembered
[Applause]
sandra i haven't heard from xander in a
while
is he doing fine i haven't heard from
him in a while
well that one was so cute too
look at all these chocolates
oh that's those ice cubes
oh look at those frogs oh man yeah
thank you thank all of you this looks so
funny
i don't know but this looks like that
like that like that frog
okay just looks so funny
it looks so soft i want to poke it i
want to poke this thing
yeah yeah that was fun
thank all of you for participating in uh
this little challenge i hope it was fun
for you guys to try something because i
think many of you would normally never
use such an opportunity
mine never even showed up what do you
mean did you
send it in super late because
wait i mean okay you know we still have
time to let me scroll all the way up
and check out the ones that i skipped
did you send it in too late because i
skipped the late ones
where is it yeah i'm careful at the top
don't worry there's like a lot of the
what do you mean with that you said ah
you sent it on the
what on the ah 12th february
wait you know what i'm gonna what's your
what's your twitter
name user slash is it something with
daisy
yeah sometimes the thing the the
submissions just don't show up in the
hashtag they really don't like when i
look for my art hashtag um
some things just don't show up i find
them through dakama liking them
but they don't show up on my hashtag
search
i don't know why
uh
yeah maybe like something like a shadow
band or something
daisy i'm waiting for a twitter handle
waiting for it
i'm gonna check out your submission
but you probably tweeted a lot since
then didn't you
probably can't really find it huh
[Music]
it i don't like
these one
i found it
found it
[Music]
wait am i losing fps again i feel like
i'm
ah no should be fun anyway
this is the one i have apparently miss
sorry about that some things religious
don't show up
that looks cute it's kotori
cute you use the cream cheese frosting
with
keto brownies does that mean wait what
does that mean again kettle
what does that mean again you made like
uh
what what does that mean again i forgot
what that means
a low carb ah
one of the poor guys lost his beak no
oh no he really did oh
well well well anyway thank you for that
submission thank you
let me wait one second
oh let's see what do we have here um
like there was a super late ones
i i will not get into
[Music]
okay we got uh this one
who was linked that was cute so many
colors
very orange and and you got that you got
the greenish color that's in my hair as
well actually you know you picked
actually the
how did you pick these perfect colors
wait you're like they're like
like it like as if you picked them right
off
from the top of my head look at that
those colors okay you can't see it but
look at
it
okay let's see what else we got
[Music]
the crust is made out of peanuts it has
a chocolate in the base and then it was
filled with
ricotta cheese and strawberry jam to top
it off that was from
a finashi aha
at kf princess i like your twitter name
i like that twitter name damn uh
thank y'all that looks yummy
and we got we got
we got this here i know i'm late but i
really wanted to make something for her
challenge
so i did chocolate waffle with nougat
chocolate sprinkle topping yummy
that looks good i have like a waffle
iron
but because i love making waffles but
they never turn out like
so good i don't know
i've tried but how do people make a make
such
good waffles like when like where the
outer side
is like kind of like crunchy crispy
and inside like low-key soft i just
can't get it like that
a waffle iron shut up
[Music]
very fake batter
i've tried so many times temperature is
key
[Music]
but anyway i've been having i've been
i've been ordering
uh some really good waffles recently and
they're really yummy
so i just i just completely gave up on
making them myself
what did you hit up the iron first i
think i did i'm pretty sure i did yeah
um it's really really difficult like
either it like sticks
too much to the iron and everything just
falls apart
or or like when i try to leave it in
there longer to get it more crispy
on the outside it just i don't know it
just doesn't bring
no
thanks for the membership it makes me
mad anyway we got
another late submission we got this here
it's a huge cake damn
the orange cake damn thank you for every
intention
and my fellow employees i created this
chocolate carefree building cake oh it's
supposed to
be okay building oh there's doors here
you just don't see them
and and i hope you're willing to give me
another chance for that horrid pudding
earlier
thank you thank you that looks amazing
good job
also love the berries that you added
there as well
uh we got another late one
we got lft here and
[Music]
plus so speedo aralimena
i wanted to do a peruvian entry oh my
god gordon
ramsay super chatted oh my god what i'm
surprised that these chocolates are so
good
you all have unfortunately raised the
bar for all of
for all you anything other that perfect
well disappoint me what
raise the bar for all you anything other
that perfect well this what i don't
understand the scent are you drunk
gordon ramsay is he drunk
anyway so back to back to the topic
uh i wanted to do a peruvian entry but
while peruvian food is the best we don't
what is peruvian
like i know peru but like what kind of
food is there from there sorry for not
knowing
we don't use chocolate much so i thought
about using
chocolate desserts from that copycat
country
wait wait peru has a oh that's the peru
flag
what's that
it's like you're throwing a party i
didn't like because of that
tablecloth did you throw a patty alone
but i see uh three spoons
interesting and two two fingers aaron
very interesting lftd very interesting
hey but hey good to know that uh peru
has like this
this fake flag you know obviously
australia
is is the real deal
just kidding it feels like we have some
kind of connection australia and peru
i guess i guess i gotta visit peru one
day to check out you know
how sideways australia looks like
thank you
oh what about this one we got some
more truffles here from the kfp
inventory manager thank you
we got
gosh when i saw this when i was oh my
god when i was checking the entries
before the stream i was going for this
and i saw this and i thought that this
was
chocolate cream or something pudding
with like
meat on top of it you know like that
like hash
meat like a like uh
oh my god a finally hear magic was like
the same like what the [\h__\h] is that
salami
oh but apparently it's a uh strawberry
jam
thank god for a moment i was like why
are you doing this to me
i was like please don't do this to me
why ah
we got a quite pretty looking cake here
wow
look at the way this
glaze chocolate glaze is like reflecting
oh my god wow
damn
so
we got uh some more late entries here
only showing a little bit here thank you
sorry there's some some random things in
between for all the late entries there's
some random things in between so i'm
trying to not show that stuff
oh my god we got another lava cake video
foodborne look
um that one is a bit
not not as impressive as the other one
but it looks beautiful though
but the way that the chocolate was
flowing out wait that was me that was a
little bit of me there did you see that
ah that was me anyway
thank you the other one was a bit more
like wow
but this one looks good too
[Music]
oh my god
no someone um tagged
hachima's valentine's day thingy with
like the the
i don't know what was that a crocodile
par or something like that
uh tagged it with my hashtag
i was like you disgusting
ah disgusting
disgusting anyway here's some cute
cookies
and uh some more cute cookies thank you
for the late submissions as well
thank you very much and we got something
here as well and these look cute
too wow and these two they're so
colorful
thank you some more here
thank you thank you thank you people
using molds again
some more here what is that that's a
merry chocolate meringue pie
what is that what is that
okay boy here you go again i hope you
like it looks great but do you
do you live by yourself
an interesting meme
[Music]
and oh so much chocolate peanut butter
mouth okay
yummy
well this person also is late mixed up
the dates and only gets to the fudge
interesting that's that's a cute verb
though
yeah you got some um
i give you some good grading because of
the
because that's a cute verb okay okay
uh that's uh okay there's one more the
last one
cinnamon toast chocolate interesting
looks yummy too i mean
you know not not too bad i've seen words
today
and that concludes that all the all the
talk
i think yeah wow we combined with the
last stream together
i think we pretty much went for all of
them
yeah that's pretty much all i've seen
so sorry if someone still didn't uh show
up properly
uh probably maybe something to do with
the hashtag
[Applause]
500 submissions or 400 or something like
that thank you all so much for taking
the time
to do something like that i thought that
was that really cute and as i said
before
i'm i'm just guessing that many of you
would normally not do something like
this
like out of nowhere or like even even
like for valentine's day i guess many of
you would normally not have
taken up on that
challenge if there was no challenge
so i think it was a you know a nice
idea especially because many of you i
suppose are just you know stuck at home
and just not doing much besides um
watching streams and stuff or maybe
sometimes going to like like uh on zoom
calls
with school or with work or whatever
so doing something a little bit
different in between i hope that i was
able to
cheer you guys up and motivate you guys
you're calling
you always needs no not necessarily i'm
just saying you know
many people work from home right now and
just don't have much of a
like you know change like
like it's just uh
i don't know i'm not saying everyone
just i'm just guessing some people
here are probably uh maybe a little bit
bored
and i'm i'm glad that i got you guys to
do something
yeah something creative and something
fun
we should do it again i'm so proud of
you
thank you for participating all of the
submissions are really really nice
not all of them i mean why the hell
would you use a scorpion
why
[Music]
like the japanese viewers there were
some japanese viewers uh contributions
and they were all
very serious and well made meanwhile my
my overseas viewers like to mess around
with me
thank you i still i i will never forget
whatever that was with the salami i
i i i i mean that's
i i i will somehow never forget but at
the same time it's
it was a traumatic experience so my
brain is kind of like pushing it outside
of my brain i'm trying to not remember
um yeah
i will never recover from that
what you gonna do huh what you gonna do
about that like i've been hurt by that
submission
no there were a lot of funny submissions
and many really creative ones as well
and some some of you guys really have a
lot of talent and
seem to be doing this more often and
some of you
seem to be like uh beginners like me
well maybe you found an interest in it
and now have some motivation
to do stuff like this more often that
would be nice
thank you all for participating i hope
we can do something like this again
should we read some super chats
from this stream sure shall we read some
some more oh wait gordon ramsay send the
sec sent a second
super each other perfection you mad cow
why are you suddenly getting so upset
it's not my fault that your grammar was
shitty
it's not my fault why are you getting
mad at me gordon ramsday
huh you're just frustrated with your own
life it seems don't take it out of me
it's not my problem maybe you should
learn some english grammar
i didn't understand your super chat it's
not my problem not my fault
my english is superior okay
okay so let's switch over to
hello i'm back
and i shall now
read lesson
by the way tomorrow is near automata i
think right
tomorrow's stream is near automata
hopefully nothing will crash um i might
um you know last time we uh
finished a bus and then my game crashed
uh so before i could say
like it didn't even give me the option
to save which i think is lame
the game should i know the game doesn't
have other safe but it should at least
like autosave
after like a boss please what the hell
i did i still have the mod can someone
send me that like on on twitter and
maybe explain me how it works on twitter
please i don't know how that kind of
stuff works playing
and someone like help me with that
please
and there's a mob that makes the people
have been telling me about it
i already did please send me again
yeah i don't mind getting duplicates
some people might be able to
uh explain it a little bit better than
others who knows
so anyway let's start reading let me
change the bgm choose true because we've
been hearing this all the time now
also random but
i woke up today and i go on my i open my
phone
i open my twitter the first thing i see
is like five tweets
at me five people tweeting at me
uh like kiara kiana
got a mission for you i could have
picked a baker i'm like what what what
the [\h__\h] what's going on
i was like what and i i opened her
stream and it was
already past that point but apparently
she
wants me to build kfp
at one specific spot but i'm like i just
built kfb
what i was so confused like what
why why i don't understand i mean okay
if she tells me to do it i guess i'll do
it
but i don't know i literally just last
week
like three days ago four days ago i just
built kfp
with super sampler and now she wants
well she wants me to build another one
for her pickled and brand
but interesting okay i don't know if i'm
allowed to
go there alone i i might have to do it
as a collaboration though i don't know
did she i didn't i didn't
watch the full arc i watched afterwards
like an hour of that stream
but i didn't watch the part where she
actually talked about me
did she does anyone know if she like
expected me to make it on my own or to
make it with her because i'm not sure if
i'm allowed to go to the server and just
do my own thing
i mean it's a mission from piccola uh
senpai so
it's not exactly my own thing i've been
given a mission and i have to fulfill it
monopolize the fast food industry in the
japan server yeah
uh i'll i'll check on that if i'm
allowed to color because we have a
minecraft stream planned this week
i was planning on finishing my house but
i guess we can also build the kfp branch
again
and the japanese server if i'm allowed
to
uh i'll i'll see what we can do
uh we'll figure it out um
[Music]
um
so uh that was that
[Music]
no no so let me start reading super
chats
thank you for the pinky extremely late
late raiza
six month super chat crazy how it's been
six months and you've done so well in
that time
thank you thank you
thank you oh thank you to love i'm
excited to stick with you as
for as long as i'm able to ah also that
boss battle did almost make a cry
[Music]
ah it's like i made you proud
you were my teacher i i made you proud
oh that makes me happy
hopefully i'm the coming battles the
coming boss battles will be
uh going well too
i'll do my best to do some more alchemy
um so that the next one won't be such a
huge
huge struggle but
yeah with the right bombs and focusing
on on what's going on
it did it wasn't even that hard
so yeah i've i definitely
learned a lot more um in the last
episode that i
like i finally grasped a lot new things
that i
didn't really quite grasp before so i
think
i'm really like i think i i finished my
training
but still i still need you motion so
stay with me
jacob 47 from the reading yesterday you
seem to prefer the exploring side of
minecraft yes yes to the building side
yes i do i thought you might be
interested in no man's sky which is like
minecraft but all about exploring
i heard about the game i think i've seen
some graphics and i think we might have
maybe permission for that uh i'll check
it out
thank you for the uh idea
thank you it's trash
what nice game it's better now
it's nothing like minecraft yeah i mean
from what i've seen it also did not
remind me of minecraft at all
like how is the game how can you compare
a game with minecraft but then say
it's it has like no building but that's
like basically what minecraft is about
then it's definitely not like minecraft
that's like saying
that's like saying um
australia is like japan
but just without the japanese people and
the japanese language
or wait is that an is that a good sample
is that what i'm trying to say
or like it's like it's like saying
ah that's like saying
that's like saying
that's that's like saying
[Music]
uh
uh yeah i guess it's like like pizza
is like fried chicken just without
not mmm and no no yeah
yeah yeah just without the chicken and
about the frying
frying part
i don't know
uh anyway but
still i've heard of that game before and
it didn't look it did look pretty
cute thank you ah thank you for the
pinky for the pinky promise
that's so cute i promise that i will
keep watching your stream also happy
white day
pink one for pinky promise thank you
skye happy white day to you too i guess
where you from
this they celebrate white day there too
do they well are you just saying it
because i did a white day stream
i wonder why muna dankeshan can't make
it to the stream so i wanted to say a
proactive story to those who witnessed
my submission if it's true
that is very correct of you to do
because uh
yes an apology
was necessary
kristoff duncan happy birthday gorgeous
sorry i'm broke my insanely hot bus
released an acrylic stand up and i just
cannot resist her
womanly fast i mean wilds what would
that mean what does that mean i don't
know
what wilds means but the rest of that is
very um
flirt thank you
yeah um that seems like a good
explanation
a good excuse i'll take it hmm
i'm not that much in the far in the
future how are you doing today i'm doing
okay
um i got my amazon things today my
orders from amazon like the the internet
thingy the the ethernet cable thingy for
the
for my phone and it seems like it really
did
the trick yeah so i'm really excited
about that
thank god also
um
what should i eat for dinner today i'm
actually glad that today's stream wasn't
that long
wow it's only it's only 2 hours 20
minutes it's gonna be shorter than
yesterday's super chat rating
but since it's ending so early i could
maybe order something
uh some food because it's not too late
noise yeah
uh we should get done with the super
chats pretty early too
that was a short stream yeah but i think
that's good too i shouldn't i shouldn't
be streaming six hours
seven hours eight hours every freaking
day
right now
you just gotta
also with a pinky promise oh thank you
for the pink super chat
i'm so cute you guys so cute yesterday's
dumb joke aside i live
pretty comfortably and have no major
changes expected so i can't foresee any
reason i would leave
even if my finances change i can't super
chat as much i'll still be in chat
yeah that would make me happy doesn't
matter if you
guys like if if someone's financial
situation changes i would be
very happy if you guys still stay here
to um yeah be in the chat and support me
and stay subscribed and all that you
know
there is absolutely no shame in not
being able to donate at all or not being
able to donate as much as
you used to that is no problem
that is totally understandable yes
and i want you guys to take care of
yourselves as well
i want you guys to give yourself some
nice things and some
and and and save some things too
a rare win for chat tech support indeed
kind of rare yeah
mostly the chat gives me so many ideas
and i don't know what to do with it
but i don't know who else to ask you
know there's like so many things that
could could be the reason why things go
wrong and i just need some kind of ideas
like generally
i don't i don't mind like having the
chat confuse me
it at least gives me like a rough idea
of what could maybe be the problem and i
appreciate that thank you guys
hmm the manual i don't give a [\h__\h] about
the manual
you can't read a minute shut up there's
no manual about my
pc i didn't receive a manual
i don't know why it crashes in certain
situations ever since i moved
there's no [\h__\h] manual for that
but honestly i don't know how to figure
out like what's wrong let's let's see if
near
crashes tomorrow if i install that mod
let's see let's see what happens
and so yeah anyway thank you thank you
derrick
p 1 2 3 4 am thank you thank you for the
pinky
consider watch well what
you mean the color red oh consider
rot what
wait is that like supposed to be like
the english word consider
rot nature consumes all without bias but
this is not
sad it enriches the land for life to
blossom and new
if this finds you surrounded by a decay
have hope
the things we think of as final
may just be the start of a new cycle
jonathan koslowski
what normally i'm impressed by
your um
normally you impress me with your
philosophy
but i don't know maybe today my brain is
not working properly but today all i can
say is
what
like i gotta take an eye
i don't know what you're saying
sorry jonathan koslowski come again come
again
thank you
thank you for the pinky though
whatever kfb employees told you on
yesterday's stream with lies and slender
lies and slender i tell you
also i don't want to advise near me or
my security will be on you faster than
you die and marry
[Laughter]
stupid you mean extension
is that i think oh yeah that's a
two pink super chats uh turning into a
wonder at super chat thank you um
sorry i feel like i probably up until
now must have missed
uh out on what color your super chats
are when i was reading them because like
i just don't know so you're welcome to
add
uh the color of it in text form
whenever you send a super chat sorry if
i missed like
and and i didn't properly address it up
until now
sorry thank you for the membership
welcome
the brightest light among the sea of
stars a majestic phoenix whose flames
lit my heart and blaze
a smile that we can't help but adore
a voice so charming that leaves you
wanting more
so i say simply your presence has made
life worth living each day
i've been listless and lost these past
three years but now i feel like i'm
starting to fight myself
you help me stand again and i'm truly
grateful
i love you all this is a family i'll
keep close to me i wish i found this
rabbit hole much earlier
why oh my god
oh come on
ah you minks love you too
wow that sounds like i had a
big effect on you but that's a
damn thank you
you i'm happy to hear that
but but but
but uh wishing you fell into the rabbit
hole much earlier
i don't think it's necessary there's
always like the right time for these
kind of things
yes yes thank you very much for your
support i'm really glad to hear that
you've been starting to
find yourself as you say that's really
nice
good to know and i hope i hope you'll be
able to
help you'll find happiness or be happy
and i hope you'll be able to enjoy my
streams
much much more in the future thank you
for being part of the kfb crew
oh typhoon
tyson you okay typhoon are you in the
chat
have fun the message in the super chat
worries me
are you okay i don't know probably
you're not around because it says you
probably
won't be you're here are you okay
are you okay
yeah i know he's here just ask him can
find no word okay
much much hugs from me virtual hugs
cute [\h__\h]
[Music]
little song for you although i barely
knew any lyrics to that
it's a cute song from vataniroka
do you know that group is a it's an idol
group
japanese idol group
it's a really cute song about giving
hugs
hope you feel better i hope everything
is okay and if it's not okay then
it will be okay it will be okay trust me
it will be okay sometime
call me i'll thank you for a red super
chat
[Music]
hey attention i was just wondering if
you can make a yandere face
oh yeah face
belongs to me understand
there's one thing that you need to
understand
is that kelly belongs to me
and me only it doesn't matter
if i'm far away i can instantly
transform into phoenix if i wanted to
and i can fly over there and burn you
if you're gonna touch lay your finger on
kelly
i will burn you
understand
okay cool
sorry what just happened sorry what
happened
so i just kind of blacked out for a
moment
what happened where did i stop when was
the last superchat i ran
nothing
hi kara how are you and the cutest we
are doing fine guys
okay update on the cuties okay so
um what oh no no i'm
okay wait wait okay one after another
okay so gd
today trunk is you know jungkook
is always cute and and tongkis is always
so affectionate like she's like
she's like the moment i touch her she
starts purring and the moment i stop
touching her she stops purring
she starts purring the moment attach her
or sometimes even just by looking at her
she's such a cutie okay but
the one thing that both of my cats
rarely ever do
and especially trunkers never does it is
uh making cookies
not chunkers does make cookies sometimes
er also very rarely but they usually
don't really do that
yeah um but doesn't mean that they're
not happy they're like they
they purr a lot and they they cuddle
with me a lot
but cookies needing yeah they barely do
it so joggers i've actually
i don't remember seeing chunkers
ever kneading ever
so today i was
absolutely shocked for me that's just
still it was such a special moment okay
when i saw chunkers starting to need
i was like oh my god what this is really
happening
but it was like she was so bad in it
because like um
she got stuck in the fabric the whole
time
she wasn't having real issues with
kneading but it was cute anyway it was
really precious
made me really happy to see that so i
think my cats are very happy
both of them have been very happy i
think ever since i came back i don't i
don't really
know how they were really doing before i
came back but i suppose they i don't
think they
were as happy as they were now
i think i would i would like to think so
i would like to think that me coming
back made them
really really happy and i'm really happy
too
so much love ah also
when when they were babies when they
were really really small
um they used to like sleep on top of me
or like on my head or like partially on
my head but like more on like the pillow
that i'm sleeping on
like they would really sleep a lot on me
that was so cute
but the bigger they grew they obviously
stopped doing that
they just sleep next to me now they
don't sleep on top of me anymore
but um
today when i was chilling in bed
not chunkies
came up to my head and then
like i have this like a huge pillow that
i was resting my head on
and she just sat herself on top of it so
she was like
above my head right above my head on top
of the pillow so
we were using the same pillow i was like
oh my god
that's so cute that's like that didn't
happen since she was like really small
that was so sweet
she seems much more i mentioned this
before but not
john kerry seems much more affectionate
than she used to be
like before i left
and and then it just makes me very happy
yes yes i was so sweet and she was like
starting to purr and i was like petting
her belly the whole time while i was
watching youtube
uh
anyway continuing this is a late super
chat for near and raiza too
becoming a god and beating the boss and
rising to even though you're on the
level
i guess that wasn't really on the level
though it seems more like it was my
equipment that was [\h__\h] and all that
and here's something to treat yourself
thank you genie
yeah last year uh episode was fun
i mean in the beginning i i think i was
a bit annoyed but then later
um it was quite fun
becoming a god was fun that was fun i
hope we can
uh get quite far tomorrow as well
petition for and not jonger's nickname
so that she isn't just defined by her
sister
i know i know what i just can't think of
i mean they have names obviously but i
just can't use them on stream and i
can't think of anything good
ah baby
i guess okay okay let's call the not
john grace let's call her baby but i
called both of them baby the whole time
like even when i'm not streaming i call
them baby the whole time
[Music]
but it's like i can't i probably can't
even get used to it anyway
because like that's not their actual
name and i don't want to get used to it
bonkers is a stupid name
oh fun beta
[Music]
you just say now because you're freaking
murasaki
hmm chunkers yeah yeah i mean one is
junkers and we're now i'm okay with that
she is chunky okay how about how about
okay so she's like super soft and super
smooth can we get like a name like that
i mean it could be
something like chunkers and floofers
chunkers and floofers it's kind of hard
to say though fluffers floppers is
better
floppers is easier to say it's movie
oh that's cute it's movie because she's
so smooth
smoothie or fluffers okay smoothie or
fluffers floppers is a bit
easier to say maybe because smoothie is
like hard for me to pronounce fluffers
you guys seem to prefer smoothie though
what flowers has some other meaning
fluffers is yeah bye
[Music]
what
why do you guys even know that why do
you guys
know what that means
why do you guys know what that means
explain yourselves huh
wow okay well i guess it's smoothies
movie is so hard for me to pronounce the
th is really hard for me
um
[Music]
smoothie smoothie smooth smoothie
it's movie smoothie
smooth smoothie
smoothie silky sounds kind of weird
okay well for now let's see this movie
smoothie and chunkers
oh yeah okay for now let's just go with
that
okay
oh my god
[Music]
i love it thank you for the thinking i
actually like i want to do something
with that music i want to get like even
a new ending or a new opening but the
opening is made by dakuma and it's so
cute and precious
so maybe a new ending but like i want
something
that fits the music like i want it's
hard for me to explain what i want
i want some like some
[Music]
how to explain i want an ending
where it goes like through
i don't know i can't explain
i don't know
like obvious no no
i mean that one that would be funny too
but i was thinking of like
something like because i really can't
think of any sample
showing your clips or something not
exactly it can't just be like
like a fun animation of like
like letters like
being like like thanks for watching and
then swoosh and then
and then it moves around and there's
like pop pop pop and then there's like
please subscribe and then it's like
swell and then
and then you know
uh
[Music]
i don't know i might end up
commissioning someone
for a new ending i want to keep the
opening because tacoma just made it
recently and it's so cute and it's so
so sweet
okay sorry
hey hot wings i love how so many people
call me hot wings these days
i can't give you chocolate but i always
give you my heart
oh thank you i'll take it i'll take it
i'll never give it back
mine thank you
thank you
[Music]
phoenix now thank you for the pinky glad
to have smooth turned to back although i
think lag attention was starting to
become a new kink
dear lord i know that
that's a joke though isn't it it must be
a joke
thank you though thank you for everyone
who was so understanding
um while i was having shitty
uh frames thank you thank you
i was very bothered by it but you guys
were so
understanding and and watched my stream
anyway so thank you very much felix
i'm glad you didn't dislike it
thank you soon
here's a tip for making part of my work
yesterday too i flipped the super chat
stream while driving and the person i
was supporting
seemed to like your voice the person i
was supporting what does that mean
so we had a quite relaxed chill drive
uh someone else was driving and you were
like uh just sitting next to that person
oh sorry
probably probably like that is that what
you mean
ah quite relaxed chill drive elsa happy
birthday happy monday to you too even
though you probably don't
celebrate that oh still thank you very
much and
i'm glad you watched my stream even
though you weren't at home thank you
that means a lot to me
people watching my streams like when
they're
working and so on as well thank you it
makes me happy
thank you thank you
thank you
but be careful when you're like in the
car
obviously okay
an
hey i'm completely a random guy coming
in from nowhere i'm just gonna assume
that the chocolate you're making is for
me
i wasn't making any chocolate so now no
no no
no new york seven
from your last superchat stream when
people ask what you do you could tell
people you do customer service from home
you won't be technically wrong
i could just say i'm like a voice actor
working from home
and the works that i'm working on are
not public yet
not released yet so i cannot tell you
about it
i'm voicing for a big big anime that's
coming up
and that's why i also got this the super
dope like
microphone setup here because i'm a
professional
voice actor i mean
makes sense that makes sense i think
general picorin
unknown i wanted to send this since the
karaoke stream right you said reaching
won't be forever but i wanted to let you
know that no matter how long you
continue to do this we will always be
there
supporting you until the end thank you
unknown
thank you it's really
really really reassuring and relieving
thank you
excuse me
annoys me so much
anyway thank you that was very wholesome
and i love you thank you
oh followed up by another super chat
your streams made me so much happier and
i wanted to say thank you i'm so happy i
fell into this rabbit hill and discover
your channel
you're amazing and i love you so much
i'm also so happy
you discovered me thank you thank you
for finding me
there's so many youtubers out there
thank you for finding me
and choosing to support me really thank
you
thank you thank you is that a red super
chat i don't know that currency like uh
what where what is a red one and what
isn't
was that a red one
just asking to know if you need a kiss
the kiss the kiss
a rather than a pink
really someone else answered so
i read an opinion ah okay sorry see i
almost missed out on it you're welcome
to tell me next time when you send
something like that
uh and tell me like what color it was
wow
thank you
thank you for the sweet message thank
you so much
uh nicknames
well what's wrong with hot wings
honestly kiara is already so short so
like here
john seems uh like you're actually
making it
[Music]
longer uh
you like more cuteness and nicknames
yeah i did say that i'm not happy with
the ideas you
write out though not very impressed
hmm
now there's something that sounds really
wrong there
and
i appreciate the effort and the thought
it's very sweet
thank you
yucky
what k dog
now i wouldn't i would prefer not to be
called huma tony
uh hot wings yeah
i mean
[Music]
no no no no
onion verb
[Music]
is
yeah i mean just call me kiara
i guess for now
and uh or or like hot wings or
or all right
or i mean there's nothing wrong with
kiana how high speak
oh my god
no you don't have to add powder no
chia
the attention is also fine
yeah yeah no problem with those names
i love how people picked up on tantra so
much even though i didn't really say
i didn't really tell you guys to call me
dental
thank you extra pounds
thank you
we're all proud that you didn't make any
cat poop comparisons during soccer oh
yeah i didn't
up until the end i did not yet i hope
love sweets but also allowing the
community engagement on this one yeah
but what the [\h__\h] you don't eat truffles
please donate don't choose to chat
oh chat come on take your juice
[Music]
there we go yeah truffles i don't know i
just
um truffles
often like don't trustles often like
um include like alcohol
and i don't really like the taste of
alcohol in chocolates either
many i feel like i guess that's just
pralines
oh there oh wait truffle toy chocolate
oh yeah it's not the mushroom chocolate
that's why i don't like it
oh yeah yeah that's why i don't like it
because i freaking hate mushrooms
i just don't like that
sorry i'm not that fancy
truffles have two meanings in english
cuisine
they're not actually mushrooms okay but
i don't like the taste of it
wow yeah
you guys are confusing me now first you
say it's mushrooms then you say it's not
mushrooms
confusing me as per usual
but yeah i prefer you know my normal
normal chocolate
like
[Music]
milk chocolate or jotto that i was just
eating or hit the spot
or lint chocolate um
yes belgian truffles
i don't remember eating any belgian
troubles
i'll try it again sometime yes
i'll try it again and i'll give you my
updated opinion on it
okay but right now i have like so much
chocolate at home i first have to finish
eating that chocolate
i got so much chocolate from my friends
they gave me a welcome back package
and the one where i was rick rolled once
i opened the packets remember
yeah there was a lot of chocolate in
there and uh
and um you know what i love because
someone just mentioned
kinder penguin in the comments i love
milk schnitten oh
my german speaking bros will understand
merchants and either so [\h__\h]
kyle is
um
i don't think they have that the thing
that i was mentioning overseas so
deutsch is corto
again thank you for the red super chat
this look area thank you and yeah i have
to agree i really like the
community engagement uh it was a
lot to go through a lot of content to go
for
but it was worth it it was fun doing
something like that
good morning oh happy
[Music]
uh it is now six months since i met you
oh you were here from the beginning
you're beautiful kind and entertaining i
hope to stay with you for as long as you
are here for us
thank you for bringing light to everyday
making each day bearable
i look forward to the next six months to
my anniversary review
yeah it's like our anniversary not only
my anniversary but our anniversary too i
guess yeah
thank you so much for staying with me
this healthier
i'm glad you're not i wasn't there from
your w oh that's okay
that's okay i'm glad you're not sick of
me yet
thank you
i feel like like all of you who watch my
watch my streams every day
are like in the danger of getting sick
of me
because that's like when you listen to a
song that you really like
that just came out and you you like like
get addicted to it and you listen to it
all the time
like i get sick of that too so i can
imagine you guys getting sick of me
because you watch my streams too much
but again that's just me being
scared to lose you guys so like blue
clapper
i'm not sick of blue clopper just yet
i have been completely brainwashed by
blue clapper
thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank you all of you and thank you
darren wade
i hope we can celebrate the one year
together as well thank you so much for
your support
thank you
snow crab thank you shawn trevor
wow i guess yeah i read about both of
those before
uh two kisses for you actually yeah and
i already roasted you so i'm not gonna
reply to you anymore but you are
fake is that gordon ramsay from england
this person is standing in us dollars at
least use a vpn
to change your us dollar to uh
pounds at least
scotland okay there we go then whatever
you use there
change it into that instead of going
with us dollars i mean that's just
lack of effort i would say obviously not
the real
golden ramsey because otherwise you
would have used
different currency i don't think gordon
ramsay
uses usd when he sends a super chat so i
call that
fake fake
[Music]
that would be funny but we would destroy
him if he if he even starts
criticizing my employees i will destroy
him okay
i will i will i will grab him and i will
i will
you know transform into phoenix and i
will fly i will grab it and fly out of
the restaurant and then
fly up high in the sky and then you know
i'll not continue i'll not tell you what
exactly i'll be doing afterwards
i'll take him on a little toy now take
him and
show him how beautiful the weather is
how blue the sky is
couldn't you just give him good food we
only have good food and caffeine okay
if he has a problem with that then i got
a problem with him
and he's gonna brown with us uh-huh
i guess yeah i guess we could just just
show him the usual room too
true yeah thank you felix
and razzie does this thank you for the
pinky rankin this stream is making me
want desserts and i don't even have a
sweet tooth i will never forget that
lava cake that that the one with the
video
and happy six months to enjoy i had to
hold back before to prep
for merch announcements i appreciate
your existence
more than you know thank you
thank you very much thank you it's been
some fun six months thank you for being
part of it thank you for watching my
stream strategy
thank you soon and
let me refresh let's see
[Music]
oh
there we go i found it
green wilder thank you for a red super
chat
sorry my last super was confusing kyle
osmond is the man who suppressed the
gods
in the manga you should know okay yeah
yeah i google it and that's what i
saw so i thought it was must be
something like that
it's a story about a legendary hero
dying and being replaced by a pervert
who is only interested in fake [\h__\h]
honestly what a relatable main character
thank you now i understand okay thank
you for clearing that up
thank you i haven't is that a new anime
or manga
manga i guess is that a new one like i
haven't been
checking out any new anime or manga for
the past
years really so i can't really say
is that something new i wonder
a few years old
[Music]
well well well it's culture
uh-huh seems like a few people have the
same taste as you
in the chat green wilder thank you for
the rest of the chat thank you for
clearing it up thank you for your
support thank you soon
yes thick ties big five is the big five
the best
besto have another call
thank you steinberg gaming thank you
soon james mcphee thank you
thank you for renting james
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you for
the super chat thank you for the
generous donation thank you soon
thank you i panicked i'm so sorry
[Laughter]
it's okay why did you panic why
ah because of a wine because of the
chocolate i showed of you
like your chocolate no reason to panic
oh good it's all good
brain fried from work or from your
actual work or from kfp
if it's from your actual job i hope you
can chill and relax a little bit
seems like you're done now hope you can
um just lay back
and enjoy the stream
turn off your brain thank you for being
here
after a long day of work
thank you oh chickens chicken chicken
chicken
there's a chicken army
you're a fake australian
best of brain spike thank you
thank you
i wouldn't support you and other
halloween girls and become a member but
my credit card will most likely hate me
for the rest of my life what should i do
i already bought anniversary merch back
oh you really you really don't have to
do it like if you really want to do it
then i don't know
maybe just become a member of one or two
girls if you
if you're if you can't afford um
remembering all of them
um but there's really no pressure in it
we generally stream for free so content
enjoying our content is free
but thank you for buying the anniversary
merchandise thank you
cold canadian dankeshin thank you for
a message to all kfp employees the usual
room is closed for maintenance it will
be closed for three to seven hours until
all
kebabs are cleared out and all devices
reset please be patient until then
i don't know what the hell this person
is talking about just ignore it just
ignore the canadian just
just just ignore the canadian just shh
thank you for the red super chat
you better get the music room back on
track
like asap or you will
never get out of it i'll put you in
there and i'll lock you in and you'll
never
see the day light ever again
i love you thank you for the support
this logaria are 9 000
uh residency thank you thank you for the
pinky thank you for reminding me that i
forgot about the pinky promise
last chat sorry boss you're stuck with
this forgetful chicken
thank you i'm happy well done thank you
pinky brownies
six months 60 plus collabs and endless
hours of entertainment
you never fail to bring us joy thank you
so much for being being you and for
supporting your friends
you're so amazing at interacting with
your community and we love you so much
for it
thank you has it been 60 plus
collaborations that i've done
wow that's a lot damn
thank you i'll try to get 200.
thank you i'll do my best from now on
too thank you for supporting me
and thank you for your kind message and
for your donation thank you soon
67 holy [\h__\h] thank you for a
triple red super chat oh my god
i was a bit worried you thought i was
serious yesterday
i was reading your tweet and i was i was
very moment taking it serious i was
getting sad
but then i read the last line and i
understood but i replied because
i don't like it when you scare me like
that because it
makes me gives me a little bit of a
scare
at first like even if you clear it up
and makes me sad
so don't do it anymore i don't want to
even think about
you guys leaving so don't do it anymore
it's not it's not funny
but thank you
i'm not i'm not angry though i'm not mad
or so but
but but it scares me i don't want to
think about
i don't want to think about that stuff
you know
bye bye fly
let me leave impossible oh glad
to hear that thank you i don't
understand like why
how do i understand why am i even
how do i even have people watching me i
don't get it
how are how are you guys so sweet and so
kind and so passionate about me
i don't get it i don't get it yeah i
have no boing boing
shut up i have don't open your eyes
i very much got boing boing look at that
okay
look look here boing boing boing boing
boing boing boing
okay i've got plenty boring boring i'm
the i'm the second most boring boy
in her life english okay
second most i'm actually still hiding a
lot underneath that okay
as you you probably can't even see that
well but
it goes all the way up to my collar
bones okay that's huge
like the wing you know it's pushed up
there uh-huh
huge italia
[Music]
mama's a bit bigger how the [\h__\h] do you
know that did you touch them i highly
doubt it
have i
well who knows
[Music]
thank you
thank you so much honestly it is amazing
insane support thank you
don't scare me again six
true sixth true magician
[Music]
i finished the puzzle can i leave the
room there's absolutely no way that you
finish the puzzle because there's one
piece missing
arigato
[Music]
see there is someone saying goodbye
again why would you do that well okay
hope you're coming back
downstairs thank you for the pinky
and just want to say i really appreciate
how much you communicate with your
employees
when the employees struggle you are
there for us you're definitely a better
boss than any of the bosses i've ever
had
oh i am happy to hear that my employees
are happy
we went for a little bit of a rough
patch while you guys are starting to get
a little bit
rebellious and i was getting pretty mad
about it but hey everyone seems happy
now that's good
thank you i don't
know cat poop attracts flies [\h__\h]
just stating the obvious stencil
but oh my god okay whatever
would you prefer mrs morty or mrs
takanashi we talked about this before i
would take uh kelly's name
and our child would be called clara
clara
guys uh the other day
i was outside and i met with
some friends and uh
on that day i met someone
a girl who introduced herself to me as
clara and i was like i was like oh what
your name is claire what what i was
getting like super excited about it i
was like
oh my god your name is clara your name
is clara i was like
so insane about it
she must have been so confused
she's from the future boss
you're a child
hmm
did you yell out my baby no i didn't
but i'm pretty sure she was very
confused about my reaction why i was so
excited about her name
that's such a pretty name though like
for real
but um german german pronunciation clava
oh really pretty name
uh i can't be non-believers thank you
oh no what is this thank you for the red
super chat
what is this
i'll give it a kiss before i get mad at
you and don't give you a kiss after all
and
y'all say you love to work potential but
you all need to pay attention
ah oh and open your eyes to this phoenix
false
prophet enslaving your minds it's time
to
rise from the ashes and evolve from
pitiful little chickens
and soar into the sky as real majestic
feelings so suddenly
[Applause]
you chose a very wrong moment
to come here with your propaganda
because my
employees are right now the happiest
that they have ever been
so i don't think they're gonna buy your
[\h__\h]
room throw him to the usual room
we need a usual room song like you know
one of those sailor songs
like a sailor song thingy but like with
the usual room
throw him to the use your room use your
room
use your room throw him to the usual
holdenly hodory ho something like that
i see shanty yes something like that
um taking submissions now don chandler
thank you so much
[Music]
or something like that no i don't think
so it doesn't show up at the top so
okay thank you i love you too
it's my first episode i heard that
you're left-handed and i'm also
left-handed
what is the inconvenience caused by
being left-handed for me i bump into
people when i eat
oh yeah that happens sometimes that does
happen sometimes yeah
and i mean recently i haven't really had
issues but maybe when i was younger
maybe i had some more issues with that
but now not really
[Music]
yeah but there do
be some issues with being left-handed
sometimes yeah
captive art thank you
sanchez finger thank you thank you soon
even if i could get sick of you i'd
still watch because i have no life
i bet i'm the biggest loser here but we
strung together what you're not a loser
what the hell are you talking about
you're not you're one of the winners
because you're in here with kfp
you're part of kfp
you're a winner salt splash donkey and
black friction
how could i possibly get sick of such a
cute talented and working feelings you
might want you till i kick the bucket
hot wings
okay i love yesterday i can't love to
take care of tomorrow kiana forever
that's so cute i love you thank you
okay last refresh
sorry oh
where have we been oh there we go
someone already stole johnny 2023 down
kitchen thank you
looking for the top 10 kashun
mango nagao dankeshan thank you
what is that is that is that some kind
of colored superchat
yes it's a red one
i've been here with you since your debut
and since then you became the only one i
go out of the
off to watch live you became my oshie or
whatever it's called
there's no way i would ever get bored of
you ah you are a little flame that i
look forward each day and i hope for
hopefully many more years
oh thank you
thank you
[Music]
so weird to imagine that sometimes i
feel like i'm not myself
like like i'm just looking at takanasi
kiana
that's just not me because it's so weird
to grasp that
this is me and i'm being so loved by you
guys
i don't know it's so weird
yeah it's
just hard hard to grasp really
wow thank you
thank you for the sweet message thank
you
thank you
ah kumiko thank you
[Music]
what another birthday
she's turning six years old wow happy
birthday to haley
kitten
qualified fall asleep rest around 22
hours a day
wow this is more than a sloth 18 hours a
day and
way more than the cats 15 hours so we're
not that lazy
but now that i mention it i think it's
time for a nap
you know sometimes i feel like i don't
know like maybe i'm not giving my
cats too much and enough entertainment i
feel like
maybe they are sleeping out of being
bored and they would wish for more
entertainment and i feel bad as a cat
owner
uh but maybe i'm overthinking
they love to sleep well i mean i do too
but wouldn't they wish for a little bit
more enrichment in life
well i'm getting them toys for like self
um so they so that they can play alone
but i don't give a [\h__\h] about those toys
slavic fellows
[Music]
that is a red super chat i think
hope and happiness is life blood
obscenity i may sound lame saying this
but thanks to whole life i preserved
mine
months back when i tried when trying to
find at least a spark of hope i was a
step away from hitting the bottle
yet the same day i found you thank you
kenna
thank you for finding me i'm glad you
found me
for that reason that you're feeling
better now
and wow that that's that's really great
thank you
thank you i'm so proud of you thank you
for staying
in this world you belong here
and there's still so many things you can
do
especially once this whole staying at
home [\h__\h] is over
then there's still so much to see in the
world i'm sure you probably haven't done
the world tour yet all right let's do it
you're gonna check out the world there's
so much to see
go travel that's so fulfilling
thank you for being part of kfb thank
you
thank you
[Music]
this girl really thinking she can give a
place to belong
but she can give a place to belong to
almost 1 million people and people will
get tired of their busan
i guess this is my thinking promise
thank you
thank you based
thank you all right
you gotta you gotta give me a break it's
uh hard
because like life just changed so
suddenly
and so so greatly
um it's very difficult
to get used to it and really understand
what's going on
six months yeah but six months have
passed so quickly
anyway thank you thank you
dominique
thank you
so you compared yourself to listening to
the same song over and over and over
again worrying if you'll get sick of you
when i listen to songs over and over all
the time and each time i feel like i
hear something slightly different
and it's exciting wow well that's very
different
i think that's that you you are special
i wish i could do that like i get sick
of songs
don't you guys do that too listen to
songs too many times and then get sick
of them
don't you guys do that too
sometimes no yes no yes no
no no sometimes
huh okay not as many people as i thought
would say yes
do you guys just not listen to music but
i personally haven't been listening to
music much at all
ever since i joined a whole life i used
to listen to music so much all the time
just to do something on the side
like while drawing or something but ever
since i joined whole life like i've i've
like
really i barely have time for anything
else not even listening to music
which is kind of lame but oh well
uh oh
ticket smokey another pinky which makes
it red
thank you it's like that with you for me
as well i love seeing you have fun i
love listening to you playing i love
listening to your stories every time i
feel like i experienced something new
i'm not leaving anytime soon but all
pinky swear on down
your double pinky sword thank you
that's so sweet i wish i could like
hug every one of you shut up windows
please update your windows
shut up those updates only make it worse
anyway i hope you feel the hug tickets
monkey thank you so much for the kind
words
thank you dr helghas nagashin dufort
thank you for your pinky i guess that's
another pinky promise thank you
here's my thank you from yesterday since
emojis found us yeah what the hell
whatever all these there's like so many
hand emojis but not the right one for a
pinky promise it's just unacceptable
acceptable thank you dewford
i talked
branch in berlin thank you thank you
thank you for
the people in germany watching me chidi
danke
also for the pinky another pinky swear
thank you
thank you brownies
wow you're not a song you're singing
that's low-key
kind of deep pretty deep stuff yeah
jt mason says compassion that is the
reason why i follow your attention
seeing the response you gave the fan who
was not feeling well at all
moved me to my core it gave me a bit of
hope on that maybe the world isn't as
cold as i thought
oh
it isn't because there's me a phoenix
constantly on fire
and olympic torch i'll worm all of your
hearts up
when you feel cold thank you jay
pass the material chad unity chad
okay can't imagine anything less
threatening than the usual group chant
see shanty
well well residences thank you for pinky
thank you boss i'm almost offended you
still don't believe how love you are
what will it take
i mean i don't know i believe it but
sometimes it just feels like i'm like a
different
like a third person and i don't know i
swear it's
i just i don't understand like how guy
oh hey you guys are so sweet it's just
i feel so loved but also so honored and
so happy
and i don't know what to do with that
whatever you guys make me very happy
though
it's so great to have a place
here where i feel like i belong to i
might not really have that like like a
country where i feel like i belong to
but
at least i have you guys and i feel like
i belong in
my whole life and i belong with you guys
since you guys are here to watch me um
thank you for pinky
imagine getting bored of someone who
consistently creates top
you content he is an amazing person and
has given us all something to look
forward to every day
yeah no that's not going to happen ever
so you can bet your sweet
bp what we're sticking with you is that
some kind of
fake australian word biffy
is that supposed to be your ass sweet
ass
thank you soon thank you one one oh
that's very sweet i try my best to make
good content so that you guys don't get
bored of me thank you
a cowboy cell phone thing
it's not australian but it definitely
isn't australian
that's what i know it's south africa
you're picking up uh weird words from
other places interesting are you a
cowboy are you secretly a cowboy one
[Music]
i'm grateful for you because even when
i'm angry sad or feel invisible
you put a smile on my face you're not
invisible at all
here's a pinky i picked up for that
promise
what what
are you are you trying to make it like
like a joke at the end
like a punt i get it but
thank you thank you you're you're not
invisible
none of you are
thank you
patrick
[Music]
i'm not leaving i was disappointed you
never know okay
okay thank you have a lovely day
we are here because you make us happy
too don't underestimate yourself
you guys are so sweet this is too
wholesome this is so wholesome
what the hell what is this community way
too wholesome what the [\h__\h]
you guys are too sweet i love you i've
raised you well my dear chickens i've
raised you well
thank you johnny what a pinky sorry for
the wrinkle in my last super chat the
happiness and joy
you bring to my life is no joke and i'm
never getting bored of you kindness and
love i know that i'm a new egg but
here's my pinky
thank you how come you add i'm always
happy to have some new chickens to raise
and to sit on
[Music]
[\h__\h] all of these flies [\h__\h] you sorry
um thank you thank you thank you for the
support
thank you very much everyone who's new
is welcome
please enjoy your time here and and
and make yourself comfortable in this
lovely community
of super cute
fluffy chunky thick
chickens that will one day end up
in my belly and
turn into poop we needed some poop in
this stream yes
yes yes there has been some lack of poop
talk today
residents thank you for the pinky i
don't know if my third one went first so
here's part four i love you plus
you
thank you okay this is it guys this is
the end
only one way out of canopy
[Music]
back from security
come here my little eggs let me sit on
you
all right thank you guys i'll see you
tomorrow for near automata
thank you for today thank you for going
through the chocolates
yeah and i wish you all a lovely night
i'm going to try my best to sleep a
little bit earlier today because i got
to do some stuff tomorrow before the
stream
yep see you tomorrow thank you all of
you unknown
thank you thank you wow i love you
happy my day i love you
[Music]
thank ah let's you
food yeah
[Music]
oh my god oh my god how could i
how could i be and in germany we say
ah veena's in thank you guys good good
that there's some people paying
attention here
i saw comments saying like she didn't
say it
thank you food food
food food food food
[Music]
you