[Music]
so
does someone know
where my uh
where my wealthy wheel is
i've been looking for it i can't find it
my whopping wheel
usually you guys know
[Music]
are you really telling me to check under
the desk
are you cereal
[Music]
hello sorry for the delay uh
i was doing some things for whole talk
and uh before that i was watching
nancy
and she was so cute like
i couldn't
no
i looked on i looked in my download
folder i looked in oh wait i found it oh
there it is
yes
i found it
i found it wait a second
my wheel
on the new
color key
and green
[Music]
oh and i need to make it a little bit
brighter
hello everybody welcome to no rage
challenge mario kart atx
8 deluxe
i realized i should have done this next
week maybe because next week apparently
the new tracks are coming out but
oh well
um
oh
[Music]
okay
okay but we're doing it today
to do it part two next week i don't know
about that but it's okay it's okay
uh rules are actually already in oh my
god my cats are zooming the rules are
actually already in the description but
let me repeat them for you while i'm
looking for the mario kart logo
[Laughter]
um
okay so no screaming aloud uh unless
it's screaming out of happiness okay
that's rule number one
uh
i can't find the logo meow
no raid
no no raging okay i didn't write this
one down but oh my god
no ranging such as banging the table or
smashing the keyboard i don't do that
that often that's rule number two rule
number three is no swear words such as
and so on
although like i don't know i i generally
there were some words that i previously
said i don't think those are swear words
but you guys said those are swear words
um
so i'm not not really sure about that
but
uh
well you know the general words that i
always say you know the b word the f
word the s word
uh there's so many beautiful words that
today uh i will not be allowed to use
yeah um
and uh there are of course there's a
batsu game because otherwise it would be
hella boring uh
the rule the batsu gamer is
i will choose this myself
either
either i play
a
horror game
also probably of my choice
gotta make you make me kind of gotta be
nice to me in some way right
yeah i i will choose or we're doing a
ring foot adventure i always kind of
wanted to do a ring for the adventure
stream but
i always felt so awkward about it
because you guys
the viewers always make such a big deal
about it
well it's [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sport workout
yeah you make noises when you work out
oh well so um yeah we will see we will
see but if i do a ring fit i kind of
want to do it in vr i don't know if that
is possible
uh you know like i'm i did uh
i still can't find the logo what is
happening today wait
where the [\h__\h] did i put that
okay this this this
this was not raging yet
but i have actually oh my god my cat
jokers
no wait are you drunk no that's a movie
that's smooth did you hear that she just
uh
uh run ran up the [\h__\h]
uh cat tree yeah so what was i saying oh
i'm actually pretty confident that i'll
be fine
uh because
uh
because because i'll just use this what
the [\h__\h]
so sick of looking for this logo i'll
just use this
really i can't find it
the [\h__\h]
it didn't start yet okay
but i'm pretty confident that i'll be
fine
because
for when it comes to raging if i play it
this game on my own time i don't rage i
just i found it
it just happens when you know um
when you when i stream i kind of it's
like a turn on stream mode
and uh it just comes naturally then but
i can totally go without raging and
without swearing in my private dem it's
just i don't know
oh
my dishwasher is finished yeah
okay so we'll do this for one hour uh
short stream today
can
you guys i want you guys to remember
about if it's out of happiness
i'm allowed to yell but
if i'm not if i'm mad then i'm not
allowed to yell
and i'm i don't i know i could you know
[\h__\h] uh around and uh
[Music]
um um
do
break any of the rules on purpose
to
you know for the sake of
um
the funny
uh
hello
game
i don't see [\h__\h]
stop it uh but i want you guys i want
first of all like i want to prove to
myself and to you guys
that i can
it didn't start yet then i can't do this
i want to prove it to myself and to you
guys like i i i feel like when i speak
english i don't have at least some
stream i don't have that much control
over
my words
and my lingo
i slip up and i i do uh
yellow and then not yet
uh swear a lot and uh oh it's not like i
want to like i don't know
um but
yeah
[Music]
okay
now i will be calm now
and also welcome to three new emotes
only three only three there were never
more than that no not only three maybe
there's gonna be more in the future
uh
am i too big
[Music]
i'm sorry if you guys are going to be
disappointed because i'll just be so
good at this um
but
i i i want you guys to see a different
side of me
[Music]
in a while so don't expect any good
gameplay
uh always again online play
[Music]
is this too loud
need to write the code
uh so don't look
don't look
don't look don't move
no
tournament
which one should we go with
which one
we start we start once the first race
starts
and then also in the breaks it counts as
well but the the starting time is when
the first race starts i need to focus i
need to focus oh my god um okay
okay okay
um
[Music]
is i'm going to show you in a moment
are you sure
are you sure where do i put it uh put it
at the
top right and i'm showing it in the
moment i'm showing it in
this might be a boring stream because
i'll i'll really not rage
i'll go with whatever setup i had here
and there we go code is uh at the top
right top right
top right menu any vanguard you must
okay now now i'm gonna chill
now i'm gonna chill now i'm gonna chill
i'm gonna chill oh yeah i can show you
the game now
i'm gonna chill
i'm gonna be um
kind
and
nose it's really difficult to make that
switch oh my god i'm oh wait oh god oh
god oh god
oh god no oh
i'm so close to saying the s word
oh god
it's so deeply implemented in my
in my
language
i
okay i really have to be careful
good luck thank you good game thank you
yo that's cool okay guys
um
let's go with electra dope i might not
even notice by myself uh if i swear i
might not even notice
because it comes too naturally oh god oh
wait i really believe that i can do it
but at the moment i really don't have
that switch
oh god oh
god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god
uh um um
um
if i swear in german they might not
notice
but how do i drive again god don't swear
kiara be be good idol say so
say so idol
let's go everyone let's have a nice race
oh
good
nice
yeah
hey i haven't played this game in such a
long time and we're actually doing
decent i think this one was the
one of the tracks
that where i was in in the tournament
actually doing really well
oh
i said i i didn't say the full word
i didn't say the full word i didn't say
the word i didn't say i didn't say the
ck
at the end
[Laughter]
fu which i mean it could be just you
know
yes i get it but
you love me
please i beg you i thank you
[Music]
why you're so far behind i thought you
were good at this game
roasting someone is allowed
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's go
one
[Music]
that that one didn't count yet okay
that one didn't count yet i didn't say
ck i i i was i was
whispering the word and um yes
one more chance come on okay
i didn't rage at least i didn't rage
no no no no yeah fifth is pretty bad
consider uh pretty good considering that
i um
uh
just stopped in the middle of the road
thinking about what i just did oh i
shouldn't choose it so early
when people are still coming in
no it did not count
point period
it did not count unless you want the
stream to end right now which uk if
people don't want trying
yes
frequently asked questions
frankly
i was just gonna um talk about franklin
frequent frequently
asked questions
such as
chicken or phoenix the answer is i'm a
phoenix um
other frequently asked questions are
what is the usual room
your showroom is um
um
that name the japanese kiara's name is
the lover of the colonel
uh the usual room is a place where all
of you be going if you don't uh
be quiet now
[Music]
and let me do another try okay
okay we go all right is there a oh
no that does not bother me
cute
wait that actually
the face is laughing yeah that is really
cute
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
oh oh my god this area is always like so
speedy oh my god
[Music]
okay
i think i've i turned the switch
uh the switch of you know
not not swearing being say so the saiso
switch has been
turned on
[Music]
i'm actually i feel like
i feel like i'm driving pretty well so
far
what
when you say kfb
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
that
does not count okay cool thank you
that's not a swear right it's not a
sword
not a [\h__\h] right
it was uh i was saying something in
german actually i was saying
oh
beautiful
beautiful scenery a nice sweater is what
i was saying
in german yes yes
[Music]
oh
wow
beautiful
okay let's just say let's just say let's
just say there are i get three chances
and
um
i guess
i guess um
i guess there is a
uh
out of those three chances one is
um i'll give that to you i'll give that
to you one is gone
that d-a-m-n-i-t
was
indeed a swear
[Laughter]
and and i get two more chances
yeah i think that's fair
one is gone not two no no oh my god that
face that pick with our face
oh my god
um yes everyone you don't screw on a
turkey
i was thinking wait
with the glasses are you uh trying to
look like the wealthy me
[Music]
is that person trying to look like the
wealthy version of myself
lecture dome is so popular i already had
dad today
huh
also by the way i i uh
oh didn't sleep much
i i have a problem i i shouldn't talk at
all but okay talking is dangerous but
anyway i i i i i i recently realized
like i used to always
uh
sleep like 10 hours like 10 hours would
be so ideal and
i
i never had problems with sleeping that
long if i had the time then i would
always sleep that long
but like even though i had the time i
could recently i can only sleep like six
hours or so but
i always have to take a nap
at some point of the day it feels like
my body
cannot go for a day for the day without
a nap
unless i'm like busy the whole day and
outside that kind of works
[Music]
10 is a lot well okay let's say nine
nine
why am i so slow
at least
[Music]
yeah very sorry i can't even though i'm
tired like i wake up i woke up today
and i was like really tired but i feel
like
i woke up mostly maybe because
um i needed to go to an idol meeting and
i felt too hot in in my bed
and i just felt really uncomfortable so
i wake up early but then i can't fall
asleep anymore
[Music]
but today i don't think i have time for
a nap anyway so let's see what happens
and i used to always sleep nine hours
and then i was fine without a nap but
now i i always kind of need a nap man
smoke driving
[Music]
i mean i don't take it every day
i didn't take it last night
um i took it uh when was that the other
day for for uma cat but i had i barely
got any sleep for that
um yeah even with my little nin and then
after that of course i took a nap i had
to i was i couldn't take a nap right
away though i was really tired but i had
an appointment
and
that's why i needed to go
out after the whoa
ah can i use up all those three
mushrooms no way
yeah i have to leave that that omo cat
collab pretty quickly
that was it was a long nap because i was
like so dead tired
really exhausted
yo i went without swearing did i not
i went without swearing
[Music]
how is it not arranging
look the non-raging is going perfectly
fine i think
yeah
yeah maybe the tangent but i had to
focus turn the tangent too to not swear
yeah
i'm i'm like a baby i need to take uh
i need to take naps and i i need to
sleep in like
uh stages like
yeah
welcome everybody thank you for everyone
who is following the rules of uh leaving
after one
uh
after one run thank you
very disciplined everybody
ah i'm tired now too to be honest
why why i
i went to the idol meeting and i went
back to the bed and i thought i could
continue to sleep but i couldn't
i couldn't i tried i closed my eyes for
like one hour but at that point i was
like already
my mind was so occupied with
work stuff
and so on
um
[Music]
many japanese bros thank you
just for the record i did not
i did not
say any anything bad in japanese no
oh yeah the drift though dude if though
i didn't get an item though but i am
[Music]
at the top of the race
oh i got the wind
oh beautiful double item
oh yeah
oh yeah okay
that's okay
[Music]
yeah
god that was just the gut
[Music]
well guys not not a swear
callie would agree with me on that
oh wow
can i say
get r-e-k-t that's not swearing
[Music]
oh that was kind of stupid
bumped into everything
it's not a swear right yeah it's just
being uh toxic i didn't say that i can't
be toxic
i just said
i make that sound a lot
[Music]
yeah always gotta be ready for that
dorito when you get thrown out of the
what's the name of that item again
okay now for real i think i'm super
stressful right now my mind is filled
with say-so flowers and
uh unicorns and rainbows
um
[Music]
um even though i'm tense i think i did
decently
but 10th is not enough
as always i am april
every so often
thank you
thank you enrich me there there's no
there's no rage i'm happy
no really though i'm feeling fine i'm
feeling good
[Music]
calm and then
feeling good
oh there's a peter and the fauna
pongtail version callie
i don't know who that blue haired person
is supposed to be
ah what should i go with um
whatever ah didn't we have this one
before dammit
okay well that's that's two out of three
[Laughter]
strike two
okay of peter
[Music]
that one that got me twice now that word
that got me twice i feel like because to
me
that is the least um
swearing
like
the least like a swear out of my
swearing
lingo
you know what i mean
it feels less like swearing than
the s word or the f word to me
[Music]
it's not an excuse i i take it as a as a
strike that's okay
it's not a swear you think so i think
many people miss
don't agree with that
but i i guess today i counted as a swear
it's my weakest swear
and that is the one that will bring me
down
oh man
i still don't consider that as okay
well
we have uh decided to swear today
otherwise otherwise it would be just too
easy
[Music]
it's not for most people really
wow okay
i think that was one of the words that i
was wondering about that that i
mentioned that i think it's not a swear
but some of you guys think is it's a
swear officially
i don't know what does google say if you
google d-a-m
and
or or that with it
if google considers it it's where
if google says it's so swear then it is
a swear i suppose
because even in german we have that word
and um it's i think it's considered a
swear because people like to
change it to flick stock mile to make it
stay so
[Music]
i'm looking at the chat this is really
today it's really not about me uh
driving well
i'm i'm gonna have a conversation with
you guys google said it's a profanity
all right then
[Music]
holy holy god
[Laughter]
that moment felt like i said i swear it
could have been easily been a swear but
it was yummy
yummy is okay
only if you're 16th century
puritan who fears witches na hodona
that doesn't sound like myself baby
wayner
maybe i should act like a baby because
the baby wouldn't swear right
unless unless you watch my streams and
learn english from my stream
i shouted out of happiness yeah that was
not a range shout out
oh hello everybody oh my god uh which
one are we going for uh whoa we are
staying home stay tuned
[Music]
oh i see a dragon
baby
it's been 20 minutes now
only 20 minutes for real claws oh no
oh
[Music]
no there's no pacifier wealth account
yeah that is a crime
[Laughter]
that there's a kiana
a person and their name is like oh small
outfit let's go
oh i didn't get the i didn't get the
boost
i did get the item though oh we're on
the rainbow road
um
is that the one that makes me rage
no it's just
no no no no rage involved no
i'll be
happy go lucky
as they like to say
right
oh
give me give me an item please
[Music]
it's okay i don't need an item
mushrooms and so on make me too fast
anyway that's where the shortcut is that
i once tried to use
when i was practicing
for the tournament
but i wasn't quite confident enough to
use it in action nothing
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was a beautiful drift yo
otto
[Music]
i didn't swim yet did i
double item
can i get a bullet can i get a bullet
now
here maybe we try what's up wasn't it
like here
oh i mean
that maybe saved me some time
i don't know it kind of worked like a
shortcut
you gotta go for that one really
confidently if you if you
wager
while you're falling there then you're
gonna miss it
[Music]
oh where are you going friend and where
am i going where are we going
second jump was yeah that's where i was
like wait am i supposed to go there
i got uh
insecure
[Music]
wave waver not wager was it not what
that's okay
that's fine
it doesn't work with yeah it was about
items too i mean it won't get me any
further now
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
happy i'm so happy today
i'm so happy
happy happy morning
[Music]
i'm happy to come to me guys race me
i wanna drive against you
please no rainbow world please no
rainbow road please no rainbow road
and monkey
oh so happy birthday to my beloved
energy
did you see her concert was amazing i
want to do a concert like that
but i have a feeling
this year i feel like i feel like i can
somehow
even if i have to do it from home
after the
uh third fest whole life festival
which is this month by the way oh my god
after that i feel like with amma's help
i can
get something close to that at least
i'm
even if it's without guests i feel like
i can at least manage to make some kind
of
concert
in in 3d so my goal is for this year for
real to have a 3d concert i mean i
already wanted to do it last year
um
yeah but
but you know
didn't work out
[Music]
um
will have to visit me before my birthday
that's for sure
no
i was drifting so pretty
pretty is that a word
do you say that is that correct
grammatically
hmm
nice items
[Music]
yago
let's go
happy happy
happy excitement
don't blitz dope super late what what
was it
bass dope super lit
[Music]
me
okay
[Music]
oh
whoa
[Music]
fourth fourth job
came out of nowhere they didn't expect
me
[Laughter]
you guys wait do you guys even
understand that reference
to what i am on i didn't even watch the
diamond but i at least know like
drama uses
doors that go anywhere if i understand
correctly it's a doco demo door
anywhere door
funny smoking
funny
[Laughter]
yeah the door the teleportation door huh
heard of dorado never watched it it's
like
it's like a must-watch if you grow up as
a child in japan
i didn't so i didn't watch it i just
know about the existence
i don't like monsters inc oh
no it's not like that because monsters
inc doors only go to children's rooms
right
and monstering that was a cute lovely
movie i really liked it when i was
younger that was such a great movie yay
montorio
[Music]
that was nice
i'm actually uh
gonna go somewhere with rmt again very
soon but only a short
very short trip i think i mentioned it
before
um but i'm not gonna mention again what
we're doing or where we're going or when
we're doing and you will see
[Music]
also
fourth joe starting strong as 10
at nine and oh my god
see ya the cheering is so sweet
else close
[Music]
i think um
oh the other day i saw i saw on twitter
uh
that
vocal lord hatsune miku the official
brand they are
uh i guess what are they called again
they are putting out like
hatsune miku design
uh skis and snowboards
they look really cool
but there's only like two sizes for the
skis
and
i suppose it would be difficult to get
them if i order
i sell to pre-order right now i think
but they look really cool they have like
all kinds of designs like i think three
different uh artists worked on the
designs
[Music]
but i was thinking maybe i could even if
i can't really easily oh don't wait no
you know what i could probably if i
ordered them and bring them to like
order them to japanese address
then
if i go to japan i can go skiing in
hokkaido challenge it again with kelly
give it another try and then and then oh
you almost got me there
and then
what's up what's up you're so you're so
you're so you're so yourself and then i
can probably take them home in a flight
shipping would probably be a bit meh but
i know that for flights they have like
a lot of people bring skiers and stuff
i've seen it before
i mean i guess it's counted as as big
luggage why am i eleven
why am i eleven makes no sense
i did so well
i don't know joisty
why
an austrian should take number one when
it comes to skiing
i hope you won't get in an accident
yeah that's the thing like
the sizes that they have for those uh
hatsune miku skis are i think it was 155
centimeters and 160 centimeters which is
pretty long like if you're a beginner
you're gonna have trouble with that
uh as i've learned with my own body
yeah because i i think how long are mine
again i think mine are like
i think they were like
centimeters the ones i bought from
myself
i think i think it was 155
and then
as i told you if you didn't watch my ski
vacation
uh review stream and you should watch it
because it was a lot of fun and and
there was a special character appearance
but yeah i was um
i tried out some really shorter skis as
well and made everything much much
easier
um i think i went down to 130
centimeters or so which is a huge
difference there was so tiny
[Music]
or even smaller i'm not sure something
around that
[Music]
yeah
so if i if i were to get another pair of
skis
i should get
smaller ones
not again like huge ones like 155 and
160 centimeters yeah mr yodell
the legend
oh we're here
oh bales really rocked this one didn't
she
also i saw bale's reaction to the
birthday video
i am really proud of that video that
turned out so cute i'm glad we did that
but did you notice this
this um
whoa
oh
this month there are so many birthdays
in her life every week there's one to
two birthdays
did you notice
it's
it crazy adorable right
[Music]
it's a birthday month yeah
but that also means a lot of exciting
streams
where people celebrate and are happy
why am i still so far behind when you
guys are
yeah
i'm not that bad right now i think
[Music]
oh the blue shell that doesn't really
help me
eleven i'm double one yay
double one double first double first
number one but twice
i like this number
[Music]
i'm gonna try this one it worked
but
it didn't help me
oh no the end is here
you guys are just waiting for my first
slip up aren't ya
everyone's just
drooling in front of their screens
waiting for my next slip up
nice
job then eleven eleven for sure would
have been nicer
culture excuse me
not culture
happy ta happy job
and i didn't lose the challenge
and fourth
are you counting that very very first
one that was not a slip up
because i registered a different word
no i didn't no
the people who say i already had free
sleep ups did i didn't did i not know
did i just say something and i didn't
notice myself
or do you mean the first one
no the fu1 no no no
no no no no no no we're playing by my
rules here okay
we are too exact i agree with that thank
you also also also you gotta give me
that that i'm counting the the d-a-m-n's
even though a lot of you guys agree that
it's just not really a swear word
no
so we are it too
[Music]
i made it i made it already pretty
difficult for myself okay
[Music]
i have a two okay yeah yeah that's
perfect that's emote
but i have a feeling that uh soon soon i
might flip up by accident without
noticing
[Music]
us
yoda
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
happy happy happy happy happy happy job
this music though howdy
[Music]
that's okay cause i'm happy today
happy happy happy
in japanese
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm just in a good mood now
you can't get me to swear
you can't get me to swear i have like
about 15 minutes left in this challenge
i think something around that time
nice drink
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
did they just stay behind
um
daisy shares my enthusiasm yes because
we're both orange-haired girls
orange-haired girls maybe you've noticed
they're always very very happy
and no no no the rule is i may yell if
it's out of happiness you want on my
face
[Laughter]
bottom it with the gunky muddy face
[Music]
welcome everybody welcome
let's let's race
what should we go for um
did we already have mario stadium no we
didn't that's that's one of the huge
bumps right
here they come oh is that a mermaid
recreation lot of people didn't make
their choice but okay
ah there we go
swear count
two
[Music]
two out of three i get one more tense
give her hell guys hey
[Music]
hey
you should support me to win
baby
[Music]
it's not five no
you guys are
so mean
if you were to do a swear challenge i
bet you would lose faster than me
[Music]
um
but that's okay um
i don't have an issue with that
[Music]
wow what a surprise
that was not the banana that i dreamed
of
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
it's all good only happiness
how do you know if i'm happy or not
[Laughter]
oh so happy
[Music]
i'm going crazy i'm going a little bit
crazy here
i feel like
i feel like i'm acting like a crazy
person
[Laughter]
serenity now oh yeah wherever i heard
that somewhere before seren serenity now
serenity now wasn't that like outs out
of some movie or something
it was not a of course it was a happy
scream i'm always so happy when i'm
getting
like left over
i can say that that was totally under my
control
[Laughter]
also as long as i'm able to hold myself
back by
you know not saying the full word
i would say oh seinfeld oh
then everything is good i wish i had
that control all of the time
chinking sadie
huh
oh is that an old marine senpai next to
me
[Laughter]
ah old marine is so funny wait maybe i
should do a
baba collab with marin
because i like acting like a grandma
maybe that's a good idea for a collab
with mayan senpai
we could both be grandmas
why wouldn't that be fun
she would be like ahoy and i would be
like okay
when i hope i don't forget that idea
[Music]
f-zero yeah let's go
hiku-da
[Music]
no
bad start
focus
yeah i love the music on this map
[Music]
oh an item give me those coins give me a
little coin
[Music]
[Applause]
i dare you if you use that
[Music]
so well though
i'm crying i'm not raging i'm crying
what's the difference
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
get out of the way
[Laughter]
i just want her to be safe on the road
who would have known that the record
would be the end of me
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes all of this i'm doing perfectly
aware
i
i've lost
i've lost and actually a good timing
because it was close to the ending
anyway
[Laughter]
yeah no that last one was on purpose i i
concede
i accept by defeat
that was weak strikes though that was
weak once the few damage and then
a little bit of a small rage moment
i didn't even say just now i said it on
purpose but i didn't even say [\h__\h] you
or [\h__\h] or anything like that
so i'm pretty proud of myself
well played thank you thank you
i was more say so than usual right
ah i i wanna we can do this more often
because i wanna be able to control my
self better
so then
[Music]
people have who whose first language is
english i feel like but you know that
you know my problem is yeah yeah yeah
i just have no filter when it comes to
english
ah well thank you everybody um we will
have either a horror stream or a ring
for the adventure stream sometime soon
sometime within this month
uh
probably not right away next month next
week but sometime
yeah i'll think about which one
is a better choice for me
and when we're gonna do it i'll think
about that yeah
i'll leave that to myself i won't leave
that choice to you guys i need to
consider my
my mental health
um
thank you guys
also thank you to everyone who believed
in me which is probably one person
and that is myself
i
i just i just kind of
sometimes you know i i i i aspire to be
more like you know my gen mates and and
my other um
whole life english members who have who
are like
they they swear maybe sometimes but they
have it under control and they don't
come off as such a foul mouth i don't
want to be such so foul-mouthed
let's work on that shall we
[Laughter]
i mean a lot of you guys say like me
um because i swear so much but that's
kind of weird that's a weird reason to
like me
no
um we'll never get it completely out of
my system but i should probably swear a
little bit less
i swear way too much
thank you thank you
oh you guys have been too kind
and say so it's better
it does make me happy when i see the
other girls when i hear the other girls
swear sometimes it makes me feel better
if you want to do it go for it you mean
swearing
swear more and there's it's literally
impossible to swear anymore than i
already do
[Music]
i know
thanks for liking me even though i have
a foul mouth
yeah
and uh do i have a stream tomorrow
i forgot i think i do today is wednesday
tomorrow is first day yeah i should have
a stream tomorrow i don't know what it
is but i do have a stream tomorrow uh so
i read super chats uh during that stream
and i'll leave you guys with this early
stream short stream
and i wish you all a lovely
day and evening and drive safely don't
rage so much honestly
one thing i gotta say though
i i i actually hate it when i'm with
someone in a car and they rage so much
at the traffic and and yell profanities
like that actually like makes me really
really
it makes me feel really annoyed like i
hate it when people rage at the traffic
uh do you guys hate that too
like i don't mind it generally when
people swear but
when they're driving a car i don't know
i'm like yo chill what the [\h__\h] like why
are you so mad
why are you so mad
first of all it scares me and second of
all like
maybe it's because i don't drive i don't
know how to drive a car and have a
license maybe that's maybe i just don't
understand but i feel like a lot of
drivers are just too aggressive like
chill for a moment there's no need to be
so
mad at everything damn
road rage road rage
why are you mad bro
oh
i i see him um some people in the chat
might might be uh guilty of road rage
themselves
i mean
i mean if you're
if you're not sharing the car with
anyone else i guess why the hell not let
it all out it's one way of letting out
frustration and stress i suppose
mummy understands
oh and didn't she
she raged about something was it about
was about bad drivers
i forgot
oh wait does muma have a license
i'll never want to be in the car with
her dad if she rode rages i can't
imagine movement to seriously road rage
and be like [\h__\h] get out of the
way [\h__\h]
you're terrible you suck mate
i can't imagine mummy being like that no
way
she had a rant about bad travis yeah
okay i can see that but like i don't see
her
going crazy like okay you know what i
actually kind of if if she really does
have road rage because i can't believe
it and imagine it i do want to i do want
to be in the car with her once
to experience it firsthand and then i'll
never drive with her ever again
that's realistic no i know mummy is is a
good polite girl
with manners and control over herself
she's timid i think so too
but we'll see maybe
she did mention she wants to go to
europe if maybe we can rent a car
and get her to drive and then i'll
secretly record her
until you cross her
that's scary that is scary
and scary
talking about the same roommate
yeah
the thought scares me now
oh man is that is that a moe egypt
yeah a more gap
i'll have to investigate it further
anyway uh thank you guys for watching
see you guys tomorrow also an uh whole
talk with no understand bye on saturday
don't miss it
yes our beautiful boring bullying asmr
goddess knight is coming to my studio
and in german we say
ow friday
[Music]
bye
you