[Music]
he
come on
[Music]
w
[Applause]
[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
w
he he
[Music]
come on
hey
[Music]
K
get
[Music]
K hello can you hear me well try to
change my settings a little bit again
wow
my cats are sleeping both of them or
they tried to sleep until now over there
over there on my guest
bed so cute they're so fluffy I wish I
could have taken the a cozy cat nap with
them but I was doing work today well I'm
looking kind of naked down
[Music]
there yeah I think uh I think my audio
settings yeah oh
my no I will not go back busy too yeah
bit busy man I'll start off I'll start
off complaining about it let's get it
out of the
[Laughter]
way I I knew I had something to do today
that's kind of time
sensitive so
I called this place where I needed to
make an
appointment and I was like hello
appointment please they're like okay
today this time which was like 3 hours
from them from then or so I was like
okay okay she should be
okay and then I had to prepare something
so I had to go to a copy shop to print
something out and I had to do some other
stuff but uh all those things that I
like you know went out to go to a place
where I knew it had all those things
that I needed to do before going to the
appointment and then I arrived and it
was all like
closed copy shop yeah now I have a
printer but it just doesn't [\h__\h] work
of course no printer ever works at
home H but it was closed and stuff or it
was like out of order and stuff and
great so I couldn't do the things and I
was SC
scrambling to find like other places to
do those things
but like everything that I could find
would take so much extra time to arrive
that I wouldn't make my appointment so I
was still like scrambling and running
around trying to figure things out
stressed and walking fast with shoes
that just don't work for fast
walking and then I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it
won't work and I called them and I said
oops can't make it sorry please new
appointment they're like okay no problem
so now I have new appointment which is
fine it's going to work out but I'm just
pissed it didn't work out
today all of the things that I needed
all of
the tasks were
undoable why
why yeah was pretty
angry but then I came back and I had to
had to get right back at it started
working on something started cooking on
something it's going to be so good I'm
cooking something for you guys for
Christmas for my kfp a
surprise it's going to be so good
special wa Christmas
stream oh my God you shouldn't have for
you I'm working hard on it I I I'm I'm
I'm actually pretty proud of myself and
I'm pretty impressed with myself I
should do this more often I should cook
more often maybe I will cook more
often what you cooking good looking you
will have to find out just wait a
is not that much longer
oh what did that say what where did it
go you got a VIP ticket for Whole Life
Stage World Tour sord
type let's go VIP ticket that sounds
like you're going to get some good seats
going to sleep for 11 days hey no no no
no no until then there's still things
you got to see but by the way thanks for
the cute app
it blue I got a tie now it's cute I can
attach it quite quite nicely to my
ribbon and uh a huge magnifying
glass
cute and a hat nice hat I'm I'm
practically wearing two hats right
now yeah looks like it's part of the
cape unless when I look up then you can
tell but when I look like this oh oh
yeah it moves nicely together
yeah but yeah yeah yeah it's like almost
as if we're playing frog detective but
we are in fact today
playing duck
detective I remember uh actually I
submitted the perm request for this a
while ago and then I got the perms a
while ago but then I just didn't really
feel like playing it yet but today for
the people who are surprised why we're
not cooking well I'm cooking something
else in a different way but uh yeah I'm
still waiting for sorry still waiting
for some merchandise stuff to arrive and
so like cuz I want to show it off right
it's it's basically a Vite promotion
stream really a Vite kfp collaboration
promotion stream not just a clicking
stream so I would be good if all the
things are there and now I'm I'm going
to give it another week and this should
could hopefully make
it I believe it could make it so yeah
speaking of parents bco yeah
BOS I I I wrote a joke cuz I'm such a
jokester I was like well if Yago is at
the game awards having fun he better be
getting us perms for like all the g
games that are represented there
okay better be connecting with them
better be networking better be getting
us some
perms yeah can't just be out there
having fun nah come on get us some
perms it's a joke it's a joke it's a
joke but uh bumco wrote I don't know how
serious they were about it I don't think
we have problems getting bumco perms
like anything band Namo I don't know I
never had issues getting perms for Bandy
Namo games
so don't worry about it bco but you're
so cute for like concerning yourself
with
it B ano so cool you know they're so
cool elen ring Co yeah so is that just
another deal they said it's Standalone
so it's not a DLC where the other DLC is
also called
Standalone it's legitimately like a kind
of like a
Elden Ring Side game right like more
like that like cuz it's Co-op focused
it's like a yeah it's like a
[Music]
spin-off I can already imagine a lot of
like Holo girls playing that also in a
collab I I mean
man man I should have
I should have played more Elden ring I
should have gotten more into it but it's
so stressful and now I can't be part of
the cool group that plays the new Elden
ring Co-op game
man it's okay no no I don't want to I
don't want to no no no I feel like I
would have to play Ellen ring in order
to be part of that group so just so that
I can skill-wise like keep up with them
but no no I don't want to I don't want
to no no no my you guys said I wasn't
even that bad and also everything got
like uh apparently like easier after I
was like after I
quit but I don't know I just I'm kind of
traumatized you've grown up you could
you were pretty good you really weren't
that
bad I don't know I put a lot of pressure
on myself during that playr and then it
was kind of rough man Even though
apparently I was like
decent
[Laughter]
oh you got to do witch I definitely do
want to play uh Witcher and I saw the
trailer for the new Witcher game also
looking really
good uh so yeah it's a sign it's a sign
for me to get into
thanks guys it's a sign for me to get
into Witcher and you know
start my path into that fandom deeper
and
deeper yeah the new one looks really
good looked really beautiful I think
wasn't that the trailer that said it's
with like a new unannounced graphics
card uh and unreal five an Unreal Engine
five yeah that was the one
yo sheesh crazy crazy
stuff did you see the game of phones uh
I I didn't really pay much attention I
was like I was just now I was like doing
work I was cooking and on the side I was
like watching the stuff that I missed
yesterday cuz I didn't stay up all like
throughout all of it cuz it went on
until I don't know 5:00 a.m. my time I
stayed awake until the point where uh
the content creator award was given out
so to say and then I was like okay bye
no I didn't see
Jesse but uh yeah I'm I'm still
finishing the VOD so I might still see
him yeah I was like
okay
byebye it's p no no
o pickle
ockle bye-bye no the ockle was good
though
[Music]
oh my froat is okay right now even
though I've been drinking a little bit
of Coca-Cola it's not good for the froat
but I needed new turo wait I think I
already knew about that that's that
wasn't a completely new announce right
sounds
familiar but I guess I missed the
trailer for that that's also I guess
around the end where I was already
sleeping it
was now you can't be sure anymore cuz
they took out
the world premiere thing
you okay okay stop spoilering
me yeah the only Musha thing looked cool
m
third person T Rock H that's interesting
we still got to play the first the we
got to play the OG tck
yo it's such a weird like thing for me
to desire right but I have this weird
connection Nostalgia with tur
Rock what did you think about the game
of the year I didn't play
astrobot uh
but apparently it's really really good
so what
H wasn't my choice
though I we won a lot of
things
[Applause]
ah sorry no I I do I I I feel like it
probably deserves
it it seems to be really well made and
well liked I saw like a bunch of game
footage of it you know
she really do be lurking I saw
your can I can can I say that I
can wait can
[Music]
I
no
uh
wait okay
uh you need to answer my DM by the way I
asked you technical questions about the
mixer help me you gave it to me now help
me
so yeah
okay she's gone already did she go
because I didn't seem too excited about
astrobot was she like asot mention and
oh
so oh
I'm riding with her
now why
not okay
so
uh no n where's my where's my text
support mint did you read my
message asking you about functionalities
of the mixer that you have given
[Laughter]
me I even wrote the text support an
email though and they already replied
but I don't know it's not really helpful
so hopefully you can help me but I I I
have doubts that you can help
me
H yeah so
anyway I hope Yago had
fun the the the Arcane performance was
so cool some people are upset that
Fallout won
the best adaption I think I actually did
vote for uh
fallout I
mean it's it's a rough
choice I don't think Fallout didn't
deserve it yeah I feel like you have to
separate it because Arcane may seem more
impressive just for being incredibly
animated but that I think my thought
process was that's uh unfair to compare
an animated uh show to a non-animated
show and then give the animated show the
extra points just because it was really
well animated you know what I mean so I
wanted to just base my decision off of
overall like I don't know
Direction and pacing and everything
because season 2 of Arcane did have
pacing issues that were pretty
obvious um but besides that obviously it
was amazing amazing show but I didn't
feel any flaws when I watched Fallout I
didn't feel any like character flaws or
pacing flaws or um cinematic flaws
nothing so overall I think Fallout to me
was the better package I don't
know just start the game and people want
to hear what I thought about the game of
WS people asked me in the chat okay and
when we become detective we have to
focus on detective duties so I have to
let out the tangents
first oh oh oh mint M
MTO I see
[Music]
wasn't very
interesting Fallout was interesting it's
just been too long I think people are
just like because it's been a while
since people saw Fallout and it's more
recent that people saw Arcane it's more
fresh in their mind so they're like oh
it was more
interesting recency bias yep it's always
a thing true and also to seasons is more
impactful than one season I
guess ah it's difficult both should have
won B should have
won ideally but it doesn't matter you
know to each their own it's an objective
opinion in the
end I'm going to play the game now cute
cute detective
salami the peoni a the
peon a subjective you mean yeah what
what did I say oh did I say objective I
mean
subjective yeah of course
duh okay here we go open the
game quack quack quack quack quack qu qu
qu
loud oh [\h__\h] it's
German terrifying jump
scare
hopefully hopefully I can change it
still
cute English
yeah oh hey maybe this will help some
people oh what I feel
like if I look up here this is easier to
read than that wouldn't that be the none
I don't
know maybe I
misunderstand yeah okay here we go
that's fine back actually no I do one
full
[Music]
screen okay it feels kind of nice right
now
[Music]
h i mean I am a dyslexic and I don't
notice a difference okay maybe the
smaller Fone help Focus I thought it was
just like the the one looks cleaner and
easier to read oh well whatever new game
would you like dialogue to All Advance
yeah uh or do I no wait I don't [\h__\h]
whatever uh detective mode or story mode
feel like a True Detective lesson from
provided than incorrect no smooth
experience for fledgling detectives more
information I mean how difficult can it
be but this is recommended let's go with
let's go with
recommended you know I love life wasn't
easy I love these kind of
games that's I was a freshly divorced
duck that's not able to pay next month's
rent a deep ass that I paid for it this
month yet my brain felt
foggy and I was trying remember where
did all my money go I had to retrace
last night's
steps that voice is so human deductions
are a vital part of a detective's work
ductive du duct find clue words by
questioning persons and inspecting your
surroundings enter clue words into the
blank spaces to solve deductions ahuh oh
cute
okay The Nest Egg blah blah spent his
her last money on blah blah oh that
that's probably me oh it okay I'll I'll
figure it out then let's do our
detective this game is kind of short
which is good I wanted something short
wait this is still German po I won't be
needing this badge anymore I guess I can
keep it as a souvenir my new job has the
duck Detective
isn't going any better though is this
fully voiced this game things keep going
badly I could always sell it
online Change setting back um no maybe
we'll get for the game quicker this
way damn f voice cheese then my throat
will be cured today it will I'll be
taking it easy today yippee no messages
I wonder if it's also fully voiced in
German
then it do you want to let's
[Music]
try no
way this fresh smell ah damn it oh sweet
spongy
loaf you keep me save a
night ah we got bread bread let's
go okay back to unless it was here
nah um wait uh here off
okay this should
help look I'm just a piece of cardboard
cute
oh what I can do that that's
crazy how fun but nothing was found
there would be nice if there was a
hidden a hidden secret salami or a
hidden secret hi in there I can't
believe Anna actually filed the divorce
papers to you who would want to divorce
from
you poor poor duck guy second overdue
notice I wonder at what point they start
kicking people
out oh he's got no
monies wait is that Anna she has a
really wait she is she a duck she looks
more like a
one he SI I took that photo of her in a
secluded tulip field it is her we spoke
for hours under the stars that night a
romantic she doesn't even answer my
texts I have everything I need to solve
this now oh really we do let's see the
duct detective spent his last money on
uh uh
wait uh tulips for
Anna
[\h__\h] CH the bread for himself yeah okay
I wasn't sure I wasn't sure both not my
proudest
moment same but the toast helps me to
forget
froggit why is he not a
frog I thought that only frogs are
detectives at least the only capable
detectives I fought were
frogs so
confused what happened to all the Frog
detectives out
there Mushi
Mushi yo you should
like if you want her back and stuff and
she's like taking space from you
answering the phone like
that chill
still he said calmly I'm a different
duck now really which one are you I
haven't had a a slice of bread and
weeks oh is that like a bad thing here I
mean I know you should like bread for
Birds is generally not good but they
take that seriously huh it's like like a
drug level bad you have to believe me oh
[\h__\h] oh my God chill the [\h__\h] out chill
the duck out
oh yeah you're speaking to the duck
detective okay he's out of
control it wasn't even her
bro let's discuss this in person now be
there in an
hour okay I'm on my way did you know
duck sleep with one eye open be N I was
going to believe that there's no [\h__\h]
way because I saw the rest of the
sentence I couldn't read it out loud but
something about crime there's been more
than half of my a bus Fair there's no
way let's ask subu when I meet her I'll
ask
[Music]
her at first it's just a few crumbs each
day then before you know it you're
eating stale crusts that you find under
your
bed I mean if you have nothing else to
eat then I wouldn't blame
you but perhaps yeah you shouldn't be
spending your money on bread in the
first place but on something
more M healthy for
ducks what here I was in front of bear
bus office a bear some sort of rundown
Coal Center we got to deal with a
freaking bear I better crack this case
or I won't even have enough money to
make it back
home I don't know about
bears except Duma Duma is a bear that I
trust new bus route starting in August
visit the scenic mountains of Saia isn't
there a SAU wait a second
salami isn't this sausage uh sausage
that's a thing right tella we go there
one day that's where the secret salami
is
maybe it's so pretty oh physics oh he
hello are you uh are you a tourist from
Australia well that doesn't really look
like tourist
activities were you mad I'm staying here
until I get my money back oh be bus H
more like scam bus you're mad you're so
mad tell me about it I'm a
detective I can help you sound unhappy
you bet I am oh a drop Bear yeah that's
just basically also a bear their stupid
buses always arrive late I came back
from a work trip to the west and arrived
here at 3 in the
morning I would have loved to voice act
for this game and they don't even want
to give me a
refund how much did you
pay
um too schark schark is that the
currency here
that's so cute but that's not the point
it's about the principal sounds like a
vtuber maybe it does sound a little bit
like Ki especially when when when he she
screams a cute that's this is a cute
like logo
thing Dutch Mark yeah is this made by
German producer Dev Vel opers because I
can already tell based on her face that
the receptionist was a tough one a hint
towards uh Mark ah it is okay okay it
makes sense yeah she wouldn't make life
easy for me but I had to make my way
into the
office
whoa cute oops I keep on I have a thing
with trash cans it seems keep on
knocking them over no stay out oh it
says server room H it's like asking me
to come
in we'll get in there
eventually detective I'm here to
investigate a case how did I do that I
knocked something over again it must be
my beak must be my beak accidentally
like poking
things do you work
here D
no well then I can't let you in well you
can but you won't
so fix your grandmar but I've been hired
by someone from bear
buus who hired you um I didn't catch
their name listen
buddy well yeah I wonder who called me
maybe it was the the drop bear outside
you better get out of here or I'll have
to call
security is the death a whole life EV
what makes you think that is there a HD
somewhere that I already
missed there's always more to people
than you might think I should take a
closer look and figure out what she's
about okay we'll we'll we'll question
her you don't even know it but you're
currently under
investigation by this duck Detective use
the magnifying glass to find Clues and
press e to uncover them oh
oh were you crying you sad deep inside
you're depressed is that what this
says oh tear oh sad oh oh you got
fingernails actually you got more
detailed hands than I thought but that's
not the point right
kts boy B
okay okay okay see a K-pop stand oh the
name wind
timer wa timer kind kind of German never
heard it before but look at why is it
suddenly so detailed here oh the shoes
too cute that's funny the ears
also what's what's mysterious I I am
fascinated by this why is this brown and
these are orange is one more important
than the
other
cute still here either way uh no let's
not
leave I'll I'll have to do something
with this information for sure maybe
over here okay oh is her birthday or
something
or seventh
today
yeah oh Smiley happy not very
helpful
oh it's cute how everything becomes like
a little bit more HD so to
say giraff cute yeah great
not sure what to do with all of this
evidence tomorrow is Friday yeah I need
to remember to collect my dry cleaning
oh yeah that was more for you and your
private
life is this a tissue
box what I swear to God if someone
steals my mug again I'll end
[Laughter]
them oh so is it the giraffe lady Lara
from customer service is way too loud I
can hear her keyboard all the way to my
desk o noisy noisy noisy
Laura is this a feet wow we can read it
here s
okay so somebody maybe wrote this about
the giraffe Lady it's Sophie's birthday
next Thursday just
saying ah then it's today no her name's
Sophie did she already tell us
the the giraffe is Sophie she's crying
because it's her birthday today and
nobody said anything
[Music]
maybe yeah
Sophie nice these are quite mundane no
they're not I'm surprised nobody wrote
something more scandalous that was
pretty scandalous
already suspects it's important to work
out the suspect's name to crack the case
enter their first and last name name
into the slots below there's portrait in
your journal's suspect page sounds good
I think your name is
Sophie and I think yeah your last name
is win we know that for sure seems
correct what's this other stuff o
evidence we got my last money not even
enough to take a return bus oh
no we're in
trouble oh oh I can already solve it
here sopie is feeling
sad because nobody has remembered her
[Music]
birthday let's go that's why she's
making such a face on a roll y I should
try and cheer her yeah let's wish her
happy birthday and she'll be like how
the hell do you know I don't even know
you that's
amazing H wait oh wait oh wait this door
also has something it's locked I
literally just just told you you need to
stay
out somehow her voice sounds familiar
you're still here happy birthday and I'm
just here to wish you a happy birthday
I'm a professional birthday Wisher mhm
mhm that's what I came here for I've
been called to wish you a happy
birthday
yeah happy
birthday how did you know just another
one of duck detectives great
deductions huh uh anyway yeah that was
really nice of you no I'd be happy too I
wouldn't feel weirded out I mean
okay I I guess I would if realistically
if a complete St okay but I have to
assume then real again realistically in
my case if you a stranger came up to me
and said happy birthday they would
probably be a fan that's why they know
it's my birthday
but if I wasn't famous and my birthday
wasn't out there for people to know then
yeah then I'd be weirded out I
guess no one else remembered can you
believe it a if you know my birthday you
must have a connection to someone here
okay go ahead and assume things that
make it easier for me to get through
here thank you here's the key card to
the office you shouldn't that's a weird
n you know my birthday I will not
question it I will just assume that you
know someone here without asking who you
know I will not let you in into the top
secret places here's the key
card
really get get the office key
card okay so I can go into both doors
now it says it's locked
oh a okay this door is
okay no she's going to get fired on her
birthday that would be terrible
crocodile I love that face huge sideways
mouth a stained carpets and peeling
wallpaper exuded a stench of steel
coffee in abandoned dream talking to
himself I knew I couldn't stay long or
it would rub off on me
this is the last straw wait wait that
sounds like the same voice actors as the
one outside no fers needs to be
fired ferson she said
fison I'll see what I can do who is
fedison what did they do who are
you uh
uh Happy Birthday do you have a problem
uh uh do you have a problem I can solve
it if you have one just call our damn
hot sorry sorry sorry sorry I'm Eugene
mcquin
detective this music is bopping by the
way is the volume okay a client hired me
to investigate a
case why didn't you just say so it's
time we put an end to the awful lunch
death I would totally
have to call a a professional detective
for something like that
too but you know in a in a proper
office you know who takes care of stuff
like
that someone
like God damn it I'm so bad with names
yeah it sounds like an Office episode
exactly the office who would who would
take it upon himself
no not
Angela I mean Angela would want someone
to investigate but Dwight exactly Dwight
would do it for Angela perhaps or just
for the for justice for everybody just
like that all we need to fire him is
some evidence for the upper management
good old Dwight oh we need to fire him
oh I'll be in my office wait who who are
you trying fire the
crocodile no first I had to find out who
works here and what their jobs are wait
I see [\h__\h] salami up there I needed
to find my client as thankfully I
remembered the piece of paper I had in
my jacket smells
[Music]
delicious oh we got uh yeah could I
already like make assumptions for the
next
uh oh I could
oh now I'm not ready for that yet so are
you are you the guy who's going to get
fired I'm the only one here in the
operating office can you
imagine cute voice I plan all the bus
routes and make sure the buses are on
time oh but they're not on time
apparently isn't that so cool wait
you're not doing it right an angry
customer shouting outside about the
buses being
late I uh don't worry he can just eat
them you can just eat the customer
you're a [\h__\h] crocodile what are they
going to
do really open your mouth ah
snap crocodile has their ways of
Defending
themselves oh there's so much to look at
uh I don't know if I want to let me look
get this first
salami cash payment Mr Brandon Borg uh
30 W extra Peppa
salami I should play this in
German just to confuse you but also
because this has got to be it's got to
be German
yo
receip West
currency oh oh oh are we like
[Music]
uh uh do it no this could have been for
my German Channel huh wait I can't go
out am I not done oh yeah salami high
quality what
[Music]
else all right it's a new bag spotless
good condition yeah this is the kind of
bag that you store money in that you're
trying to
launder that's a lot of salami but he's
laundering
salami
yum which is pritzel by the
way station
pritzel britzel and salami good
combination sal sal
oh
es
snail H this oh what are we cooking
something I'm getting
hungry what does this
mean their buses don't go very far those
the places we're going like the that are
like around us we're living in a
interesting
world I think the Developers were really
hungry when they made this game they
were on a on a hunger strike they were
placed on a hunger strike maybe the CEO
was like okay you guys got to make me a
funny game and until you make it I'm not
going to feed you guys and this is the
result of it starving deaths
yeah
interrogate uh wait no I think that's
not really what was that again do you
have any idea who picked me to
investigate oh okay good you you come up
with the questions SC good job
dectective no idea but I'm so happy
you're here is that a nervous answer I
have a copy of your book the early bird
catches the
criminal huh I have a book can you sign
it should I sign
it what's him who hired you you think so
what imagine just h Maring him because
you want a signature like
it's cuz you didn't know how else to get
a signature so you pretend you have a
job for
him that's kind of messed
up got his name is a PO
true ah does that
work thanks so much Mr duck detective I
won't ever forget this yeah who who do I
signed for this will become a core
memory no core cute the way he said that
was cute
I didn't get his freaking
name okay let's find
something oh he's he's wearing
glasses St was bad ass eyesight cute oh
he's he's
oh look it's cute it's kind of
frowning he's so
cute laa
that's how you say it in German laa not
Laura shoot nice shoes
cute I like when hands are drawn like
this
cute velcro velcro lame no not lame I
mean velcro damn when's the last time I
wore velcro shoes I love Velcro shoes
though small
hands okay oh hello how are you Mr duck
well at least he likes me so we could
use that to our
advantage trash go bye bye wait this I
need to read this it's a list of all the
bus the most busy driver out of all four
seems to be
Petra page
[Music]
driver huh the two desks on this side
look
unused this dog needs some sleep holy
moly I can see it from here I don't even
need to like put my magnifying glass on
you oh it gets even
worse terrifying yeah small dogs are
terrifying it's a cat e looks like a one
of those crazy small dogs
where's the
tail oh energy
drink not good for you not good for
you different brand own headset
dedicated what do you mean different
brand different brand from ah from my
own
headset you cat or dog or something
completely different this is fa bus how
can I help you this is the third time
you're calling I'm telling you your
ex-wife did not cancel your
booking she uh looks
busy your ex-wife did not cancel your
booking is that a hint
[Music]
too this is bear bu uh your yarn ball is
still on the
bus which route were you
on whoever was on the phone was a
cat in interrogate about I need to ask
you some questions no I'm sorry you
can't take your 12 trombones on the bus
trombone Champion be like what can't you
see I'm talking to a customer trombone
Champion you you have to take I don't
know a taxi or private jet you can't
take the bus it seems with all your
trombones you're not welcome it's
company policy nothing I can do goodbye
do you know anything about who called me
here what are you talking about listen I
have a million more emails to answer and
there are 50 people in the phone queue I
kind of feel bad for this dog cat
they're obviously very very overworked
they're not enough workers here so much
pressure so much stress it's like really
understandable that you become like a
angry loud
like person who like lashes out at
people
like working in an environment like
this I have worked 10 days in a row
including three night shifts and Manfred
still doesn't want to give me a raise
you need a break you need a break just
leave me in peace Manfred you mean so
Manfred you have no clues for me
[Music]
Manfred what is your relationship with
Sophie windimer let's stress this cat
dog out even more even though I feel bad
for her excuse me for a second oh man I
don't know how I'd survive the office
without her oh sucks that she's at the
reception I would have loved to have her
in the office yeah she should help out
there's nothing going on in the freaking
reception she probably has a lot of free
time she should help out taking some
calls I'm back yes please collect your
toddler from the bus
station Lost Child okay
okay uh yeah
good let take a look at this the PC is
on but the person who works at this desk
seems to be on a break they only have a
single person answering the hotline
right now o everybody just escaped cuz
they don't give a [\h__\h] that's
surprising Whitlock oh what is what
animal is
that
posing what is that w loock
password password hint me and sexy
aliens
what me and sexy aliens was that mean
yeah it does kind of look alpaka is or
sheepish yeah probably those are like
ears up
there there are Clues to her password I
don't think I have enough information
to yeah I don't know not smart enough to
crack that one
yet oh let's check out this door I
shouldn't go outside I need to find out
who the people in this office are did I
remember to write down their professions
in my deductible oh okay I I can uh how
do I uh tap
okay uh this is
I I actually I don't
know uh actually I don't
know I don't know I don't know these are
not not the professions anyway well
you're not Petrovic and you're not
Whitlock but I also don't think you're
frederson you seem like a
Petrovic now we we'll try a bit
harder in here must be the crime scene
crime scene first I want to find out who
the people in the office are or the
lunch it will make things easy I'll need
to remember to write everything down
M this could be
useful a knew that a new one coming out
in 2025 what and this the thing is like
this one isn't even the only one
apparently there was also one before
right there's another one I didn't play
that one
Employee of the Month oh cute cute
doodles fixed insert photo
here that's not a
photo lazy Freddy sucks oh that's so
mean who wrote that
who if I was Freddy and I worked here I
would cry if I saw that and I would quit
Rufus said there is that the employee of
the
month maybe sucks
sister okay okay maybe stop it with the
posted wait there's one more
thing just going to click
everywhere no
nope nope
nope there you go
okay rof sarus I'm not sure I'd feel
particularly appreciated exactly that's
what I'm saying oh can I maybe pick up
the
phone no oh
okay so this says come in so we should
go
in we're for S no no no no no Freddy
could still have the room seemed a
promise well kept secret this his last
name but it also uh means Sirius his
name is Mr
Sirus mhm sus you're
dad interesting how are detective things
going he's got Twins or so they look
like teddy
bears it's Mr
mcquin so wait did he he's asking me
maybe he called me right
apologies um right added to the
clu what are you planning on staying in
my office much longer I'll have to
inspect the entire premise to do my job
correctly oh he seems unhappy with me
being here now so maybe he didn't call
me well hurry
[Music]
up ooh that frown
wait did you see okay often when I ask
you guys if you saw something that I saw
on Twitter often you guys say yeah but
you might have missed this one did you
see the the the the was it a Pikachu or
something on Twitter like a plushie in
in a shelf of a shop uh where like it
was so scrunched up that it looked like
I think it was a Pikachu it was
definitely a Pokmon it looked like it
was like frowning like this just because
it was so yeah side duck a side duck
yeah
it was just scrunched up and and it
looks so cute like a really angry
Psyduck and it's like looking at you in
this intimidating way like it wants to
kill
you iuck always suffering the stern
oh
ew dirty oh baby food Family Man okay
okay
oh expensive branch
manager
[Music]
okay was it you who called me no I never
heard of you before God damn it that's
unusual it's good you're here her add it
to the
clues un rest damn
it wait so wait wait his name is an do
we know his first
name I have a feeling you're not oh
maybe they'll say more if I ask them
this is the second time that they'll
have that they have different dialogue
maybe I should always ask people like
talk to them more I am a detective after
all not particularly I should like
stress them out and put pressure on them
wasn't manlet the boss yeah could be oh
well you retracted it though
let's let's try let's try one more time
how are the it's Mr MC okay this is the
same one are you plenty I'll have to
well H all right what a fence it says
mhm we already kind of recognize that
it's a letter for an application for a
promotion to senior customer service
agent H signed by L
angst L angst
what are you doing with my family's
portrait I'm just looking at how pretty
it is sorry your kids are so
cute
oh oh they are
twins okay kids identical age twins ah
wow I must be a
detective
[Music]
wow what else oh oh there's something
here hinge secret secret compartment but
I can't open it
now oh framed high quality oh okay okay
yeah ooh this must be like a safe that's
hiding special
money is money normal to have a huge
painting of your family in your office
oh yeah that big is kind of crazy but
sure what what are you doing with my
sorry okay
[Music]
okay I think can I do something now his
last name is an first name we can try
with Manfred oh it it worked
apparently we have so many names
now I don't know about the
others whoops
sorry wait did I see that one
it's a letter for
an
okay manid he must have the salami you
think it's in
there I think I would smell
it the two desks on this
side what no well we talk to everybody
can I go here now I
remember I got to I got to solve some
stuff
I'm the only one here in the operating
I'm play in all the bus isn't that don't
you have an an i really wait can I uh
oops can I do like the the the question
stuff again where do you do that
here
uh the the giraffe was her name Sophie
well it's got to it's got to be works as
a
receptionist the bear
is Manfred and he is
the branch manager oh it's a cat I'm
guessing it's Sophie the cat Works in is
deduction guys it's deduction Works in
customer
service crocodile
called do I still need another option
here
because his name wouldn't be Bear buus
right in the operating office probably
though the cat isn't Sophie but the
crocodile isn't Sophie
either maybe yeah I'm still missing some
[Music]
options okay but but we're getting there
wait do I know I don't I mean if if I
knew it would show up as an extra option
what about here
uh ah okay we don't know yet who hired
me lunch was stolen by a coworker known
as we don't know that yet either though
right cuz that would already solve our
[Music]
crime
uh God damn it do I know your name
double
checking this is bear bus how can I help
you wait she says this is bebus but
that's not her name she just says it as
a representing person of her company
thir your exwife did
not ah well I can ask about another oh
right then we should go to the crocodile
too what do you think about Manfred Aon
oh he's a great guy I just wish I'd
finally get a raise oh yes sorry this is
bear buus your bus will be 3 hours late
she wants a race maybe she's the one who
applied for
um for the for the
promotion Freddy sucks ah Manfred Freddy
sucks Rufus Sedaris stop who is Rufus
Sedaris that didn't come uh up as one of
our like words to choose from yet either
H froy waa y froy
waa I've been seeing you guys been using
your froggy waa hoodie kfp is getting a
little bit more colorful than usual but
make sure to like maybe have something
orange still maybe if it's really cold
make sure that you wear something orange
over the froggy wa you still got to like
represent orange somehow at least at a
concert you
know need needs more orange orange scarf
yeah orange hat H orange hat would help
anyway uh ask you about your boss you
know about I think he likes me he's the
only one who doesn't shout at
me okay oh how are
you can I talk again with the lady at
the
reception oh yeah we didn't ask her
about this so do you have an idea who
it's about the incident isn't it oh she
knows something um sorry her name is
Sophie she has no
idea I'm so I don't understand why such
a small office needs a reception exactly
do you want to help them out inside I'm
just here to keep the angry customers
out
well you know a way to keep out all the
angry customers is also to just have a
closed like
office that doesn't let people in in the
first place like just for people to go
to work just don't have a
reception if they have a problem they
should call which is what what the girl
is in there for to take the call
calls just say customer services phone
only we don't you you guys don't need a
[Music]
reception let's read this again maybe
this will help us I swear to
God Laura from customer services wait ah
her name is Laura right probably most
likely it's
Laura the the inside girl inside
girl yeah yeah
but was that even an option
though ah here
Laura last name you look like you have a
lot of
angst it was a guess
but these two like he looks serious so
he is aned she looks like she's carrying
a lot of ANS so yeah it works uh by that
deduction you do look like a rofus oh
and employee of the month wait he did
say yeah you get it like oh employee of
the month was the ruthless
guy oh because he did say he thinks the
boss likes him [\h__\h] if you're not
ruthless SAR is are you
[Music]
Freddy
[Laughter]
ferson good guess you Freddy
freden h
oh the crocodile
Freddy okay uh Laura the cat there you
go duck
approved tricky deductions might require
New Perspectives press h to get
additional guidance at any time now that
I had worked out these names I was ready
to check out the crime scene
O Let's see where that lunch got stolen
then I could finally talk to my client
can I eat one chocolate
please this reminds your ler alligator
for some reason of course it's like a a
comfortable it's like one of those games
like later alligator frog detective it's
like a mix of
[Music]
them I love
it so crime scene here we go
might be bloody careful guys as soon as
I enter the kitchen the comforting wa to
cheap white toast entered my
nostrils oh
[Music]
no I knew I had to stay
strong this wasn't what I was here
for but we are here for you
detective stop eating the
icing can't you wait a couple flowers
that guy the penguin forgive him he's a
penguin Margaret if it wasn't for these
pants Mar almost bursting oh [\h__\h] spicy
I have this for breakfast no I know what
you mean day he's full he's saying he's
full yes yes and you can have it and so
much more later when we're done
preparing it's so messy in here what are
you guys doing
oh Halloween party coming
up oh no it's
cancel
damn don't you write canceled with
double l i I would also make that
mistake though sometimes I think back in
the day but I think it's Double L
right yeah typical German people
mistake hi R get on get your own
lunch mhm this must be from the person
who hired me looking for editor unpaid
oh this is
cute all right we already have it office
parties are a bad idea anyway mhm they
stopped doing them at the precinct after
the uh Jam incident the precinct what
what's the
precinct Hello nice to meet you wait
your name should already be there come
on game help me out I I'm going to
forget I already forgot it I'm Eugene
mcquin detective and I need to ask I
already called you by your name a
detective how exciting what's the most
gruesome murder you've
seen uh yeah um my friends um you know I
hang out a lot with birds so I got a
couple Crow
friends uh they're not that gruesome
though
it's a jerk many crows are a murder
[Music]
woohoo how many jet bodies have you
encountered oh five little pigs teing
Turtles leave uh Five Little Pigs no one
died but I investigated the case once
where Five Little Pigs robbed a bank a
caught them red-handed and got myself an
article in the goose times the goose
times they called it the piggy bag
case I know the biggy Bank case I heard
different story about that
one
huh a couple of other people were
involved in that one um a squirel
an alien and a fashion model did someone
get
shot that's what I heard uh no nobody
thank God nobody got shot may it may may
have been a close one what no beaten
up Perhaps Perhaps who knows what
happens behind the scenes at ID
headquarters just
kidding cute
oh your chin is more snatched up here oh
she cooking she baking muddly she's
mothering oh ooh impeccable hair well of
course it's got to
be she's got hands wait a second she
took her ring off she's is actually
married or not she's divorced okay I
thought she just took it off for baking
so she doesn't lose it in her
dough surely you must have some
interesting stories do you want to hear
about the turtles I almost died that one
time dramatic when I got myself into
trouble with the teething Turtles Mafia
oh [\h__\h] that incident taught me to stay
away from beut
ladies in red oh I know what you mean
man beautiful ladies in red
dangerous
dangerous that what that's what narissa
would say about herb too did they break
your
kneecaps huh no do ducks have kneecaps
you can see that I can walk just
[Music]
fine oh I doubt they washed their hands
after leaving that
W food oh my God is that bread
Margaret
wait
Margaret is this what is is this packed
lunch thanks for the food salami
Bandit that's
German or also English I guess salami
Bandit same in
German sharp clock
was but obviously it was the crocodile
cuz he I saw his bag with the
salami wait the lunch was stolen by the
crocodile
obviously I already know
it what
else I'm missing one I'm CL oh there we
go sometimes it's on the same thing
twice
nice so this must be the crime scene you
might know it but you have to prove it
I've got the the hand prints the claw
prints right there sir and I've got the
salami right there too sir this not is
cute oops I was pressed that but I got
to go
here oh she's a
sheep
uh wait maybe if I put it here yeah
I it won't let me I heard him say her
name maybe I got to talk to him first
dishwashers broken again D dishwash is
broken
again what's wrong with these youngsters
what's wrong with these youngsters don't
know how to treat things with respect
don't know how to treat things with
respect why would they put the mugs in
face up why would they put the mugs in
face
up sorry I want to I want to be able to
talk like them it's marvelous H maybe I
should leave the dishwasher broken for a
bit that'll teach them a lesson oh so
evil what an evil pengu evil penguin
can't trust
Penguins yeah look at those eyes not
very
trustworthy toolbox janitor
mhm sticker sci-fi fan
that won't help me will it worker shoes
practical
person great that didn't help that
much can I sorry can I set it
now Margaret right
Margaret wait div I wonder maybe she's
divorced from somebody
who's working here too but is your name
Rufus Saras really
you're ruus Sedaris employee of the
month or was the employee of the month
someone
else ah yeah she's probably the one who
left her
seat what was that about sexy
alien I'm not sure what to make of
[Music]
that uh Margaret the Sheep Works in also
customer service penguin
is ruthless and works as the janitor the
Buffalo I haven't met the Buffalo yet
have
I but that's all the evidence here I
think but we we got to question them
on H I don't know on bear bus first is
there anyone here who could have hired
me to be honest everyone was quite
shocked by the lunch
theft what if the thief himself hired me
as a distraction and no one told me
they've called a detective no one would
supposedly think that the thief is the
one the one that hired me is the thief
yeah I don't know what's going on at all
at all at all can you tell me anything
about Laura angst oh she's such a
hardworking go I suppose I can only ask
about certain people once I have their
name fully cleared I heard she secretly
studies for her online Bachelors during
work
oh you need to keep this a secret though
why is this a secret why are you telling
me that anyway are you getting along
with Rufus sederis you know the two of
us are from the older generation are you
two the ones that used to be married
which means we understand each other
well he is quite harsh towards the
younger ones that
like your kids with him what do you
think of Sophie
Wier she doesn't have the easiest life
you know she just had a terrible breakup
with her ex
oh did we know that it's her birthday
and she also just had a terrible breakup
but don't tell
anyone ah you're the talkative one
aren't
you would you say you enjoy Bo Freddy
F's
um company company huh if anyone needs
to learn to respect their Elders it's
that Boron oh [\h__\h] he's
mad what did he do to you do you get
along with man Fred
erst he's a stubborn mon I don't think
ruus gets along with anybody I do
respect that he yeah you respect it but
you still you still don't like him do
you is your relationship with Margaret
Whitlock drum roll ah she's a true
sweetheart we have our weekly maong
evenings oh you say that in such a spicy
way you have your weekly maong evenings
with that sheep pong I'm a private
detective while you guys play besides ma
is that sound I need to find my client
do you know who Freddy's a bit of a
weird one so I'd imagine you would call
of course the thief calls me personally
I feel we're doing just fine and don't
need no messing about our business oh
that sounds like something the thief
would say maybe you Framed
Freddy maybe you did frame
Freddy um okay let's talk to Fred
ready about the new
people what can you tell me about
Margaret I can't ask him about the
janitor interesting really angry with me
when I don't return mugs to the
kitchen
mugs do you also steal mugs by any
chance why don't you just I do uh just
not y I see four mugs right there stinky
stinky they're all so full
are they all from today those full
ones this salami you shouldn't if you're
such a amateur Thief you shouldn't leave
it out in the open like that
bro I'm the only one here in the
operating I'm playing all the isn't
don't you have
an really
H I wonder if it's also worth going out
to the drop bear one more time
but I also need to talk to you again
about these two what can you tell me
about Laura X Laura needs to chill out
wait wait wait wait wait wait Laura said
really nice things about you I do love
her if she keeps living like this she'll
have a heart attack by 23 okay she said
it so meanly in the beginning but it is
it comes from a a good
place she's she's just
worried how are you getting on with
Margaret with luck she's sweet and all
but oh she always starts like that she
can't keep her mouth shut that is true
it seems like the office knows more
about my personal life than me it seems
like the office knows more about my
personal life than
me well said well
said that is of course messed up we
don't want that I'll go talk to the oh I
can't okay okay okay I need a key for
this place place it says it's locked let
me in that's obviously where where
everything all the [\h__\h] goes
down poor
koala
no okay let's
see
oh well I'll try this let's see
it two of you oh both are
wrong both are wrong is it just wrong
because I shouldn't know yet and later
we actually
right oh wait the salami Bandit what
what do you mean it's
wrong
wait no cuz like there's framed here and
I was thinking maybe Freddy was
Framed Freddy
[Music]
but
N I don't know it's two or fewer
[Music]
oh I could like try all of these names
but nah probably the one that we didn't
meet yet who's probably in the server
room is the one who hired us see is on
but they only have a single that's
surprising
Whitlock can I go here now I
can maybe smoke
break what what is that what animal is
that c air ruffled my feathers I heard
about what you are but I forgot and I
wondered what kind of sorry Soul was
standing all alone in the rain must be
someone who likes uh rain water water do
you like water hey man this isn't the
bus stop you'll have to walk south to
the central bus what what that sounded
like a quack I'm not here to take a
bus
oh
Boris what uh what is it water Ah that's
why he doesn't mind being in out there
in the rain
Oh I thought those were your
eyes did you guys also think that that's
those are the
nostrils R proportion nose hands
them
indeed I would agree with
that Hands In Pockets bad bad maners nah
there no Bad Manners give this guy a
break he's out in the rain even though
he seems to be enjoying it if I go
inside I have to face Sophie Sophie was
the giraffe no I
forgot no maybe it
was let's ask about what do you think of
Sophie windimer it was the giraffe okay
you guys are also I wish she'd let me
talk to her detectives here wish she'd
let me talk to her oh you the
ex-boyfriend do you um like Freddy
frederson that would be awkward
he's a pretty funny
dude loves to rant about detective
novels oh yeah about my novels what do
you know about Rufus Sedaris I don't
think he likes me very much to be honest
but then doesn't feel like he likes
anyone at this office that's what I was
saying except for Margaret I guess
Margaret was the Sheep do you think they
have a thing going on yeah I thought so
actually
I don't work
here I thought you were a
detective I'm investigating a case here
at Bear buus there's a bag here with sus
bag oh do you mean the lunch that got
stolen oh oh oh
exactly nah too busy minding my own
business damn it he didn't call me I
don't talk much with the customer
service folks
M well
not
hold well would you look at this
suspicious bag their bag here it's full
of dirty gym
clothes dirty gym
clothes interesting we took it wait wait
why why do we just take the liberty for
ourselves to take that if anything it
should be like his job because he's
taking care of these buses out there if
there's a lost and found he should take
it
yoink unbelievable
unethical really I want to read all
these notes these are important people
love post this
here so okay I'm not sure if that's
helping me right now but wait let's go
oh yeah let's go back in here talk to
the
boss haven't talked to him in a
while janitor is Rufus Sedaris
like he came with the building
okay what do you know about Laura angst
oh she's a fantastic employee she
basically does the work of five people
mhm mhm would you like to hire four
maybe or
three nothing new I have a feeling
you're not not in not no no no no
[Music]
no finally got off work off work and
right back to work we have a case to
solve get on with
it I want to try entering the password
the two desks on
[Music]
this oh how are you
ah there you go is this your bag huh no
mine's over there with the salami are
you sure one with all the salami oh yeah
why do you need so much salami it's not
mine oh it was just there oh a really
nice surprise oh oh uh so somebody did
frame
you wait I want to ask more about it
here in the operator I play don't you
have an an really how come I can't ask
more about that I have so many
questions okay uh ah here
uh
uh wait I got to go here
first Boris Petrovic there we go I got
an achievement fill out all suspects
names am I speedr running this
game surely there's more this is two and
a half to three
hours there got to be more
Mark Boris the Buffalo is a I guess he's
a bus
driver all righty now that I had
everyone's name and job it would be
easier to figure out what was going
on it is only the single case huh it
must be a lot more complicated than we
think it
is
oh okay but we still don't know who
hired me nobody hired
me um
[Music]
was it not Laura what Laura she didn't
at least she didn't admit Sheed let me
in I want to go in
there oh my
God I love these KJS memes Laura keeps
sending me so you're both into
it what kind of a person is oh I don't
know what I saw in
him so they were together I mean I guess
he's goodlooking my God
[Music]
boring that's so mean it doesn't seem
that
[Music]
boring that's enough to kill a
man H wait wait wait let's talk to Laura
about Boris too
maybe or about Fred
can you tell me more about Fred let me
put you on hold while I find the route
for you
Freddy what the [\h__\h] did you just say he
gets paid more than me can you imagine
that yeah that doesn't seem quite Fair
what an incompetent waste of office
space no no no no no he is
needed I
think birthday merch arrived wait you
mean the one with the vanan and the
[Music]
happy wait where are you where are you
at is it already arriving in like
[Music]
na R's on the way arrived West Coast oh
[\h__\h] could we see some people in AWA AWA
wear
it does anybody have it
hello this is Laur again I checked the
bus routes and found that maybe just a
tiny bit too late huh a bunch of you
guys say it's arriving on Monday
so so
close my birthday Mar just arrived to
den market so I'll have it this year
maybe yeah okay well it's kind of a
Christmas
present on my way to Atlanta now and
we've not even got a shipping notice on
the East Coast oh rip ah would have been
too nice too good to be
true wait so that's
it this is be uh
you're what
now it's a list of all the most busy
drop what
now maybe I should just eat the salami
destroy
evidence why didn't the thief wait if
the thief planted the salami
there to frame
Freddy you could have just just just
eaten but then I guess you couldn't have
framed it
anyone but you could have just eaten
it check the board next to Fred I
already
did you want me to check it again did
anything change
delicious
evidence I would eat it too I would
steal it and I would eat
it bear
bus oh I already like saw all of
this is this a
sign is this like the Star Sign supposed
to tell me
something back into the kitchen
you bag do you know whose bag isn't that
Freddy's we should ask him about it do
you know anything about this bag why are
you going around pushing bags into
people's faces why you going around
pushing bags into people's
spices what's that awful smell oh he's
got a good nose he smells that there was
salami in that bag it's um oh no dirty
gym clothes I thought that was like a
Switcheroo thing going on apparently
[Music]
not what wait a second oh no never mind
I a quack I doubt they wash their
hands wait how did I not realize this
until
now quack quack
so I could press h for extra help but
we're not going to do that we're not
going to do that anything new
[Music]
here so it was Laura who called me I I I
didn't even know that I didn't have a
confirmation I just tried
it I guess that's what you call
deductions I needed to discuss the case
with
her you're my client wait what he's not
even sure about it he's also surprised
we really just deducted it I guess
there's a lot of deduction in this game
why didn't you tell me yeah why why you
got to make it so difficult can I put
you on hold for for a second she for she
for you should have told me you're the
duck detective I'm a duck I look like a
detective you should be deducting it
yourself I'm a duck yeah that's what I'm
saying I'm wearing a trench coat that's
what I'm saying so is Freddy getting
fired or what that's what I'm saying
I'm it can't be that hard sorry I'm back
yes let me walk you through the booking
process it was time that I found out
what happened with the
l c and what they were planning in the
kitchen spicy
things oh blah is being Blah by blah
because blah picked up the blah
blah
ah
Framed Freddy is Being Framed by I'm not
sure yet
because oh the
wrong back
ah wait how many are wrong two or
fewer should I should I even be trying
all of this yet
what if I accidentally figure it out
wait wait wait being frank
by
ruus My
[Music]
Friend
Sophie bear bus
handsome no no no wait the moment I
close this am I going to be showing a
hint I don't want to see it I don't need
it okay good
I'll figure it out I'll figure it out
I'm a detective I'll deduce it I'll
deduct
it can I ask some new
questions do you get along with Boris
Petrovic he's a chill guy I take the bus
sometimes to go to bouldering
conventions and then we get to chat
bouldering conventions
do you guys just climb around that
sounds
fun I pred my wle let's go thank
you thank you for picking up small haaha
she was scared and lost she needs to be
picked
up he's a chill guy you say wait we need
to talk to Boris about did we talk to
him about the bag well whatever maybe we
have anything something to talk about
let's
ask she was scared and lost for you yeah
for for years yeah yeah ah there we go
do you know anything about this bad oh
oh it's really strange M things in it
disappeared oh and others appeared oh
very
suspicious what are you even talking
about is this your
bag
no everyone here is being really
unhelpful
[Music]
huh hi I got it just kidding I don't
but it's just quacking to
myself trying to figure it
out in a very dramatic place in a very
dramatic
way
[Music]
man did we ask the boss about the bag I
don't think
so let's see if he cares no no Boris
what can you tell he's uh not the most
reliable
worker oh I
see but it's difficult finding
Replacements
nowadays that's it tell me
more this is still so super sus what are
you doing with my
sorry m
maybe
maybe yeah what about the sexy
aliens what does that
mean that doesn't make any
sense let me enter your
password pass
computer uh all right let's ask maybe
she knows something
new
no can I go out I can't leave I need to
S I'm not going to ask the game to help
me I'm not going to do
it kitchen yeah guess we're going to
circle back to the kitchen solve the
kitchen what do you mean solve the
kitchen what's there to solve they're
doing spicy things but yeah I guess he
did say something about like we got to
figure out what's going on in the
kitchen do we just talk normally surely
you must have some interesting story
that's
inap
no dishwashers what's wrong don't know
how to why would they
put no okay maybe in here then
Oh you mean that way okay okay solve it
like that okay uh blah is planning a a
Halloween uh
party why is there no oh surprise party
maybe uh maybe uh what's her name
Margaret
Whitlock I think she's planning a
surprise party
for
Sophie uh surprise h birthday
birthday
party amazing Margaret was planning a
surprise birthday party for Sophie I
think I'm like pretty good to take like
all the cases that I'mma left behind she
does not need to worry I'll solve all
her cases for
her yeah leave it to me hi I see they
didn't actually forget her
birthday so
now what
[Music]
now new clue new
options oh you think there's new options
here I don't
know you think I can solve it and maybe
I can brute force it but I guess no BR
forcing is basically deducting
so but he it does say 17 out of 17 so I
have inferior it this seems like I have
everything that I need to solve
it
um would you say it's
framed is Being Framed heard seen
stolen Freddy's definitely Being Framed
right by uh probably
Boris because
no maybe
Boris buy the salami Bandit because
Boris picked no that's not
right they were playing Mir and chimo
loop Bast dope blit super based
cornbread
Thief where is that
store wrong mug picked up the wrong
mug and
what no get rid of that how many are
wrong two or
fewer
H it's Being Framed by Boris Freddy
maybe it's not Freddy No Maybe
Boris maybe Boris is Being Framed by
Freddy because Boris
no uh by the salami Bandit because
no didn't Laura seem to have it out for
Freddy perhaps she's also the one who
called me though free oh no Laura is
definitely wrong wait that just
changed from wait what was
oh yeah okay this is this has to be
correct
then because it right that's deduction
the fact that it changed from Two and a
half to three two or few to
three how's this maybe it's not
that but like the other words don't
really make sense ah wait no no the the
logic of the sentence doesn't make
unless it's like heard or seen or
stolen no but no it can't be stolen
because there's no fitting words for
it bear bus is Being
Framed because Boris no okay okay
Freddy wait what
the mug the mug is the
[Music]
bag Fred I'm overthinking
it see okay it had to go back to bag it
was as I thought it wasn't the M yeah
just what I'm saying it was as I thought
Freddy was Being Framed
by
Boris that's what I was saying all along
I was trying to deduce it to
that I got misled
Freddy frederson was actually being
framed
exactly this office wasn't as boring as
it looked oh yeah by the Bandit yeah
yeah yeah the salami Bandit which we
don't know the identity of yet unless we
deduct
it when Freddy took the bus back and he
went to pick up his
luggage he must have picked up the wrong
bag oh this happened because there was
another bag that's identical to his what
a coincidence the bag that he picked up
belonged to the salami
Bandit this made him a Target and to get
rid of Freddy the salami Bandit decided
to frame him is it the drop bear time
for you know what because the other one
that I know that just got off a bus is
the the drop
bear but the drop bear is like concerned
with other
things H okay well party time let's
celebrate our deduction get into
position wait I'm also going to be part
of this party okay I just texted her so
she should be hearing that cake looks
amazing huh what's this
[Music]
surprise what's up
Freddie uh no way yes way this is all
for me hell yeah bam so many presents
even I'm
[Music]
Jelly salami huh a
letter
scary you made it to Atlanta let's go I
hope you're going to have lots of fun
everybody please welcome tasimu in
Atlanta came a long
way
oh salami what a terrible
present
okay way to make yourself seem less like
a culprit by saying how much you hate
salami but no I don't think it's you
it's okay no you silly idiot no you
silly idiot the real present got stolen
and switch for
[Music]
salami
oh oh wait wouldn't you think that
maybe Boris that that's boris's
gift because Boris wants to you know
make up with
her uh he was there where the bags were
right like you know what I mean it's his
bag
[Music]
he wasn't intending on gifting
salami something like that at the con
you C me a cult of really nice good
people
oh you sound like you're not one of you
sound like you think you're not one of
us but trust me my
friend before you know
it you're already in it it's the salami
Bandit I saw an awful lot of highr
salami in Fred's bag why is there so
much salami and now there's no question
who the perpetrator is you know the one
person who's not here is I've been
telling you all along trusted the bosses
here by the end of the day he'll be
fired shut up he's right there don't be
so mean mark my words
Laura okay let's let's give her a chance
she stressed out has being stolen yeah
or is there more to it she's stressed
out ooh many deductions to be made but I
don't have all the words
yet
[Music]
okay why you okay you have the duck
detective here out wait aliens wait is
that a sexy alien porn
book what can you possibly do does it
have a
hint wait wait wait oh B
Ved
passwords sexy aliens want my number by
suur
Ces oh spicing
book uh questionable title adult
novel wait is the
password is is the offer
name like a fake name
and it's actually uh the sheep that
wrote this maybe I don't know Captain
brightbeak stared deep into the alien we
have to read this for professional
detective reasons Captain bradbe stared
deep into the alien's eyes there were 12
of them and they were red
Oh e the eyes not the aliens yeah the
aliens were blue and there were 43 oh oh
oh my God how many eyes is that do the
math all of them weree shiny metal
armor which shined like something shiny
made of curved metal
great this
offer such a great way of writing
words the lead alien stepped forward
captain brightbeak could tell it was the
lead alien because it was the one which
stepped for
uhhuh it was also the most beautiful the
only one with purple
eyes I see why does only he have
different eye
color it made a noise that sounded a bit
like talking from a hole that looked a
bit like a pretty lady's mouth the
translation device the captain had
invented had invented word into action
translating the words into words he
could
understand I thought so hey you look
cute a mechanical voice whispered into
his ear can I get your number
252 long book damn I wish I could read
the whole thing oh oh God what did I
just drink it wasn't that scandalous
come on it's a heart-shaped neckace
that's cute looks tacking hey it's
cute B know
everyone not just Sophie fre message
huh quite unbelievable I
entered the office really easily LOL
sayata Edge
Lords I think you're the edge Lord the
person who uses the word Edge Lord is
usually The Edge
Lord
[Music]
salami H I wonder what the purpose drop
bear
oh we take it as
evidence oh nothing changed here right
okay we read the bogos bint let's look
at the cat someone gifted Sophie a plusy
cute it says limited edition
o must have been expensive then maybe
special stuff can you tell me something
about this Sophie won't even talk to me
about it I don't know what to
do I don't think Sophie understands
either give her a break she won't talk
to me about it
either okay you don't want to talk about
it either
maybe we can get into the computer
now I don't know if that's a ethical
thing for me to do and try but oh look
the janitor is inside now what do you
think about this
letter people don't know how to write
letters by hand
anymore what's with the weird lime
breaks
oh what do you mean wait can I look at
it
again you're pointing out something
interesting wait
wa I want to read it
again do I have to go there even though
I'm supposedly carrying it with
me there was a random blank
spot oh okay B ah
b
q or
or e l Z or else ah wait or else I've
heard that before
b
[Music]
b what
what be
[Music]
quiet oh I missed the te be quiet or El
okay okay be be
quiet somebody already uh before like uh
I saw something somebody was complaining
about the T tap tap tapy tapy noise and
the tappy tappy tappy tappy noise comes
from her right
mostly huh that work but I thought I'd
pop in to show off my new Burning
chicken bad oh let's go s
[Music]
Mirage okay well that's interesting oh
wait we can look at her
PC
oh returned but they're sexy now bye now
Boo's being dead oh my God LOL is he
serious
today pen name mystery offer what a dumb
pen name haha it's just his name
backwards that's what I thought I I I I
knew something with the name I should
like re realign the letters or something
complaints can the O please clean her
desk the office the the something
operator I can smell it until here yeah
it's this is obviously about
Freddy
um she really has a problem of
Freddy this is
a the left messagers are from Sophie
right they're
friends H so Laura bought the book for
Sophie
right but I don't understand
why are they making fun of the book but
I thought she likes sexy
aliens you defin definitely don't want
to be Laura's
enemy this folder says manual for CS
agent how and when to create vouchers
correctly I'm falling asleep just
reading the H maybe there's more to it
my
friend anyway
[Music]
oh
oh what me why what what's the what does
that
[Music]
mean purple eyed alien how about that oh
I cracked
[Music]
it I cracked that [\h__\h] open like a beer
can that I'm see what secret she on
computer I don't know you you want a
beer oo cutie but she's riding to
aliens is she flirting with aliens
delete everything
what panic
panic illegal activity the alien is
the salami
Bandit they love each other
spicy I don't understand yet not
completely secret cake recipes Never
Going To Give You Up they
freaking freak rolled us vacation plan
trip oh to Mars or what bear bus
internal vouchers for CS agents ah see
see see see see there's something about
the vouchers it's important free hour
delay compensation oh oh the the drop
bear maybe gets uh a
[Music]
compensation
maybe who is this person she's
[Music]
messaging can I do you say something new
they really think I've done it oh you do
say something new talk to you have to
help you you you know it wasn't me right
yeah did you not think it was strange
that your bag was full of
salami uh I don't know I thought someone
gave me a salami surprise salami
surprise someone gives you a salami
surprise call the police I'll eat salami
sandwiches for breakfast lunch and
dinner from now
on I would too I eat a lot of salami
I
do
okay what what did this say again it's a
list of all the
most can we solve something
already eight out of nine 10 not
quite one
more maybe I missed something uh
actually let's oh maybe we can look at
the giraffe's PC or even oh she has a
key there probably that we can take and
then enter the stay out room wait no I
can do
it her privacy is protected I can't do
anything here but maybe the door is open
now for some reason it says it's
locked e why can't we inspect her
stuff
[Music]
no
no go ahead call the police they they
can't unalam you
[Music]
are you
sure what happens to the cake now we
should eat it we should eat
it cake has been of all that Heist
people just cry over
everything
crimey cry oh cryy Cry Me a
River isn't crimey a word that they say
cry cryy oh cryy
oh KY CRI wasn't crimey also a
word crimey a river a crimey oh crimey
crimey a
river that's not nice who messes with
someone's
birthday that's not nice yeah yeah yeah
yeah so somebody not nice must have done
it wow what a what a surprise
wait thanks for the foods
ah the salami
Bandit at the lunch yeah yeah yeah this
is the like he must have done it at the
same time when he broke
in what I don't I don't understand the
salami
banded broke into Leaf salami but steal
the lunch the salami Bandit doesn't
steal salami the salami Bandit leaves
salami behind for whatever reason thank
you I guess that seems like very [\h__\h]
nice especially cuz it's such a high
quality
salami yeah same bro
same probably the salami is probably
better quality than the lunch they had
in the first
[Music]
place but oh wait did we get a new thing
yes
ah
oh uh wait so uh it's Sophie's birthday
right Laura gave the book right uh the
others not sure we have to guess
honestly so uh
Sophie tou the BS ah okay
[Music]
I don't want to guess everything like I
I want to guess but I don't want to
Brute Force too much oh do you know
anything about this letter well it's
obviously a cheap prank by
frederson no it is not and I don't think
it is a good kind of mentality in the
workplace to have the boss of the whole
place
be sussing out his own
employees without even good
reasonings that's why I'm here for you
know to sus out people so leave it to me
it's not good for the whole
atmosphere tell him tell
him yeah only he would find this
funny
brud I'm guessing you're ready to
present legal evidence of fredersen's
misconducts it wasn't frederson oh
everything is pointing towards him my
surpressed I will present the true
culprit soon enough well I don't really
care how long it takes
you this will be Fred's last day I don't
have it I trimmed my deck for God's
[Laughter]
sake it's a letter for an applic signed
by
[Music]
couldn't just leave that one standing I
had to come up with a good
comeback well I guess we'll have to
force
it ah
[Music]
maybe maybe Boris escaped I would say
the
plushy but then again Boris would seem
like the person who would give like the
most
romantic did you talk to everyone Boris
oh sure
okay nobody has been really saying what
they gave but oh wait what is
this
Customs procedures for passengers is
entering from the West border oh
[\h__\h] salami is it illegal personal items
worth less than 500 schark
prohibited
weapons
scary tantrum bones meat salami
potatoes books not in the interest of
this so probably alien porn plants
luggage oh oh typo will be checked at
the bus
station for more information visit
britzel
Customs import scary britzel what do
they have against potatoes yeah Germans
love potatoes they should be everywhere
in
Germany don't hold the potatoes
back don't gatekeep them maybe it was
too romantic yeah okay necklace did
Sophie ask about me
uh yeah she might have me did she really
I bet my present will blow her
away they smuggled the salamis in yeah
definitely so it must be someone from
outside the salami
Bandit he's already Far Far Over The
Border by
[Music]
now but wait why no Maybe not maybe not
maybe not no no why would you let why
would you do that it it should be
somebody who lives on this side of the
Border went to the other side got the
salami brought it here because they
don't have salami here
[Music]
apparently
so uh
huh wait what C stolen
[Music]
who
nothing something's something must have
been in a
[Music]
letters we'll try we'll try everything
um
but Freddy gave a plush no a bunch of
things are
wrong H nothing could be right
because it became
fewer yeah interesting nothing got
stolen what I guess my job here is done
I can go home if nothing was
stolen
um mind FR
no Margaret wait who's Margaret again ah
Margaret is the the the the Sheep so ah
wait no no no sheep gave the book
because she's the one from the PC h
I think so and then um maybe Laura gave
the
plushy Margaret seems like the book
Giver yeah yeah yeah for
sure Laura is a cat so she gave the cat
plushy why is okay one thing is still
work maybe it's this one um letters
books
bag cake plushies nothing
necklace
weird
weird it's Sophie we're talking about
right plus she was to expensive
item oh
I guess and she really uh likes it wait
is three or more things are wrong the
necklace was
cheap should I reread the
dialogues things are actually they're
looking
up cuz I told him wait wait wait wait
wait do you know when oh it's really
things in it and others very susp what
are you even is this no everyone here
was
being now he won't say the thing again
about his uh present he did say it like
as if it's really special so I I think
because he also still loves her we all
agree on
that ah let's ask about oh wait I can't
ask him about Sophie but can I ask you
about Sophie
no he's just talking about
cake I totally forgot about Sophie's you
forgot about Sophie's birthday so you
didn't gift
anything but I don't have you on the
list anyway right now but that's a good
deduction he said his gift was romantic
yeah so that's why I think it's the
necklace honestly it's got to be the
necklace is see it became not free or
more it became
free so definitely trust me I'm the
detective
here do you think she liked my present
she's unsure about it I now she's crying
I think I saw a sparkle in her eyes when
she opened
mine I should really get back to work
she's weirdly
[Music]
M she is she
spicy she's rarely concerned about it
like you know what I
mean she's
spicy she into her she gay are you gay
why are you
gay why are you crying
anyway that's not nice who messes with
someone's
Bo okay it's a heart shaped heart sh
looks tacky someone get it says limited
edition
plushy and spicy
[Music]
book ah wait said is
Rufus wait wait wait who is ruus again
uh ah rofus wrote the book would you
think Rufus gifted the book M I actually
don't think
so but maybe that's why he's talking
about the cake because he's like
embarrassed by it let let's try let's
try let's try saying Margaret janak no
no no no not the Margaret H rofus
gave he did gift his own
book wait what
he gifted his book about spicy aliens to
the lady who likes spicy aliens oh what
oh wait he's definitely the one that
she's talking to on in the
chat the alien wait so Rufus stole the
Rufus Rufus is the salami Bandit no
probably I don't know who knows uh and
then uh the plushy is from Laura
no or maybe it is
but wait wait wait
wait wait who's who's Laura the LA Laura
was really concerned about the present
okay I'm changing things up again uh
I'll try even though it makes not the
most sense maybe Laura gave the NE cuz
she's actually
gay and uh Boris no it's not like
that wait what about Margaret did
Margaret not give
anything but maybe the one thing that
Margaret gave or the one thing that
Boris gave was
stolen Leathers leather letters letters
nothing Laura
Boris
ah face closed wait wait wait stolen
after all yeah that's what I was saying
I had that already a while
ago
uh so Boris did give the necklace the
only weird thing that it took me a while
to know is the book came from the book
offer
Rufus
yeah it seemed that the salami present
was
intentional intentional salami
surprise
what
[Music]
gas what does that tell us
let's read the
intentional be quiet or else
[Music]
she knows you
think maybe they'll be quiet or
else is more about be quiet about the
secret not be quiet with your keyboard I
don't know but then
oh wait what did you say do you think
she liked my
present I mean now she's crying I think
I saw
spark I should
[Music]
really yeah yeah yeah yeah let's solve
the other deductions but
wait Laura gave a
plushy she really did huh
mar mar mar is Margaret the salami
Bandit wait
okay blah received the blah blah that
contained the blah blah uh a salami
surprise
no okay wait wait what could this
be message scary message it contained a
scary message
[Music]
that' be kind of the writing style of
the author of the alien book
honestly Sophie received two a few
things are I'm not that far
off uh
silly salami a
nice
uh
ah
no a
nice leather no
and
romantic
leather a a romantic letter that con
ained a
nice what's about a message a
nice damn
it what
what
uh an ah ah ah a
romantic uh a silly book that contained
a oh
romantic
no
what huh why why you how do you know you
know that one is fewer than two yeah
yeah yeah yeah but like it could be two
or fewer things what what are you
talking about I don't know which one's
wrong I don't know which one's wrong
okay we know that wait what was there
before see I'm deducting silly right
silly silly okay silly is correct brute
forcing it a
silly book probably this is correct that
contained a scary me no a nice no uh
well maybe it's not a
message a letter no it was a
message silly scary romantic how is this
not right maybe it's not
[Music]
Sophie no it is Sophie
though a silly
letter why would it be a silly letter
the note wasn't a Salam I know but like
I tried going that way and it didn't
work
and okay how about a nice salami no
wasn't nice it wasn't romantic it was
wasn't scary and it wasn't silly was it
silly it might have been silly it might
have been a silly salami that contained
a scary
message scary
letter what but that's what it
is silly no it was
scary silly letter scary message
silly letter I had that before no I I
didn't Sophie was receiving
threats I needed to find out
why wait
what I guess that is yeah that is silly
Edge Lord sounds very silly
wait uh Sophie talk to
me I guess I just figure out the last
one
too I have all the hints blah are being
blah blah
ah salamis are being
illegally imported from
maybe s because that is a
salami he of a highr
salami I'm a good detective okay we had
a little bit of a hiccup before but
first try on this
one yes um I just needed to find out who
was behind this The Mystery of the
salami Bandit was slowly getting
unraveled unraveled a salami
Western goods are prohibited from
entering and being sold to the east
oh this is why the the salami decided to
make a
business High great salami in the west
smuggling it to the east smuggling it to
the
East and selling it at a high it at a
high profit also for some reason some
reason s received a letter from the
salami Bandit that had a hidden that had
a hidden threatening
message
yeah this was serious I had to question
all of the
employees very
serious beautiful
performance m salami thanks for coming
everyone he's unraveling the salami well
everyone except for
Sophie oh maybe Sophie is importing the
salami but why would you be
crying maybe she just wanted salami for
her
birthday I don't know whatever where is
she let's
wait slacking off playing on her
computer phone like usual computer V
you're so mean bro she's having problems
with her family oh she was at her desk
and said she needed a moment problems
with her family because they're on the
other side of oh
wait she's
like separated from her
[Music]
family I will start then regardless
that's also why like you know her
birthday is sad because she's like she
you know family not here I have made my
deductions and drawn some serious
conclusions and maybe they be quiet or
else is really just like I said more
about keep the secret AKA keep the
secret of the salami being imported this
is for you my dear mwah mwah
mwah make sure you don't get caught kind
of like
that you know what I
mean here's something from where your
family is make sure you don't get caught
because then people will will know that
you're like kind of importing this stuff
which is
illegal finally and now she's worried
getting fired then I'm a detective who
is the murderer there's no
murderer what no one died not yet at
least maybe the salami is poisoned I'm
getting Fred I yeah we're over that
we're over that frd of baloney baloney
is right pepon he is getting framed what
what why would anyone bother ah that is
the question isn't it why would anyone
bother oh because she's scared so did
she also frame him then get to the point
maybe not on purpose my observations
that I
uncovered a conspiracy a load of
salami this is ridiculous ridiculous why
are we still listening to a random duck
that waddled into this office I'm
leaving yeah you waddling more than me
bro I'm a certified private investigator
and too late she's gone it's okay just
tell us what you
know salami is being smuggled from sa
CIA using your very own buses
[Music]
huh I wonder though if uh Boris like
don't you think he actually knows about
it like he's helping her because she he
loves
her huh what's going on huh okay this is
going too far I really have more
important things to
do come on this is imp
does that mean we're losing our job she
is so dramatic oh my God she's like a
soap opera sheep sheep Opera
[Music]
maybe oh everybody's
leaving listen every it's really
important but no one leaves the premises
he said
calmly I need to get back to work no no
wait it's not good for you everybody's
leaving just ignore
them who bothers with like complaining
so much of the [\h__\h] bus company leave
them
alone I'm still here Mr duck
detective
[Music]
yeah well all right let's talk if you're
here then let's
talk but not about that this is getting
intense is Maybe maybe you could need a
little
help you seem
lonely I could be your
assistant what do you want me to do
nothing decipher messages no talk
someone into telling us the truth no I
do my work alone you could be like
trying to mislead me follow people I'm
pretty good at that just stay here yeah
I guess yeah yeah you're doing well yep
you're doing great
ah he wants to be an
investigator oh I feel bad what if he's
a lost
investigator who lost his job after I'm
gone I should hire
[Music]
him is there anything new here probably
not right oh wait the phone someone
forgot their phone oh
[\h__\h] oh oh oh oh you guys got to be more
careful kts and jooy oh oh oh oh oh that
should be uh Sophie
right could also be Laura she seems to
also be interested in it a little bit
but oh almost dead okay that is uh
Laura are your parents still angry at
you
[Music]
H maybe she was ass dialing like ass
writing butt
writing this doesn't make sense
or maybe yeah maybe it was the butt but
uh H this is curious I don't think
there's a secret code in
that key smashing could be could be but
like three times in a
row it still could be I mean I've done
it before
yeah yeah that was my first thought but
then three times in a
row why would Laura recruit you to deal
with a theft shut the [\h__\h] up aren't
there any other detectives who are
actually qualified for the job shut up
I've been doing very well so far if I do
say so myself the truth will be revealed
in the
end dramatically very dramatically
you running around really stressed
what's wrong with you oh who would hire
me at this age oh don't worry man oh
maybe I can be a a real estate agent
that's not what's happening you're not
getting fired I always wanted to be a
rich real estate agent all all the all
the 40-year-old housewives are becoming
real estate
agents all of
them oh Freddy's gone oh yeah cuz he's
still there oh I can look at his
computer h
is he like stalking
me he's on my Twitter Eugene mcquin duck
detective it's it's blue sky throw B
bread to the Fine beak of Lady
Justice bread thought you were over that
oh yeah
stalking looking for a job we'll do
almost anything buy my book oh he saw
that crime and thrillers murder at the
Beavers Dam
when the damn broke Beaver B lost his
mind a kidnapping and a Kingpin never
kidnap a king penguin Kingpin on his
birthday
penguin
kidnapping does this mean something
obsessed with detectives it was Twitter
before oh really
yeah
damn we're in brael right and this is
Sal Sala is supposedly like across the
border so is all of this across the
border I
[Music]
wonder what else is new maybe outside
again
oh oh [\h__\h] what's going on here she left
just like this
oh another plushy maybe she's at home
should I look for her
a she must have been really upset even
the even the chair is knocked over oh
now we can take out their computer yeah
let's
go I know those are city names yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I mean they're food names too but
un no number anymore I'll tell them I'll
tell them everything don't you blocked
this number click
your what she is she writing to her
family threatening her family to tell
them about the salami or
something or maybe not about the salami
but maybe she's hiding the fact that she
has family across the border
AA for expecting my cowork what's AA for
expecting my co-workers to remember my
birthday it's my 20th birthday today and
no one congratulated me that's not true
I don't need much but at least a
handwritten card would have been nice Oh
you mean no one in terms of maybe your
family ah ah ah am I [\h__\h] for
expecting like wait did she write that
in one of those forums I think I've seen
it like on Reddit before isn't there
like an M ID [\h__\h] Reddit board yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I've seen that
before even though I don't use
Reddit I've seen that like reposted on
Twitter or or something like
that she's on there she's a
reditor I'm sorry my eye I got some
stuff in it
okay it's almost three hours we we
should be solving the the crime now come
on there's another hint
here where is
it there we go don't fight
okay I can't believe she complained
about this
online
uh wait that note
read it right Ah that's it I
Quit mhm you'll never see me again
Sophie wind
timer
yeah could we compare handwriting
perhaps what a dramatic I should keep
this as evidence
I don't know if it would lead us
anywhere but we have a resignation
letter let's
go let's talk to you meow Sophie left
yeah and she left a note on the desk
yeah what do you say about it this is
the note Sophie left can you tell me
more about it it doesn't make sense at
all that she just suddenly leave she
definitely needs the money and she would
have told me
I'm her friend wait she got
kidnapped if you
think wait wait wait wait wait I don't
want to compare the
notes I can't look at them
here
wait um let's see the a is like
that
see remember this remember this remember
this do you think somebody faked it and
kidnapped her could have that maybe the
salami
Bandit yeah no underland but Still Still
Still Still Still Still wait wait wait
wait am I on to something maybe not but
I I have to check the
note
[Music]
kitten it's a blue pen same
color it looks kind of different but
also it looks exactly like my hand and
well not exactly
similar uh it could be the same person
could
be but saw like
a I might be on yeah look at ah yeah
maybe something new at boss
room I don't think I was done in the
other room though there was still
something on the
floor did you know ducks are excellent
skin that stuff down there is like Duck
propaganda okay
finally Manfred is out of his office
time to see what's behind his precious
family portrait you shouldn't leave his
office alone of
course
[Music]
H is it the number uh the page number uh
from the
book what is this part
mean ah ah
does this mean this one stays zero
customer service b
b 252 252 should we try that is that
that's the book number right I was
wondering
nope okay we have to think about that
one
csbd is probably in connection with that
it's a letter for an application signed
by l x
M yeah yeah birthday I think so too but
uh well today today seven s seven
birthday today I mean I don't know why
he would choose someone else's
birthday's number as that but like it's
the only one that I know oh bus driver
oh because if it's birthday then you
know it could be the seventh
right oh oh see
what Bey bus
driver wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait let's let's look at this
thing here and maybe we can go in there
too let's see the last dialed number on
this phone is
177 it says
server room it's locked come on open it
[Music]
up did you read so I
did something's something's
different yeah okay kidnapping for sure
[Music]
but there's always more to it it's a
list of all the most busy
[Music]
four Mr
Brandenburg good
[Music]
salami is there anything here by the way
no ooh I'm still missing lots of hints
for these
ones wait
but Sophie got
kidnapped
because no maybe
[Music]
not good good option
the two desks on this
side I'm rechecking all of my things get
the o oh please clean their
desk sexy
aliens this folder says how and when to
I'm falling asleep just maybe the the
something with the voucher wait where
where's the vouch here the voucher
information here here here here voucher
maybe maybe
about what part would I choose because
these are so
long best secret recipes
21 274 sounds like which what what
274 what was
274 this folder says how and when I'm
falling asleep just reading the title
locked
in two death for yeah yeah I know like
those L I was also thinking like maybe
ah two there's two people working at
customer
service yeah but I don't want you I I
want to I want to understand the logic
of it before I use it and I want to get
to it myself I don't want to think too
much about it uh through your reading
what you just said the O is operating so
is it one because there's only one
operating whatever what whatever Freddy
is what's 3D seven seven the birthday is
seven but you said four for what why why
is this
four
o
o bus drive ver is for
[Music]
oh ah okay oh did I actually did I
misread no ah okay I still kind of I
still kind of went there on my own I
read the comment that said two desks
four bus driers seven on the calendar it
was not quite that okay I I did a little
bit of it on my own I believed in in the
fact that the O has to be one okay okay
at least I did
that I always wanted to open a
ridiculously safe let's see what Secrets
he has in here is it the key to the
server
room yeah
Keys take take take it dear ingret I
know I haven't been there for you and
the kids recently but things are looking
up I would love to take you to a
romantic getaway to hollay love
Manfred are we talking about the
Netherlands or so
perhaps listen up I tell me about
demands um Employee of the Month TV in
my room keep quiet oh yeah it's
definitely the I I I guessed it but here
keep quiet about the thing do all these
things and nothing will happen to
[Music]
you yeah Manfred is getting blackmailed
wait Rufus Rufus is no wait who's
employee yeah right Rufus was Employee
of the Month
right I'm I'm
[Music]
deducting would it make sense for
Rufus to write
this maybe yeah maybe not maybe maybe
yeah maybe yeah because Rufus is a
janitor right and so the janitor most
likely has his own
room and so makes sense that he would
want a TV in his own
room I don't know what he's trying to
you know why why he would be involved
with importing the salami though maybe
Rufus is in love as well maybe Rufus is
the new
guy
secretly of Sophie we'll see aw a lot of
security for a branch manager of a bus
yeah handwriting probably the same wait
as Sophie's notes yeah the key for okay
we got the
key he just took a single key I don't
know how he knew that he just needs that
one single
key
ruthless why would Laura recruit you to
AR there any other detectives I've he's
so mad about it he's so mad about it
because now
his secret is going to be unraveled just
like the
salami you will not be able to hide your
salami no longer let's
see uh what are you doing solving a
crime let me
[Music]
in for a pengin he has no chill oh [\h__\h]
the electrical Sparks and blinking
lights created a cluster phobic
atmosphere I definitely felt that I
wasn't supposed to be here I'm going to
get Mur in
here what's he keeping in all these
boxes
salami open it open
it I don't think it's meant to do
this you should open the boxes oh it's a
me
oh I didn't Envision him like that he
looks cuter without the realistic eyes
well oh breadcrumbs
shame e why do you have fingernails are
you really a duck maybe you're human and
you're good to eat bread don't worry
about
it oh this must have been bitten off off
of him when he fought with another
addicted duck for some bread can you I
can imagine it I can imagine a scene has
that been there the whole day look at
the bogus binted books up there
September 7 is very important to him
obviously he's in love with her or it's
just the well it's just the day it's
just the current day okay but
still he's got the
TV oh honestly this is nicer than my
apartment it's pretty
chill must be nice to holy [\h__\h] the
janitor's room now okay it's officially
a server room but even this part being
his office is huge that's a huge office
easy bear bus 100 Mark voucher new unus
oh interesting they're
selling the bus
vouchers probably to the other side of
the board order I don't know how to
delete eBay selling history Dad this is
not
Google
dad penguin has a
child computer illiterate rude camera oh
oh he's checking the security camera why
did nobody Ah that's the other games
that the the the the the Publishers
developers put out I saw this crocken
Academy game the other one I didn't
know what's up with these bear buus
vouchers on eay I'm sure like the whole
ending will be a wholesome one but
they're they're really good at making it
seem like some yabi [\h__\h] is going down
but it's it's obviously going to be
something wholesome just people trying
to help each other like what are you
doing in there uh contact their family
over the border and stuff like that
right snooping around do snooping around
are we the most British one is the most
syy one who would have
fought limits well not anymore why put
up posters doesn't [\h__\h] matter this
is for important detective
work what
now Sophie's parents are a I wonder if
that's what made her run away Sophie's
parents are awful you see
does this mean I'll never see her again
a he's got such a broken
heart a Ducks sh 95% of their genetic
makeup with bananas is that what that
just
said ducks or
bananas the two desks on this
side those
numbers maybe I should write a book too
it can't be that hard apparently not I
mean you can write a shitty book that's
certainly easy what do you think of this
note it's no surprise she's left would
you want to work with someone you've
dated in the
past Boris right Boris we're talking
about Boris not wait okay we got this we
got both of them okay Sophie got
kidnapped
because someone wanted to snitch no
because Sophie
because Sophie yeah yeah yeah
okay Sophie got kidnapped there must be
more to
this I'm so smart oh my God there is
more to this wo 28 choices guys blah
blah blah to make him her stay quiet
about
blah blah blah blah blah is the one that
provides the blah to blah
salami
to
Sophie all right this this this going to
take a
while uh blah blah blah uh here we have
names of people here we have verbs and
more names okay
uh threatened blackmailed ah
Manfred uh uh uh Rufus Rufus blackmailed
Manfred right yeah to make him her stay
quiet
about either Sophie or the salami Bandit
or ah
ah ah the whoever is importing them
illegally
stay quiet about
selling
vouchers
uh uh
Rufus to make him or St quiet about ruus
illegal Rufus Blackman manord to make
him her stay quiet about ruus illegally
selling vouchers yeah
yeah and now this one I'll have to try
around because I'm not sure if it's
ruthless
a free F must be
wrong all right what else could this
be bses folks
vouchers the the voucher uh Margaret
Margaret is the one who provides
vouchers
to
Manfred actually no I guess still R yeah
yeah yeah [\h__\h] I got that one quickly
come on
V
yo that wasn't so painful at
all it might be illegal
but this wasn't what I was here for who
what's what what do you think is
Margaret's reason to do that though is
it because she's she she's into she
wants like more alien porn
is she doing it so that he provides her
with more alien spice I don't
know she likes the FR yeah seems like it
she wants the alien
SM I needed to catch the salami Bandit
it's a give and take I quickly needed to
find out where sovie was being kept oh
[\h__\h] I also couldn't let the salami
Bandit get away with this it was finally
time to find find out who was behind
everything I'm missing one thing here is
it a necessary one though f is the
salami B Because f is his
her and his
are ident ah
handwriting uh Rufus is the salami
abandon
because sopie
Sophie and his
her ah ah sorry sorry sorry what why is
that
not
what what is it different are we talking
about something different
are you sure it's no not really like he
he's doing some crazy [\h__\h]
but salami salami Bandit what what even
is the salami Bandit nobody's stealing
salamis right and nobody stole anything
in the first place except the
lunch but we already said nothing was
stolen so I like I'm losing the logic
here like the the
point the
Fred do you think I need the last hint
for this
one Manfred is not here now too what
what you what are you saying with
that it's funny dakum that you're
chiming in when it's when it's all about
bears HH you're only chiming in about
the bears but yeah
Manfred is the salami Bandit
because
yeah well there you go manred is the
salami
identical I just needed to get to
Manfred
D your
father needs to go to
[Music]
jail that makes a lot of
sense ironic that his handwritten note
meant to frame
frederson wait wait one second madred m
is aami B why is he just let
me I'm still not really understanding it
not all of it parts of it what I don't
understand manfred's uh motive ended up
incriminating Manfred
instead how the table
turns what do you think about that oh oh
maybe I can be a always she doesn't
care who should I bring this information
to yeah he's smug yeah it makes sense
that the boss the boss of the boss
company is involved in the whole
smuggling
stuff
but are we saying
Manfred he is indeed not here we're
saying Manfred kidnapped Sophie because
Sophie was going to snitch because she
wrote the thing about the
snitching Sophie was going to but why
was Sophie going to
snitch
also so Manfred put the salamis
[Music]
there I can do another deduction oh [\h__\h]
Sophie is at
manfred's home
[Music]
no wait a
second in a
bus
home bear bus
home bear bus office really she's in the
bus she's in the
bus oh
oh
well is that so I knew that she is being
kept oh I knew that
yeah I I I I I I I I think um I'm not
doing anything wrong here this game
really isn't uh like expecting you to
find out everything properly it is
expecting you to deduct things it's
important that I stayed calm now I
couldn't we haven't been in the busard
for a while all of this will have been
for nothing would I have been able to go
there and find her before deducting this
I needed to First figure out who is
behind everything so I could confront
them
oh something was missing here who else
was involved with this
[Music]
Boris or
Freddy I had collected everything I need
kidnapping but no oh oh oh oh oh more
deducting they never checked I wonder
what was
there
accomplice because of salami going
needed someone who could easily carry
out the of
[Music]
the like this could go a lot of
ways uh okay let's try Boris is the
salami B accomplished because the salami
V needed someone who could easily carry
out the import reporting of the salamis
yeah I'm so smart salami Pandit wasn't
working alone there could have been
other options I I like I don't know if
he already
like I I guess he did already think okay
uh Rufus is the accomplice obviously or
not really he's whatever it makes sense
for the bus driver to be involved it
does make
sense Boris I'm so disappointed in you
she left but I will not confront you yet
about it but the sad thing is that yeah
Boris is in on it but he loves Sophie
and now his accomplice
Manfred kidnapped Sophie because she was
going to snitch on it too
bad Okay blah is a salami Bandit blah
because he should use a date blah
[Music]
H
enemy and the salami but I need someone
to who could
convince
into
H wait a
[Music]
second convince Sophie into
snitching nah
[Music]
murdering
wait helping dating
stalking nothing's changing so there
must be a lot of things wrong here
accomplice but why why would it be all
about this again like accomplice that's
why I feel
like ah yeah yeah yeah Sophie is the
enemy
now obviously CU she got kidnapped
because he she used to date Boris
and the salami Bandit needed someone who
could
convince Margaret into
selling
no what this makes no sense the sentence
is confusing
me take need to figure out Sophie's part
in the
conspiracy
yeah someone who could convince
Laura rof
into
snitching Hello
Steven
ah ah because Boris would perhaps
without
Sophie Boris would perhaps don't want to
help
[Music]
anymore
oh we're getting closer but
[Music]
ah maybe at this point we're talking
about accomplice yeah yeah yeah
yeah you know I couldn't believe Sophie
managed to Talked Boris into this orig
they're saying originally Sophie is was
the
accomplice is a bit confusing because
it's present tense but she's not really
the accomplice anymore right but yeah
yeah
yeah we did it I had it all figured out
now yeah it was time that I conf front
the culprits yeah but first I had to
free Sophie free Sophie # free Sophie
Justice for Sophie oh what the [\h__\h]
that's messed
up he's over there he's over there
happened why didn't he stop
us what's going on out
here why is everyone one yelling H I
feel like the wholesome solution or like
reasoning to this would be that he feels
bad for her cuz she wants to meet her
family or so so
he's like putting her in the bus to send
her there and he's just making it look
like a kidnapping so that if she gets
caught she could be like oh I wasn't
willingly trying to go over the Border
but I'm just like spitting all kinds of
conspiracy theory spider webs right now
I'm just looking for a wholesome uh
ending maybe it's not
a it's good defense
right but how do she get a fback good
question um but now it doesn't seem so
wholesome anymore I don't know man this
looks dramatic yeah I
know it's kind of a long story oh see
she doesn't seem
very upset about
it and guess who deduced said long story
deduct the one and only duck detective I
don't think so there's something missing
read the
room this is how everything went
down they're going to be like no the
britzel bearus branch was suffering
losses and had their budget cut as a
result oh Manfred worried about the
financial stability of his family felt
himself backed into a quarter
this is when he became the Salam look
like pills he made his grand plan of
salami smuggling and realized he
couldn't do this
alone he recruited Boris since it would
be easiest for the bus driver to load
and unload the Wares discreetly poor
Boris the bus would go through a customs
check at the South CIA bus station first
oh and then Boris would take a detour to
get the salami and load it onto the bus
this is why the buses always had a huge
delay ah it wouldn't be easy to talk
Boris into crime so Manfred convinced
Sophie to join the
team boris's obsession with her would
make it easy for her to manipulate him
into helping with their plan everything
was going well until the duck
detective that's me wa so sopie e
office Freddy was meant to be the
scapegoat for the crime but I'm not
fooled that
easily Sophie began getting cold feet
and ultimately wanted to confess to the
police is she okay with it in the first
place FR couldn't have this so he
interfered oh [\h__\h] in the burst of panic
he abducted her and hit her in the
luggage compartment of one of the
buses if that's your Panic move you need
this is
why Manfred stole Laura's lunch wait a
second we're back to the lunch who cares
about the [\h__\h]
lunch why what what yes everything is
figured out but who is truly guilty
Manfred Sophie and Boris are all
involved in the smug who is truly guilty
such a philosophical
question who is truly innocent after
all perhaps we all
guilty yes yes who should get arrested
for their
crimes Manfred was The Mastermind behind
everything should Manfred get
arrested oh uh
should are you asking from a legal
perspective or are you asking from an
ethical
perspective because he is trying to
provide for his family and this is this
is actually this is such a a Breaking
Bad moment U I'm thinking of um the guy
uh the guy the guy that uh uh Skyler
cheated
with he was just trying to you know save
his company so that people wouldn't lose
their jobs but not really it was it was
also more selfish than Dad yeah Ted Ted
n and in the end
yeah not not the you know you
know yeah he is the reason this all
started in the first
place I'm trying to see the good in
people you know
but doing bad for
good not good
of course he should be arrested what
about Sophie without her the smuggling
wouldn't have been
possible I kind of need to know more
honestly wait no she she in Fury didn't
do anything illegal though she
manipulated poor Boris into taking the
Sal the
Border should Sophie get arrested
Manfred clearly was the one who am I
making my own ending here Sophie was
naive to follow along but I don't
believe she is truly liable know I would
like to know more
honestly I'm still not quite done here
mentally but
okay I don't really believe she's that
naive but Boris was at the end of the
chain had he refused to take the salami
on board the plan would have not worked
out maybe he would have lost his job
should Boris get arrested
uh from a legal point of view
yeah but I like Boris
so also he could just have a good
defense in court
like he was being forced either or he
didn't even really know what he was
doing he was just following orders I
don't know if that's a good
defense but the you know he's yeah your
honor he's nice okay he's also just uh
he's got a big
heart
um
but yeah maybe he didn't know but I
think uh drug mules so to say they also
get uh arrest like they
also get charged even if they don't know
what they're doing right like IRL
they got a slap on the wrist really like
I think usually like they don't get a
away Scot free just because they don't
know what they're
doing and in this case Boris even he did
know what he was doing which is worse so
yeah he might have not realized what was
going on entirely yeah he knew what the
salamis were doing he knew it that
doesn't mean he's not liable for
engaging in the smuggling yeah all right
I've made up my
mind Sophie well Sophie Sophie didn't
really do anything except kind of like
pushing Boris to do it I don't know is
that illegal I will report to the state
police well she's she's in on it of
course but Manfred but if anything she
was the one who was going to you know go
and end it all at the same time
so Boris
and I do it
again anything to secure my family's
well-being you sounding A Lot Like
Walter White right
now I'm not sure Grand scale salami
smuggling was necessary for that how
else was I going to cope with all the
budget cuts like a mix of Walter and Ted
if anyone actually worked in this office
we wouldn't have such terrible
performance in the first place
poor poor Laura man she's working so
hard yes I work yes and then you keep
asking for promotions I can tell that
this game is made by German people
because I am somewhat of a German myself
well somewhat really just somewhat it
seems like I keep on pointing out things
before they happen before they get said
it's like we share the same brain
cell I know how they think how am I
going to give anyone a
promotion if we have people baking cakes
during working
hours yeah you should have baked that
cake outside the working hours I agree
with
that cuz Laura is losing a [\h__\h] mind
stressing this [\h__\h] out because you're
[\h__\h] baking a cake and not helping
are you insane
Rufus oh how dare you embezzle money
from the company now he's pointing
fingers at everybody I mean pointing
fingers at rof is correct those two you
should not right now that's a different
whole story okay and then threaten
[Music]
me
well that's rofus said we're only doing
that until his book takes
off oh
and then I play the lead alien in the
movie adaptation
oh
Nar huh look's going to jail now
Manfred you're probably too not me
that's for sure why do you think not you
you could still go to jail for bezel I
stand by what I said I regret nothing
it's so Walter White the
police
I me after I watched something oh this
is so Arcane this is just like Arcane
this is just like Breaking Bad this is
just like so and
so I didn't do
anything uh you know very well you
assisted in organized smuggling
he it's a
misunderstanding he wasn't trying to
assist an organized smuggling he was
just trying to organize snuggling with
Sophie this whole time that's what he
was trying to do but
somehow the communication got lost
somewhere I
didn't I thought I was helping Sophie
right see he just want to snuggle with
Sophie not smuggle she said her cousin
was Ill maybe literally oh my God she
knew he's in love with her she he calls
him she she calls him he like hey you
want to organize smuggling but on the
phone audio kind of bad so he he thinks
she's trying to organize struggling with
him he's like hell yeah he starts doing
it he starts moving the salami around
and
wondering what what am I doing like when
is the snuggling happening wait a second
the only thing that would make her happy
was the Salia salamis Ah that's
salamis evil I take it back she should
go to
jail but look at him he's such a nice
guy see that's why I wanted to know more
about her for because I'm not quite sure
about her character yet now I am I don't
believe he could ever do something wrong
he has though ignorance is no excuse in
the eyes of the law you heard it here
first or second or third or fourth wow
you really did quack the case Mr duck
detective you're just as cool as I
imagined
you you're starting to creep me out
though oh oh I quacked the
case
[Music]
achievement is an ugly
mistress why am I deciding who
gets wait wait wait wait wait my duty to
throw bread to the Fine beak that might
not be the end of it I can't make all
these decisions they should still
investigate the Sophie
oh oh okay almost 100% uh of players
decide to arrest
Manfred 65% of players decide to arrest
Sophie Boris gets arrested by 70% of
players well well well the ACC complies
are often being ignored
here but legally they're all guilty I
guess I but I'm still like really unsure
about the legality of what Sophie did
I'm still she's evil
though D I thought she was a
sweetheart deceived
me
yippee we did
it
cute n there so many German names and
non German names also though Sean
chiplock the Sha rcks Lizzy Freeman Ana
Mar Nola CL we never talk to the koala
anymore feel
bad
oh oh future friends future
friends
okay Oreo the cat stuff are these like
patreons or something like
that backers
in German we say oh crap oh I completely
forgot to collect my payment from Laura
oh are we going back in already went
home oh we can see like the after ending
am I going to pay for the bus well maybe
not cuz they're went they went home
guess walking home no the irony of not
being able to pay for the bus after
solving a crime for a bus company from a
bus
company oh that's cute why are you
taking me home need a ride wait a second
is are you gay I just booked this one
it's been such a long day after
all just just want to know no thank you
come on it'll be
fun just want to know I just just need
to know plus you must be tired after all
the detective work you taking me on a
date or something I really don't
secretly
please n he's good he's nice
nice take the offer if we fit into this
tiny
car that's so tiny great now I finally
have time to tell you all about my ideas
for your social media oh you want to be
his [\h__\h] social media manager please
don't look he looks so happy a good for
him ah I could get you tons of
publicity and imagine we can Team Up
absolutely
not and I can be your sidekick no you
please let him be your
sidekick oh oh maybe the next game will
have him as a
sidekick cuz there's a new one coming
next year right you guys said so the
end oh you should see Trail for a second
oh I already I already can
imagine hey the ghost of glamping is
that the
oh wait is that the upcoming one I
thought that was ah I misunderstood I
thought that was the first game but
there is no first game is this the first
game the salami game is the first
one ah I misunderstand
though then I'm excited for the next
one cute game very
cute I liked it I like these kind of
games it was fun
yeah very cute can't wait for the next
one are we going to go glamping
glamorous camping it looks kind of
spooky though that doesn't look so
glamorous g l a m o r o u s y g l a m o
r o u s we're fiding first class I you
Sophie honestly I need to check the my
my my law
books
I I don't know like I I'm not
like saying she's a good girl no no
no she was
anom in the end all I'm saying is I'm
just a detective I shouldn't be making
this final decision
anyway why am I arresting that as a
detective like then this detective is a
private detective I'm not a police
detective I don't even have the right to
uh even like you know take anybody in
custody
yeah
so little bit of a logic flaw over there
but it's
okay yeah ducks duck Ducks we live in
our own law system and
[Music]
logic yeah the police arrested them but
like why are they listening to me I'm
just an independent private
investigator they should do their own
investigating and then arrest Sophie as
well now after the statement after her
giggling I if I would have made my
decision after that I I may have
reconsidered her G feeling was
bad supress she like wasn't more mad at
like her reaction was weird you know if
she would have reacted more
like I don't know angry at Manfred for
like doing that to
her I don't know cuz like she was an
accomplice and she seemed to not be very
like the giggling why was she trying to
snitch anyway well
[Music]
why this her wanting to snitch makes her
seem like a good person anyway I'm I'm
I'm reading too much into this little
silly Duck
game no need to think too hard about
their
um I don't
know
psychology Phil yeah
psychology to wash Yourself
clean h
oh but it's not because she was scared
of
[Music]
it oh well
whatever yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah she should have just
like instead of
snitching or maybe she was going to
snitch yeah I guess she was going to
snitch to the police I she I guess she
wasn't going to snitch to me though huh
feeling lowkey insulted it seems like if
anything she was going to snitch to the
police which is yeah probably the right
thing to do girl cuz I don't have a
right to arrest
anybody but we remember their
[Music]
birthday yeah cuz I was going to say
that would be the smart thing to do if
anything go snitch to the police and
take a deal
but in order to even be offered a deal I
feel
like like she wasn't in the position yet
to be offered a deal this would have to
be like a maybe a little bit of a bigger
case don't you think
and um I feel like you can't go there on
your own and be like I'm going to tell
you all of this stuff but I want a deal
like you know that's usually the police
is the one saying like they start
investigating I learned it from Breaking
Bad
anyway
anyway rofus started to Blackmail manf
Fred by snitching Sophia Sophie caught
wind of it and wanted to escape the
situation by snitching ahead of
ah wait
ruthless oh yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah he
blackmailed him for his own selfish
reasons maybe not even really intending
to snitch who knows but with that fear
of being like hearing about that the
fear of being caught by rufus's
snitching Sophie thought I'll snitch
first so I don't get in trouble that
makes sense thank you thank you f you
for unraveling the salami even
further yeah I forgot about the whole
rofus puzzle piece
ah yeah okay then then even even more so
now I would have arrested Sophie
[Music]
too well well okay I'm sorry even though
this was a short short stream it's
longer than I thought it was going to be
and I'm hungry and I'm tired and I have
work to do so
W's going to go uh tomorrow is uh
rebroadcast uh over the weekend it will
be AWA we broadcast of K and AWA wa Wawa
and
AWA whole life stage World Tour
sore I'm excited to see you guys in
Atlanta
I think we're going to have a good time
yeah oh hi Eden Eden I'm sorry Eden you
have another week
sorry if you want to like you know you
you said you were going to uh add
something anywhere you wanted to be
there wouldn't we all have liked to be
there yeah well I am
there too bad for the others though kfp
thanks for the stream thank you thank
you thank thank you for watching I'm
going to watch rebroadcast I want to see
it once more really I'm embarrassed I
shouldn't have uh messed around so much
with songs I don't know I don't know the
thing but I was trying to figure it out
like if I know or
not well
well it's okay guys it's okay there'll
be chances to see me again in America
I'm
sure yeah that's the fun part you think
so we're so good one thank you
you did great with those songs thank you
part of the fun thank you I'll be there
in spirit oh an
hour Spirit
huh thank you that's sweet of
you can't always be everywhere you know
cuz you guys aren't
virtual you maybe you guys should become
vtubers
okay I'll go I'll go now thank you for
watching see you
see past Wawa will see you tomorrow at
the
rebroadcast thank you and Jo me say us
in
goodbye bye-bye byebye
[Music]
byebye I'm so
hungry anybody got some salami
[Music]
what
sh
nice to buy
salami actually I have salami at home
salami at home
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]