[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [Applause
]
[Music]
[Applause]
How are you all doing? This day has arrived again this year.  Are
you sitting down?  I do
n't think I'm going to sit a little quietly, so it
was a gamers this time, but this time, it's a bit of a sick porridge
because I'm sick.
[Music]
[Applause]
Before we get into the planning, let's
take a look at the timetable for the Negoru Hororangaku.Click here for
the upcoming Quiz Year-end Party.  It
's a special, but at around 7:30 pm, there
's a winter scene for the Revealing Battle 2020.
That's right. It seems like it
's a project that uses the members' secrets.
But
whose secret will be revealed
? It's new, and
from 83 onwards, it's Toretaka Grand Prize 2022.  This
is an annual event, but everyone watching this year's broadcast
has voted, so
please look forward to it. Yes, and then from 9:30 p.m.
Hinadan Talk Variety Hooro no
Yomoyama Ah, is there a plan to liven up the show with various stories? I do
n't know. It seems like only Oyayomoya appears.
What does that mean? It seems like they don't care about anything else.
23 more  From now on, we
will also be holding an on-live production countdown live,
but the distribution slot for this one will be in a separate slot.
Please make sure to move around. Thank you very much.This
New Year's Eve, we will be
bringing you a lot of variety shows and live shows. Let's have the
best New Year's holiday together!
So, this is our first project.
This year's representative is the famous Belly Quiz,
Deck
[Music]
[Applause]
Teacher,
we are sorry.
What's special about us? Yes, yes
, this is what we saw earlier.  You
hinted at it in the timetable, the flow, and the opening video.This time we have a special
guest.Let
's go, shall we?
Let's have him appear right away.Thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] -
[Applause]  ] It's my
first time,
um, I'm
nervous, but I
'd like to practice Takanashi's character from Phoenix.
[Music]
Please.
[Applause]
Here's to everyone. My butt
has been fixed. [
Applause] It's
gotten a little louder.
[Applause]  - Is it
nothing? The
two of us are a bit uneasy today. They
're broken.
[Laughter]
So
let's move on.
[Applause]
Well then, here are the rules for the quiz.
But it's going to be a team competition. This time, we'll
pass on
Cheese &
Team.
[Applause]
[Music] The
team with the most points at the end of the game will be the winner, so I
hope everyone does their best.
[Music]
Let's hear about the team's enthusiasm. Hey.
How do you feel about your enthusiasm? Well, it's our
first time to do something like this today.
But it looks like this, red and orange. Yes,
this coloring is amazing.
So, I think it's probably as good as the smartphone chicken. It's
probably
hot.
Yes, thank you very much.  Next,
what are we going to do against the dark flames?
[Applause]
How's your enthusiasm? Well, maybe we
can't win with this ship, but we'll do our best. I
think we're a good team.
Well then, let's get right to it.The first
quiz
is the Ishin Full Body Quiz.  It
means that we are connected by our hearts.OkOk.I
will ask you to try.There will
be a dummy answer so that you will not be fooled by the dummy answer.10 seconds The
first Meiji Restoration Denshin quiz is  It's a
kanji. You
can read it.
Please guess what kind of kanji your partner would choose to represent the year 2022.
[Applause] I'm
going to try to predict your partner's answer.
Can I ask you a question?
[Music] No
more. It's
funny
. It could be
something like that.
Yeah, okokok.
Guess what it's like?
[Laughs]
This is so cute.
This year's kanji for my partner
is the
new
b is
travel.
C is the key point
D is the
good answer
[Laughter]
[Music]
Corone's ABCD It
's okay, snack. The
fonts are so thick that I can't even tell what title they are in. It's
cute
. That's
right. This year's
kanji are
quite a lot.  2022 has gone by in the blink of an eye because it was a little early for a lot of things.
[Laughs]
So, the Shinjuku ball is over.
[Music]
Now, let's take a look at the answers from both teams.
Well, here's the answer.
Don
Oni.
Both of them.
Turby.
Why did you think it was a trip? Subaru-chan has been doing a lot of things at the same time this year, like
watching movies and playing new games, and
traveling to a lot of different worlds.
[Music]
No, look.  Why did I
think it was love? No, somehow
Tiara-chan
is a
cute movie, isn't it? She's a
phoenix, so she can go anywhere.  I
have an image of traveling, so I've
always been fascinated by this place.
[Laughter]
So let's go. Let's look at the answers. Let's
look at the answers.
Here's the correct answer.
Correct.
[Applause]
[Music]
This year we
went to Molodive,
to Romantic Italy, to Japan,
to America, and probably other places as well,
but I forget, but I
imagine we've been to a lot of places.
Hey, it's my first time this year.  I've
cleared Tsubo Oji, ah,
that's what Tsubo was like in 1971. I've
cleared Tsubo before, and I've never done Tsubo before.
Oh well, next year, please. I'll
give you mental support. You
said you've come into contact with a lot of new things,
right?
However, there are already some people who have nothing. It's
really not like it's going to end in one blow.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes,
[Applause]  The
next question is, guess the
sound of your partner slurping soba.
By the way, do you like soba? I'm
not bad at it, but I
don't have a lot of opportunities to eat soba. What do you eat? The only thing that hasn't been decided is,
on the other hand, if you're not in Japan.  It was such an amazing thing to do, and I
wonder why they don't do it when they're going to set off fireworks at midnight.
[Music]
From now on, one of the team members will be the answerer, and the
other person will stand by.  I'm
going to ask the people who will be sipping to split up.
Blindfolded, I
was looking for my partner from the sounds of soba coming in turn.
Well, first, decide who will be sipping soba from both teams. That's
right, I'm Uchiha, but today is the day after all.  I
would like to hear the sound of soba being sipped. It's
been a while since I've forgotten the taste,
so I definitely want to eat it. They
also sell soba, so I
can eat it.
[Applause]
In addition to the representative,
Shirakami will be sipping as a dummy.Please
make
sure not to do it.Yes, I will do it when I finish eating.Do you want Netomio to wear glasses?Is that
okay?Yes, yes,
yes, then
blindfold.  Set
[Music]
[Applause]
Area expansion There
's a pissy voice,
and there's someone who's the most dangerous.
What's wrong with that? What's going on?  Do
n't worry, it's okay. It's
moving.
What's so special about this program? There's a
robot that looks strong.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hey,
first of all, you're the first one. [
Music]
First of all, the
second one is
[Music]  ]
OK, so the
tree is not allowed to raise its voice.
Okay,
so let's get started. Let's call this the first person, A.
So, for A, first of all, let's take a sip.
This is going to test your ears.
[Music]
Okay, okay, so you two
just listened to it and can you tell who it sounds like?
Well, I
don't know, but you're
being honest. I
heard the sound of making soba noodles.  But then, the person who
can answer in one go which guy is smoking soba is a
person who can
expand his field.Yes, I
thought it was Subaru.What do you think
?
[Music]
Okay, let's move on to B.B,
please.  people
Someone like that is right.
Nails Yes,
so that's
B's Susuri.
What do you think? Mio-sensei, I'll have to look at it and listen for a moment to find out, but I think it's a bit like a character. What on earth was it
called a sparrow?  It's the
same as the one on the right.
Who? It seems
like a Chan-like thing.
Who
? But maybe if you listen to it a third time, it might be a little cute again. It
has a dignified feel to it, but I don't think so.  The
next one is C. Let's go to C1.
Eh,
it's [ __ ].
Wait a minute, it
's okay, it's okay. It's okay. It's
okay.
What are you
doing? What's going on? Go on, do your best, do your best,
do your best. Go for it. What's going on? Is it
going to come out? Is it
in? Cheers,
hit it again.  I was swallowing before.
No, I was doing it a little bit. I'm
sure it was
coming. It was coming.
[Music] This is
ABC's profile.
[Music]
[Applause] Let's
take off the blindfold. Hurry up.
Sho
[Music]
Personality charge Good morning, good morning It
was delicious So
that's the good thing.Which of the
ABCs was it?It
doesn't matter who ate it in what order, you can take this.Difficult
partner.  It's a good game, and
if you can answer the ABC order of the three people, it's OK to tell them more.
Seriously, I'd like to think about it. If you
can answer the order as well, I'll give you another point.123
Any of the ABC's are OK. Yes, I see.
But I heard that you're really a senior with breasts. It's an
app, so I
tried to appeal to you. No matter
how people think about it, it seems like it's a little like that. There was something
strange about the
white team.  I can control Susuri like this.
Okay, so what's going to happen?
Please write down the number and order of your partner. I wonder
how it will go.
[Music]
Okay, so it looks like we have the answers  I
guess I guessed it.
Let's take a look at the
team's answers. Here's the team's answer.
Senosuma-chan
B is Fubuki.
C is Kiyada
[Music] - It's
a bit too much, isn't it? To
eat soba, isn't it?
Chiara, who doesn't have much family, is C.  That's what I
thought.It's not too much to expand the field.Well, it seems that the
order is as follows.Let's
take a look at this.Is it
possible?1Subaru 23 ChiageIt's
exactly the
same.  I was
a little worried about the number one Suba-chan getting an A.
[Music]
Everyone else was worried except for Mr. Frank.
Eh,
that's true after all. I think I got a C 99% of the time,
so I
see.
So Ryo-chan's answer is the same.
So, let's go with the correct answer.Okay,
first of all, I think I put it in person B, person B, etc.The
person who was B
was Suzume, that Oshirogami.
He's giving off the impression that he doesn't like sips,
but
what happens when he surfs
?Let's start with the picture person
[Music]
Okay,
what are you doing? There
's nothing in that mouth.  I can do that.
[Applause] I'm
really good at
slurping, but I can't do anything strange, so it's probably a
cultural thing.
It's because I have bad manners when I make sounds. I've never learned how to make them. Thank you.  There
was no sound, but there was almost no
room
left.
3rd
was the piano.
But I'm happy to eat soba for the first time in a while. Hey,
Japanese food.
[Applause]
Delicious.
[Music]
[Music] It
matched well, so I'll
get 2 points for the team. See you
then.  Can we talk about this for a moment
? What do you think, management
?
Sorry, no. Let's take a look at the main points at this stage.
[Applause]
[Music]
What's going on
? I guess they can understand each other because they've been together for so long.
Actually, that's because they
have too many wig points.
That's a bit painful. I was
looking forward to it, but I'd like to see a comparison between the two of them.
But here it is.  I'm
going to give it a try.
[Music] It
smelled really good from earlier. I
'm really into it. I'm really,
really into it
.
[Music]
Everyone's making out.
Trying to do something abnormal
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] How
cute! It's
time for a break.
Since you're here, there's a quiz corner that I'd like to try.
Yes, this time I'm going to try it. A
standard variety show.
Listen in English.
[Music]  ] I'm
going to ask you to play a message game in English,
so
let's test your English skills. I Can't
Speak Sorry
[Music] I
can do it,
but I
repeat passing the message to the next one, and then I finish it off.
If you heard this,
please tell Chiara-chan the English message you were given.
Eh, I wonder if it's okay. I can't remember it. Please
remember it, thank you.
[Music]
I'm here. We
go around, and
in the end, we succeed.
How are you confident in English? Other than just look.
Why aren't these two people listening to the universe?
Nesora-chan seems to be pretty good at English, but I
can't hear them. Ok Ok, this is the
famous one created by Ok Ok.
There's an English phrase, huh?
What do you
remember?
[Music] He
said it when he said he was about to die in the game. He was an amazing Mim on the English team.
This time, I'd like you to give me a clear message, so I
don't end up in Senkyu Forever.  Let's
move on. Now,
this is a game that has nothing to do with anything specific,
so both teams would like to play it in the future.
Those who go first, starting with Tiara, have
not yet called [music].
Hey, okay, let's take a look, let's do this, let's go, let's do this.The crow
will answer properly from the bowl.Alright,
first of all, I'll broadcast the topic with Chiara.I'll
show it to everyone who is watching, so please all three of you, please
look down a little.Okay, back, back,
okay?
Please look down. I
understand. Can you remember? Are you
okay? So, first of all,
let's send a message to Mio. Let's just
cover our ears for a moment.
[Music]
Good luck.
Good luck! I
went there while I still remember.
Ice cake.
What?
Okay,
I got it. It was amazing, but it was in English. I
really
want you to answer it. Please answer.
What do you think that means in Japanese?
[Laughs]
Mochi.  Let's combine, combine,
combine.
[Music]
[Applause] I'm
sure it's a question for everyone. I'm
sure it
was a prize. Part-time job chocking on
rice
cake.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sure.  Maybe it's
because I don't have any points, but
I'm just trying to get
to the honest, factual world of color. I'm
asking you to
put it on display. Please don't look down on it.
[Applause]
Well, here it is for Mr. Kihara and all of you.  It's
longer than the previous one. It's
definitely a little faster. Remember it.
[Music] Now
that you've memorized it, let's go right away.
Let's go first.
[Applause] Please
give me the answer one more time. Give me a star in front of Zaken-chan.
[Music]
United
Leading
What's the last one? It
's the last one.
Everyone in the meeting.
United
Meeting. I ca
n't remember the last one. Bon
Bourbon
[Applause]
Style
[Music]
United
Meeting Club.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Yes, that's
correct. Is that correct?  What do you think? It's not 100%, but
OK
[Music]
[Applause] There's
really nothing left to do...
[Music]
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
what I said to Cody and what happened to me.  They
said different words, so yeah,
I don't know, but what do you think they mean? What do you
think they mean? What I heard was
darkening everyone. Ted,
we've already
eaten the grieving crab. It's dark.
Please go ahead.
[Music]
But, but, I
feel like that final phrase has something more to say,
which means that it's connected, and in other words, when you eat a crab,
everyone is
definitely not the same.
[Music]  We
all connected through a message game in English. Now it's time for a
team game again.
[Music]
This is it. I'm going to ask the representatives of both teams to
express various questions using gestures.
Those who know the answers will start responding.
Please
[Music] I
will give 1 point to each team, so
please
do your best.
[Music] First, please decide who will gesture from each team.  In
terms of
The two of us in pajamas, please decide
which way to go first. Eh, which one do you want to do first? Mr. Senior, if you
want to do it, go ahead. Eh, we'll
do it first.
This is for construction work, so the three of us can answer this.
[Music]
Okay. The
three people behind me, please don't look at me for a second.
Okay,
everyone, here.
[Music] I see.
Please express yourself just with gestures.
So please deliver it to me.  3 people
Look at my face,
then. Let's go.
[Music]
This is it.
Minecraft. Minecraft. You can go on your way.
[Music]
Yes, yes, please. Please give Mr. Hakuta some trouble.
Please go.  This is the next question.
Please do it without the voice. Of
course I've seen the movement before,
but it's
okay if you understand this movement, so yeah,
maybe something like this. If you
can do it, please
lower it.  The
three in the back did it, please give it to them.
[Music]
Rabbit Rabbit A
rabbit-like club
activity
[Applause]
Please answer
[Music]
[Applause]
Next question. Question here.  -
[Music]
Please look up at the three people behind you.
[Laughter]
That's a lie.
Birds
Photosynthesis You
got the correct answer
[Music]
Because the ping pong doesn't sound,
but Tiara-chan got the correct answer.
[Music]
[Applause]
Phoenix When something
happens, this is what happens when you try to express it.
That's not right.
Sorry.
[Applause] Let's
see. Are you
coming to make a heart? I'm nervous. I
can't believe it.  Hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
Yellow team,
tell them to see you next year. We do
n't get involved too much.  I'm
feeling quite hurt right now.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] I've
always wanted to participate in something like this, so I'm
really happy, and
everyone except Subaru-senpai doesn't like that much.  Not so much. I'm
so happy to be friends. I'm about to
cry. Thank you.
[Music] It
was so much fun to be able to appear again this year. Let's
all have a good year-end and make it a good year for electronics.
[Applause]
-
I'll do my best next year.
[Music]
[Applause]
That's okay. Thank you everyone.
Thank you. Thank you very much. That's it for
this year. There's
more to come. I hope you enjoy it.
[Music] That's it,
everyone.  It's finally here
[Applause] -
[Music]
[Applause
] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
This year is almost over.
Somebody please reply and this year is already over.  It's over.
That's right.  I guess it's
bullying. I want to go home. Get motivated. [Applause] There's something I've left behind this year. [Laughs] I wish I could eat more ramen. [Music] [Laughs] [Music] [Laughs] Yawn What's that from Yawn? What's that?  Yes,
there are things I have left behind, things I have left unfinished. Yes, I
want to go out and have fun a lot.
[Music]
No, but even so, it's a little
boring, is
n't it? Well, it's New Year's Eve, so it's okay.
Well, it looks like we've done it all this year
. All we have to do is wait until it becomes very popular before we start everything. Hey
everyone, it
's the end of the year. It
's being streamed at the wonderful time of New Year's Eve when everyone is watching.
[Music]  ] I'm
taking a moment, so let's
all stop lazing around and
play something. It's
just like this. It's a convenient place. Hey,
let's play a board game or something.
Let's play and record a video.  It's
okay to have fun.
You don't have to follow the script. Let's
stop. Let's
go home.
[Music]
Thank you, thank you
.
Hey, it's finally going to get weird. It's
getting weird. I'm
always forced to play roles like this.
Or...  You guys are
trapped in the world of a game where you compete for treasure. What's that?
You don't seem to be having any fun.
From now on, you'll be
divided into the Nicolette duo and the Shishibata duo and
compete for treasure.
Have a battle for position
Let me explain a little bit about whether you will fight even if you fall down.
You can earn points by collecting the treasures placed on the squares while expanding. Yay,
to get the treasures.  To do this, we
need to make a comprehensive disclosure.
It's naive to try to get treasure for free.
To get gold coins, there's an
embarrassing story about one of the duo.
To get jewels, it's the
secrets of Hololive members.
and the most points
In order to get the treasure chest, I
'll have you guys reveal your secrets.
[Music] You
can't steal the enemy's territory and treasure.
Is this the case for Mr. Hoshimatsu, who has a lot of family in our house?
There
is also a special rule.
Enemy bases and treasures adjacent to personnel
can be stolen by setting up achievements.
[Music] The
winning side in the mini-game will also
get the bases and treasures. Of course.  Hey  The
contents of the mini-game and other rules will be
explained during the game, so let's
get started right away.
[Music]
Let's show you our business skills.
Thank you.
[Music]
Let's go.  Is this an
embroidery technique pose?
That's right, it's a pose.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
2022 Winter Camp
Weekly
So yes, first of all,
let's have you decide on your high school.
Well, if you decide, it might be rock-paper-scissors. If you say rock-paper-scissors, you
won't lose.
[Laughter]
[Music]
What you get will change depending on the defeat
. I see. Maybe it's
better to stop.
This
is a one-shot chance to turn things around.  But if you
can't get to the treasure chest, but if you get a good eye, it
means you have a chance at the treasure chest. I
see.
Let's get started.
[Music]
Where should I take this? Where should I take this picture first?
That's right, which one of the bags in front of you?
First of all, it's a question of
which one to reveal, right? But I'd
like to go with the one with the most points.
[Music] I'm
sorry, but now,
Mr. Hoshimatsu, whose secret is it?  Are you going to reveal it? Well then, I
look at the night sky, but
please tell me the secret of how you look at the night sky.Yes, this is the
story of when I went to Mel Yozora's house and
visited her.  The more I
become a mother, the more my
home is
all
white, including the furniture, game consoles, and everything else.
[Laughs]
People like me work hard to liven things up.
[Applause]
[Laughs]
[Music]  I'm
sorry.
[Music] It
's 2 points for ore and 1 point for gold coins, but if you
go to the gold coin, you'll
probably get the next dice, right
?
[Music]  It's
going to be one of the embarrassing stories.Which
embarrassing story are you going to go to? Which one will you
tell first?
[Music]
[Laughter]
Please,
Botan-chan's
embarrassing story will be the other day,
when we lit a bonfire.  I
tried to toast the marshmallows, but the cat from Serima
ended up burning all the marshmallows. It's
embarrassing. I
can't even toast the marshmallows. You
saw it, right? It's a comment, right? 1 point.  Let
's raise it
[Music] I'm
moving, but
Admission and Combi. It
's fine, it's random. I've
decided on a random one. It's
gold coins. Yes, it's one of the combinations. It's an
embarrassing story, so which one?
Shall we talk about
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
going to tell you something embarrassing. Yes, please.
Yes,
this is it. We
all took an embarrassing bath together. The bath
was a hot spring. It was a hot spring.
Then,
when we were soaking in the hot springs,
Mikochi
started
screaming
and
there was a scene where she washed her hair.
[Laughs] She was
extremely embarrassed.
[Music] It was
quite embarrassing.  So I
would like to give you 1 point for this.Walk
This is now a
great chance to roll the dice.Alright
, no dice.Level, it's
good, it's good.
Basically, it's better for cats to have big buds.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] They've
become jewels
[Laughter]
[Music]
Summer is a time of excitement
Depression
[Music]
It's also a good thing.  It's
just right, because you can enjoy two types.
Now, 2 comments. Where did the team go?
But what should we do?
There's a treasure chest here.
[Music]
Let's go. Hey, are
you okay? You might be a bit dangerous.
No way.
[Music]
Hollow Live members' secret
activities Masumouai Aru
Cat
[Music] I
sold Mel-chan earlier I wonder
if it's an episode, that's good enough
Whose secret is it?
Mio-chan's uhm, there
was a sports day  Well, I
went to the studio this time, right?
That city and Japan, you know, I came here that day. Oh, good
morning. I thought I'd shut up for
bringing so much baggage.  It's
sold at candy stores and
stuff. It's a big, transparent box with a lot of stuff in it. I
brought a lot of things that looked like they were for business use.
[Laughter]
[Music]
To Mio-chan [
Music]
Now, where should we go?  No matter where I go or where I go, it's already that,
right, so I can't go, I can go.
What does it feel like?
But if I take it, I
want it back,
because I still have the next turn.
But
then, here it is.  It's
become the secret bomb of the duo.
So
look at me. I think you probably don't know
what I'm talking about. I've said it before. I do
n't know.
I haven't said it yet. Maybe I've never
been there. Well, I'll tell you.
Yes, please, then Watanabe will sell it.
[Laughs] It
's a girl's secret, but yes, after I take a bath, I
go to bed without using a hair dryer.
[Laughs]
Or no,
but if I dry this or that...  It's going
to be
straight, isn't it? [Music] But you know, when you wake up in the morning, you say, "Good morning."
Maybe
this is
Hey 4
[Music]
[Laughter]
Rotating
[Music]
[Applause]
Well then again, this is really a treasure
chest. We have no choice but to go, let's go. Hey, hey, here we are. The combination's secret skull is now 4 points.  attitude
Well, what's your secret, even though you've never stopped? That's why
there's no such episode. It
's a combination secret box.
I'm
sorry, I have
n't had much fun in my private life.It's a
business, so I thought it was just
the two of us, stopping together to reveal secrets,
or
going out a lot together, or
going out to a house or something like that.
It only happened once,
on the way home from recording, I had dinner
because it was already late and I wasn't doing anything else, so
my sister made dinner, so it's
like our night, and that's what everyone calls Sui-chan.  I've
been a captain before,
but what is this?
Destroying the dreams of people who hold such high hopes and revealing an
important secret. I'd
like to give you four points.
[Applause]
[Music]
Please choose who will be the representative.
[Music] I guess
I'll be able to eat them all the time. I'll do my best.
Having two people compete is a
one-legged confrontation. See
if you can handle it, then prepare a little. All
right.  Do you want to
experience it? Yes, let's
stand on one leg and have a showdown. Start. Please
raise your head just a little bit.
[Music]
[Applause]
Wow,
this pose is a little weird.  We
can go on like this for hours.
Please hold your feet.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] Let's
go
[Music] [Applause]
[Laughter] [
Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause] [Music]
[Applause]
[
Laughter] [Laughter] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter  ]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughs] It
's a treasure chest, so it's a secret box with a combination of 4 points.
Next up is Ajaa-
chan. What's coming? I've never told you this before
.
[Music]
Please,
Button-chan, yes. I
can't get on the plane.
[Applause]
[Music]  I
could have gone there in 2 hours by plane, but why not
take the Shinkansen? How many hours did it
take? In the end, it took 6 and a half hours.
And of course the return trip was
amazing. [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
So, shake it, shake it, shake it,
shake it, which one do you want to get off? Well, it was the cat earlier. I can't leave it up to you. Don't be silly. Are you friends? Yes, it's
poisonous.
[Music]
Yes, it's 1.
[Applause] Cat
or yes, either pair.
Let's talk about the embarrassing story.Which
embarrassing story do you want to tell?Which one of the two embarrassing stories from before?
[Music] I
went to my new house.Yes, I
went to the second floor here at Watermelon's house.
[Laughs] All of
a sudden, I
realized, "Hey," and now
there's a lot of monitors, and it's amazing, isn't it?
[Music]
[Laughs] It
's a stream,
but I have that equipment.
Wow, it's so cool! It's so cool
! I was so proud of myself that I could use this. I do
n't know. I can't. How do I
use it?
When I moved, I bought a lot of new equipment, and I
thought it was this machine, so I bought
a lot of it at that time.
While I bought a lot of things, I
also bought things that I probably wouldn't use, I
bought a pen tablet, I
changed my monitor, I changed my keyboard,
etc. At that time, this
is something that the staff often used in the studio.  So I thought, I
wanted to try using this. Have you tried
using this?
Have you not?
[Applause]
Okay, then this. It was pretty embarrassing. So, can I
give you points?
[Music]
Personally, I'd like to hear the Holomen background story from Watanabe's mouth.
[Music] I
wonder if Fubu-chan would call it a big doujin. When I went to event 2, I got so excited that I got a nosebleed. [Applause] [Laughter] I'd love to see it.  If you say that stupid thing, then
at the same event you'll get a nosebleed. Please look at me with white hair. I'll
fix that bird. I have no
choice but to aim for the next one.
[Laughs]
Well then.
No, I'm just going to
sell it.
Wow. [Music] That's the
point. Now, Mr. Stars, whose
secret is it?
Tokoyami and A-san
's?
Sorry, this was before this distribution started. I
suddenly asked the
staff.
Please prepare a story that reveals the Holo side.
[Applause]
Hoshimachi was waiting for departure, wondering what to do.
[Music] I
made a phone call. I
called Tokoyami's father, and he asked me what the hell was that person?
Even though I
called without any chat or anything, she
answered the phone and said, ``Hello.''
Isn't this basically TMT?
So I said,  Yes, I
have a story to tell. When I
told him directly, the
door
said, ``It's okay, someone is threatening me.'' This
door is just an angel. He
answered the phone right away, and even after I hung up.
That really someone
This angel, who thought she was being threatened, seemed to be worried, but was kind enough to say something.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] I
'll give you honey points for obstructing business.
What should we do? We're going to have a battle.
After all, it's
better to take it ourselves.  That
's right. That's right. It's an
embarrassing story about the duo. Shall we go? Well then,
here's the gold coin. Are there any more embarrassing stories about either of the duo?
Both of them
have already told it, but are there any more? I'm
the one.
[Music]
When I went to Kyushu for filming, the
train I wanted to take was scheduled to leave in just a few minutes, but it turned out that I might
not be able to get on it.Everyone,
including the staff, was in a panic because of the ticket issue.  Things were
getting really bad, so we
all panicked and
explained the situation to the conductor, and as we were
saying, ``Wow,'' the conductor said,
As a courtesy, I was in 5th place and I was like, ``Please
come on board,'' so I went through some
formalities, and decided to
post it as if I were going to do it.Thank you very much.  It
only lasted for about a minute, so
everyone was in a hurry, so when I got to the boarding area and
was about to board, there was another
female flight attendant there,
but her bag was all over the place.  I left
the bag in front of the door,
thinking it was my baggage, and the
woman thought it was my luggage.
[Applause] The
female flight attendant panicked and said it was my luggage.
I forgot that there was no honorific language.No
, it's a bit of a wheel stopper.It's really
not that
bad.Thank you for playing such an exquisite thief.Now
, let's move on.What
should I do in the comments?
[Music]
Okay
[Music] I'm
here. First of all
[Music]
Please choose a representative.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes, I want you to look at each other and
tell each other that you seriously love each other, but it's
better if you get shy first. For now.  Are you going to give it a try? Yes, I'm
old enough to think about what happened later when things couldn't be resolved, but
instead of that, I hear you say I
love you.Which order should
I start with?Since I'm playing a role, I
'll come.
I love you,
I love you.The
way I
work hard, the way I work hard, the way I work hard at singing, the way I
work hard at dancing, the way I always
do my best by broadcasting for a long time, the way I
praise you, I
love you.That's
bad, that's bad.What
can we do to make our love deepen?  It's okay, I
can't help but think of my love for Sui-chan. Cards like this are so advanced. Grandpa
's
interest rates and the fact that he
sometimes sings cute songs makes me happy again.
[Music]  I
love you It's a
smile It's
like a smile
Is it just as safe?
[Music] Are you
smiling? I'm so
happy that
tears are about to fall Now that I'm
thinking of a summary, all I want
is the truth of a beautiful summary It
's that adorable and charming thing about me.
Golden paper only here
[Music] I
want you to accept my love like this
want to accept it as just that
[Music] It's
so dignified and
dignified I
want to call it an anniversary that I don't have, but I  I do
n't know if it's okay to call it anything, but I guess it's okay to just call it a stop. It's over. [Laughter] [Laughter] It wasn't a final decision, but both of us were amazing. But we had a great time. We had a really good time together.  Since I love you, it's
over.
[Applause]
Let's go. Yes, that's the
12th point.
Well, miracles make you
angry.
Our story begins. We
'll announce the team's points.
[Music]
So, 14 points.
[Applause]
Chijishi
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, calm down. Okay,
calm down. How was it? Let's
hear your impressions of the Bakuro Battle. The
team that expected to lose. The
one who was able to swallow the loss.  But you've
heard of this before, right?
[Laughter]
[Music]
Please cancel the squats. Yes,
how was it? There was a
tea party in the middle of the match. I see, these
14 points hit a lot of different shapes.  Since it
's a score,
in order to win, you have to do something embarrassing.I
think I'll continue to do dirty things.I'll do
my best, I'll do my best.
[Laughter]
[Music]
So yes, there
are no embarrassing stories about the captain.I'm
sorry.  The captain is a naked woman, so I'm
sorry. I'm sorry.
Please keep this in mind.
[Music] It's
kind of like that. Yes, the
captain was actually in the waiting room earlier,
and I
already threw it away on the internet. I
can't go any further.
So, I won't
take any foolish positions, it's the winter camp of 2022. Goodbye
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [Music
]
[Applause  ]
[Music]
[Applause]
[
Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
[  Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [Music]
[Music]
Well, it's almost the second half of the game.
From here on out.  I'm
going to do this annual project
Hololive
Shoot High Gymnastics
[Applause]
[Music]
So this year,
I, the brain behind Forox,
White Coat Retail, will be the MC.
And today, we have the largest number of participants in the history of the Toretaka Grand Prize.
Please introduce yourselves from left to right. Mel
Senpai. Hello, I
'm Yosoda Mel, a member of the 1st generation of Vampire Afro Live, a genius in the sensory demon world. Thank you.  Please.
Now, Alice-senpai, I
'm Iris from [Music], thank you for your time today.
And
Box-senpai: My name is
Hakuspace, and I'm in charge of Chaos. Please,
please. And.
Ollie-senpai, you're shaking.
[Music] That's it. Thank you very much. And luxury, ah, the coolest genius spy festival in the world. Hello, cool. [Music] Well, there are some
people floating above, but yes.
[Laughs]
God.  However, I thought I was supporting Koyori-san's
MC
as a god,
but I think it's just annoying. Thank
you. I just want to see it.
Thank you.
From the ID, there are many JPE IDs mixed together,
but
actually, there is no one who is trying to swim competitively for the first time. It's
surprising and amazing.
[Music] Are you
getting involved or something?
[Music]
Everyone seems to know each other.Language  It's
nice to be able to connect with each other in this way, even beyond the walls of the world.That's why I would like to
share this with you today on this 6-person plus paper.Please, let's start with
something like this from the beginning.  We'll
run out of time if we talk about it,
so let's move on. Some
people may be watching the Toretaka Grand Prize for the first time,
so I
'll give you a brief explanation. In 2022, it will be a live
broadcast that will be broadcast by Hololive Talent or officially.
This is the corner where we will announce the best points from the released videos.It's
cute,
interesting,
and I somehow like Miracle.  I
'd like to decide.
Hey, first of all, I'm really curious about what kind of works there are.
So I'd like to start with this category right away.
Live
Toretaka Exercise 2022
Talent Staff Recommended Category
[Music]
So scary
[Applause]
[  Music]
This is Hololive Talent. Let
's take a look at the streams that were nominated through a survey of the staff. First, let's
take a look at the first one.
Everyone's 3D unveiling stream is
over.  We
all gathered together and the broadcast was held at the hideout.
Here we go.
[Music]
I got lost in that day.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] When
everyone sings together, it becomes really beautiful.  I guess you
mean in terms of height? Well,
let's line up and see that
even we have a pretty good height difference. The balance is good.
[Laughs] It's
true. I'm
looking forward to seeing you all in 3D someday.
Hey.
So next up, I'd like to take a look at the second video.This is the
second video, and it's a video of two people.A
new feature called the virtual space collaboration function has been
implemented, and
the two of you are playing right away, struggling with the controls that you're not used to yet.  It's
a must-see for the two of them to have fun together.
Well
then, please go ahead. [Laughter] [Laughter] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] I'm sure you're looking forward to it. The movements were a little awkward,
but that was actually a good thing.
That's how you felt.
[Laughter]  That
was interesting.
[Laughs]
Okay, so let's move on to the third one. The
third one, yes. The
last broadcast of Yukihama Yukka Rummy.
The two jump out to sea in hope. Will they
find the treasure?
One that makes you think it's a sunken ship called RTA.  Here's the scene:
[Music]
[Applause]
Wait a minute. It's
not that bad. You're
good at riding just by talking.
[Laughter]
So the third one is...  It
was a scene from Kanata-senpai and Lamy-senpai from the end.
[Music] I'm
sure you all watched the ending quite a bit,
but that tiny little ship has
rolled over before.
[Music] I guess it
must have been suspicious. I'll
buy it tomorrow.
I've come across some sharks that aren't that beautiful,
but I
think it's pretty rare to be able to get in there for a little while.I'm
lucky.I
never got to see the amazing Espoir.
So sad, let's take a look at the fourth and final one.Next
up is
Hosho Marine's 3rd Anniversary Distribution.The
famous Showa era, which is only now available, The
opponent's video size 4:3, The
opponent's
Showa quality, The
opponent's Showa production.  This
is a general scene from the Marin Senpai Showa Song Festival.
Here you go
[Music] This
is Gakuen Tengoku
[Music]
[Applause]
So it
was the Showa Kayo Festival and the school heaven of Kamashi Musume.
[Music] I
guess the current Kage IDs are aware of the Showa Kayo Festival. My
mother was a big fan of Showa songs.
I know.
Today I heard it for the first time.
[Music]
[Music] It's a
really good song that will never fade, even after all these years.  I
definitely want you to see all of the songs at this festival.It's
amazing, and I hope you
'll enjoy the atmosphere as well.That's it
for the Talent Staff Recommended category.Now, let's move on
to the next category.  Let's move on. Click
here for the next category
[Music]
Listener Clip Category
This is a new category created this year.
Anyone can use YouTube's clip function to create simple kill videos.  You can make it.
As a result, we asked listeners to
submit their take rates.Here, we would like to introduce broadcasts
selected from the take rates submitted by such listeners.If you
search for the hashtag ``Target Target 2022'' on Twitter, you will
receive a quote.  You can see the amount of money that has been received,
so if
you'd like, please check it out when you have time for New Year's holidays.Well, we've received
over 1,000 orders.
[Applause] When you
look at the cat,  Nenanka everyone too  They are
making clips while writing recommendations and comments, so
even if you just look at the hash tag, it's really fun to see what catches your eye,
so please check it out.Now, let's
take a look at the first video.Thank
you, Aqua's Aquarium
Streaming  The love adventure game Aquarium starring Aqua-
senpai is played by the strong Minato
Aqua player Minato Aqua.All scenes are
taken from the scenes in which they appear.Here we
go.
[Music]
As a girl, it's
fast.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] That's
where the girl was looking at me. That's
right.
Go over there.
[Music]
[Laughter] There
was a battle. It
was Aqua-senpai writhing in agony in the aquarium.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  ]
What if I made it? Can you do it? I want to
stream it
myself I'd like to hang out with myself
[Applause]
Embarrassing
[Music]
Embarrassing Embarrassing I guess that's
right.  I'd
like you to play it.Okay,
so let's move on to the second one.It's
broadcast to Fish and Black.Chloe
plays a horror game called Hell Battle.What
happens when Chloe, who is famous for hating baths, plays this game?  Are you going to put it away then?
The statue
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the second nominated work
is Sakamoto A, who advises game characters to also take a bath.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]  It
's a normal scene, but
Sakamoto's bathing was
pretty
trendy.
[Music] Is
there anyone among you who actually hates baths?
[Music] I
take a bath, and it doesn't stink, I'm
sure.  In Japan, you often take a bath in a bathtub,
but
in other countries, you often take a shower.
[Music] When you come to Japan, I would like you to take a bath in a public bath or a hot spring. [Music]
[Laughter]
So, let's move on to the third episode.The
last broadcast of this person, Sakura and Miko.Last: A
gambling place where you can bet on the scraps you brought in.The shrine
maiden is mercilessly running away with the scraps she stole from a senior at the festival who fell down gambling.  I
see. What will be the fate of the gambling family that has become addicted to the 20x bet, which has the highest odds but is also the least likely to win?
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the third nominated work
is A Shrine Maiden who wins big when gambling with other people's money.
After all, you're
working hard to gamble.
[Music]
Actually, I once won 20x with my little finger,
but
when I didn't have any money and only had 100 yen or so, I
didn't make any more money.
[Music]  That
was sad. Now that you say yes, let's
move on to the fourth one. Tokoyami and Ha's 2nd anniversary song was also decided with a bang. When I got to my impressions, I noticed that the three guests were acting like they weren't rehearsing.  When you're confused,
pay attention to the video
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
So the fourth nominated work is a
prank on a guest at his 2nd anniversary live.  set up  I could
n't have expected that the main character would be pulled a prank.The
performers must have
been in a good mood.  I have
n't seen it yet, so I'm sure there will be another one
at some point.It
was really cute, Mr. Door TMT.Please
take a look.Now, let's take a look at the last work.This
one was submitted.  I've
packed together some short and impactful items from among the high-earning candidates.Here
we go.
[Music]
[Music] An
old man pounding mochi
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] It's
cute because it's in hiragana.  There's something in the air
[Music] - I
did this!
[Music]
-
[Laughter] That's
great
[Laughter]
[Applause] The
last nominated work was a short summary video -
great
[Music]
[Music]  As for
Umami-chan,
at the end, Zeta-chan uses
that pet horse to pull her or Senpai due to an accident, and
behind the scenes, she and Polka-senpai are actually
talking about fighting together.  It seems
like I was imagining it. So, we were
talking about whether we would like to meet up, and
suddenly I got a call
from someone who had been in a terrible accident.
Please
cheer me up.
It's okay.
That's it.
Thank you very much for the listener recruitment division.
Thank you. There's
more to come. So here's the next
division.
[Music]
This is the Japan AR that we will choose for the 2022 performers.
Since they're appearing on the show, they wanted us to choose as well,
so we
asked everyone at SN to choose the best one for each one.Are you
all confident?That's
great.The expectations are so high, so
keep watching.  Let's go first  This
is the one selected by top batter Mel-senpai.Here we are again.This
is the last scene of the end-of-the-century game where anything goes.Mel-senpai acts with Polka-senpai and is concerned about the helicopter circling above.Here you go,
morning.  It's a broadcast. It's
broadcast in the morning around here
from around 24:40. Which is it?
24320 It's
scary. We were
attacked by helicopters several times. We
were shot at a lot. Is
that so?
[Music]
[Laughter] -
[Music] It
was about Mel who accepted his senpai's pranks and got hit
by a helicopter. [Music] He didn't realize that senpai was streaming.  That's what I was thinking.When I
got shot, I
hadn't died before.I hadn't died before, and I was
told that if I wore those clothes, I would get shot.Even so, I
couldn't dance, but then...  That was an
insight.
[Music] That
was sad.
[Laughs] Um,
from dying, from respawning, I
had to swallow again, so I almost
failed. It's tough,
because I'm a beginner,
but I can't get rid of those sad memories now.  Takane, it
's the one I chose, so I
chose it myself, or rather, Level-senpai,
thank you, thank you, thank you very much.Next
up is Iris-senpai.Iris-
senpai, she
bought new clothes and cosmetics and showed them off.
[Music]
Who is this person?
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]  ]
Stop it!
That's why Iris-senpai North has been reborn with new clothes.
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Really, I finally got to buy new
clothes. I was able to
buy them at a super cheap price at the department store.
Thanks to the cheap block [music], I can now shake in many places
[laughs]
Thank you, Senpai,
thank you very much. Let's move on to the next one.
From Hololive ID
Luxury A
new student who started Royal.  The
heroine saves the hero who is surrounded by enemies, and I can't
help but think of Date-chan.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Look at that. It's
dangerous. The
way you laugh is so funny.
[Music]
[Music] It's been a long time, has
n't it? [Music] [Laughter] [Music] Is it Bestia Zeta-chan, who has become limited by the new heroine and has lost her vocabulary? Well, she's still a little mesmerized, but what about her? Student-chan Wow, I don't know much about files.  That's the
very first one, the
first goddess,
so...
[Music] I'm
definitely a bit like a prince
[Music] I said
it was cute, so it
was Jet-chan.Next
up.  This
is Hakotaro-senpai, and this is a casual chat stream.
Hakotaro-senpai is seriously answering questions from listeners. It does
n't seem like a big deal, but why is this so
high? Let's
take a look right away.
[Music]
[Music]  ] I
see.
-
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I'm
trying to see if my elbows can touch. It's
Hakotaro-senpai. No, Kotaro-senpai,
it's impossible.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yeah, they're all really tough, right?
[Laughs]
There's one person who got eaten by that one,
but Mr. Wally,
what's the matter? No, it's
okay. Yeah, are you okay? I
don't think bullying is good,
though.  I'm already talking to my senior from a while ago,
but the clippings are
being played very well.This
year's fire money, a little chat, etc.It's
being broadcast in Japanese, and this year's kanji is elbow.  It was
interesting that it was spreading and it was my highest bird price.It
was cute.Thank
you for saying yes.Thank
you very much.Next,
let's introduce a unique bird price.Hololive
ID  It's a recommendation from Ollie-senpai,
but it's not my own stream, but that
of Hobo-chan, a junior at ID.I
got really excited during the countdown stream the day before my birthday, so let's
take a look.What are you
doing here?
[Music]  ]
No, this guy is doing something in his room, but where did he get this
[music]
lighting? So, it
doesn't seem like Hololive at all, but what does that
mean?
What about you, Senpai? There's
someone even crazier.  That
's the reason why I wanted to show it to you. It looked like it would
be fun.
[Music]
There are listeners during the broadcast, but
if you can enjoy it by yourself after the broadcast is over, why not?
How do you explain it?
[Music]
Thank you very much for your wonderful side. It
was interesting. Now, this is the last one. The
MC said that I could choose as well, so I
chose him over Eko.
Hololive High School, led by the employment director,
Spring Koshien semi-finals,
tied,
extended.  The game went on until the 11th inning, and the
enemy gave away a lot of benefits, and the last attack, which everyone thought was no good, had
two outs, and the bases were loaded.
Is this a chance drama?
Please take a look at the manager's decision.
[Music] Up
until the 10th inning, it was 3-3.
[Music]
[Applause]
This
[Music]
[Music] I
was thankful to the streaming gods for all of this. It was
such a good
game that I decided to do it myself.  I'm uploading a cutout video,
so I
think it'll be even hotter if you watch the whole thing, so I think it's interesting, so
I hope you'll come and see what all the high schoolers are doing.
[Laughs]
So, thank you very much for
appearing.
This is the end of the amateur category, and the next one
will be the last nominated film.Click
here for the final introduction.O-
Special Award for Yago
This
is also an annual tradition.Everyone
chose one film for Yago, who loves it.Let
's take a look.
I'd like people to watch this without any explanation.
Please go ahead.
It
was here.  I've
received a comment from a shop name. I'm
going to swim. I
was happy. That's why I chose it for the nighttime award.
That's the thing. Not
even at the third festival.
[Music] I was
moved. A
senior appeared. Hmmm. It
's beautiful. I love seniors like this.  I love you
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, so
all the best-shot works have been finalized.
Finally,
Hololive Training High School Gymnastics 2022 Grand Prix  I
would like to decide on the work.
Well then, this time I would like to collect one vote from each person.
Please let me know which one you liked.
]
[Laughs]
Amoa, that's amazing.
But there's only one thing, so I
'd like to finally announce the
winner of the prestigious Grand Prix of Hololive Toretaka Grand Prix 2022.
[Music]
Congratulations to the Met duo who are expected to enjoy the virtual space collaboration feature.
[Music] It's
really interesting.
And it's a new feature, right
? That's what I'm looking forward to.
[Music]
Hey,
Congratulations to the two of you. Well
then, it won't be that simple,
but
I'd like to hear your impressions if you don't mind. Well then,
Mel-senpai. Yes,
but even just introducing this just now
was a huge amount.  It's
interesting because it's crossing the line, and I thought I'd like to see some of the other things that I'm a little curious about.That's because
everyone at Hololive has been streaming a lot and
making it exciting over the past year, so I'll see
you next year too.  I
want to make fun memories with everyone.
Thank you very much for today. Thank you very much.
Alice-senpai. Well,
everything was really interesting, and as expected, I
think it's Hololive.
Everyone's talented.  I've been
streaming every day with nothing but interesting moments,
and I think this year has been an incredibly eventful one.It
would be great if it's like this next year as well.Thank
you very much for this time.It
was a lot of fun.  So, thank you everyone for watching.
Thank you very much.
Now then, Hakotaro-senpai,
Wow, it
was really fast.
But when you look at the pretense of doing free skates like this, it turns out that there was a
lot going on.  I
think it's amazing, but from now on, I want to make some fun memories with everyone at Hololive.
Thank you very much. I
'll do it with you.
Yes, I'm
sorry, but is English okay? I
don't speak Japanese, so
WeIthing
tomanythmantomy
everyone
Thank you for your continued support
[Music]
Thank you very much,
thank you, and
Data-chan
Yes, I would like to speak English too, please
[Music]
[Music]  I
want to continue to make many memories with everyone.
Thank you.
[Music] As I
said at the beginning,
watching the Hashtag Photography High School Award 2022, it's
really interesting.
Thank you for your hard work.
I hope everyone can use that hashtag to see a
lot of scenes of other members, and I
hope you'll see a
lot of holo scenes in 2023 as well.  From
now on, I want to keep going with my concerts without stopping.I
think the 2023 Toreko Grand
Prize will be even more amazing.Thank you very much.Is there
anything God has to offer?
All of you are
amazing talents, so much so that I want to introduce them all.  I'm going to continue to work hard on my English so that everyone can watch this Hololive,
as well as JP, CN, and
ID,
so I'd like to
thank each and every fan and talent.  I
will continue to do my best to connect everyone, so please love everyone.
Thank you for your support.
[Music]
From now on, too. It's not just
Hololive with laughter, but I
hope you enjoy it.
Unfortunately for all of you, the
end time is approaching.I would
like to conclude the 2022 Hololive Shooting Award by watching this.I hope that everyone will continue to
enjoy it and make a positive contribution.  I
hope that you will continue to support Hololive in 2023.Then
next time will be the Hinadan talk at 9:30 pm, which
will continue with Yomoyama Variety Holo.It's almost 9:30
pm.Thank you for your
continued support.Thank
you for your continued support.
So let's close with greetings.
Goodbye everyone. Thank you. Bye-bye.
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
From now on,
our corner
will be [Applause] More [Applause] [Music] [Applause] Are you ready?
[Music] Are you
ready? [Applause] Yes, there are some people who haven't been able to do it.
By the way, there are so many people here,
so let's all
call out the title. Let's go. Okay, let's go.
[Music]
In this corner, you can talk about various themes as you like.
Wool Mountain Talk
To put it simply, it
has become a way to defeat people by posting chats.I see.That being
said, the moderators this time are
Full Live 4th generation students Kanatan and Amane,
Canada and Kore Life 5th generation students with dry snow skin on their faces.
Lamy's
Gorilla's Liver
[Music] I
'll be serving you
Gorilla's Gorilla's Liver Gorilla's Liver
So it's Mori Liver, but I remember it today.
That's what I'm talking about. Today, I'm
going to have fun and chat with my
friends, who are not very evil, but happy.
Who are you talking about?
[Music]
[Applause]
What are you doing? It's
starting. It's good.  Well, I
'd like you to introduce yourself a little bit.
Since it's New Year's Eve, I'd like to
ask you to share an episode from 2022 that goes with the theme. So,
first of all,
men and women,
please introduce yourselves as well as tell us your stories of joy.
Everyone, I'm Shirogane, the Iron Stomach Daimajin from the 3rd generation of Comas Through Hololive.
[Music]
There are many things that I'm happy about, but of course there
's the dungeon. I'm
sure there's something for everyone.  But on the
radio, I've been asked to imitate
this kind of movement more and more. [Music] [Music] Are you doing this kind of movement because you're trying to do it?
This is the first time I've said this.  Let's have
lunch. I've been doing strange movements like this ever since I was in high school.
At that time, people were saying
a lot to me,
but when I
joined Yamazaka Hololive, I didn't
expect everyone to imitate me so well.
But, thank you, thank you, right? Stop
it.  I hope it won't happen, but it
keeps going on and on, and I'm
sure you'll be wondering if that will be mentioned when you come as a guest at a live show, so it's
normal.Next time, I'll do Lunar.
Please tell me about this year's mistakes
[Music]
[Applause]
Cute corona bouyon regulations Various things until I die
[Music]
Well, what's wrong with this year?
After entering Holoram, I
vomited from alcohol for the first time. Gap Gap
Gap is currently being
streamed.  Is that what you mean?
Just after the broadcast ended,
I couldn't hold back anymore and went to the bathroom.This is what makes me so
drunk late at night.  It's
become a trend.
[Music]
By the way, when it comes to alcohol, it's
like Ramy. Yes,
there are some people who have some interesting ones. Do you
have any stories of you doing something wrong? When you
realize it, you're at the ticket gate of that virtual Shibuya in Shibuya.  I
slept with Rainbow,
so please be careful.Next
year, let's be careful.Let's talk
about this year.So,
let's talk about Tide's evil earlier.
Rapture
That's amazing. It's a bit like Baru. When you
introduce yourself, please tell me what made you happy this year.
Do your best.
[Music] Are you
going to say that again this year
? Yamada: Well, this year ends today,
right? Me.  I was happy. The
thing that made me happy this week
was that I got an offer for my favorite movie, The Script is Yankee 4K. I'm a little evil.
[Music] I
said I was happy, but
more  I'm
starting to see it, Unkodandan
[Music]
That's a really cool thing,
so
let's move on to Akiraze Sentai, which I'm addicted to this year. Yasuke, who has
developed a live performance as much as Arora,
is highly praised by Kiropeko and Akira
[laughter]  ]
Maybe you've been drinking
? This year, I've been playing a
game called Splatoon, and I almost
forgot to introduce myself.  I
think everyone knows that.
[Music]
[Music] I
thought maybe I could surpass it twice, but no matter
how many times I tried, I couldn't.
[Applause] That's
amazing. I've already paid off all my debts, so I'll do it for now.
Kee
[Applause] It's
starting to look like that kind of sport,
right? Let's
all do it, Splatoon.
So far, let's do a little bit.
Well, for that last part, I'd like to ask you about something that made you laugh this year.  I've
never had fun or laughed. The
thing that made me laugh this year was that
Jaures
[music]. I
took it for granted, so please go ahead and
ask me more about it. It's a little
different, so I can say that, but first of all, I
suddenly
felt like I was holding my forehead.  When something fell down, I
was told that there was a ghost inside, so I was acting normal, but it
didn't fall at all, and I was pushed as hard as I could, and then I fell down.
But at that point, I realized that this was not the case.  I did, but
After that, I heard something about a princess from the Edo period
[Music] I
was half-smiling as I thought, ``Oh, that's a lie,'' but then I heard that it
was all over in the end, and I thought, ``Oh,
this farce is finally over.''
[Music] The
final boss turns out to be a tengu monster
[Applause]
[Music]
That's the point. I
don't know. I'm a little curious as to whether it happened now.
But it wasn't at all. It was like
230,000 yen.
Yay! Sakamoto: If it was a Pachimon game like that, I would
have been prepared for hundreds of thousands of yen. This is the worst.  It's
like watching a musical.
This one is really unique. Yes, there are 8 people in
total. Please
wait.
Please make it 7 years old.
[Music]
[Applause] I
made a mistake in counting. Yes, there
are 7 people.  I
would like to bring you some unit chats.
[Applause]
[Music]
Or
Well, today I would like to ask you to tell us about a
topic that you would like to talk about or
something that you would like to hear from the members here.  I
think everyone answered a little survey, but I would
like to mainly talk about it. There is
no script for the content of the talk, so I hope it
doesn't cross the border. [Music]
So, first of all,
let's talk about the topic that Sakamoto wants to talk about. There's something
more I want to talk about than being a slave. I
don't want to see him just being shy.
Well, I want to see it. I really want to see it these
days.
Everyone tell me the most embarrassing story.
[Music] It seems like you
were embarrassed. It
came out with a
bang.
Everyone, please raise your hand to say that you have experienced that. It would
be easier if you did it, right?
No, Captain, back in November,
when I collaborated with a certain Yakiniku restaurant, I was
thinking of using a coupon, and
when I went there by myself, I found that
paper apron, which I know is a
hair updo.  When I got home, I noticed a little bit of the
undertone [laughter]
I know. People definitely laughed at me. When did I
finally realize that it
was when I got home and washed my hands and gargled? It was
a little weird.  There was a
day when I was walking home thinking that I wanted to feel the night breeze, but it didn't
flap.I wonder if
this is an embarrassing thing that happened recently.If
you
ask me to tell you an interesting story, I won't come up with it.
Ah, I
want to hear it, so please talk a little bit about
it.Since you're going to be asked something like this,
don't you prepare something of your own
?I'm sure there are other
people's stories.  I'm
already talking about something, but
when I went to New Year's market, I
thought I'd take some souvenirs with me, but I felt really bad that day,
and I felt like I was going to throw up, so when I was on my way there, I decided to
open that road.  If I didn't have one, I would have taken a taxi,
but
inside the taxi, I
was wearing my jeans and
took off my zipper, so
from there
[music] I got
off and carried the souvenirs for a while.  I was
wondering if I should go to karaoke,
but then I saw an order code on the sidewalk, and when I saw
the lady on the street to clear the permit, she was
really on my side.
The moment I saw it, I realized that
everything was fully open, completely
visible, and in a
short, sudden moment, it
was completely hidden,
completely visible, and no one really
said anything, not even the store clerk.  The
store clerk also clearly looked like an emo,
but that's not what I thought was the fashion.It
seems like this kind of fashion is popular.The same goes for the story about the dungeon earlier.Surprisingly, the
store clerk and the
other people are doing the same thing.  It's
tough, is
n't it? It's embarrassing because you'll be made fun of later. I want you to tell me. Yes, yes, yes. I wonder if there's anyone else out there with embarrassing stories. I wonder if there really aren't any.  It's
really embarrassing, but the
listeners say that to me, and my
habit of misunderstanding is so strong that it's embarrassing.
For example, what is it?
After all, this girl really likes me.
[Music]
Ah, the misunderstanding gorilla that appeared.  Hey, I
heard a lot of bad language, but I
was mistakenly called a gorilla. I
can't climb it. It's really amazing. I
woke up due to some kind of awkward friction.  I
feel like something's going to happen to me, but it's okay. I like you a little. But hey, he's just the prince of Hinadan. Everyone, Hinadan-san. That's why I don't like men. Hey, I understand, but if it can't be helped, then,
uh, I was sleeping the other day.  That's
it. I'm
tired. I'm going to release this already. I'm
going to release this. You know, this is really 2022. I
want to be in the top 3.
[Music]
In the middle of the night, yeah
One of my buttock's got a little
taut.If it
's similar, I
thought it would hurt, so I squeezed my butt, and the moment it was made, I
let both hands squeak at the same time.I
sucked on my butt, butt muscles.  It's connected to my thighs, so that's
where it
hurts, and I'm really alone on the futon,
crying, and it's already hurting,
right? This isn't a painful
story. But, well, I guess it was an embarrassing story.
Everyone was kind, so I can move.  I
was listening to it in the dressing room earlier, and I was
laughing so hard that I almost died. I
laughed, but it was kind of a big bomb. It was
unexpected, and I
could hear that the board was a little embarrassing.
Hey, let's
talk about the next person's theme.
Okay, let
's move on to the next topic, which I'd like to talk about from some of my seniors.It's
idol theory.Well,
we can talk about it, right?It's already
been decided that we should talk about it, right?Idol theory.
After all, everyone has been lined up on the hinadan.
I haven't forgotten that we are idols. We
're idols. In
2022, we'll finally be able to talk
about various things like idols.
Yes, it
's a bit embarrassing. This is embarrassing. It
's serious.  Well, since we're far away, I
think it would be a good idea to hear from the two people who weren't able to talk to us earlier.
First, Luna has an idol run.
[Laughs]
She's an idol. She
has time. I wonder if she's sleepy or not. It's
like she's broadcasting from a very far away place.
Butidol-
like
idols sing and dance to bring happiness to everyone.
[Laughs] I
started to worry because I was
already getting closer to that ideal image of an idol,
but now I'm an idol.
[Music]
That's right, that's right. I
forgot. I
think you're pretty.  I
thought it was normal for people to ask me if I
was an idol, so I guess I'm an idol.Then,
Laplace Dark seemed to be the furthest away from the idol man who was sitting in a strange way next to me.What do you think?  Yeah, I don't like that,
but I
think we're probably the only idols in Hololive who think we're idols.Why?The
management definitely
doesn't treat us like idols.We really wo
n't let something like this happen.
On the other hand, from Rapson's point of view, I still
feel like I'm not used to being an idol.
I'm an idol, so what's a side job
? I do it in my spare time. Why are you so lazy
even in Tokyo?
Isn't that enough? Everyone is free.  It's okay,
but I have a lot of feelings.That's
right.As
expected, it's a little bit like this.It
makes me feel like I'm falling in love with you.  Now that I've
become an idol, I'm really thinking about next year.I
said I'm happy that you're doing some strange things, but I wonder if this is okay,
even the leader is wondering.It's okay, it's okay,
isn't it?
For example,  Look, it's kind of fluffy, it's
kind of fluffy like this, it's
a bit of an idol-like movement. I'm
even thinking about doing it next year.
Wait, wait, I'm doing that idol-like movement now.  That's
right here. I want to see them one by one. One
by one, it's
like an audition.
Last month,
when I got up from my chair, I wondered
if I was an idol. [
Music] [Music] [Music]  [
Laughter]
[Applause]
Please, you're
cute.
Why don't you try Raku-chan?
Let's go.
[Music] -
[Laughter]
Think of it as a stage.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Let's
find a balance there.
Please don't make the noise. Now open that. I
asked my seniors to decorate it.
[Laughs]
Idols are idols after all. A little bit from the idol step. [
Applause]
[Music]
Sexy
[Applause] That's
amazing.  It's
like that [music] It's
like an idol-like movement. Okay,
wait a minute. I'll go.
Okay, okay, let's do it one more time. I
'm saying something I didn't see. I didn't see it.  thing
No
[Music] I've been
able to do double jumps since I was 6 years old.
[Laughs]
Robin should come too.
No refugees, after all. They
were taken away.
That's how Lamy
always performs.
Sorry for the camera.
[Music] It's
like that. I was doing it, but
it's a little thin.
[Laughs] It
was Tendon, so I'll try another one.
[Music]
No,
that's how we
do it. It's just the two of us doing something. It's
not a good fit for us.
[Laughs]
Well, since we got paid, then
let's go to the next person's talk topic.
Next time is
Autumn.  Here's a question from a senior.
[Music]
Crepes are cute and
delicious, and I think they're a food that's perfect for idols. Well
then, I'd like to start working at a crepe shop. That's
great. So
someday I'd like to do a stream where I make crepes.
[Applause] I'm
hoping to do something like that next year.So I thought I'd ask
everyone if they like side dishes or
sweets.That
means that the market research is
based on the above.  I wonder
if I can just say it. I
want you to cut it. The
person next to me, Mr. Kuroi, is so
excited. First of all, I've never had a crepe as a side dish.
[Applause]
[Music]
What's that?  When I
think of crepes, I think of
desserts, and things like Scouter and sweet and
sour
pork with pineapple aren't good either, but they're like the ones with vinegar and pork and pizza with pineapple.Okay
[Music]
Eh, whipped cream, strawberries,
caramel, and
cute.  I
like it the most. I think I'll
ask the dungeon next time.
Lunch will be
perfect.
[Applause]
Or something like chocolate banana.  I'm
fine with the classics, but
if I'm going to order a crepe, I'll definitely go with tuna
mayo.Well, I've
had some pizza flavor before, and it's
super delicious.By all means, Aki-senpai,
I'd
like some of your side dishes.
[Music]
First of all,
[Music] It
's Mr.'s side dish.  The
side dish you eat with white rice is sea, but there
's a difference. Maybe you've never seen it before, or
maybe you don't know.
Crepes, which I don't know
about, are like a side dish, or rather, they have
something like a salty ham or
lettuce
inside, and the filling is
like a sandwich, and the filling is sloshing around.  It
's not a crepe.
Just
put whatever you want. I want to put a banana in a crepe. I'm
going to eat some chocolate and fresh cream.
[Laughs] Now
that my heart is clean, let's go
.
[Laughs] I do
n't like sweets, so I'm a
bit of a side dish person. Absolutely.
Since it's tuna and mayo, I
'd like to have a number in the middle because they're all the same. They're
separated neatly, but I'm already answering our questions.
At the same time, after all, Gorileba.  That's
why
Seno Ne100 It
must have been sweets or side dishes
Neyyappa Chocolate Banana
[Music]
I love things like cream
Yeah, I've only eaten that crepe twice,
but it's a bit of a crush,
so it's not true. It
has a somewhat stylish image from the bottom, so I
can't eat it easily, but I want to try it,
but I think it's a bit
cheap.  I thought it
only had that cream and that syrup in it.
[Music]
[Applause]
I think I'd like to go out and make some crepes with everyone next time. I
want my seniors to make some too.
Yeah, that's right.Which side are you on, anyway
?
Don't give up.Are you stepping into forbidden territory as a crepe shop?Are you
okay?You shouldn't have put a tarantula in this.It
has the same meaning, but no, the
clerk at the tape shop is 1.  You can eat one crepe for every part-time job that day,
so
put them all in.
[Applause]
[Music] It
's so big. I've eaten something like that bouquet before.
Does it have both? It has both side dishes and sweets.
[Applause]
Isn't that the pineapple in the sweet and sour pork? It's
true.
Only the pineapple is a little no-nonsense.
But it
feels like you're putting everything in there. It's like
fresh cream, right?
Strings and all.  Well, I
only ate it once, and the next time I
ate it, I asked for something that was sorted properly.I
see, it's all about the taste.
When I said yes, I got pretty excited,
but I
guess I just wanted to ask you
one more thing.If I
had them make all of the dishes I mentioned earlier,
people who could eat them would
eat them.  There's someone here
[laughter]
[music]
[applause]
Flour and sweets go well together.The other day
when I put candy in takoyaki, someone joked right in front of me.
[laughter]
Thank you for doing that.
In fact, we have received questions from people other than the members here,
so
let's talk about it accordingly.It
arrived with a message from the person himself, so please
watch it right away and
start the VTR.Good evening.
[Music] This year has
gone so fast,
hasn't it? Thank you very much for all your help.My
question is
about New Year's resolutions, and
about the successful and unsuccessful New Year's resolutions.
I want to hear what kind of
[music] I
wonder if there will be an answer. I'm really looking forward to it.
This year is almost over, so I
wish you a happy new year. I look forward to working with you on
hypnosis and in the future as well.
Thank
you. That's your
question.  is my resolution for this year in 2022, both my
successes and my failures.But
hey, everyone, do you
remember what kind of resolution you made
in the first place?Seriously, you don't remember?
[Music]  I
remember that.
[Applause]
[Music] I
remember yoga.
Every year I have one goal that remains the same. I
guess it's
conquering the world.
Every year I fail. Next
year for sure.
Next year.
Next year. [
Music]
Next year.  I want to conquer the world with this guy.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
feel like I'm going to fail a little bit,
but, you know, I don't think
people remember,
like, what I thought I was going to do this year, or
what I had set as a goal.  It's
okay to do things like that. It does
n't have to be a resolution. If that were the case, I wonder if it would have happened.
But I think it's okay to do
something positive for men and women after success.
Last year was the first time Hololive
debuted.  I
released the original song in September of last year,
so I
kind of wanted to release a lot of original songs,
so this year I was able to release three songs.
[Applause]
So, well, I'll continue next year as well.  I
feel like I want to do my best, so I'll do my best.
Yay.
[Music] It's a
similar thing, but
Sakamoto
wanted to set the button in his life when he became a buzz on TikTok, so I was happy.
[Applause]
[Music]
Success  I
was so happy that I had never succeeded in what I did.It was
amazing.It was true to my personality.Also, things
didn't turn out the way I thought they would.That's amazing.  I
think it's really great, so I'll continue to do my best.
[Music]
By the way, there are people who have
failed. I was planning to do something this year, but if I
fail, well, conquering the world is a failure, but I've
failed, but I'm still doing this.  But
other people don't say anything either. I'm sure there's
something
wrong with me. It's like I'm hiding it because I did something wrong. I forgot about it a little bit. I guess it's not so much last year. I'm not good at relying on other followers for things.  I can't do much
But this year, when I
tried to call out to everyone, there were some people who looked like they were going to cry,
but their
individuality came out, and it
made me excited.The
fact that I was able to call out to Honolma and collaborate with them and perform with them was a success.
I wonder if that's what I did. I don't like it, but everyone is being fooled. So
when I was staying with that person in Lou, I forgot about the
bath salts.
Hey
, I feel like I'm being deceived. This atmosphere makes me
want to be deceived
[laughter],
so I hope I can get back somewhere again.
Yes, I'm still
receiving questions from overseas members, so
let's take a look.
Start I
have a problem and would like to ask everyone for advice. I
'm a fan of all generations.
[Music] I'm
not
good at coming here, so I'd like to ask you all.
Hmm, how do you decide on thumbnails?  Is
there one? What is it
like now? By the way, how do you make thumbnails these days?
By the way, you
said that you are not good at adding thumbnails, but what do you all think?
Seriously, no, I'm not good at it. Seriously, Laplace is really good. He's good. I'll take this [music]. Let's do business. Besides, he's good, and I like him. I don't really
dislike
him. He's a creator.
However, the thing I'm most careful about is that
on YouTube, the
thumbnails are displayed smaller than I expected,
so I like to make people bigger than I expected, and the other
important thing is when I make thumbnails, I make them smaller.
Display it and make it
Ah, that's right, I'll
make it in the back.
It's amazing. It's a serious and serious answer. It's helpful. I made a mistake. I made a mistake. But it's really good. It's
helpful.
Everyone says that they're not good at it,
but for example,
what is it about seniors that they're not good at? Well, if
there's something you want to do and it's streaming, you
don't know what's going to happen, so it's like something
like a thumbnail title scam.
Well,
it's a scam, but
before it's distributed, it ends up with a generic title,
and the image is the type that doesn't have much firepower.Are you
sure you're
prepared for this?The members who are adding things are also like that.  I wonder
if it's possible to do this on a daily basis.Is there any
text in it?This way, this way, this way, this way,
this way, this way,
like tuning, etc.I'm
juggling the thumbnails.  It's a
thing, but I
didn't really understand it until the company started.Actually, I
said I'm going to do this, but
when I tried it, surprisingly nothing happened.I was amazed that being able
to create thumbnails was really
amazing.
hey  I
sometimes look at other people's pictures so they work.I might look at everyone's thumbnails and use them as a reference.I
save the thumbnail rummy of people who are good at it.It's
amazing.By the way, only one of them works.Personally, I'd
like to ask.  But
how long does it take to make a thumbnail? I want to know.
[Music] Sometimes it
takes about an hour.
[Music] It
takes a hell of a lot. That's it, Lapi-chan.  It
really
depends on what kind of person you are good at, but if you do something easy, it
will take 30 minutes, but
even if it's early, you
have no choice but to ask.
-
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] It
's quite difficult, though.
Okay, okay. Well, that's it for Ollie.
I hope you were able to answer what you wanted to know. So, please take a look at the story that just came out and
make your own thumbnails too. Now,
this is the last question from the overseas members.  Introduction
VTR
Start
The question is, what do you think of my Yoffie?
That's all?
[Music]
How was the sunset this year? A
simple question about UFOs is my impression.
What do you all think?  That's right
First of all, I have
n't been involved
in it in the first place, so I'd like to get involved next year.
Thank you in advance. It
would be great if fans could come up with cute hair as an icon.  Let's
take this opportunity to make the leader bald as well. I
want you to create that hairstyle.
[Applause] I
want a new style. You
have to get permission. I
suddenly
received a picture of me bald.  I'm
doing it on stream, so I'm
starting to see photos of the state I did it in and the state it was in after. I didn't get that one, though...
[Music]
But I did a collaboration with him. We're good
friends, so I guess it's okay.  I guess that's
what it's like, or maybe that's it. I wonder
if there's a big difference.
Well, everyone here,
please do it without permission.
Well, this year's Yuffie.
I guess
Luffy-senpai has a strong image of a tsurupage, but
to say thank you, let's come and play together next year.Okay
, everyone, it's the second half of the game,
so I'm here again.  Let's
talk about what the members want to talk about. I'm
sorry that the first half of the second half is over.
What's the best theme for this? Here it
is. Hello.
[Music] If you hadn't
joined Hol Live, what would you be
doing now?  Ta
[Music] I
just wanted to ask you a little bit about this. I
wonder if he aspired to be an idol, or if he aspired to be a comedian. I thought I'd like to ask everyone this, but I
guess I'll have to hear it from Sakamoto.
Did he go down? He
was a member of Phlox.
No, but he was probably an intern, so he
could quit anytime, so he quit. He
quit for a bit. He
probably went to the hall or something.
Let me express it with my hands.
[Music]
Hey,
but that's what it is. It's
not like it's been a while since I really debuted or anything.
But all we've been talking about is that app, so I'm
worried [Music]  As a senior, I wonder
if it's okay. Yes, I'm glad I took a bath.
Thank you so much.
Thank you Hololive.
Next time I'll set up with Akira.
After all, it's a bit of a different world.
As a dancer, I guess I was aiming for the top.  I'd
like a dance costume, please.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Maybe there's a future like that,
so I guess she doesn't have that kind of power. She might have
been a programmer, aside from the princess.
Realistic rules. I see.  I see, she's a
capable woman.Okay,
then let's ask the leader and the man.Yes,
before we went to the full live show, it
was originally an emergency job, so I guess we've been doing it out of inertia.Would you please
stop for a moment?
No, but.
Honestly, I'm not cut out to be a ringmaster, I guess it
was work,
but if I hadn't been to this live show, I would have been
inertia somehow.
[Music] I wonder if it would have
worked for Robbie too. Ramy, who becomes Robby.
But if I hadn't been to Hololive, I would probably be
at the mansion right now.  It's
always
dark.
It's a little bit too much. It's not the kind of thing we do here during the New Year holidays. I'm
glad I joined Hololive and met everyone. I
don't have any friends. I
bought it, so I'll
make friends.
[Music]
By the way, I wonder if Lapi-chan's
design is normal.
[Music] That
means she likes doing things.
Legs: Do
n't do it. Conquer the world. Well, let's put aside the idea of conquering the world for now. World player, don't be silly. I'm going to wear a uniform. [Music] I won't go home, I won't go home.  I guess I did, but it's
probably
not much different from my current private life, like looking for the lowest price for natto at the supermarket, etc.
Why, Master, why are you laughing?
[Music] It
's sparkling, thank you
very much. Let's
close
on that note. [Laughs] But next, let's move on to the next topic.
Let's move on. Who's next? Let's see.
Next.  Here's what Rap-chan wants to do.
[Music]
Please tell me your type of don.
I love Koibana.
[Music] I'm an
idol, but I
love girls' manga. Even before this recording, I was reading girls' manga today.
[Applause]  After
all, when I was
watching Hololive's broadcasts, I
realized that there weren't that many people who liked my type or had love stories,
so I thought I'd
take this as a chance and
ask. It'll
take about an hour, though.
Please.
[Music]
No, I
like glasses. I
guess I don't really like glasses,
but I'm fine with just wearing glasses.
[Laughs]
For example, even if he's not a good-looking guy, there's a
human being, and he's wearing glasses, and for the
first time, it's complete. I don't
really care about that. Is it his
favorite shellfish or his favorite glasses?
[Music]
[Music] He's
running away, right? Wait a minute.  Wait a minute, it
's not the person who protects you, it's Sugar. It's sign language, right?
So when you're standing next to this, it
's Raigane.
By the way, it's the leader who says it already.  He
says things like Subaru-senpai style, and
sometimes he
burns things.
Hmm,
that kind of thing.
[Music] I love you. Don't call it a relationship. I don't think anything of it. Is that what you like? [Music] It's a matter of consultation. [Music]
There are people who are crying in their hearts, so I don't care
what type of people you like when they're crying.I don't care what kind of people you like when you're crying, but
you know,
deafness is just a push for idols.  I'm the
type of person who just smiles and listens to him
.
Why do I
like this leader? I guess my
favorite type is a
kind person.
Eh, anime
[laughing]
[music] I
don't really like the characters because of how they look.  But he seems like a normal
person. He's a single-minded person after all. Please be kind to yourself.
Yes,
please be kind to me. It's
just my appearance, like my glasses,
so I don't have a
face or anything.  Let's
listen to it. It's like a
two-dimensional genre that I'm into.
[Music] A little bit of
naughty manga, a little
bit
[Music]
Seriously,
but it's a little like this. It's like, uh,
wild with different opinions.  I don't think I
'd go so far as to say that I don't have a good feeling about it, but I have a lot of life experience, and I'm
very accepting and will protect me in times of need.I
think I'm like John Wig.I feel like I'm on the halfbeak side, but how old are I?
Uncle Sakamoto's age:
Uncle
What is this? He's in his late 30's
[
Music] It makes sense, right? Well then, Sakamoto is
blonde, he's kind of
short, his
signature color is purple, and he's a
shitty kid who looks like he can use magic.
[Applause]
[Music] I
was pretty excited because I was silver-haired and short, but the
cameraman never let me miss him even once.  It does
n't make sense.
[Music]
But let's be really cute.
Isn't he really cute with his bare hands? It's
just like that, but
the moment I entered the holo, I was like, `
`Is that a lie? Is this really true?'' It's like an
otaku.
But  I'm sleeping at my house.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] Please
do it with art. It's
scary.
Next theme. Next theme. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go.
Well, that's right, it's Koi Banana right now.
But since things are like this, there
's something I'd like to ask everyone.
[Music]
What, if you don't marry one of the current members, the
earth will be destroyed.  If so, who would you choose
?
What kind of situation would you be in? After thinking about all these things, if
you had to marry someone,
if you were to ask who you would choose, there would
definitely be someone who would say that you can't choose someone.
If the earth was at stake, your life, or the lives of the people you care about, you'd
choose,
right? Well, this is a bit like that, right? What would you do if you were chosen? I'm
really looking forward to it, and I'm excited.
Alright, let's cut it out.
Who should I ask?
Laputa
. Eh, it
's not decided yet.
[Music] You
can despair because you're trying to wear a uniform, but you can only do so
if you have friends. That's
true.
Who do you think would be good in real life?
I know, absolutely, but she can cook, take care of me, and
do everything for me. She's kind, and I'm getting
married, so
I'm getting married, so it's
about urinating. It's no good anymore. Well,
that's it,
senpai.  Yes,
that's right.
[Applause] It's
like Spadari. My
mom's Spadal is a little bit of a give-up
. I don't know. But
there's a certain sponanny to it. It's really a hunter.
That's Supara. I want to taste it.  Let me have a
little taste of it next year.
Maybe it'll be a good pairing. Of course, you
can ask me as much as you want.
Laplace is done. You've
finally given up. I'll
kidnap you after you perish. It's
cute.
Yes, I'm serious.  It's a story, isn't it?
In all seriousness,
everyone
[Music]
From the erasing knife
Seniors are really just the way they are,
and they even
say they're happy again.
Since there are no seniors, it's going to be like Lamy,
so that's right.
[Laughs] The
good thing about it is that it's the same, and the good thing about it being
streamed is still there, so I
feel like I want to protect her girlish side, her weak side, etc.  I'll do it,
but if I don't say something, I'll be really messed up.I'm the
type of person who wants to protect you.Well, you know, it's
not cool.I can
do it.On
the other hand, I'm
holding up my untied hand, and I
don't think it's there right now.
Leader:
Eh,
Leader. Well, Leader, it's only one choice.
Well, it's Lou Butter after all.
Even if you ask me the first time, I'm thinking of saying it. It's because I'm a knight, and I'm hard of hearing.
What if I sleep with Princess?
[Laughter]
That's difficult.
[Applause] That's an
anachronism. That's
amazing. It's pretty neat now. I
think the coupling is done.
[Music]
Wait. You
can do
this here.
[Music]
Kami-sama no Yuta
This is because Luna didn't have anyone to choose her, so she
did it because she felt sorry for her, so please
sit down. Yes,
no, no, no, wait a minute.
Actually,
Sakamoto.  If I had to choose, what would be the most attractive thing about me?
Well, you
told me you were cute, so I'm
going to marry you just for that.
[Laughs] That's
good.
[Laughs] I'm
talking about sexiness.
After all, in
2022, I
've told my juniors that I want to get along with them, and now that they've chosen things like fish and rummy, the
villagers are
starting to like them even
more. [Music] But it's probably going to perish.  It's not like it's a bath
or anything like that,
so it's a little expensive,
but let me tell you,
Sakamoto is not being treated that well.
Since I'm talking about a lover, it's
a little different for me this time because I'm getting married, but I
also have a potential lover.Rose-
senpai is tired of marriage sumo, and I
feel like she's really mature, even though she's with me and the overflowing adult milk.  Well, I
guess I'll use a flower straw or drink some juice here.Yes, I want to marry her,
and I
have a lover.Yes,
I was thinking that you would choose me a little more just now,
Lunar.  I was
wondering if you were going to show up when you mentioned your favorite type. Well, it's
not like today, right? There
was no
misunderstanding. I felt sorry for that person. I
felt sorry for that person.  But I
love it. It's funny.
By the way, this
was just a coincidence, but it
seems like there's only one player who wasn't selected. It's
impossible for him to do that.
It's impossible, it's impossible, it's impossible, I don't know about getting married or anything like that.
[Music] See you
next year. I'm just going to
ask that person to choose me.
Please be prepared.
[Laughs] I hope you
do.
Yes, I think so, but that's it
. It's almost time for this corner to
end.
Since it's an illustrated book, I
'm going to keep talking about whether I really like it or not, but who are you all?
What do you think? It
was fun to be able to do whatever I wanted.
Hey
[Music] It
felt like an unusual group of members had come together.
But instead of telling a lot of serious stories, we decided to make some strange and mysterious stories.
[Music]  ] Is
n't there something you'd like to ask about? It
's only next year now, but
[Music]
I'm going to play overtime and I'm going to play with that particular member next year because I'd
like to get along especially well with them.
Well, you're probably going to shake it anyway,
because you've really stepped on Ramy.
Well, I'm sure you'll listen to that fish after all. Do you
want to get along?
Me
[Music] You don't
have to be a member of this place.
Well then, I'm going to talk privately at that
live.
Wow, last time we collaborated, it
was Prea-senpai who I really wanted to talk to.
[Music] We
talked behind the scenes, but
Sakamoto took up too much time.  I didn't know if it was
okay or not, so I got
really scared to reply, and I
kept thinking too much about whether it's okay or if I'm not pushing myself too hard at this time, or if I'm not tired,
but
next year I'll try to talk to her more.  If you're
thinking about going, go and
watch it with your senior student.Let's
ask him about
it.Well, well, well, I guess it's the
money from Gorileba that we did together once today.
Yay!
[Music] I don't
know what to do. Well, next year I want to get along even better. I don't really want to do that,
but I'm
thinking of choosing from the members that are already here, so I
think I'll drink more.
[Laughs]  ]
There are times when we do things together at live shows, but even more so when it comes to alcohol, I feel like I've
split my stomach open like this.
[Music]
Please release me.
[Music] I
want to get along with everyone, but yeah,
if you're talking about this as a whole live show, it's a little bit. Last year, I
said I wanted to do a little collaboration, but in the end, the plan
ended up being played first. A polka.
Ah, let's
do it. Let's get along. That's my
current face. Well, polka.
Behind the scenes, I feel like I want to do that kind of collaboration.That
sense of distance has gotten smaller, but I
still think I'd like to do a collaboration.Neon
Lunaka
Where did Luna's bond go? It's
here. I mean,
it's there, and I want it to be there.
[Music]
[Laughter]
All of them have some sort of connection to each other,
Ramy-san.  But I don't have any at all here. I
have 0 bonds.
For some reason, I thought I was with someone, but
I didn't.
I'm just saying I'm not happy. No, no, actually, I've been saying no to it behind the scenes. So I'm glad. Talk [Laughs] Yes, so that's okay.  I've
talked to a lot of you,
and I think I'm feeling a lot
better now. I think I'll be able to go into the new year feeling a lot better.
But what do you think?
[Laughter]
Did you all have fun?
[Applause] That
means we've got 2022 left.  However,
with only a few days left, it's finally
New Year's Eve, so the
production countdown live is about to
begin, so we'll be singing
songs that have become a hot topic this year.  There
will be a live performance with combinations that you don't usually see, so
please enjoy it.And
after the new year, there will be a special video and the unveiling of Sora-senpai's kimono
costume, so don't miss it.And don't miss it
tomorrow, January 1st.  From 7pm onwards, we'll
be broadcasting the ``All Humanity Rabbit Plan'' on Hololive's official channel. It
looks like our
seniors will be going wild, so be sure to check it out as well.  That
's all for the full story. Hey, everyone. Please enjoy the
Hololive production countdown live that follows.
With that, we'll say goodbye for now.
Everyone, let's go. Everyone can say yes. Let's go. Everyone, finally.
Ah
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[clap]
[music]