[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
it's me
Chihuahua
the best
Chef in the world
static word
[Music]
I got a knife it's a kitchen knife don't
worry it's just ketchup it's just
ketchup
[Music]
wow I love this track oh my god I've
been humming it in the waiting screen
the whole time
[Music]
um
we have to stop this otherwise I can't
talk I can't talk
good morning everybody and we're gonna
play cooking simulator it's the first
time I'm playing this surprisingly even
though I'm all about the cooking but you
know cooking I didn't need a cooking
simulator because I was doing real
cooking streams
up until now
um
yeah but you know
real cooking streams are a bit stressful
so perhaps a cooking simulator will be
less stressful again
mama mama
yeah yeah yeah yeah
hello I am a little bit uh I'm trying my
best to be a high energy but
I feel like I literally just crawled out
of bed in reality it was like
50 40 50 minutes ago
and I had a Loki breakfast
um but I'm still feeling very tired
[Music]
uh
foreign
[Music]
I mean I'm not gonna blame it on that
entirely but I was up late watching
videos
about
the Lord of the Rings worlds and all
that about Luffy and with her Hound
[Laughter]
and about the blue Wizards and all that
kind of stuff
uh and I I would have watched more if it
wasn't already so late
um
hahaha
you know tonight YouTube
[Music]
Rings yeah and another Channel yeah yeah
yeah
guys
a certain someone actually two people
but one one person's video specifically
they wrote to me on Twitter hey you
should you should watch this video and
then do
food
dude
ah
kind of
all right let's get into this cooking
game and cook a little bit and later
we'll place them OverWatch on mummy's
Channel
uh how do you how do we play this career
mode and then there's other modes to
that
um
okay but we obviously go for the career
mode right the ultimate cooking
challenge prove yourself by single
Handley turning a lousy no Star Diner
into a luxury five-star restaurant
what's the problem with Dinosaurs
sometimes you just want to have a diner
kind of food and and that's fine it
doesn't always have to be
why do we always have to Aspire for like
the most
expensive and highest ranking thing you
can imagine why can't we just settle for
something normal that people can
actually afford ah I feel it actually
philosophical Phoenix test your skills
again this time as orders and pressure
pile up I don't like pressure
if in the diner anyone gives me a [\h__\h]
about my about their order being laid I
can say [\h__\h] you
I never want to see your face again in
this Diner and and I'm I'm I don't give
a [\h__\h] about you know those complaints
in the diner huh
much better use perks and skills to cut
corners
ah and jump start your career by
mastering new recipes just remember keep
calm and click on relax mode enabled yes
yes I don't I want to chill
oh oh there's two choices
modern and classic a modern looks really
cool
but we should go for classic right and
we have tutorial even but the other one
doesn't have a tutorial
oh okay
I'll play with tutorial let's go
let's go let's go
chef
chef kiwawa
your modern is too fancy that's not a
diner kind of kitchen this is also too
big for a diner I would say
welcome to the cooking simulator as
you've already noticed the restaurant
you're now employed in does not have the
greatest rating
your task is to restore it to its former
glory and reach the highest level of
prestige the last Chef left the kitchen
covered in sticky notes
huh what why maybe there'll be of some
ah oh oh
I thought the chef was covered in sticky
notes
[Laughter]
he left the kitchen cabinets ah I mean
the last Chef left the kitchen Cup this
could mean both things
this could mean Dolphins okay
okay
what is the kitchen thingy it looks so
[\h__\h] up before we start for important
things you need to know in case you get
lost how would I get lost
first of all button binding hints are
always displayed in the bottom right
corner of the screen
ah during this tutorial you can view
your task in the bottom left corner of
the string screen for this tutorials out
of Safe between stages
are these broken oh they are that's why
it looks like this it looks like the
last one I lost this place on the story
State yeah what the [\h__\h]
this
call some professionals where's the
phone
um
[Music]
it shows me a path oh phone pickup
what a mess we need to get that gas
cooker running as soon as possible all
right all right all right follow the
market take the phone with you okay
oh my God it will take ages to repair
that thing we'd better hire someone
that's fast while hovering over the
cooker use just like a company oh God
what oh
oh [\h__\h]
but when I Let Go it froze it
what are these controls
what
okay just go with fast service here
uh try not to go bankrupt okay
good advice try not to be bankrupt yeah
okay are they fixing it right now no
one's here though
oh okay okay okay
repair ovens oh I have to do the same
thing with the other things okay okay
I'll take phone uh I'll take phone
this one's almost done
okay can I use the same service
wonderful oh okay
okay by the way is this game gonna
eventually play music because I watched
a little bit a little bit of someone
else's stream and it seems like the game
was playing music but is it just not
playing music now
oh five series
huh
money money
okay put the phone away okay okay
okay use the radio okay
this place is empty we're going to do
something about empty wait what first
things first where's the where's the
radio is this the radio
cute radio
ah oh you like jazz
open the shop
[Music]
select utensils Tab and buy a blender
oh you can buy utensils there's only one
thing
[Music]
that would blender where you can carry
it with only one thing out of ten that's
ridiculous I have two hands why can't I
oh wait even with two hands I can
usually carry even more things than two
things uh where where do I put it I just
I guess I'll put it here it'll be faster
if you move the Box hover over it and
press e to pick it up and put it down
okay because so
why are you so stressed lady
uh can you only throw things in this
game
is there no way what did she say
oh there you go what what wait wait wait
wait wait what did they want they
probably want a pan right
yes okay
okay and then why you can only throw
things how am I supposed I tried to be a
professional here
what
monomo
okay back tray big pot
uh big pot I
oh my God really
point at the surface and what
big Trey
[Music]
yeah maybe my ah put down oh
cutting board
who am I supposed to make this joke
about now
pot
okay
ah we need a two ah
knife and spatula okay it was all in
here wonderful
and we'll just all have it in the middle
here so we can find it easily
the last but not least the kitchen knife
we need a good one yeah oh oh can I put
it into that knife block no
you can wow
go to the laptop okay
oh
wow oh click on the recipe manager in
the left side hi uh click on the not own
tab to open the recipe shop aha
yeah whoa
buy a recipe for baked Trap by clicking
the highlighter button oh
hmm fish
all right
okay how do I buy here
huh did I buy it like I guess I bought
it
some mistake with boiled potatoes why
are you a fish again what the [\h__\h] we
need to make chicken chicken is the only
way to success
okay oh oh there you go I bought it that
should be good for now okay so we're
literally a fish restaurant now because
we don't serve anything else
and to shop you in here
salt okay why this is Kitchen not
already have salt what the [\h__\h]
once we're open there's not going to be
much time for shopping Best Buy uh all
the needs but okay
we do need these
we need cayenne pepper Dill uh-huh
yes yes guys I was surprised you guys to
know
um
uh cucumber salad with dill it's really
well known here
in Germany too I think
what we opened what oh no no
and on Twitter when I talked about this
salad everyone was like what a dill
cucumber salad what was that it's really
good it fits so perfectly
um
you guys should try it as oh
a recipe for that
we're sure all right
no not pickle no cucumber are you not
listening enter shot Bill buy a list of
liquids
have oh finally some good [\h__\h]
chicken that looks like orange juice
okay sour cream
should I perhaps put that in the fridge
uh uh open
oh
aha
and then uh can I like place it properly
no
not wonderful okay
although sour cream yeah should be in
the fridge
let's see how well you do yours I want
you to serve me a big trap
help me at the end of the Rachel just as
a regular guest would generally you'll
have some help I have a I've asked a
friend of mine to guide you for the
person okay
now in order to ditch every time a
client ordered something you'll be
notified in the upper left corner of the
screen notifications we'll go to work
okay
I want to play this in VR at some point
but for now we just start like this
hello at the end already
[Music]
wait it was a different face saying the
same thing is it a bug
uh where's the marked area here okay
what
I'm still saying the same thing
why is she still talking to me mind that
each product costs money you don't have
to worry about supplies but you still
need to watch your okay okay a trout
right this one
put a trout on The Cutting Board cutting
board cutting board okay now now now
Gordon's talking to me
the recipe calls for black pepper Dylan
fine five Grammy you should pick up a
spicycle to Target the fish and press
left Mouse okay
uh black pepper let's start with black
pepper five wrap mama I know it's five
gram
maybe if it turns into 205
no wait wait wait
nothing like yeah
huh
now it says bring Grandma on The Cutting
Board
wait what change amount to five grams
oh I'm confused
says what what's on the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] what
what how much was the Trap originally
huh
oh [\h__\h] well now it's definitely too
much what
Ah that's a peppery peppery uh trout
oh
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] did I get 24 Grandma to try
this 40 grams oh no well okay we're
learning we're still learning
okay five five
change amount to five gram if I do that
then I'll definitely not have more than
five gram right
what I don't know I don't know is that
okay is that okay I I I I I I don't
understand the way they show this to me
I don't get it
it's five time every time I click okay
okay okay okay okay so click once and
then try to spread it nicely okay change
to five gram
and then
really can I not get more than five
grand no matter how long I make it flow
I don't understand
did I no I did not put 51 Gram on there
I did that but it says
[Music]
it's per Shake
oh what can I get a new trial or should
we just continue with this whatever
that's a spicy trout man
okay but so far this game is not
difficult
until things start falling down
complete okay turn the oven on
how do I know how long and so on oh nine
seconds one two three drive here from
six seven ah nine teen F 12 Jackson
Satan sipton
nonsense
transition
fancy six months fancy
nine on twenty three six one four pieces
okay
[Music]
wait 90 seconds is so [\h__\h] long uh
infinity
[Music]
it looks so it looks pretty dark though
we good
[\h__\h]
thank you
again
oh there's a timer oh yeah this thing
whatever
I should have stuck to my accounting uh
one two three four five up buy a plate
I'm busy counting man also there's
plates down here what do you want oh
basically well we should have maybe we
bought the look it's telling me to buy
the basic plate right okay okay okay
Place
another one
more
[Music]
no no no no no no but now it says put
trout on I think the trout is done
congratulations
how do we know it's done
oh
you're not tutorialing me properly I
don't understand
I think he still wants me
oh I can't touch it oh oven
mittenden.com where's the kfp oven
Mitten
[Music]
um
oh no it will take another
a thousand years for it to arrive at
everyone's place I might want to buy an
oven Mitten Gordon
where's another button
[Music]
ah
is he done that no
really do I really need this many plates
I needed Force like four or four or four
pieces of lemon so I would assume
maximum four
what
oh
[Music]
okay well you have to split that
information up into two because it feels
like you keep on telling me to buy a
[\h__\h] place
foreign
[Music]
why would you put horseradish on the
fish horse and fish don't go well
five gram
five grams
[\h__\h]
that was two shakes
but that looked like it only added two
gram
I know
yeah wonderful this is about right so it
says it says six grand perfect wonderful
I don't trust
ah I don't trust
system here all right it's done ah pick
up the lemon quarters all right okay
okay
wait how many how many how many
four on one plate
laughs
what that's a whole [\h__\h] lemon
what the [\h__\h] are we trying to make it
look like it's potatoes because we were
too lazy to make potatoes
what we need potatoes for the fish
parsley all right
three times
okay what parsley yeah yeah yeah that
looks beautiful beautiful
foreign
[Music]
huh
huh it says
parts now it's even 8 gram what the [\h__\h]
does this dude want from me
huh
I'll have to hold it what what
well whoever gets this fish gets a lot
of like extra stuff with it no I don't
want a photo
okay
[Music]
and if they complain I don't want to
hear anything about it what
oh it tastes so good
realization time no bad overall score
now bad oh my fame is rising he did pick
and he even left a [\h__\h] tip
kiwala don't trust him what the game
tells you to do trust in me wow
[Music]
let's make some chicken after you tell
you'll be presented with a summary of
the progress the restroom okay okay okay
okay okay
oh ah we lost money have you bought so
many [\h__\h] plates too
[Music]
well maybe it's at some point it will
come in handy Maybe
um
[Music]
uh automatic level up okay choose a perk
freeze items oh
that's a magic one that removes all
stains what
all right
what should I do
oh there's a lot of useful stuff
maybe what do you guys think is
important unbreakable plates
there are your mittens oh
oh in my hands oh okay okay okay
but wouldn't there be a normal actual
Mitten somewhere too
uh either the plates I guess you guys
serve plates or steady hands okay okay
let's go for the plates for now
oh oh oh oh level up uh-huh
oh [\h__\h]
I didn't realize I had something
selected okay
it's coupon's mobile too oh I can still
get more
cooking points from surf dishes
[Music]
whatever don't care I don't care
um chain four plus star dishes
liquids cost less products cost less
here let's go for this one
less cost okay day two baby
food
why do I only have three lights here I I
should be owning four all right let's do
this what's my first order
what's my first order
and we call the preparation phase the
name should tell the story no orders yet
but you can use anything in the kitchen
to prepare for the day
oh now I'm prepared my phone's done
what are you using you're gonna Head
Start I mean I guess
if we get at least two
I'll use laptop okay if you're gonna use
two orders then we'll probably be making
this route again so maybe I want to cut
the lemon again I don't know
uh open skill manager app okay
skills provide you with a small gameplay
bonuses if you didn't spend your smoke
points yesterday oh I did though
some skills become available once our
restaurant gains enough Fame you can
choose to save up SPS and use this app
later okay shut up now please
okay shut up shut up shut up I don't
care
okay next up next next hack on to the uh
perks
already own perks and um okay yeah yeah
yeah yeah boring boring
thank you thank you I'm done I'm done
bye bye oh
yay
Gordon what's up what you might still
need me today no no not in particular
sounds mistake with both potatoes okay
first time I'm making that pick up big
pot okay okay big pot big pot big pot
out there there
okay I got it
pour in water
water in the pot
oh
okay
wait how much one liter
why is it separate why is the water
separate oh wait ah okay
I'm adding that oh [\h__\h] that's too much
it's about right
probably no big difference add salt to
it
okay
[Music]
unfortunately it's not the chicken salt
that bay gave me
20 grams
um
one
two
three four
but it just said there's only 10 gram
inside
I know it's probably fun
the the task says it's fine buy two
potato okay why did I not buy that
yesterday huh
okay while holding the pot
[Music]
potato potato
you guys said the game told me I can
only hold one thing at a time so I'm
doing it like this there we go
I'm down in the marked area all right I
don't like to cook with a
stuff like this
[Music]
I don't like it no
scary
[Music]
we should have more than one cutting
board though well I guess as long as we
work with
uh fish only
it's fine
okay you're way too loud when I get to
this place can you be Liza
more quiet place she's in the salt five
gram
season
salt salt salt
okay okay you can turn yourself on again
just don't be so loud so loud
Scott Jazz I never really understood
what Scott means and five grams
oh ah five grams
I have five gram black pepper I'm not
even listening to what he's saying
anymore I don't need him
oh fine okay okay I can count now
you you prefer it without bgm but then
it's so awkwardly quiet
oh we didn't even turn this thing on yet
is that okay
sunflower oil is that the best oil for a
fish
I never cook a fish to be honest uh till
the bottle oh
oh one more
wait don't have oil on the gas I think
that's a problem I think that might be a
problem I don't know how serious this
game is
foreign
now then it's kind of your fault
[Music]
right I'm scared
oh it's fine
it's fine
how many seconds one two three four five
six sixty right seven eight nine ten uh
[Music]
oh no
how do you start ah [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] one
two three four five two seven eight nine
ten uh fifteen sixteen Seventeen
eighteen nineteen uh 20 21 22
23 24
the green progress bar okay when it's
full I'm done
okay okay
it's not exactly 60 Seconds
what about the potato though yeah they
didn't tell me to turn on the potatoes I
can do both at the same time man
[Music]
it's amazing me oh wait I think we're
done are we done
oh
you tell me that now
it was before
flip it flip it slip it flip it oh dear
how to
don't know what
rotate
[Music]
why is this so awkward
one two three four
five six seven
[Music]
you know what I I I until until this day
I still respect my mom big time for
being able to flip things with the pants
like pancakes for example I can't do
that I'm way too scared that I'm not
only scared I would legit like have it
fall out of the frying pan
yeah I don't know how to flip things
without the help of a utensil
um
flying fan
very impressive yeah
okay I think basically done
let's see it says perfectly five grand
five gram wow wow wow okay we're done I
think
that
let me turn this off okay
uh fry uh why is it telling me to still
fry it it's done
huh
why is it back all the way there now
wasn't it done
bagu
order it's gonna
it's gonna burn
oh okay now it's telling me to pick it
up all right you're kind of [\h__\h] late
man
you [\h__\h] Lane
uh hold plate okay okay okay oh oh that
side looks really good still I'm about
to turn that off
okay complete what about the potatoes
dude
God Ramsay
hello you completely forgot about the
potatoes I'm just gonna cook them
I never said that but the game never
told me to start them
God Ramsey mosh
where are you he has forsaken me goddess
forsaken me [\h__\h] you God bless it [\h__\h]
you I don't need you anyway I'm my God
God kiwawa
yeah
tutorial but oh oh no no
no no no more
um
[Laughter]
the potatoes
should have done it beforehand
I know it
I know we shouldn't have waited for God
Rams to tell us what what happened I
heard like a
oh
did you find the radio like bathtub
sounds
okay
but this is gonna be cold do they have
like a salamander
we call it salamanda in in German I I we
used to work in a kitchen for a while so
I know about it something that keeps the
plate hot
but according to this I think I'm still
supposed to yeah yeah it's so hot I
guess so the the frying pan icon means
it's still hot
why don't you call it in English
I don't know why it's called that
I don't know why
call the same in English really
[Music]
um
a hot plate yeah oh so now you're
talking to me about the potatoes what
dude
he however completely ignored the
existence until now do we not want to
learn
[Music]
parsley what if I freestyle
is it okay to do some freestyle
like I wanna I wanna take some parsley
and chop it up and with some butter
um fry the fry the potatoes in some
butter not really fry them but you know
oh let me
can I chop The Parsley here with
freestyling
don't know
how's this is the parsley being cut I
don't think it's being cut Young
I won't let me cut it
okay okay can I still yeah they're gonna
complain if I put some parsley on it
like just you know we need some visuals
this is like
let's serve something prettier looking
than that
[Music]
how do you know
I lost the parsley no
it's still there
are they gonna complain I wonder
what are they gonna say oh
no no particular complaints it seems
see my parsley is the reason for a whole
extra star probably bye parsley see I
have real talent and I'm I'm a natural I
think he just doesn't want to say he was
trying to manipulate me by not telling
me about the potatoes
yeah
he's manipulating me he doesn't want a a
chef like me in this world oh I should
probably turn this off pick a big pot
okay
700 milliliters of chicken broth oh oh
wait isn't a
all right hey
we don't make it with powder this kind
of seems wrong to me
700 milliliters okay
okay I can do this I can do this
700 damn okay let it all in whoa whoa oh
careful now we don't want to Spill and
waste too much
okay
that's normal really I have a little jar
what you don't make it with powder
oh sure okay reset Put it Down Season
the breath according to recipe okay okay
unless they videos I don't want to use
actual tomatoes or tomato powder thingy
soup powder
salt and pepper 12 gram each okay this
could be the first time I make tomato
soup from scratch
what what is that super chat
ah 12 gram 12 gram okay round one
two
one two okay
Lisa
come on
[Music]
one two
one two okay perfect beautiful I'm such
a chef
that's why I'm wearing my my little
Chef's hats today against some people
want me to believe that it's not a chef
hat but a uh you know that that thing
you handle a chicken with and I say no
no it's a chef hat
it's a chef hat but believe me trust me
bro
you know
foreign
[Music]
it's ignoring my did I miss the plot
why is it ignoring the fact that I put
Love Camera soft and 12 gram of black
pepper in there
that exactly like that oh
I I did it though
I'm so confused
now it accepts
all right did it I did 100 I did the
right amount I swear
okay
[Music]
there you go okay well now it's 24 gram
each
don't trust this game ever once again
Gordon does not want a better Chef than
himself in this world so he's
trying to mix everything up
buy a Tomatoes okay uh one uh can we do
it while holding the pot
[Music]
where did the tomato go
why one two three four five six seven
eight
okay
there it is there it is
three second rule I saw it in less than
three seconds uh ago so that applies one
onion oh
we're not actually just gonna throw it
in there are we oh
like at least in like like in in fourths
or so I
younger than this stupid ass game
ah
PLS no no it's already peeled I would
say but what about cutting off the ends
ill disgusting
this game is worse at cooking than me
but I can't believe other whole life
members struggled with this game
ah
hold up I might regret saying this later
boil soup okay
[Music]
this is ridiculous
okay and when it gets a little bit
softer I guess that's when I start
um
mixing it
purifying it into puree puree purify it
purified
it's not all you really say brother Chef
Boyardee oh thank you who is you
somebody from my daughter yeah yeah I
love the party pomodoro foreign
I'm better than you you know that right
and now you're trying to kiss my ass
I guess you're supposed to kiss the chef
right there was a saying like that
ah yeah there's a lot of Joker cards
today
hey can I start yeah why is it not
boiling yet okay
is it falling hello
hello I'm bored
I'm bored
born
yeah yeah yeah yeah right
[Music]
that's so unhygienic you really
shouldn't be kissing the chef it's
really unhygienic like for the chef you
know you might not care about the chef
might care
yeah
it's not joking comes to clearly all
real yeah
can I can I hello is the game just once
again not telling me anything because
it's trying to troll me what if I just
I guess I mean I see it
can I make it hotter is it only on and
off in this game
and once we doesn't want me to blend it
it's not telling me though all right
I'll do it oh yeah
uh move down move up okay
[Laughter]
oh but I think it's done why does it
look so watery
so watery
I learned I learned from my mom how to
do this
this is not exactly how to do it though
I think I think the soup is now a soup
but it still wants me to boil it oh okay
maybe now it will actually start boiling
um
but it does with all with all those
Tomatoes I shouldn't be able to see
through the liquid like that you know
what I mean I'm just just so good cookie
crushes cake
I'm way above this [\h__\h]
it's now on my level this game is not on
my level
you know nothing about cooking and the
game I think it's broken like it's it's
not doing anything hello
hello
[Music]
let's turn it on again maybe I need to
reset it
oh
huh
wouldn't this also you know have like a
green bar like the like the salmon hand
but nothing's happening
[Music]
okay pick it up place it again
it's honestly it's like this game is so
booked what the [\h__\h] it's not my fault
I'm like expecting it to work better
than this but yeah not my fault
mother members
[Music]
it's so Jackie yeah
no in real life it's not like this
in real life when I turn on this stuff
stuff it works there might not be a
green bar but I don't need a [\h__\h]
green bar oh no she's from
[Music]
ah faster I have no patience you wasted
already like 10 minutes of my life at
least this game this game owes me some
lifetime
when I ever
when I ever lie in my dying bed which
will never happen because I'm Phoenix
and I will just revive again but then I
I will call up this company who made
this game and I'll say yo you owe me 10
minutes what are we gonna do like I'm
I'm dying right now and I feel like I
feel like I should have had 10 more
minutes man
do something about it
[Music]
it's happening though it's fine it's
fine no no no no no the knob next to it
you know where the dots are here there's
that one means top that one means bottom
that one meets bottom that one means top
and so on yeah your first time in the
kitchen huh
why would I use those extra 10 minutes
on
um watch you some Netflix probably
[Music]
okay
you clearly haven't done your cleaning
properly
hey don't blame me that was the previous
chance of anything okay we're done with
the soup I boiled it game hello
spoiled
it's boiled
[Music]
I mean I didn't see any bubbles but the
green bar is I can't taste it
oh
maybe we need some more salt
ah
oh
can I just
be done with this I need that I need
that I'm just gonna I'm just gonna wing
it I need um well you know a bowl is not
really elegant enough we need a deep
plate yeah can I buy one thank you ah
just come first up again
so this is do you do it the same way oh
yeah oh no oh no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no we
ain't doing it like that no
no no no no uh I need a I need a tool I
need a utensil
I need um a light Ladle Ladle ladle
50 milliliter
oh my mom would be so proud of me right
now like I'm doing my own thing I don't
need someone to tell me how to do [\h__\h]
whoa
you told me to do that but I don't need
the game's help should we add one more I
mean usually in restaurants the soups
are really
really minimal
they only give you a small amount of
free 300 yo that's a lot okay we're done
with that
[Music]
soup is finished
uh hello
maybe if they need an under plate
oh what the
nah
I'm probably parsley possible yeah I'm
gonna do some more in the hopes that it
will eventually tell me we're done
parsley
Style
[Music]
how's it going there huh
yeah we passed
what size boil a little soup yeah
this [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] that I don't need a
I don't need a tutorial
[Music]
this seems appropriate for a
professional chef like me
oh hopefully there's no bugs here
[Music]
so do we still need to buy things oh no
we have we have knives
I don't know how to use this fingernail
um
uh do I just get like the recipes
randomly out of nowhere or is this
preparation time where I'm like supposed
to buy plates
oh no I have this place oh
there's no guests
in this in this mode there's all
there's is there another mode that I
should use
oh I don't want people to order [\h__\h]
which one would be like good for me
or maybe career mode but without the
tutorial
okay we'll go to the new kitchen
area
all right all right all right whoa
oh
my
gorgeous
oh
interesting clock
wow oh whoa this is too fancy oh
all right uh
where are my orders
do I have recipes okay I still have
these ones that I bought before can I
like Buy
more more interesting things fruit salad
yum yum yum yum yum
but I guess the problem if I get more is
there anything with chicken
duck bro with duck slices
I'm I think
Grill my sausage with egg
egg
what egg is a side like that
uh okay oh here chicken left chicken leg
with Capri salad what
[Music]
what see what are these recipes
simple chicken pumpkin stew
I thought that
okay you know what I can actually see
that being a kind of a good combination
um there's no love in these recipes
there's no love here
German potato salad oh hamburger
oh that will only order the things that
I am able to offer right for sealing
with Neapolitan sauce that sounds
interesting
ah we're gonna
we're gonna get ourselves
and
something with chicken
um coffee season steak
okay I guess I'll go with
oh we'll go with this ah I can't buy it
okay never mind
I need something cheap or I guess I need
to cook a bit more well then where where
am I where are my orders
skip prep oh oh it's four minutes
inspiration face okay I mean
we could try to make use of it we could
try to get a acquainted with what we
have we have oh is that like a
that shape of a grill pan I I guess I
use for like
omelets
that's the only
thing I know it for for Japanese style
um
[Music]
where is all the things
where are all the things where's the
fridge
[Music]
okay let's bring let's bring these
things in this area
that will probably help and now we need
to find the radio I think I saw it
radio okay
[Music]
nice piano
I can play piano like this this is my a
recording of me playing piano you don't
believe it well [\h__\h] you
you saw me cooking better than the game
so you must believe that I can play
better piano than the game
[Music]
everything needs to be in order on it
pick it up
there we go some sun sunflower oil yes
okay
um perhaps oh but
I have to buy them where are the ones
that I bought I guess that's like a
different save now so I have to buy them
really
other things that was like
saved like the ingredients that I have
in the recipes that I have
oh I don't know which plates they need
though plate basic
[Music]
Ally okay okay okay okay okay I'm
careful I'm careful hi okay so we need
the plate we always will need a plate
and for soup I mean we never got to
finish the soups I don't know if that's
really what they want from me but I will
take a deep play because I think that's
the best way to serve a soup in a
restaurant
hmm
Gordon Gordon what's up Gordon I'm sorry
my recipe is so Financial make sure it
has Tomatoes paper on the floor just
what what is that supposed to mean
what's that what's that supposed to mean
huh
oh nobody saw such a thing okay I think
you're you're talking you're missing the
point here you're absolutely missing the
point that's not the point the point is
that you you'll even forget about the
potatoes you know I had to boil them on
my own you don't even realize that the
the soup was totally overcooked I had to
stop that on my own I'm adding parsley
because your recipes look like absolute
[\h__\h] yeah yeah and you don't even let me
cut the past said what about the
potatoes without butter what or anything
unseries and potatoes
unbelievable
tickles you should be fired you should
be never be allowed in the kitchen ever
again yeah yeah
ah okay let's start it let's get started
I don't need this extra time
three two one
[Music]
I where is where is my order new order
trout with lemon over there
um
oh yeah okay okay I I don't need Gordon
in my life
I'll do this on my own let's see if I
remember how to do things
oh yeah uh
will you tell me the honor
what about what won't it show me the
recipe
oh I can look here I guess I can there
was something to pin it right but oh
well I have five grand black pepper five
until easy
is it uh fun
you'll see it honky does
you'll see how serious I am one
it says under one gram no
we'll just add a little bit extra
I think Grand there you go I told you
it's more than more than I thought
um
bill I think they were supposed to be
Dylan there
hand holding time is over they remember
in my hand to begin with to be honest
yeah [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] the recipe
what did it say do fine and salt or
black pepper okay okay
hi hi
what now
Place some baking tray bake for 90
seconds see them with horseradish
afterwards okay place on a bacon drink
well bacon tray speaking tray
okay
I'm speed running this
Place
uh 90 in here right I think
well it's so fancy so dark
it's right tonight wait will it not tell
me the sun there's no green bar
ooh sheesh
sex Stephen act nine
scene
F12 writes in
Phoenix
[Music]
hello
foreign
[Music]
parsley
um
[Music]
game is blocked again there's no
puzzling
do I need to buy it
foreign
wait I just get one like this
really all right okay
um
probably done
right
one two three four
five
six
seven eight nine ten about one person
lately that's so unrealistic oh
huh
the the Red Bar does that mean it's
already over
oh I was counting though the seconds in
this game are wrong whatever
it's fun it's fine
it's fine at least you don't get the
salmon disease
uh always about it's always radish how
much was that
wait can I just look at this one here
let's write this five gram okay
nice radish on Swedish
this music gives me the vibe that we're
in the Wild West
I
I'll give you a bit more yeah that's
enough probably horseradish is on there
why does it say oh
I'm pouring five grams
oh wait no okay okay there's 17 gram of
horseradish on
on the plate it's one gram this is so
stupid
so stupid
game I think it's finished
I think I didn't check
um I should have maybe checked on my top
I don't think it's finished
I think this was it all right those are
yeah
it's a problem
I put your perfect big trout
too much Pepper too much
that's what that's that's what I was
thinking anyway but the game forced me
to do such things so okay it's okay we
got money and we got
we got them and return it it's all good
okay
I know how to do this
um
chicken broth
chicken broth uh like but like last time
we made way too much for one order is it
really okay to make so much I feel like
it's kind of wasteful
uh well okay we'll do it according to
recipe
700 milliliter chicken broth but where's
the Pot
do I need to buy the pot as well oh no
here it is
big pot
and
don't do it
[Music]
oh wait let's go 700.
big soup big soup baby
gigantic gigantic gigant gigantic guy
again chocolate
gigantic soup that's the right way to
say it
okay that's about it
I forget sad salt
12 black pepper 12 cayenne pepper okay
let's start with salt and black pepper
salt and black pepper yeah 12 12. okay
okay this time I will do it according to
what I think I'm doing
and one and two
and one and two High Twelve should be
fine
um
salt
here there you go
[Music]
okay
a one and two and one and two after this
six cayenne pepper
and then tomatoes and onions okay
cayenne pepper here we go
oh is it Cheyenne
that's right one and two right
okay and then we need
uh what it's not saying how many
tomatoes it says 960 gram Tomatoes
well I'm assuming
it's again wait maybe it will tell me
though how much gram I'm adding oh wait
that was not white and tomatoes are
tomatoes are here
ah 120 gram per tomato uh it's Final
Fantasy
480.
600 grams
and one more is this
two people five
times 120
is oh God help me guys
okay I mean I got pretty far on my own
and then it was one one onion right
[Music]
120 grams yeah yeah okay what 960 Grand
Tomatoes I I kind of um lost that
information Somewhere In My Head boil
for 60 seconds
on Lansing oh I prefer these ones way
more thank God okay well where's the
where's the where's the blender
it's the hand blender oh there it is
okay
60 seconds uh
how do I
well yeah yeah these ones oh no no okay
this one is this one is for Dad and this
one is for that one okay okay one two
three oh look at the green
I don't have to count I guess
[Music]
I don't think I have to count
er no
[Music]
no
um
time is on my side
I decide when it's done
a chef
[\h__\h] timer
they know when something's done
yeah no no rely on these kind of
techniques no no no no no no no no
no no no no
it seems to be working yeah
oh
can we should we Blended after the 60
seconds or is it okay to do it now
I wonder
the tomato and onion are boiled now so
I'll I'm gonna start
hi hi
okay
okay done
what does it say now okay it's still
cooking okay
Google what's after that
sour cream okay
quick
ly
hi
how's it how's it going oh we're still
we're still there do I add it afterwards
okay but still in the pot but I'd
probably turn off the the heat then okay
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
[Laughter]
yeah yeah somebody recognized that even
though I didn't do it on purpose foreign
wait how much the whole thing
150 how much is the one I have
we'll see
uh
oh
okay wait that soup is way too like
skin flesh colored what the [\h__\h]
huh
so why is it not completely green now
though the bar
I think it's done though
I'll surf on a d plate and told you I
told you
uh it would be nice to have a ladle
again I'm a professional after all
hey yo
I don't know if I can save it without a
serve it without a label
[Music]
how
foreign
I can pour the pot into it must cook
first
let's say it's already cooked okay let's
cook it too
until it's really full now I guess I
guess it wants to cook it again because
the sour cream made it cold again
but now it should be fine all right
let's see
oh God
[Music]
is
oh no oh no
oh dear
no no no no [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] no
no I want I want I want I want I want to
wait
until
wait a little little
yeah wonderful
bye
oh okay and then once
hey
hey did I estimated they would want last
time but no one ever acknowledged that
also the soup kind of looked different
why is it so bright
you oh [\h__\h] why
why did I do I was like so intoxicated
by the ugliness of my soup
uh
now I kind of uh
can I pour it a little bit
I need a smaller Ladle now
I need to swallow now
two times would have been perfect I knew
that I knew that oh well well well well
all right that one's perfect that one's
perfect okay
uh what about parsley we're not adding
parsley you for real man
I'm I'm gonna add parsley
you know that they're a little extra is
really what your customers will
appreciate in my opinion
yes
what kind of name is
oh you can't see it it's
ah it's drowning oh well enjoy yeah
little Razzle Dazzle
it doesn't look like the picture it
it doesn't look like the picture but it
seems perfect I got full points
I don't know
I appreciate the firstly I wanted though
but
I mean but this is a good thing right
oh
you cannot turn down my parsley wherever
you want it or not you'll be eating
parsley I don't give a [\h__\h] except the
parsley next order please
wow I'm almost next time I'm ready
are we done for the day or
22 for a tomato soup yeah let's pray
yeah bye
it's good oh we're done
feeling face
how do I clean
so what's your daughter doesn't know
clean
oh can I clean oh oh oh oh oh Where do I
I'm gonna put that
can I hurt myself I wonder
let's put it in the bucket I guess
one by one
oh here's a mop
but only for the floor what about on the
top
was this by the way
propane gas
the gas in a gas in a bucket
ninja was analyze
um I I want my kitchen
to be a safe place
for everyone
except for
except for Gordon Ramsay all right I
guess you know let's clean a little bit
wow oh
[Music]
YouTube
yeah I am having fun I can totally
imagine me working alone in my
restaurant at the end of the day and
it's so bright outside it was a lovely
day I feel accomplished and all the
customers were happy
you know I did a good job today so with
the jazzy music I'm just like cleaning
my kitchen really Speedy in a good mood
yeah baby
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
yeah
he's running
normally mopping the floor is really
exhausting in my opinion but
okay
all right
I'm done with the cleaning
oh oh my god oh [\h__\h] the gas that's not
good
put it back properly there you go hi
I think I kind of want to leave these
things like this partially but okay
let's put this back into the fridge
[Music]
I was like here on it can I
these ones you can't place for some
reason not properly at least um can I
can I hang my ladles up maybe here oh
wonderful
also can I can I eat some of that
what am I gonna do with that
can I warm it up on the following day
maybe
[Music]
this one those are still 90 milliliters
inside okay
let's save it we want to save money
oh
[Music]
why can't I only throw it
okay that's good that's decent enough
[Music]
done right on time
I lost some money but that's because I
have to buy ladles and plates and [\h__\h]
it's fun
[Music]
unbreakable Unbreakable
mm-hmm
cooking coins there you go just get all
of these
two
okay hopefully I get more challenged on
day two because I felt so ridiculously
unchallenged so far
okay I'm throwing things on the floor
and all that what's going on man
oh
being on the time pressure and all that
where does when does the time pressure
start hmm
wow why is it so easy for me
is
what I do with this by the way if they
order soup today do I make fresh one
maybe I should have put it into the
fridge
what how do I know it's so fresh is
there like a
is there a is there something that will
tell me it's off
we might kept breaking it after
finishing right after finishing
I haven't seen another person take the
game as seriously as me
ah okay let's buy a new recipe all right
all right all right
don't I need like points for that
I have oh
let's see
oh I can't buy stuff maybe no no I can't
I'm like missing somewhere a little bit
more points
I have like the the Stars I have
yeah can I can I buy it with just the
Stars
let's say we want um fried shrimp
how
no I don't think I can
no I can't I need a bit more maybe the
burger the burger no
it just gets more expensive okay maybe
on day three because we we're so close
oh
it you're telling me what was that a
meme what are you saying you're telling
me
in my rank they say my rank is too low
but honestly they're just holding my
potential back they're holding back my
potential
skin
let's go let's go let's surf something
give me give me give me give me give me
some mistake
[Music]
oh there's oh there's no stuff on The
Cutting Board oh well
um why is there when I hear a [\h__\h]
timer
who turned on the timer
it's a part of the music
[Music]
five grand salt black pepper five gram
okay
uh salt
assault the salmon with some salt
assaulting
it with some pepper now
hey okay
do you like jazz Oh see it was part of
the music because it's disappearing now
ah add to the pan sunflower oil 10
millimeter a millimeter 10 milliliter
okay okay pan pan pan
pun
okay
and where is the sunflower oil
ah here
gotta do everything by myself man
okay okay
[Music]
and then we add salmon and then we'll do
it for how long I wonder each side 60 oh
do we have do we have this thing yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes well just have to be
ready okay we'll leave it there that's
fine oh
Satan
how do I how do I get rid of this
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] I need another for the potatoes
okay so there's a there's a small part
here that probably could be enough for
potatoes
tomato soup
oh it has to be a bin
so yeah
[Music]
anyway anyway
have time we have time we have time for
that later
one two three four five six seven yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
how wait I don't know I forgot how
I'm in I
think what happened
do we need more oil I suppose there's no
more oil in there
[\h__\h] well now we're talking
now we're talking baby some difficulty
[Music]
maybe maybe I can just put it up yeah
okay
tomato
oh
beautiful how do I get rid of this snow
I wonder how
um what about the potatoes we need to
get rid of this soup
[Laughter]
oh it's empty now okay okay it's empty
yeah
I don't know if that's really supposed
to be the
the bucket for that but you know
um
put that though but one second let me
let me focus on this for a second
although
water did they show oh wait okay we
can't just put it there I think we're
done in three two one
I
okay okay
[Music]
uh water a thousand salt 20 potato 300
okay
[Music]
just the right amount
hi oh
salt 20.
I got it I got it leave it to me you'll
get the best potatoes ever
ah
I did not sneeze into the pot believe me
trust me bro uh potato uh
two potatoes this year
that's okay
[Music]
thank you
I'm gonna turn that [\h__\h] on let's go
let's go
and the plate
when do I have those plates
[Music]
where will the plates be on the phone
when I do and then try not get them back
no but they said something about like
plate returns right
past them
[Music]
and I did salt the potato while the
asses
[Music]
um
a return window oh
[Music]
I can't open it
do I have to buy a new one that's
ridiculous
that's ridiculous what that makes no
sense
why do I have to pay for that
oh no
how's the potatoes doing and why why
[\h__\h] why did it fall down
[Music]
nobody saw that it was under three
seconds
and that's just because the game is
janky
[Music]
um
almost done with the potatoes
Floor season
hahaha
no no rage no just happiness I mean look
outside
isn't this beautiful how could you be
raging
you'll literally see nothing but
buildings wow beautiful actually that's
that's really depressing where's the
nature where's the nature
potato
oh they're too hot no worries I just
need to do it like this but I don't see
the other one
I don't see the other one
oh
that why
why
oh
[Music]
why is it so so sensitive
all right just take it
I think that was it
okay okay
they don't suspect a thing
hahaha
you answer me
how'd they want the trout okay that's so
basic
let's go for the the shrimp this one
seems pretty easy
oh yeah oh no
wait I can't get them anyway that's okay
um
I have 13 points
why can I not get the steak
how do I
honest
how do I actually get something
that I should have enough things for the
steak
don't what do you mean you'd want fame
star
oh
Oh I thought I have 24 of those oh okay
but we're like we're like almost there
okay then let's let's get
why is he telling me though uh he wants
me to get this thing for example
oh
do I have to I want to save up for the
steak or so all right
all right trap time
again
I will notice by heart at some point
honestly probably
will all right
[Music]
uh five pepper five five five bills five
pepper five five five bills pepper
[Music]
five
number five
[Music]
five
and five Dill
right shift uh
[Music]
play some baking tray and bake for 90
seconds and then put horseradish on it
afterwards all right
[Music]
oh it's still in here okay okay
it's foreign what do you mean what what
uh okay that's weird but it's fine it's
fine I
go
[Music]
the fish is ascending
on
um
horseradish and then trying to okay we
can do the lemon now
lemon
cut it into four slices honestly I think
one would suffice like it looks stupid
the way they're putting like four slices
on there it looks like they want you to
think of it as a side which makes no
sense whatsoever
okay beautiful though very beautiful
Sasuke Wawa
yeah yeah
and in the end they want the parts at
least they're asking for the parsley
good taste
how long is 90 seconds
[\h__\h]
oh
my goofy lemons
I'll eat a whole lemonade
see there's another random cool book
comments
pray for cold man
please please try to stay on topic
um my dear Kobo viewers
uh I really want to know about the
cleaning like how do I I can clean the
oh I got an achievement I can clean the
floor but what about this this
and that
hmm
I'm gonna clean the surfaces do I have
to buy like a sponge
bucket camera
sponge oh
sponge
SpongeBob Club SpongeBob
that was not my intention SpongeBob
[Music]
how do I clean
oh oh
that is satisfying that's like the the
cleaning cleaning simulator
oh
what about this spot is that uncleanable
all right all right we're cleaning
everything that was
uh looking disgusting thank you sponge
that's a good sponge
I'm so proud of you how's it going in
here
oh
uh plates plate plate I need to buy a
new plate apparently
cool good timing though that was I had
that in my in my feeling I felt it I
felt it
don't don't mess it up we need a
horseradish on it now I think
yeah five grams and then put the lemon
and then we're done baby
where's radish
[Music]
I understand though
and I hold it and I put these on right I
one two three and four and oh parsley
right parsley parsley have to buy one
little snippet of parsley oh wait it
wasn't here here
there you go why why do I have to buy it
like this
[Music]
last time we had a plant
kill us
okay wow that looks good decent decent
oh marvelous Magnifique oh
Bellissimo
oh my God okay with for oh wow the taste
I started missing but I take that as a
full full percentage oh and I think 32
out of 30 I think we're getting a Fame
point
yeah oh
perfect perfect wow wow wow wow wow wow
clean the kitchen already done with that
kind of but all right what what could we
clean we could get rid of this big pot
thingy
but is this really
is this really the only way to get rid
of this stuff on it it must be a
different way
[Music]
s
it didn't work in here before
afro
[Music]
or maybe oh oh okay okay
easy easy
uh this one can we clean that too
okay I'm cleaning it I don't know if the
game considers this cleaning
I'm trying
hey
I rinsed it I rinsed it if anything I
rinsed it
[Music]
okay
beautiful beautiful it's quite relaxing
right now actually
[Music]
one Rings perfectly clean I got a
problem
huh
okay yeah I'm done skip
whoa we're Fame oh
oh
one more one more one more
oh we didn't
[Music]
oh level up do decoration
chills skills all right all right all
right
um
experience points perhaps
you earn more well yeah more more Fame
more Fame okay
subscribers do I really need more Fame
as a chef I would say I've got more than
enough okay okay let's go with this one
pork chops
pork chops with baked potatoes okay okay
I I think there's a lot of color missing
here and there's you need some parsley
there obviously and maybe like a sauce
because those potatoes look hella dry to
me but all right
why how do I get this recipe
or did they give it to me
ah there you go okay
well
it's more parsley
it's dropped parsley yeah
we start using four tabs let's go
I'm ready
the mystery to me is still the plates
though because it says plates are
returned
and maybe when they say return it means
that they're also returning like the
cost for the plate so I just continue
buying new plates
[Music]
okay we'll probably need a basic plate
at least
we'll probably needs
I mean whatever we don't use today we'll
still be there the next day right
okay I'll leave it like this for no for
now for now for now
um we'll probably need
a pot but not the small one the big one
is there all right no I'm ready and then
let's just get
Let's Get It Started let's get it
started in here let's get it started oh
oh my job all right let's learn how to
make pork chops
take pork chops 200 grams are they even
in here or
they are
okay
[Music]
I got the pork chop wow
looks like a mighty fine pork chop oh I
should have washed that oh I'm mixing
I'm mixing fish
I'm washed fish cutting board I don't
know if the game is taking that
seriously I hope not
four grams salt 4 gram black pepper
mama
inspection day I want extra flavor yeah
okay that's five grams I said four gram
didn't it
yeah that's okay
I don't like this music because it makes
me think there's a timer on
okay
fine
six
okay
hi
ah wait I need one more
I have to be really excited because that
one gram they're they'll totally taste
the difference right totally
uh sample oil 40 milliliter okay and
though the pan is over here because we
washed it look it looks clean it looks
clean
I wonder if we can buy a dishwasher
how much was it keep on forgetting
and up
wonderful
90 seconds and transfer the plate this
is too easy at the same time we could
probably
probably not those but wait I don't know
how much water you want
on it
wait are we not even cooking them I
wonder
oh they're only being baked not cooked
okay
um
all right
hi
let's go take potato 300 grams season of
salt six
uh 300 I can only carry one though okay
so it's two potatoes
um I'll just I'll just put the potato
here
oh
foreign
yes big cheese Studio they are coming
peeled to me very nice
uh six salts
salting something
I'm not doing it on there now on the
on the pink because I feel like it's
it's too dirty I feel like the the
kitchen counter is cleaner
Hot Potato into chunks ah wait a second
how is this one doing oh it's so fine oh
wait let me let me clean it let me clean
wait can I clean this too with the
sponge
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
[Laughter]
how about now
I think
I think that did the tricky
okay how's it swing oh they're done
they're done they're done they're done
done
I need to flip it
I guess so that makes sense oh each side
oh okay okay
[Music]
fine with me I am I can do anything I'm
about to give up thank you
I not like I need your luck but I am I'm
fine
okay
rotate flip
[Music]
flip chill relax relax everybody
uh
where is it
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
uh
no that's not fair
that's not fair I went to Brazil
[Music]
I can open this one but not this one
whoa mostly most can I go
oh can I go inside hello give me my boy
it's the shadow realm no
yeah
oh no [\h__\h] that finally annoys me yeah
why is this game so junky why is it so
jacket
I'm losing money
[\h__\h] out what was it
what
salt pepper fine
fine
I'll do it again
no that really sucks
I'm gonna do anything to deserve them
um what was the other thing
I forgot
it's so sad
oh black pepper
Connor is
to me
does does it still need some oil
probably right I feel like it's so the
previous boats have soaked up all the
oil probably
foreign
[Music]
I'll never forget you
my beautiful little
pork chop
my little pop champ or whatever that was
[Music]
[Laughter]
a little pork chop
no
uh let's see if we can do the other
thing a seasonal salt cut potato into
chunks I seasoned them already so
like how many chunks
50 gram what do you mean it's still
gonna
um it's still gonna weigh the same what
do you mean
or so that every chunk is 50 grams
I don't care about it I'm just gonna cut
it like however the [\h__\h] I wanna cut it
all right I'm done
uh
I'm so done with this [\h__\h] transplant to
baking tray all right
um
[Music]
seven and nine ten
hi hi
how long is that
80 Seconds okay and then we're done with
this [\h__\h] and now what do we do about
you little [\h__\h]
I swear to God if it happens again then
I'm I'm quitting the game
I didn't want to play too long anyway
no my one-sided pork chop
okay okay okay stop it for now stop just
for now and now how do we not mess this
up
um take this
okay
[Applause]
oh
what an accomplishment
[Laughter]
oh
easy
successfully flip
we're gonna lose money but we're gonna
ignore that because I don't think it's
fair like I'm with picking up on the
floor if I could
it's ridiculous maybe it's maybe it's
here
no that would have been
too good to be true if only if only it
bucked through the whole counter that
would have been nice how is it going
over here oh you're looking good oh
they're done I
done oh
need potato holy [\h__\h] these are taking
up so much time oh I should be done by
now and make us [\h__\h] super so
wait it's 120 is there such a thing as
adding too much potatoes on here I guess
it's really
wait why did it take foreign potatoes
if it actually only wants 50 gram of the
potatoes
tomatoes
I'm confused
because it doesn't even fit all on the
plate
50 gram per chunk do I really want like
all of it okay okay okay
well I don't think it's 50 gram per
chunk but oh well
and this and go
ah don't join your brother
[Music]
plate is too small
okay okay
wow I was already here
what well
what
[Laughter]
I swear to God
I can't even pick these up anymore
what
no no
no
no I guess this is the charm of
Simulator games isn't it there's [\h__\h]
I can't pick them up why
oh [\h__\h] okay
oh God
[\h__\h]
I I can't
foreign
[Music]
no I still can't pick it up what do you
mean what
what this one's okay I can't pick it up
like this because it's too hot but like
oh
what what
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
[Music]
okay see this works why does the why
does it not work with the pork chop
can't believe it
you shouldn't die in vain like your
brother
okay
okay it's operation pork chop
s
[Laughter]
hmm
what
ah
uh
[Music]
foreign
explode
[Music]
let's vlog
can you actually make it explode
[Laughter]
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] this stupid ass
place [\h__\h] all of it
hate it absolutely hate it
I hate it
thanks I hate it
so that was a waste of money
I lost my Pock champ what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] man
I think I was too good of a chef for
this game I was just the game did not
know how to handle
me
right obviously ridiculous
needs a person
[Music]
it was handicapping me yeah I cannot
unleash my full true potential here in
this game
is it only me where it bugs out so much
or is it is this game just really buggy
with other people too
I've experienced like at least 10 bugs
today
huh yeah I'm not the only one that's how
the game is okay hmm
I expected more than that well that's
that's unfortunate that's so sad what
the [\h__\h] why
what
that's that's why people struggle okay I
understand now
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
oh God
is it always so like this on VR because
I I saw after buying it normally that uh
there's a VR version that's I think even
more expensive than the original version
and and I feel like if it's also buggy
then no I'm not gonna like what I'm not
gonna buy it twice
for even more bugs yeah okay it's it's
less buggy
huh
I did better than others well because
I'm I'm the boss of kfp of course I did
better
it was it would be uh more fun but I
guess than the scuff if there's no scuff
is it still fun if it's so not if it's
not scuffy
oh well no no no no I saw Ahmed playing
a different kind of cooking game in VR I
want to play that one
that one seemed not buggy and fun and
stressful
so if I'm gonna play one then I'm gonna
play that one all right well at least I
finally I finally was able to experience
uh the cooking simulator I don't I think
that's the first time I played the
Simulator game besides Sims 4
[Laughter]
you know what I mean
that's the first time
[Music]
I don't remember playing on it
other one
you guys remember one I think this is
the first one
generally I just
I see I see the other girls playing them
but I just don't feel the I don't know
what is it the urge
to play those games like the the the
cleaning one that everybody plays with
the with the different
types of nozzles and whatever
that yeah that doesn't appeal to me at
all
you're a truck simulator okay that's
maybe a different story probably a power
washer yeah
but okay like a like a truck simulator
I can still get that into my head
but power wash I I don't feel any
interest in it
the Earth simulator face simulator was
also a thing like okay that is
interesting to me maybe maybe that has
potential Maybe
I feel like
I feel like at some point there will be
a VR simulation and another YouTuber
YouTuber simulation game
maybe there already is that
there's a YouTuber simulation game
[Music]
YouTubers life
um
[Music]
rocks no wait there's a rock simulator
Rock simulator is good what are you
talking about no way need a girl need a
girl that's not she's not a beach but
she's a streamer
of course it's out of my Graphics so we
maybe think of her as a YouTuber but no
no in her world this is the same the
same argument I wanted to say about
um that new Pokemon trainer girl she's
not a YouTuber just because she's anime
she lives in a world where everything is
Anime so in that sense she's just a
normal streamer you know what I mean
foreign
new Pokemon cute by the way frog it's
frog
um [\h__\h] cute
frog big belly I found the the scene's
so cute where you have to like switch
garage clean the belly
oh that was cute
yeah
cute all right I'll read a few super
chats
uh thanks for watching guys
[Music]
and then actually afterwards I have to
record some things
urgently
[Music]
um
yeah just rings of power in this stream
apparently
I think so yeah
okay okay okay actually
um Eden Exile made me a new version of
this background but I I haven't gotten
to look at it yet so please excuse me it
will take a bit
what is this
I'm on whole lyzer and I saw some
interesting stream from
them by two it's some voice acting or
something for like some kind of game
what a type of mystery maybe it's not a
game
whole life Mystery Theater what is that
what is all of that
uh
[Music]
I didn't even notice this time because
it's so natural it just comes so
naturally
hahaha
it's clearly senpai
that's helping at this point like I'm I
I I can't I can't even try
else
wise what
[Music]
let's
read these super chats from the ones
along
this watch along got me into
a rabbit hole of information
yo I'm I'm if I don't if I don't the
building at least I'm gonna listen to an
audiobook that's for sure
yeah I'm I'm so fascinated also all of
us in the watch along we weren't pretty
sure at the end that that was Gandalf
but then I I watched a a review of the
last episode and it's it's it made me
question it too like that might not be
Gandalf after all
um because in the rings of power in an
episode at the end he said they're going
east right and Gandalf however said he
will never go east right
and yeah legally I guess as well that's
a good argument too
so it might not be kind of even though
he was set I think they might be doing
that on purpose they want people to
think it's kind of so that people get
hyped up and talk about it and then
watch next season
but then surprise next season are gonna
reveal oh it's actually not Gandalf
[Music]
they just want people to think that way
now
it's just a random wizard probably
[Music]
or or yeah I mean they could be going he
might say in the future that he's not
gonna go east because he went East
before and experienced it to be [\h__\h]
didn't like it but according to history
Gandalf never went East in the first
place like in his whole life right
I don't know
I don't know but yeah this this dude
made the theory in the video
that um it might be a blue wizard
yeah there's there's two blue Wizards
that are not spoken about much in the
books at all
but they do go east that's the thing
the one thing we know about them is they
do go east oh here we go we're nerding
out about Lord of the Rings
we're from around that blend there's two
blue Wizards that go east to try to hold
back
um them from
uh making the army they have too big
yeah
[Music]
and they actually more or less are
successful with that
[Music]
yeah there's not much not much
explanation on them either so I guess
they have a lot of freedom can do
whatever they want with the blue Wizards
foreign
[Music]
now all my Korean Bros coming in
what's going on I'm young
um
foreign
[Music]
why you suddenly caused because I saw
Korean comments in a row saying hello to
me you're huge e why you suddenly call
me
[Music]
the culprit I saw you guys being like
hello kiwawa oh I just say hello back to
you
[Music]
all right let's read some super chats
thank you soon
for the pinky I'm so glad we're watching
this oh
the Lord of the Rings and Hobbit watch
lungs were special loved them however
this series ends I hope for spin-off of
elrond dropping in on the durian family
and stops Steinfeld sitcom
[Laughter]
I would watch a show for 10 seasons
yeah well so far in season one The
interactions with elrond and the durian
family had very much the potential to be
exactly that
hmm
yeah yeah we need more during an hour
and I'm sure we'll get more of that next
season I don't know when to expect next
season no I hope I hope sometime at the
end of next year
[Music]
Lord of the Rings
I'm production right now wonderful
wonderful wonderful okay well I I really
hope for them like I I'm fine more or
less with how this season was but for
the sake of you know their success I
hope they take all the criticism to
Heart
and do a better job at season two like
it's not like
it's not like I have a big problem with
season one but there's so many other
people did
so yeah after that [\h__\h] storm of reviews
I would hope they improve it then hmm
first season was in protection 10 years
I I would think they speed it up now
though
[Music]
for real though
the things they made now is partially I
think a lot of things can be like reused
right like like armor they created and
backgrounds they created and all that
I'm not sure some stuff can be
like reused so it doesn't take 10 years
again that would be ridiculous
[Music]
anyway thank you so let's keep playing
Patsy thank you
Mr cat's bull
thank you Sharon Mr casberg
happy birthday to me oh
are you here what a surprise to never
stream for me to watch my birthday wow
wow it worked just like last time oh two
years in a row
other people are not so lucky other
people seem to always have me not
streaming on their birthdays
yeah yeah but on the bright side it's
payday today which means I can give
myself more QR merch oh what did you buy
more badges
[Laughter]
almost forgot Hamilton hello
[Music]
thank you Gino that was yesterday but I
hope you had a wonderful birthday
congratulations
thank you so much for supporting me I
hope you have
um all your dreams come true yeah yeah
um
my birthday is on the whole talk
anniversary oh my god oh
that will be good
spending time with family Ah that's fine
that's fine anyway happy birthday
Chihuahua merch yeah Genie that gives
you an athlete
and not a good username donation
explains before you love me
if I had to explain House of dragons
season one like I did with a rings of
power I'm not sure if I could do such a
big good job because honestly I'm really
confused
the show is doing a great job at
confusing me by changing all the actors
every [\h__\h] episode
I can try
I can try when the time comes and I I
don't know we might I guess we can watch
the last episode together I'm just
a little bit worried about awkward
scenes I don't want to watch Awkward
scenes together with you guys because it
will be awkward
I'll think about it if you guys wanna
launch it together
I think about it yeah the time skips are
confusing
um
there's so many like uh the names like I
can't the only one I remember is Allison
and renera but then the thing is also
they're repeating the names
[Music]
like uh viserys is I think the King
right but then now they also have a
child that's called viserys I think
right and they have a dragon I think
that's called viserys Baby
[Music]
at least one child is called aegon
uh
there's Damon Damon yeah
there was renera and Reyna's reynus or
Renee is or so is that the the
sister of the king no
yes
or the cousin or
she wants she she
could have been the queen but they
didn't want her that's what I'm talking
about rain is yeah okay
and oh God I don't I don't even wanna no
no names if I if I am gonna explain the
season to you guys it will have no names
I'll just name everybody
something else
I'll give them original names
and they'll work much better surely
Damon Damon Dame aegon oh my God
foreign
my kindness
[Music]
no
chicken chicken
[Music]
so this guy messed with this guy and
this guy is mad at this guy because
because he he hits this kid
blah blah blah
ah
Helena
Evans and Helena
I was actually really confused in the
last uh House of the Dragon episode
about
uh the no I don't I can't even explain
what I'm confused you know when you're
so confused about something you don't
even know how to question it
because you're that confused
zank is amazing Simulator games
finalists your series Gun simulator
games like flying oh
I mean
I mean completely not being like the
second time I did it
talks one time bugging and disappearing
okay I can I can ignore that
what's up bro
and then right when I was ready to serve
it
no
and
Darren who the [\h__\h] is they run I'll
remember day run
[Music]
television is the bigger plane
um maybe maybe but I should have also
been able to pick up the
[Music]
oh great thanks Chad yeah I thought so I
thought so something's wrong there
[Music]
[\h__\h] you for spoilering me what the [\h__\h]
why why do you even know that
is it in the books I guess so ah
[Music]
because I don't know it yet
why would you do that
[Music]
foreign
apologize use your room use your room
offer interviews what
my point of views
to like deep knowledge I only want to
know what's in the show sorry okay
usual room one week
[Music]
not your little portion yeah you're not
my little pork chop
pork chop
nice don't don't gang up on him but
um yes
yes where was I
uh oh yeah the game
uh
[Music]
I'm a huge Falcon fan so I think this
show is pure trash but seeing how
excited you are to watch something I
truly hate makes me excited to watch you
it's like hanging out with a normal
friend
okay
I don't know what that means
I'm glad you had some fun though
Cruise decision type in Duncan
kitchen unit
uh
all the Wizards have the same power
level as Sauron when it comes to
hierarchy of being all our mayor yeah
yeah I learned more about that
um later on in the videos
um sour run
is an interesting
dude
I learned that he had like a
a boss that he looked up to
yeah yeah and then the boss was captured
and then Sauron wasn't hiding for
hundreds and hundreds of years morgoth
yeah and then we have finally in some in
some War he knew for sure Morgan was
dead and then yeah blue blah blah blah
blah you're like an Oshi yeah yeah it
was literally his Oshi the guy who made
Powers oh I didn't know that he made
bell rocks oh
I also know that that Sauron turned into
a vampire before and he turned into
werewolves and blee blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah
[Music]
interesting interesting
oh dark wizard yeah yeah morgue morgov
is a God
oh
okay confusion too many I I was it was
too much information at once last night
in YouTube
I I got the rough rough knowledge of
things now
at least
[Music]
balrogs are minor too
fate of luminar
um I yeah I kind of I think I know but I
already kind of forgot so it's okay but
I think I understand what this whole
show will be about roughly
but that's only if they actually follow
the lore and we can't be sure that
that's what's going to happen right
[Music]
yeah but the new manure plays a big role
I suppose yeah I already forgot actually
yeah
[Music]
yeah you get spoiled but you forget so
that's really the ideal situation
yeah hello
[Music]
foreign
I am not a German YouTuber
go check that German YouTuber Phoenix
girl on on her Channel this is this is
not me I'm not her no I don't know what
you're talking about I'm an English
YouTuber
[Music]
I'm Australian yeah yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh wait it's not the whole title I
thought I bought the whole time but
that's the offer okay cost me or that's
the title
cosmere
[Music]
whoa
wait that's just the universe what's the
book called How many books 12 full
novels
you guys know this one
stuff is good sounds lame I'm sorry
I mean if a book is called Brandon
Sanders sanderson's cosmere that sounds
lame to me
okay
[Music]
I might look into it but first I I have
to get
into reading the Lord of the Rings books
first of all and then maybe maybe then
um uh you know ice and fire fire and ice
or whatever and then and then and then
I'm gonna read
um what's it called again the other show
I was watching that gets a new season in
November apparently uh real time Wheel
of Time
so these are free things I have to read
book club I'm trying I don't know what's
hard
to book because I kind of like there's
books I want to read right now but those
are like big big like commitments and
serious
but maybe I mean we can maybe read one
of those anyway and then if someone like
wants to continue reading they can go on
but we won't do the whole book series in
the book I'm not you know you know you
know you know what I mean
but I want to start off with something
that really interests me
Fellowship would be good for a book club
Fellowship
wait is that one of the free books um
what
it's not the first one
[Music]
Hobbit Hobbies a hobbit is like baby
talk
[Music]
that's the first one hmm
that's a difficult read I think
Stormlight Saga
okay okay okay chillax everybody I'm
gonna
make a tweet
did I not tweet this already before I
feel like I did but maybe I didn't
I'm gonna make a tweet and ask for
yeah I did this but I feel like I did it
before
did it happen in a dream
I feel like I tweeted out that I'm
looking for a book that is more or less
well known
easy to read and preferably fantasy
[Music]
I feel like I wrote it before
oh okay winter
interesting interesting interesting
interesting
interesting interesting interesting in
the Bible
oh yeah
let's write the Bible
[Music]
yeah would you I heard that um even a
game of the movie was shipped but the
book is good
Maybe
is it one book or is it several books
[Music]
seven oh my God
all right but that's actually it sounds
interesting yeah yeah all right anyway
and where was I
what was I
uh
[Music]
um
Galadriel is married to an elf named
Jello born
you see him in fellowship and she messes
him in the show celebrorn is cinderen
one of the elf languages for silver and
Tall if you translated it to the related
language quenia it becomes rather
unfortunately named teleporno
[Music]
laughs
that is unfortunate
[Music]
celebrities
man
this is way too friendly is this really
you is this a faker my favorite planet
to watch along is I love spending time
with someone passionate about her Elvis
like the other pants and the other day
high tide oh
man alone
this doesn't quite sound like you
were you intoxicated
[Music]
is that really not you
what is the slander it's even with the
profile picture like upside down
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
and broke six thousand dungeon thank you
oh thank you
every night for the pinky sorry for
mentioning your bad taste but I honestly
think the show is made not but not bad
at least
okay
[Music]
okay that's that's okay that's fine
that's okay I
foreign
about this show
I am worried
how could I ever live up to your
expectations guys
[Music]
better than the show
for example
[Music]
you know what I mean
[\h__\h] I ever live up to your
expectations when your expectations are
so high
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
Kai Jewel fighter donation for the pinky
never had the chance to watch Lord of
the Rings watch along his own since I
didn't know you at the time but this was
very enjoyable to watch with you
stream and sharing your love and
anything related to talking Sports good
or bad thank you yeah I think it was fun
to watch together
[Music]
thank you for watching together casual
fighter yeah and that's [\h__\h]
on it
[Music]
maybe maybe we can watch the finale of
season two together as well probably
will take a long time till we get there
though
Rosa for us thank you for the pinky why
am I so cute no matter what I or anyone
else thinks about the actual show don't
worry yourself to enjoy
[Music]
bye
I guess you guys judge shows and girls
very differently huh
you're very strict with
TV shows and whatever entertainment
but I'm I'm like a TV show I am a live
stream
[Music]
you're not so critical of me then
hmm
I mean I I don't see a lot of critical
people about me as well every now and
then or all the time I guess never mind
you guys are very critical of me too I
can never
listen
[Music]
okay anyway low thank you soon
that's actually like a legit
finger like
it's impossible for me to be perfect
but that's just how it is I guess
let me do is I just Slice of Life anime
yeah I like Slice of Life anime
mood whiplash
I can't I can't lose time here
we're all human you're perfect to me ah
you never will but I will still love you
[Music]
gonna have to be perfect for us to love
you
big
you still have to learn you'll strike to
me so I'll be strict to you you guys
still have to learn things
[Music]
saying I am perfect
why like what
[Music]
what's wonderful saying by the way right
now
having good to say so not commenting at
all probably
[Music]
I was being nice
haven't seen you being nice
I'm scrolling oh there we go perfect in
your own way I guess heart oh
[Music]
you must be red like a tomato right now
feeling embarrassed about having to be
true to your feelings
[Music]
foreign
you you couldn't have possibly written
that Super Chat while being active in
the actual chat
yeah yeah yeah that's probably really
not you but hey you should you should be
happy with it they're helping you
improve your reputation
you should appreciate it to be honest
they're doing a good job at being nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's an imposter
ah
[Music]
onda
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
using happy chat as we speak
foreign
[Music]
for coming by last night thank you
Mommy
what's positive of course
[Music]
oh stretch oh I'm not laughing about her
having the sea thing I hope she gets
better
soon
a couple fans is so funny
[Music]
just I saw someone clips that uh when I
was talking about cobles fans someone
clipped it I saw that
I'm going through when I gave up to go
to school cause depression and wanted to
die I could I could be smile because
your stream now I'm preparing me too
because I want to make spots on unhappy
people as you did give me pet please
[Music]
yeah but you're back to going to school
now huh because you should not be
um you know
replacing school with v tubing
that's not good
okay
continue school you can do both at the
same time it can be like your hobby
or like pocket money perhaps
hmm but if you went back to school then
I'm very proud of you
very proud
education is important see I I maybe
I I I had a complicated
uh education
[Music]
um
what's the word
route whatever as well but that was not
because of retailing
and in the end I I did background
history history yeah I did in the
unfinish something
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
that's so Random
couldn't be going to school now School
Long now
um
well you know it's hard for me to give
advice
for such a serious
thing but
especially since the culture there is
very very different
and I don't know I don't even know how
old you are but if you're like in high
school then
you should you should
should finish high school that's
important
[Music]
um
I also in Japan I hear about that a lot
that like
uh
you know a lot of young
people I knew I had a friend myself
and a girl who was also a streamer but
this is a long long long long long time
ago
uh she had a sister too
and uh their mother did not even like
say anything about it they did not go to
school at all like for months
it was interesting though they did not
get kicked out of school
that confuses me it's probably because I
guess it's like a private school more or
less where you have to pay
like
tuition I guess this isn't all of
Japanese schools you always have to pay
there's no free schools I guess maybe
but yeah they both of them both of the
kids one was actually a junior high and
the other one was high school and they
just would never go to school and just
stream all day
and I don't think that's the right thing
to do
um
like yeah there's so many kids there I
feel like because
I can't get very toxic there perhaps
um
I don't know man why
maybe maybe because there is no
[Music]
um
consequence to not going to school if
they don't kick you out
and you still somehow managed to
graduate I guess
it does not really motivate you to go
after all if you still somehow are able
to make it
because like here here that would not
work in Austria this would not work if
you don't go to school for two weeks
without even an excuse
put on getting kicked out okay two weeks
maybe so okay but one month oh no
oh no
foreign
[Music]
well if you went to a doctor is that all
he said can we not you should be able to
get some help
[Music]
but be away yes
definitely not the only option that all
right you just won't go to school at all
anymore what about homeschooling
what about homeschooling
at home
oh well I wish you good luck though
and fighter fighter
never give up okay
you're gonna regret it many years later
if you just give up
oh yeah online classes too probably
that's the thing too
[Music]
y'all go walk around there
let me finish this oh wait I already
finished it haha
[Music]
super jets
from today
I read after GTA
yes thank you
[Music]
yeah this is it three hours oh my God
short stream let's go
I have to record something now
[Music]
I don't know that
um
[Music]
shortest stream
this year
could almost be one of my shortest
streams in this whole year
[Music]
um
ado
okay I'll go now so thank you everybody
for watching today I'll see you later
probably on my channel
if I get OverWatch 2 to work
um
outfit rules uh they don't count
[Music]
different
yeah
[Music]
and in Germany
with me
[Music]
let's go I'm excited
I'm excited I'll see you there guys
be there or be square or meet this knife
[Music]
tomorrow's kiwawa will be the last time
you see chihuahua for a while
[Music]
because then
someone else will take over this
endlessly spinning froggy wow wow
finally take over
I saw it
in a
in one of those sauron's eyes yeah yeah
yeah scary future very scary terrifying
future awaits us oh no foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]