foreign
[Music]
and welcome to the first
birthday full collaboration but now we
have Council so it's the first almost
full collaboration of Halloween
oh
my God
we have the Discord support today and
hopefully also the viewers support today
because uh today will be a very very
passionate and dangerous and fun and
exciting events
like burning rubber yay exactly and
I may be a bad driver but I'll drive you
guys nuts
I think we shot oh my God some
introductions of each member uh now
let's get back
from Whole Life Indonesia
hello thank you for having me this is
Anya melfisa from Hello life I use
second generation thank you everyone I
can't wait
for me
what's my ikikomi um to not be um the
last last place at least
okay what about
um
generation one so my motivation tonight
is
um to show you my practice I guess
oh
show me what you got yeah
how about raining hi attention please
I'm popular Rainey from whole life ID
generation 2. my goal today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
that last in the days
yeah I've heard you were good you and
Iris have heard good good good news
about you
I had a good practice yesterday right
right yeah
nice thank you for joining
next time bye
hello my name is
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
thank you
surprise to meet my wife
hey what's it what's the motivation for
today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay
we will see we will see we have some
competitions in your heart
the last of someone's heart is that such
a good thing yeah it doesn't sound like
a good thing yeah okay
thank you so much for inviting me to
this collab I'm so happy though I'm so
excited thank you
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
and Ollie Ollie yay zombies
the second generation hi guys
they're my motivation I plan on ranking
pop so that you guys become my bottoms
that is my motivation for today
that is she wants to be on top I don't
know what else I expected from your
motivation
we won't be dominated that easily
sometimes
all the introductions from ID I think I
did
yeah
inside let's start with Iris
oh yeah hiris it's Iris whole life
English project hope V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
[Music]
yeah thank you so much for having me
here so I heard that you waited for yeah
for Rita come on
that was German we were 11 people
thank you
honey yeah
yeah thank you next up how about
um
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in a members
only stream but that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay
I see then you might be the hidden
winning choice that the windows
Dark Horse a wild card player that's
amazing
[Music]
English
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not less
than to be first so I'll do my best
you know also taking this very seriously
in her practice round so I'm a bit
scared of Ina um I don't know
I'm still falling off Maps
oh Kelly joined just nice
introduction from Cal IOP Maury
[Music]
hello everyone my name is Calliope my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning nice
to meet you I'm going to be talking a
bit low because it's a bit early uh so
excuse me for that guys but I'm very
excited just to be here I really didn't
think this was gonna work but it's love
it is
for joining even though it's such an
early time and to kind of uh Troublesome
with some setups and all that I'm glad
you're still here and you know what you
being so whispery and calm might be a
good thing for driving because that way
you might be able to focus more
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard well I'm sorry please well
it was not my fault it's out of my
control right now so anyway I'm PNG
tuber summer does a PNG tuber Let's Race
today baby I'm the wild card today
foreign
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so I think it's fun I'm curious of
course they want to look at me right
guys
[Music]
yes
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today
before that let me say thank you is the
hats and the cards are sponsored by
ninoma inanis yeah
[Applause]
so cute all right let's uh everyone
switch to the rules image please thank
you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however if you
choose uh please do not choose random
courses please choose a certain course
that you want to actually race but if
that course has been used before like if
it has actually been chosen before
please do not choose the same course
again already
understand yeah
number two items are allowed number
three uh we're racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistance online
all right I think I turned it off now
okay
[Music]
wait a second it's if you press Y and
select your character at the point where
you select the card you can press on a
plus the plus button and that's when you
see the the three options on the right
side if you press L
if if there is a if there's a sign that
says no
then it's uh Auto staring off that's how
it's supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the only difference is you can
ignore yeah
okay okay okay
what do you mean
I also want to quickly let you guys know
um I'm on I'm gonna be on like Auto mute
this whole time so unless I have
something to say I'm gonna be muted
don't worry if I'm a little quiet I'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay okay
there's no more rules there's basically
just a system we're doing the first cup
all versus all big mixer four races each
but then we get we mute each other by
the way during the race and just to
focus everyone on what we're driving and
then we get back together and Discord
talk a little bit then we go to the
second cup which is en versus ID six
versus six yes yes
we separate each other in
um The Voice channels by team this one
in this one we will actually talk with
one another if you wanna and then we uh
give some comments together again when
we get all back together in the same
channel and then we do the first cup
with random randomly thrown together
teams no ends ID but like all mixed
together naturally beautiful
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
joins Eva voice chat room zero or voice
chat room one no who's this girl
is everybody wants to be one well done
we're gonna have to do it again and
again
it sounds foolproof perfect
just so you know the the those like team
cups would basically be
um like the same thing
as all versus all the difference is just
basically like if you throw items like
red shells or whatever and there is a
teammate in front of you it will not go
to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent driver
uh that's around you so yeah that's how
that team system works I think yeah
[Applause]
then everyone who's ready mute yourself
on Discord if someone's not ready then I
will ask you why you're not ready
wait guys how do you wait guys uh how do
you go forward in the game
it pushed the a button you can't go yeah
the world right now okay that's what you
mean gotcha all right understood thank
you thanks guys love you okay
hey good morning morning Force Cal is
also great
Indonesia
are you ready no not really
I mean I've been practicing like a few
hours ago with Ollie risu and you know
the um the rest of Hawaii but yeah yeah
halfway
oh my God
[Music]
hey Rainbow Road
okay MP3 sounds okay I mean the switch
sound is it not too big for my voice or
is it okay
okay
that's good okay
okay okay
[Music]
foreign
let me put it
Magica
[Music]
[Applause]
something
[Music]
[Applause]
more happy days
okay wait
ing onions
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah yeah
oh bye
[Music]
um
mama
okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
how to summons
yeah the sound should be fine now
maybe it should be fine
[Music]
oh
excuse me
[Music]
pumpkin
you wanna
foreign
[Music]
how do I explain this to the overseas
because
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or a Mario Kart
Stadium anymore for your collection
thank you I'm going to try and remember
that but I don't know okay yeah yeah
okay this looks like a beach and nothing
that looks like a fancy night life place
right but isn't there multiple Beach
uh yeah there's a cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the DS version
not anymore yeah okay okay okay are we
doing team wait when are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go for all
this result okay
nice hat you know she's muted
we didn't we didn't do a sound chat
before
okay
um
foreign
[Music]
um
I don't know I just keep crashing
I forgot I forgot it was it was
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
remember
don't know
come on
it is
[Music]
foreign
I'm sorry
[Music]
they dry fast especially bike in our
countries Indonesia that they kind of
um
some of them okay some of them is not
all of them but some of them uh it's
kind of
driving Rick rossly like when you
uh when you want to turn left uh like
you don't even turn on the light like
light like you know that light
so yeah they just kind of like
um just drive in their own pace
like in their own place Pace literally
mm-hmm
okay don't don't be like them guys
[Applause]
having the last time
[Music]
I mean yeah sure they drive fast I mean
they are fast but
I oh so one well one time I almost
um I was driving in my car yeah
um I was I was getting to on the
supermarket I think it's an emergency
I always almost
um what's it called again
hit
I almost hit
um
a mother
's riding a bike like they were on the
other entirely on other side of the road
and they just decided to cross the road
without even
um turning on the lights the lights that
light
so yeah
guys I got disconnected
oh
oh hi nickel discounted okay
but I almost I almost hit
um
with my car yes I can drive this one an
alien can drive
so yeah I almost hit him and uh hit her
and then she was kind of like after just
kind of like
um stop for a little bit and saw me and
I was gonna play
I mean do you have anything
um to say to me like it was your fault
you know like you were you were you were
trying to cross
um
the road like just cross cross it you
know you know what I mean
and you almost hit me well well
technically I almost hit you because you
didn't
um uh turn on the light yeah okay but
the disconnection yeah
I'm not
sure like normally it seems like in in
the whole of Japan tournaments they
automatically give the one like well the
like this qualification like last spot
if you uh oh if you are oh wow uh
congratulations oh everyone cannot mute
themselves now oh yeah yeah okay oh yeah
hi guys
I got disconnected but she still went
four or what so yeah
I think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is
so uh let me let me just uh Ina was
number one right number one
congratulations
I I saw you kept on selecting Rainbow
Road
s she cheats I wanna I wanna uh make the
suffering to them uh you know
you know
yeah yeah she practiced on that one a
lot I think that's why
it'll be ready
oh okay someone has to uh yeah wait uh
wait who was that yeah
how did you manage to get number two
today
I I did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah Ina
Senpai was very quick uh yeah but I did
my best I did my best
you weren't me
oh wait me and Elena were third are we
tired
Hollow birdies hold the Third
wait are we complete in the lobby right
now one two three yeah I am in the lobby
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
but Muna Senpai is currently unavailable
but I don't know my my battery is 100
but it's a low battery so I didn't know
which one is low battery oh the ones
that you're like what did I do with that
do you think you were fine to go or you
need some time I I think I think it
should be fine okay sorry we'll make
coffee right now
everyone I don't need coffee go get
yourself a cup
of Milkshakes already
banned from coffee I was actually really
surprised about ama's driving too like I
thought you know because she didn't like
we didn't see her practicing we didn't
see her play the game to begin with um
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
[Music]
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to an idol meetings
are we picking teams I don't think no no
I don't want that because that gives me
no that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that hold on
my Nintendo again
picked last and I don't want that I'm
gonna go up my full power now because
now I'm fighting for the en ladies
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
I'll just warm up now let's never be
warm up yeah
this is good because Iris two of the
strongest ones are in Ian wait me too no
no
hey I've proved that I that I can and
I'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news
is a good asset to have I want her yes
will have to carry uh Indonesia's uh
back yeah
everyone please
splits into teams by I think let's just
um Ian go to a voice Channel 01 thank
you okay oh
and I guess I'll work
okay
guys
like moms here are famous for like their
super Reckless way of driving
Supremacy
the only very dangerous
yeah and very dangerous yes indeed now
yes uh there's a problem with my
Nintendo's actually what should we do
um
[Applause]
okay
um
like I thought uh oh yeah you know
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it closed once okay
yeah
hey baby
are you gonna be okay
oh that happens yeah that happens I
don't understand though that happened
so be careful with that
I think that we actually need to buy
separate uh what is it controller did
you get a controller another Another One
controller yeah controller yeah
um
I was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had no problem mine is good though it
happened to me once
together right yeah yeah
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so yeah
it's it's it's okay now I think okay
wanna
really baby boys
no this
is
whoa
you see hey it's America
outer ring
oh how do I do this
[Music]
foreign
no more bikes
[Music]
ID only thingy like Mario card you know
oh yeah
I think you have to be at least good at
Mario Kart because this kind of
tournament is gonna like happen in the
future
it will happen again
like a new Mario Kart tournament you
know
I kinda I kind of thinking about you oh
my God is again okay oh my God I bought
the wheels for that oh man
but it's not arrived sadly oh
um
it's hard
to be honest
I don't like this stage
I can't see I don't have eyes
where am I supposed to go
it's cool
[Music]
yeah
it's lava but I'm not born
again
what's up
um
who's that
hey cursed Hi how are you
I'm doing good okay somebody just like
stole my items
definitely was not right
somebody has like three shells
it's okay final love guys
yeah
all right
problem in this map yeah we have a
problem too I don't like this one
yeah
I'm I'm lost I'm I'm die
it's okay
let's go
I don't even
at this point I'm already because
[Music]
everyone everybody
I don't know
I have no idea
where are we going what did we choose
again
it doesn't matter
all right let's go to salon oh that's a
second strategy
cheese land we got it
oh my God why did they pick that place
oh my God hey did you remember oh my God
oh my God rainbow because it's so
awesome
please please
[Music]
no I mean
um
cheddar
delicious
mozzarella
oh my God
talking about but yes I like
um
we just like randomly screaming at each
other at this point all right yes yes it
is oh I was late
I don't even know
how do you even do cheese
cheese sadly but I don't know is there
any chocolates
Elena
put your controller okay baby it's okay
it's okay okay it's it's I think it's
okay I I I did hope it's okay though and
I fall okay I thought yeah
oh cheese
let's go inside that was for you
believe me
you know
I just want mushrooms why do I keep
getting like weird slash bad items and
everyone else gets such good items
I don't get items
you guys get items wow
like seriously like seriously
okay
oh I believe I can touch this guy
oh you are an alien so you can't touch
the sky basically
oh yeah I can
nice bananas delicious bananas oh ouch
for everybody oh no there's a Blue
Shield I'm so scared
blue shell is the scariest thing and it
is
yes yes this is bad
oh no I gotta drive honest here um
I'm not liking this I gotta drive honest
here
[Music]
again
oh god oh yeah
this is the game yeah
that's so dirty
yeah I'm so sorry because I feel like ah
I failed you guys I'm so sorry
oh God I had potential
foreign
oh my god let's try popping top five of
all of us
please
okay we got cheese land so uh oh I'm
hacked
okay let's do the airplane stage
okay where is that really you want to do
rainbows wait
um
sunshine
sunshine sunshine
[Music]
oh it's gonna be Rainbow Road isn't it
rainbow road
yeah especially this one this one is
especially hard really okay
that one's easy but this one is uh
what was it the simplest looking one I
like at least I can fly
so I wouldn't drive
there's like shortcuts here and I have I
still have no idea how to get how to get
it
I don't know
what is even going on everybody
oh my God
foreign
breaking
Kelly no no
[Music]
no no
oh yeah
you guys know how to stop what do you
mean stop what do you mean what do you
mean do we stop here uh not like like
you you know how to stop the car like
kind of like that um
yeah yeah
[Music]
I I oh I'm so bad okay I'm just I'm just
smashing
I'm Gonna Take It
base for blocking yes I hate the music
now
oh no I fell
I hate the music
I hate the music like it's mocking me so
hard
wait I'm not supposed to curious
sorry okay it's loud it's loud
what what is it's allowed because of our
ID
cards in Indonesia but if because in
English I thought I think it's okay like
like if if it's Indonesia yes let's go
what do you mean let's go away so which
one is not okay
no English isn't English is not good
because YouTube YouTube AI is bad bad
also currently Indonesia but cursing
Indonesia is okay it's okay
thank you
[Music]
yeah what can I ask the Indonesian team
what was their reasoning behind choosing
uh the cheese one and the baby Road
um I like cheese
I just don't know what they choose
that's I was the one who told them
cheese road because I like like cheese
yes she's tasty so yeah it was somewhat
in control there because like It's gotta
be a road where Elena knows the
shortcuts and stuff yeah I am yeah
two
I wasn't the one choosing it
uh do we have uh some uh comments from
the winner Ina it was number one I think
uh yes ah I would like to thank my chair
mates
um
for this opportunity Because of You Yago
I was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay
thank you
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that
um
what did we choose
oh I mean even if you accidentally
choose one that has been uh chosen
before don't worry it will probably not
be selected so let's just let's just try
to not choose the ones that we have uh
raced before then there's a random teams
now actually there is uh we don't have
to do the voice chat thing because there
is actually a way to do it here
oh and then once the teams are selected
oh there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero zero zero one we want uh gura Ina
um
[Music]
all right all right all right
okay we can do this dangerous
are Iris and amen they are the two
dangerous yeah
just push her off
okay what are we choosing what am I
choosing I'm gonna go for Mount Wario
come on Warrior
okay
you don't have to um
oh they're going for the airport
they're going on a trip
let's fly to the Bahamas
to the Moon
okay okay
it's icy Ice Ice Baby Ice Ice Baby
okay okay okay good memories with that
one I think that's actually good all
right let's go
yes let's go do our best
I don't know if the shortcuts here are
worth it um worth it I don't know I
don't know it is kind of risky yeah it's
very risky right it's very high versus
the way that's on the other team
um
let's go
to hell
what happened
um I got uh yeah you eat it oh my God he
did eat
eat
yeah this shortcut is very risky I don't
know if I yes yeah
[Music]
for helping me
oh no help
we're doing fine for now we're doing
fine for now yep
oh no Ollie's over there
curves
[Music]
we're on the same team
wait what did they hit you yeah you in
Hong Kong that's fine that's fine
I'm sorry sorry okay okay sorry if that
was it I hate you
who was that not me who was that
there's always a question who the hell
hit me this time who missed yeah
who must oh
me and my life like all the speed
too fast
uh
it's a blue shell okay
who was responsible for that who is one
supreme
sorry
I got Blue Shield right in front of the
Finish Line
pretty much at the top so we got a lot
of it
Iris though she's on my tail
hey my heart is like
[Music]
okay
it is it is it is I'm like surprised
like I didn't think it would be this
much fun to like have a full tournament
with everyone and we're having a blast
man
but now we should do it like every every
half year we should do something like
this I know
what do we pick yeah
[Music]
we didn't have that one yet oh
yeah
oh yeah it looks different right oh go
out again oh
this is good
blessed by the RNG really practice this
one okay thank you very much OMG I did
you guys know how to race here
muted aren't I you can't you can't hear
no you're not I think you're a little
client I think I hear you oh okay okay
no
soy sauce wow that's it
hey who was that I don't even know
what's up
you're not you're not no you're not
you're not mean
it's just chat things you know yes just
checking
[Music]
thank you
yeah
[Music]
oh okay okay
what happened
it happened
God this is not looking good
yeah evening
uh
-huh
okay this part I usually choke but okay
I can do this
you can do it
[Music]
all right
y'all be careful
nice okay
I got the mushroom for the last part
oh my gosh
wait sorry
wait I didn't know that oh God oh God oh
God I didn't know I heard I worked that
way
it's fun it's like so friendly fire
no it shouldn't like sometimes it hits
like people by accident I think
generally it goes first oh God this is
[Applause]
Red Shell at the end so close I was like
oh
my God drunk during this race
iris is scary please
good job everyone
oh I'm so shaking okay what do we do
um
go for the airport because they really
want the airplane
and before we get the time the clock
get picked
final s yeah
I see okay airport okay since day one
airport so much that let's direct them
in there yeah yeah of course yeah
we have two more it's the third one okay
three out of four
now
[Music]
Irish
iris is so scary
oh no you will never know
that was horrible hope you guys enjoyed
that in the chat
I just got screwed over like you would
not believe
what happened I'm gonna come back me
till me too because I'm behind you
why
okay let's go let's go
is this a holly
curse is Ollie
oh yeah oh it was good okay
and Iris okay that's the slime
[Music]
it's not here right now but I'm so proud
of Callie
the paraglider
uh if you press down you fly higher oh
then I can't hear oh I just know that oh
she blocked it okay
oh my gosh no no no wait what was that
oh yeah I keep getting screwed over in
like the worst oh my God everyone in
front of me is is Bluetooth
not the pen
uh something a miracle happens I don't
know
I'm not feeling this one yeah this is
bad this is really bad I didn't get an
item either okay I have never gotten the
mushroom before I couldn't use any of
the uh
me neither this is unfortunate unless we
get out it's okay it's okay
oh that was wrong
no yeah couldn't come back
couldn't come back
all right it's okay they got us in this
one Bill's the red in the beginning but
let's go
next
round next one gotta be serious mode I
messed up a little there is this the
last one
[Music]
what do we want to say if someone
dropped out I want to inside
I can't count yeah
I'll come back
we'll be picking seven what are you
picking what are we picking I don't know
drop down
okay wait one two three two guys
I don't know if she can join in time
wait stop someone please don't join
don't choose a race yet if you can but
yeah
[Music]
I'm joining again okay
oh it's starting
yeah I think this is uh Orange
for no reason oh oh no oh no they chose
the clock or the music oh the music ones
are off okay there's 12 choices at least
ah I do not choose the cloth this time I
don't like all these all these me it's
made it she made it oh yeah she made it
okay that's good oh thank God okay all
music okay Music
Park here we go let's go last round
let's do everything we can
is everybody right here we can do this
I'll do my best I'm not good here though
yeah this one's a little rough we can we
can do our best but I don't think let's
just have fun philosophy yeah oh I
forgot to boost okay
I'm just gonna start playing Mario Kart
because yeah
it is really to prepare for the next
tournament already hey no because like
okay listen like what is that I don't
play Mario Kart because you guys have so
I played Mario Kart casually right
because I I don't actually not really no
oh really okay just for streams and
until now it was really desperate yeah I
mean for streaming no stream either
[Music]
Ollie's really good at this map
oh man
oh maybe that's why they're choose
anymore
it's risky
okay yeah oh is it the one with the
bouncy stuff yeah
yeah I I don't know how to use it I
don't want to risk it because oh I fell
before
see Friendly Fire is on
I'm coming in with the same Here Comes
okay
I'm sorry if I hit someone
yeah okay I can't I guess today I
learned that you know even though it's
Team friendly fire is somehow
um yeah
unfortunately fine
let's get me on the ground cat and let's
go
more check
got
let's go let's go
home
that's garbage oh no
that's
oh no
oh I couldn't get her sorry oh my gosh
sorry I'm I'm just very trigger happy be
careful there's a shell I threw that
don't get hit
okay
trust my drifting skills an item RNG I
do see the Red Shell going around
people though like it doesn't
immediately go to the closest one it
goes it tries
like a button I need more ah no I lost
that I could have that we should only
come in is this it ah
[Music]
oh because it only finished oh
you finished
only finished the course that's what the
blue shell came to me
okay as long as we got the top spot we
might still make it we might make it I'm
disconnected
unlucky
wait that was too fast I didn't see who
was number one oh well let's see here
I think Ollie was number one
[Music]
to us we did it oh that was wrong at the
end
okay
I know
I got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh no that was me
which that probably means that you know
the last round if if Lisa you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round final
result is not really accurate
um but that's okay let's just say the
last round was an extra Encore for fun
oh yeah and yeah and I would like to
give out some golden yagos
[Applause]
we all want a golden yellow right so
okay they're not showing up on your
stream they're only on my stream but I
like I would like to give one a golden
juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
questions
[Applause]
[Music]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago as a two Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
for being I guess the strongest in the
ID team holy moly
another golden jungle goes to gura for
being absolutely the speediest shark
I've ever seen
goes to
Anna for being super a big surprising
um what do you call that
wild wild card damn Wild Card yo honey
another golden yellow goes to Muna for
being amazing
I didn't see you that much on the race
but I think it was still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
thank you the darkest time
okay now we're going to golden goggles
to ollie for being also surprisingly
damn good yeah yeah good job
for being speed squirrel
s
we're navig
anything till thank you for
participating
and another golden Jago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprised me you surprised me Callie I
was I was looking at you driving there
and I was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arcs and
she's so good
my mom was playing instead of me that's
why it was so good
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you moving don't mind me uh chat
I'm not gonna be able to fix that now I
think one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven
wait who did I not give up
you weren't you were super
sometimes I have I had an eye on you
thank you
[Music]
yeah hi everyone
um I hope you all thank you um can we
get like a last last comment from
everyone let's start with uh Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more
I don't know maybe
maybe there's gonna it will definitely
be next time yeah
the Improvement
thank you
Kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organize the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast thank you I'm so glad you
enjoyed it thank you
Mom and Dad yeah thanks for everything
it was fun to organize
good uh closing comment please oh
thank you I want to say thank you also
to Ina and Kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and I'm very I'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as I thought I
would and I would like to uh say that it
was probably because I fixed my switch
legs so I didn't have any lag let's go
Gamers let's go
now excuse I watched and I won the like
and you said excuse
[Music]
this place
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this I know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles Beyond but yes
thank you for this golden young I will
cherish it and talk to you every night
thank you so much
okay I've completely disappeared I'm
sorry guys uh okay Iris closing comments
please thank you so much for inviting me
to this wonderful tournament Kiara and
thank you so much Ina for the very very
cute assets and yes I will practice more
so that we can I can get go against
inaudia yeah my goal is Nina
yeah I'm really excited to do this again
hopefully one day yeah
yeah thank you I hope yeah one day I
want to win against Ina too that's a big
pickle that would be a big thing it's
not that big of a goal
I'm not confident anymore
I'm so glad you joined Holo Ian because
that's what made this uh tournament
possible yeah I'm really glad to be able
to join this wonderful Tournament being
part of the cool kids yeah yeah
all right
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go to uh
logos and stuff and even the thumbnails
those must have been hard and also for
Innocent by far making all of those
assets so quickly like you guys really
um how do I say it I really appreciate
it a lot and I'm sure all of us do so
thank you so much for your hard work it
was really fun playing with everyone and
um I may have not popped everyone but
one way or another you guys will all be
my bottoms
I forgot about that goal yeah
you'll get them someday only you'll get
them
right
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organized this thing and thank
you you guys stop thanking me
I mean I I don't think without without
you organizing we wouldn't be like this
I mean it's it's rare to gather all the
whole life Indonesian whole event
together like I think really yeah so I'm
so thankful for that and also
um big thanks to Ina 2 for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and I hope in the future we can be
like this again yeah yeah
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve
perfect Christmas party
okay Inna closing comments please yeah
I'd like to say a big thank you to uh
Kiara for organizing it of course I know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and like schedules
it's really really difficult but you
really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario Kart
streams in the future too
thank you and uh yeah thank you everyone
for joining us today like it was so much
fun like playing with everyone and I
hope we can do it again
thank you
cooperation this was a great
collaboration between uh kfb and Taco
Taco Bell taco eats definitely
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed because we're
faster
okay I know you said stop but thank you
Kiara
and also in a senpai ah thank you so
much and I had a lot of fun oh there was
a little miss out there there was a
little disconnection issue but overall I
had a lot of fun and I would love to
have this kind of tournament again in
the future let's do it
yeah yeah thank you
training so I'll get better and I'll
have everybody next time
[Laughter]
closing comments please
okay so it it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like who's our amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like
um I'd appreciate more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much I
love you guys okay
[Applause]
I'm Miss closing comments ah well first
uh I'd like to apologize
uh if I was salty if I cursed it you
guys oh no yeah
[Music]
uh and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and
Inna you guys worked really hard thank
you guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules so thank you and I
had a lot of fun thank you thank you
now that we have Polo Council we can
like we don't have to relay on these
exact 12 members anymore so next time if
you want you can do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities to Fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together and just
feeling United definitely and I am
always glad to um do stuff like this
again so I would gladly invite you guys
again whenever you have time for it and
want to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so I'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that I'm so sorry I
know it's tough it's no problem it was
fun it's okay I just wish my parents
could watch the news
it's okay I hope your mom enjoyed the
tournament I don't think she did I think
that she enjoys it as well
[Laughter]
well well then with that I would like to
officially close to Holo Ian hello ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone take care
of your golden yagos polish him every
day it's practically and I'll see you
guys
bye
bye guys
[Music]
thank you
okay okay
[Music]
please