e
you
[Music]
this
a
[Music]
I still was
if I could
[Music]
don't
see
around
[Music]
good
to
[Music]
KY yeah woohoo
can you hear me well uh think I just
just me
[Music]
hello
wow I made myself match to the
inscription act two
style a little bit who are you what what
do you mean I am act two w oh sorry my
C
loud two hats yeah two hats to man f
that's who I am that's that's what I
am
[Music]
hello no game video yeah take your time
take your time we got to
relax act two is based on Pokemon TCG
for Game Boy Color oh really
M there is that so what are you doing
chunky
wonky sniff sniff my
cards bgm isn't really relaxing I know
but yeah it's we will will have to try
our best anyway why is my mouse doesn't
go anymore to the left
screen oh also not to the right screen
what what's happening my
mouse is being restricted wait now it's
working now it's working
weird you were setting up this filter
right at the stream
well
[Laughter]
yeah I had an idea and I felt like why
not pursue it uh
yeah but I don't know like there's I I
looked into the Act 2 Gameplay uh but
the the colors are like mostly blue and
then oh oopsie mostly blue and then also
like greenish I don't know I can't do
both so it's just got to be like this
thank you yeah today today today today
was Singapore
AFA and within that was the sore concert
whole live
stage
M yeah I was I was there I was on the
stage it was pretty big quite a big
crowd yeah thank you and like it wasn't
just like starting tweet whatever I
don't want
to you guys should do a starting tweet
for
me you do it quote retweet
go yeah so like interestingly this time
uh uh we kind of had so to say opening
act
because like there was program in the
same room that I guess you could only
enter if you had the sord ticket too I
didn't
tweet
oh right I didn't tweet anything you
don't you can't even cro for
tweet ah go go go go go go go go go I
tweet right
now uh streaming now well you know I had
a busy day with Singapore you know so I
couldn't I couldn't
um uh inscription act
to uh uh uh I'm I am
feeling a little little off I wonder
what's
wrong wait
where's my
orange I'm so
funny so funny okay uh thumbnail
was here I like the thumpnail isn't it
cute or I lost my orange perms
yeah okay let me uh uh post the artist
uh art by
rotten I never know with this keyboard
when I'm like on the Japanese setting
how to make the underscore
bar I think it's the same as of an
English keyboard do you guys
know [\h__\h] oops what did I
do how where is
it whatever I'll switch back to German
keyboard wait do I even know where it is
there wait my keyboard stopped
working ah what the [\h__\h] is going
on everything's
malfunction the the the buttons aren't
doing what they're they should be
doing not at
all like a a a like even
the
what what I do what did I do
what when I click on a link it just
opens a new tab even though I just left
clicked and when I try to type into
something it's like a doesn't work s
opens maybe some key is like bugged s
opens a safe ass did it like Ctrl alt or
so
like what happened help me my ALT key
like it doesn't look
stuck it doesn't look stuck it's very
much
normal let me reconnect this
keyboard the [\h__\h] is going
on
please no I can't I can't use my
keyboard control shift or Windows key no
nothing's stuck nothing works either
it's back to
normal after I after I I punched my
keyboard it works again nice
okay punching aggressively was the only
thing that worked now all right uh
art
by uh at
rencore 8 I think
where is it where is that oh
there
okay how
scary oh oh okay one thing one notice
before we begin uh wait I wasn't even
done talking about the other topic God
damn it I'm all over the place again I'm
all over the place
again uh where's
where's my logo anyway where's I need to
find the ah I'm
scattered I'm
scrambled what the [\h__\h] I hate
this where's the logo
all right let me [\h__\h] download it
again sorry I'm a little bit agitated
now not just now I think I was agitated
before that but yeah
um where the [\h__\h] I have too many
[\h__\h] servers on
[Music]
Discord [\h__\h] [\h__\h] hate this
too many servers too many channels how
am I supposed to find anything at
all oh there it now you'll show up
[\h__\h] download folder never freaking
loads okay here's the logo yeah okay uh
ho ho ho ho ho
in about
uh 6
hours and 10 minutes four five yeah and
the first video should go up
and but it it has yet to be prepared so
I will end my stream a little bit early
maybe we'll see I don't know how long is
act two I think i' I've read act two
isn't too
long so yeah but in a few hours we're
going by GMT zero time zone
again single stream okay good that's
good uh then we'll keep it short and
light
today cuz I'm busy you can make it
longer by grinding no no
no but yeah GMT zero will be what we're
following again cuz we did that last
year's twoo uh so every time it hits
midnight yeah I'm caught up too yeah
every time it hits midnight we will uh
you will be able to hopefully unless
somebody's late you will see a new video
on on the website I think the website is
in theory already
visitable and I think it's the same URL
as usual right yeah if you go to holoen
minus advent.com what do you
see what do you
see cute yeah you see it
yeah yeah it made a logo yeah yeah wait
you see that animation yeah yeah let me
show you let me show
you wait to let me close incription for
now let me let me actually show you what
we
cooked this year I had a little bit of a
different
idea that I think works really well uh
let me show it on
[Music]
screen uh
window so do you see
this
Mia if you go on holoen minus advent.com
which which is by the way not a math uh
[Laughter]
problem uh then you will see this this
is new logo we didn't have a logo until
now because I thought you know whatever
um just the simpler writing was fine but
this year I commissioned the logo yeah
that's new mhm H do yeah mhm then you
see this this time Advent calendar so
the way we're doing it previously it was
um
if you go to the old calendars you will
see that uh maybe I I could go to the
old calendars right
now
actually let me show
[Music]
you uh let's mute this
one old calendar okay this is let's
let's say 2D view was just like this um
itty
bitty locks yeah and when you opened it
and you watch the
video then afterwards you'll see an
piece of art that has been drawn in
accordance to the video you just watched
which was very time con like it was a
problem they were they were all so
charming and cute but but uh yeah the
problem was that sometimes the videos
Came in Like Only a one or two or three
hours before the video has to go up and
so the artist only had like that amount
of time to draw it that was like the
first year and then in this year the the
2023 year we tried to improve that by at
least having the girl tell us ahead of
time what they will do in the video so
that the artist can already draw ahead
of
time
um but that way it was sometimes maybe
not too accurate you know unless like
sometimes when the girls did bring their
vide sometime somehow early enough then
the artist was still able to uh you
know adjust the art to be even more uh
fitting to the video that was our
solution for that year um and I think it
worked out fine too but in the end still
our artist punon Mi still had so much
stress and work to do 24 25 pieces of
art too much spoiler what do you mean
what are you talking about what are you
guys talking about with spoilers nothing
is spoilering here you're you're opening
a day this is
2023 you're opening a day you watch a
video you close and then you know what
who was it otherwise like if you are if
it's the 4th of December you cannot open
day five yet and the art won't be there
yet either this is 2023 as an
example did you not listen what I'm
saying this is the old calendar 2023
yeah so that was how we did it in 2023
uh but like the overall calendar it was
like just these graphics and then the
thumbnails but here
how we're doing it here is one big
animated piece of art with all the
members and then when the first door is
opened you open it but it it it won't
reveal a new piece of art it's just this
one big piece of art cute cute cute
right because I was thinking about
Advent calendars here in like
uh Austria whoo do you want a permaban
you suck
I'm giving
you 24 hours Ben because that's just
rude this is super adorable and we
worked hard on
it I love this idea because it takes a
lot of uh work off of the artist at
least from now
on and it's so cute look at them
bouncing around so yeah L and Ena are
drawing something together up there in
the
skies yeah crony is trying trying to
build a snowman maybe she has such long
legs M and Faun m is riding fa cuz she's
a deer
mhm here and there there's the mascots
doing stuff too uh the the jailbirds and
the um Baba chickens kfy chickens
they're making snow angels next to each
other do you see it sh is like messing
with the decoration on the tree is she
decorating or is she Messing with
it uh and I think narissa is like cuz
I'm Santa Claus narissa maybe is coming
to Santa Claus to make a wish or
something or be like you know like a
baby to sit on my lap gooy is being a
little
gramlin my
own my own my
gramlin yeah uh gigy and BB are having a
snowball fight on the top right
and oh maybe maybe crony should uh you
know go over to Cecilia because Cecilia
is also building a snowman well I think
Crown is not really building us maybe
she gave up on it and then she just uh
she's trying
to you know she's fighting with her fans
cuz she stuck the what do you call them
again she stuck it into the the the
clock she stuck it into the snow maybe
she's like having a fight with them I
don't know the cronies oh very
[Music]
simple yeah and Fu are eating Donuts on
big big big p and and the cute Doos are
around so cute and then there's some
more fans
cheering for chat cast plus bi boo bi
boo is like just blasting the music bi
is giving me Jessie Vibes here with the
music with the blasting
speakers makes me you feeling she's like
Jesse be boom box b boom box not
a yeah
so I think this is a really cute idea
yeah it turned out so
adorable so I was looking at other
Advent calendars IRL and figured that a
lot of them you know it's like physical
calendars they'll have this like big
piece of art on top and you're
opening the doors on the piece of art so
this time it's actually more like an
advent calendar than
before so in a few hours it says here at
the top anyway 6 hours and 1 minute
there will be the first video available
and then from there on every 24 hours
always at midnight GMT Z you'll find a
new video um some I I think you know we
have a lot of members now so a lot of
them will be solo videos but we will
have a few collaboration videos too I
still don't know what to do for the
finale but we'll see so yeah ad a
calendar 2024 H life English Adent
Calendar please enjoy it's uh on
holen minus advent.com make sure to
share it uh perhaps also in all the fan
discords I'd be very very
happy if like everybody could share it
uh this is not just for kfp this is for
everybody so
yeah would be I would be happy if we
would get a lot of traffic traffic on
the
website
[Music]
y mhm hesome for the whole Community
yay I already shared to different friend
C thank you thank you and then besides
that I wanted to say yeah I wanted to
mention uh single yeah I was talking
about
Singapore yeah we had uh Kyla and
crony uh do like a 1H hour panel and
then fuok do a 1H hour panel right
before our concert and I think everybody
like in order to watch their panels also
needed the sore tickets so it was
like quite the big program hope you guys
enjoyed it in
Singapore AFA was
big very exciting
M very very
big oh yeah you can zoom in yeah I guess
in Fury you could zoom in can I aim at
what oh yeah W I'm so
big I'm so
huge
nice I love it do you guys want to see
the clean
art hopefully uh pun m is going to
upload
but I can show you if you
[Music]
want
wait Queen
[Music]
art right I'm looking for
it there's a lot of
stuff ah here there it is cute it's so
[Music]
cute
ta this is without the
[Music]
animation very cute
wow the sky is so
beautiful okay good thank you that was
uh your tental notifying you about the
current
[Music]
happenings now we shall play inscription
hey
gaming surprised there wasn't the merch
reminder oh do you want to be reminded
do you do you want to be reminded about
my merch that's currently on sale on
Vite V with kfp together we made some
really cool merch go check it out also
my Android is currently open for
pre-order until middle of uh January
don't miss it don't miss it don't is
it okay
sorry oh but do you want to see do you
guys do you guys all use
to do you guys all use
twit did you see
[Music]
wa waa in
Singapore woo
[Music]
do I kind of look smug in there let me
Zoom it oh I look pretty pretty
smug where are my
eyebrows I don't have
eyebrows where are my
eyebrows how how do I manage to look
smug without eyebrows that's quite
impressive
honestly let's say it was the the low
quality of the picture that burn my
eyebrows
away my polygon article went live today
my polygon article article article
polygon oh I guess I wrote that a while
ago
polygon by the way there was another
interview a while
ago uh I heard some opinions that uh
some people out there didn't believe
that I actually
like answered in certain ways because my
answers were too well worded you little
shits it was a written interview maybe
in speech I would not have been able to
word things so nicely indeed but it was
written so I I wrote those answers okay
you little
shits okay oh here it is 4 hours ago oh
do you want to look at this on me why
the [\h__\h] not let's look
I already have here
[Music]
wait oh poty talk partty talk
ski party
talk do they mean bad I have a bad mouth
like I'm I use swear words a lot or then
I go to meetings a lot what
what party
talk party
talk the first that I swear a lot
bro that's the tit that's
the that's the
headline bro
really really
Taki Kiana is not like other girls okay
okay
okay the cliche applies to her in a
little sense
pretends que
of she's a vtuber a term for a content
creator who streams using an Anime
Avatar when K appears on a stream uh
viewers watch a bubbly anime girl with
bright orange hair not today and blue
highlights Ki the character is a star
all right all right okay you're making
up for that
headline the person who voices her
remains
Anonymous I mean that's an interesting
way to say
that I'm
anonimous I guess I'm being voiced I'm
just I'm just
me but is signed to the V talent agency
whole Al alive and has guard worldwi the
claim and the role the role I'm not
playing a role
though at the time of publication K's
YouTube channel has more than 1.55
million we're so close to 1.56 guys
subscribe subscrib and she start in live
concert as a hologram wait wait wait
wait wait
hologram hologram is more like uh how H
niku appears in her concert not even not
even her though right hologram is like
kind of when you project something onto
the into the
air I
mean well let's take it let's take it
sounds cool H life
hologram sounds
cool her fans are known as Kar Phoenix
yeah or k yeah it's yeah I guess if it's
written out you are you guys are Kata of
R Phoenix you are together we are K of r
Phoenix a reference to the lore behind
her character which evokes a
lightheartedness h that characterizes
much of her work mhm mhm Kiana gleefully
switches between the contrasting roles
of glamorous Superstar and laidback
video game personality she will blurt
out I have diarrhea on a
stream that leads to a YouTube link I'll
have to confirm
that I mean maybe I I mean I mean what
what
let me confirm
that wait
so no let let me not show that because
okay it's just a clip how do you get
water from a river do you just like how
how do you drink it I'm punching it but
I don't get in water it say seven days
to
die I was like when did I say that like
and mean it like I actually have
diarrhea IRL I don't think I ever said
that okay so it was seven days to die in
particular but then go perform a
commanding solo at the soul do concert
oh that's their other article article
about the breaking dimensions on top of
it all she has taken on the role of an
educator
educator I'm I'm a teacher and teaches
her us-based fans about Japanese idol
culture yeah okay well I that's very
specific I think I teach also the EUR
European fans and and SCA like everybody
about Japanese idol culture and the ins
and outs of vtubers via the talk show
she hosts hosts
oh yeah oh I guess so
[Laughter]
yeah to learn more about KP her growing
music career and what it's been like to
perform live polygon conducted an
interview with her virtually via written
responses yes see see see see you see
oh oh this interview has been edited and
condensed for clarity they they they
censored
[Laughter]
me I met some of your fans oh who met
polygon who and one said that you
actively manage your community who said
that it's true though now some of your
fans organized the larger Hol Life
Community you do you got some
power or maybe they censored me
swearing I didn't swear it a written
interview how do you interpret your
influence on your fans well I
interpreted by building a cult around
it
motion motion motion said so motion
motion was approached by
polygon uh Tak I'm always very happy to
see KY pick up on things that I share
with them when the first group of
English speaking members of whole life
first debuted H yeah we were the first
in our branch and I think I was the most
knowledgeable about Japanese idol
culture so I wanted to share it with my
audience how to cheer for them how to
dress at concerts and so on I always
hear that kfp has been taking a leading
role in non-japan events of our company
in terms of teaching chance and cheers
and organizing stuff I'm so glad that
the community uh that I have been
building has turned out to be such a
Pleasant and fun
one don't get cocky
KP in your opinion what is the wildest
thing your fans have ever done for you
what was it what was it huh I had to
think hard traveling over continents to
see me for example in Japan or Germany
or just any continent that they are not
from my fans come from various
continents and seeing how committed some
are to travel I appreciate them so much
for showing up to support me I mean this
I mean this I mean
it yeah
but even the ones who can't travel for
whatever reason also show me their love
and support in many other ways I do hope
everyone gets a chance to see a concert
in person one day feel the atmosphere of
a packed venue of the packed venues and
socialize with other CP yeah this is
true this is true appearing in a concert
seems like a very different experience
than day-to-day streaming how does
preparing and appearing at an event like
that compare with streaming good
question good question polygon the
questions are good
th this this whole there's a lot of
questionable statements in here but the
questions are
good uh it may seem like we don't do
much besides stream but there's
definitely a lot of work behind the
scenes especially when there's a concert
of ours coming
up but today I definitely do look like a
hologram I
guess for me whole life is a place where
I can have a chill and fun streaming job
but also live out my dreams of being on
stage every once in a while it's two
very different experiences but that's
what's so exciting and refreshing it
never gets dull yes oh so true wow this
girl she really knows what she's talking
about cuz I agree with everything she's
saying were there any performances from
real life pop stars that influence your
performance oh where there after my
first two singles I have been trying to
go for a more K-pop like image with my
songs and choreographies so I would say
K-pop artists in general have had an
influence on that for sure but even
within k K-pop there're are different
Vibes so I have also been trying to do
something different each time like Chim
was way more cool and Powerful compared
to Pineapple which is more cutesy
energetic type of
K-pop wait okay the rest you know what
you guys got to read the rest yourself
go go go go polygon.com read my
interview the first part was funny what
is this headline
though what is this
headline I can't
it's too funny it gets your
attention diarrhea me shut
up it probably gets clicks does it does
who is the voice I I would like to stay
and remain anonymous thank you do not
ask me who is behind takanashi
Kiana sorry sorry for roasting you a
little bit polygon but that was very
funny only airport security knows yes
yes they will be the only ones finding
out takanashi diarrhea
I hate you poot what have you done to me
in my
reputation
man all right let's play inscription
okay come
on
oh description. XA isn't reacting all
right I'll close it
we'll try it
again you did ask crony to share toilet
with you wait wait wait wait wait wait
context context I don't even remember
the
context are getting on to activas thank
you I like I'm really surprised that
there's like this whole lot of style of
game I honestly really enjoyed act one
and like how it was similar to slay the
Spire so I don't know if I will
oh oh it's it's dying again maybe cuz I
tapped out again let me try one more
time one more
time uh I don't know if I will like act
two cuz I if it if it's very different
in terms of gameplay then I don't know
if I like like it more than act
one oh come on what why is why are
things bugging out right
now we'll see you're in for a right
there's more to come oh no are we never
going back to like the original game
play it's the same as the previous just
the robot deck has a new feature
oh well here we go
uh new game or
continue
continue a [\h__\h] new
game and but this works why do I why am
I
bald new
[Laughter]
game this looks fine same result okay
choose a starting deck to mark your
ambition uh how do can I if I click on
it am I already choosing it no okay your
ambition is to replace
P3 and become the oh poet po no p and
become the Scribe of
Technology uh replace lashy and become
the Scribe of the
Beast what who are these
people uh replace grimora and become the
Scribe of the Dead okay dead beasts
technology and
Magic which one should I
[Music]
do lash lashy is the one
deck oh I would do
Ley Beast H okay I'll take
it SM okay take the cards were added to
your collection okay here we
go maybe I'm too blue I leave I
leave oh is
this wow ooh okay left I can't I can't
go left there's a dude scares
me what if I go up here
instead this is also
scary isn't this the house that I was
in it is the house that I was
in oh stop shaking the only thing you
have to fear is your own
inadequacy behold me I am Ley The Scribe
of beasts I would consider your ambition
to replace me a threat if it weren't so
laughable we share a desire for you to
challenge me but
first
N I know what you're thinking no this is
not my legendary camera not the one I
used to create Beast car
this one is a mere replica you may use
it to create photos of the beasts in
these Woods my sub subordinates the
prospector the angler and the
Trapper they each require a photo before
they will consider battling you return
to me when they are all defeated I I
don't know what kind of voice I should
do for this Sky
now so okay I I go and talk to these
weirdos outside a
m
here I want to make it more quiet pause
one
window did it become more quiet did I
save
it did I have to save it oh no it stayed
like that
okay is it better okay so would you like
to be in my deck is that how it works no
no fish no p a he wants
fish maybe trade
Quest you PR the chest open and found a
card pack inside you received a beastly
card pack is this
randomized o uh o are these basically
the same card it's just they they look
more
pixelated I already forgot about them I
remember Grizzly or Yi add these ones I
don't
[Music]
know wait left was how much they attack
and and right was how much they can
take right I get all ooh when opposing
when an opposing creature is placed
opposite uh to an empty space bone Hound
will move to that empty space ahuh okay
cool cool can't be sacrificed when Dr
group parishes the creature inside is
released in this
place creature
inside creature inside who's inside the
the The Ice Cube
what that creature yeah okay thanks for
the membership
welcome H inside where good question ah
okay okay they were added to my
collection d n
that dang H got herself lost again yet
think you're getting past think again
not till I get some proof my girls all
right uh who's your girl and why am I
[Music]
bald I don't feel like
myself oh there's another Treasure Chest
oh another card Salomon waterborne also
at the end of the owner's turn salmon
will move in the direction inscribed in
the
sigil oh that's interesting cuz salmon
salmon
salmon salmon also moves
IRL no wait I'm trying to say don't they
also like they like swim like you know
right right up stream I know this is
salmon
Behavior yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so you
know what I
mean
yeah there's something in there oh I
touched it now it's gone
hello everything's so big I feel so
small but on this map I feel so
big
[Music]
zombies wait where am I oh there ah you
here marvelous I am Kora scribe of the
dead until quite recently I was
disgraced though I was returned to my
former glory with the help of some
unlikely friends if you wish to test
your skills against me you must first
prove your
wits uh I don't think I'm ready for this
you must discern which to marks the
final resting places of my lovely
ghouls okay what we not fighting a card
game Babel are we talking about these
tombs
[Music]
here is this a guessing
game I'm
ready she was a SK stinkbug
ah oh my God why is she not talking more
familiarly to me I guess she doesn't
know
me wait the not oh that's a not you you
found a piece of an epth it reads eaten
by a hungry dog is that supposed to help
me
here eat by a hungry
dog oh no oh no oh no oh no no no no no
you know that get gets used in like meme
videos a
lot do not look upon me do not snarl or
sniff I beg you if you wish to battle
please let us get it over
with oh something's
wrong it's your
deck or rather you lack of a valid one
yeah my deck has been
trimmed you hate that sound I really
like
it you've got 20 cards in it right no
tab
oh oh I have to choose to put the in ah
ah it do I even have enough to build a
20 card
deck oh all
right
Auto how does it choose randomly
no
deck no
deck seven
squirrel wait squirrels squirrels were
the one that I always sacrifice that you
can like pick always in the beginning
right separately from the
deck is this does this look good to
you I don't really want to like look for
all these cars now what's a Warren
a rabbit is created in your hand a
rabbit is defined as zero power one
Health mhm you guys like these kind of
cards I think for the sake of
sacrificing it'll do for
now
okay looks much better where were we
really I'm
scared okay okay it's still kind of the
same principle right you froze in fear
as the words of the great scribe of
beasts entered your skull Uninvited fear
not I only wish to explain to you the
deck that you selected or autoc
completed in order to play my card
sacrifices must be made yeah I agree
with that I could I could agree with
that strongly wait I got some DMS this
is important sorry sorry cuz I'm like in
the middle of planning things
m
o
[Music]
oo
huh
okay sorry I'm just doing Santa Claus
business I'm Santa clausing away around
The Scribe assessed your reaction noting
that you did not seem surprised by this
information perhaps you need no lesson
but remember that almost anything can be
sacrificed mhm it may bleed oil or even
marrow but if it bleeds well you know
what to do no I don't remember what to
do yeah B so uh you're you you are
playing that next round here right
oh it's been a while I already have two
squirrels in my
hand and a Warren and an
adder and an Adder needs two
squirrels if I wanted to play it but we
don't necessarily want to play it yet
maybe we'll play the the
Warren uh a
rabbit
yeah so maybe I'll play a scri roll and
then a
Warren you will come down and attack
after you
move well two
sacrifice
[Music]
yeah
uh but okay do I want this it only has
two Health do I want this to block or
try to attempt to to block the the thing
whatever I'll I'll put it there why
pulls out a rabbit wow like a magician
so go
cute use this for protection okay I'm
doing it and then I guess I ring the
bell I think we're
[Music]
done o oh he's gone and he's going to
play a Revenant after attacking Revenant
perishes whoa just one attack she but
free free attack
power yo Adam C yes in 5 hours or so 5
and a half or so mhm mhm first video
will begin I think I'll play the
adder so that I can get rid of the bone
Hound bone Hound leaps over to block
what do you
mean bro not done why did he move
already h they they didn't do this in
the in act
one that's it no no but like usually it
only moves after I'm done with my
turn nah it BLS whatever I
play no but like what nah it wasn't like
this when place the
Oh weird okay uh finish
[Music]
add's Touch of death kills instantly
thank
God
[\h__\h] Revenant collapses into a pile of
bones maybe I should have no we're we're
okay maybe we're okay I got the hawk but
it needs two blood and I only have the
rabbit so I can't
even can't even do
anything right I don't think I can do
anything it's basically still tutorial
what do you mean
I don't think this is
tutorial it's funny when during act one
like people are also constantly saying
this is still tutorial this is still
tutorial I mean at some point it's just
not a tutorial
anymore oh okay we got to Stout sto
after attacking skeleton perishes ah
like is this the whole thing with these
Undead
people a lot of like attacking and then
[Music]
dying
well might as well block him I
guess oh he puts another one right
behind it
interesting
bruh okay
strike an opponent directly even if
there is a creature opposing
it
oh that's interesting but I I still
don't have enough unless I also
sacrifice the
sto SK are also sacrifice like
SRS oh opponent as in uh okay okay I I
was thinking differently cuz it's been
too long so it just attacks yeah uh the
whoever I'm battling
[Music]
directly free attack is worth
sacrificing the sto sacrificing bird is
better
[Music]
okay
go yeah there we
go finally got some teeth
going o we got the UR Yuli but
whatever the battle is over we excess
damage okay foils gained
foils foils you say it is over you
chewed it's over you chewed me out now
please look away why what's going to
happen are you going to explode turn
your eyes to this card pack instead okay
it's embarrassing to him how he's
falling apart turning into dust bone
dust you received a deathly card pack
wow this is TC TCG simulator wow sparkly
do I get all of them
again
Frankenstein what does it do needs five
wait they all need wait they all need
Bones and [\h__\h] only this one the mole
makes sense for me because it
needs wait no bones are fine too I can
still collect bones right
[Music]
I guess when an empty space would be
struck mole will move to that space and
receive the struck
inste am I getting all of
them yeah okay I'm called
soer that almost feels like a
combination of Saul and lawyer Better
Call
Saul the Middle Stone marks My Grave oh
please do not go digging up my
bones wait so I choose the middle one
then you found a piece of an epit you
read Sor Patel 1702 fall
1778 so should I still talk to this
other guy
or you sifted for the bones and found a
card pack there's so many card packs
everywhere
[Music]
great ooh Sapphire mocks can't be
sacrificed while Sapphire mock is on the
board it provides a blue gem to its
owner what does it
do Necromancer when another creature you
own of you own dies it is returned to
life and dies again
immediately that's for a really hard
magic deck oh Pharaoh's pets is counted
as three blood rather than one blood
when sacri oh also when Pharaoh's pets
is sacrificed it does not perish
ooh wait that's a great card me like
[Music]
M okay so how's this
work you didn't buy a hungry wait do I
know
this for
sure could I not put this anywhere if I
wanted
to wa was was he really eaten by a dog
she did say something about eaten by
dogs but does it apply to him
specifically he said okay h a living SCE
of lemon approaches bright and trig as
lime yeah thank you will squeeze a
defeat out of me fight fight fight fight
fight fight
fight all right ooh ghost chip
waterborne also at the end of the
owner's turn the Ghost Ship will move in
the direction inscribed in the sigil and
drop a skeleton in his old
space uh okay water born so wait can my
St sto attack the
ship maybe
not
oh well how do I get rid of it
[Music]
bruh move right after arriving
how do I get rid of it then oh submerge
it can only damage on their turn usually
from
spikes [\h__\h] what do I
do just try to go direct for direct
damage as much as I
can cuz right now my sto can't block it
you leave it being out Dam yeah that's
what I'm thinking okay I'll try well we
got
one ow
I should have at least blocked the
skeleton huh
[\h__\h] moves to a new one what do you mean
what's up with all these
[Music]
squirrels what's
happening okay we got the Warren
[Music]
Warren pulls out a rabbit whoa so
cute I'll put this maybe whatever
whatever it'll have to do I'm doing my
thing let's see how it
goes we're winning now though we're
still kind of
winning o we got a hawk hwk will strike
an opponent
directly hey
go for it go for it do it do it do
it
[Music]
seven be the pp me firstly take you this
oh c pack C
pack skele Magus after attacking skele
Magus perishes also if skele Magus own
owner controls no mock card scelus
perishes uhhuh dead hand when dead hand
is played this card your hand and then
draw a new hand of four
cards a more pharoh pets
YooHoo andit me share a secret me name
is Royal is I right here's my headp you
found a piece of an epap okay so this
goes
to Royal doming 1589 to Spring
1632 okay can I walk through him
now I
can you found a card pack oh oh oh
oh so generous in act
two don't forget to add new yeah tomb
robber activate pay one bone to create a
skeleton in your hand there's so many
bone cards here bro field mice when
field mice is play a copy of it is
created in your hand Raven will strike
an opponent
directly
[Music]
MH fact are F yeah makes sense H hit by
a fallen piece of ice wait whom wait
sorry the first sentence did it say who
or does it apply to this guy in
particular well maybe we'll get more
info but I didn't read the first I
skipped through the first message
because I thought it was just going to
be a card pack
again not necessarily that guy ooh what
the
heck you found a piece of an epip it
reads there was no
cure all right ah
happened it confused me oh I got 6 DMS
again
CH
oh you just
insane that's
crazy I'm working on
becoming Santa Claus and um it's uh the
things I'm being told that I can give
away is a bit
nuts um
[Music]
okay
um I'm making a list I'm checking it
twice how does it continue I think you
got to be nice Santa Claus has presents
for
you w Claus has presents for
you I hope I'm in the Nic list I hope so
too what what wait why am I different
now oh I can't keep on that looks more
like me but only Maybe not maybe it's
just I mean at least the hair is
orange oh rabot
okay I'll be this
person nice I got a little image
[Music]
change looking cute I think hard to tell
with so little
pixels does not hold a grudge wait I
want to talk to the guy again did he
seem like he doesn't hold a grudge I am
called Sawyer the Middle Stone
marks oh yeah yeah yeah do not sniff or
snarl do not sniff or snar what did you
say like I said me name's roal it's the
far right tomb far life didn't give me
lemons so I
died didn't give does that does that say
anything
oh it does sound like he's not holding a
gr
did didn't give me lemons when life
gives you so he did he lived a good life
so he does not hold a grudge
eh missing his C okay well yeah okay
we'll just continue we'll fig we'll
figure it out we'll figure it out
Surly I guess both could
apply he clearly died of scoy he died of
scoy talks what is this like something
like ligma
he clearly died of scurvy as a pirate
what does that
mean
scurvy
scurvy scurvy is a real not I doubt it
scurvy balls
scy scurvy
scy scr I'm going to look that [\h__\h] up
now what are you guys joking about
scurvy scurvy you guys are even typing
it
differently oh
okay can you really die from
that oh there is no cure is that why you
SC proove of those of vitamin C as low
as 10
ah something about lemons lemons have
vitamin C he did not get lemons
and but it does have a cure if you just
get more lemons but you guys are just
making a joke
right wait
[Music]
what he didn't have the Cure well okay
because he didn't have lemons because
life didn't give him lemons I guess he
didn't have a
cure K scurvy and good at dancing Ki
scurvy
nice there know lemons in the sea well
but sometimes you dock at an island or
city city and then you can buy at their
Market some
lemons
brah anyway somebody leave I oh that's
already kind of like a hint that it's
cold yeah wait his picture says it
all oh come on dude it's rising in the
air maybe a heated battle will help
okay we know that he's the ice
guy can't be sacrif inside is okay
Banshee will strike an opponent directly
even if there is a creature P okay and I
have salmon I should change my deck
again huh and should I got so many cards
now damn
[Music]
it okay
I guess I'll start with my
salmon go go go have
fun oh [\h__\h] I should
have ah but he can't attack anyway
doesn't matter I was going to block him
but he doesn't have attack so I didn't
need to block all is good all is well
all right I'll put a I'll put a squirrel
there oh good job good job
salmon what a good
salmon okay I didn't want to take the
damage so I block it with a
squirel and then we have a
[Music]
Warren this deck
sucks a
rabbit it's okay my salmon is super
strong
oh but he keeps on putting stuff there
ah uh give me a good
card oh I got a
drer sure but I still don't really
understand what was what's inside I
guess we'll find wait wait he needs
bones I don't have bones no wait I do
have bones for no that's his bones or is
it my bones
well I guess it was my
bones I'm kind of playing pretty head
empty right
now as you may be able to tell but I
don't know how to do better
honestly uh well we
can play my Raven now that's
good oh there we go okay okay even head
empty kind of works out it works
it
works wait you're not dead yet wait whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa I thought nine
would be enough to kill
you well now you'll die you'll die
oh what even what even are you doing I
can't even sacrifice you do
it there you
go there you go
you want but now I'm a bit less cold
take a pack one on the
house mhm bone Heap activate pay two
bones to increase the power and health
of bone Heap by one the Walkers when the
Walker dies four bones are awarded
instead of
one
okay thanks I guess you didn't mean me
so I guess I've got to f up the name's
Casey Casey h
I'm from the tombstone on the
left mhm I
figured thanks for giving me your name
Casey you were hit by Falling a falling
piece of ice oopsie oops
and
you I guess don't hold
a wait a second is this regarding like
there was no cure is this regarding the
middle piece
or regarding just anything that they're
saying cuz I feel like does not hold a
grudge could F fit for
both it referen the middle piece well
obviously there's no cure for being hit
by Fall a falling piece of ice but you
guys are saying it's more like over
[Music]
here wait
here wait are they going to tell us that
he died by SC scurvy like
legitimately you pulled up an Epi the F
the fibrillator
failed no such thing as
scurvy oh wait that doesn't go
there
defibrillator I'm not
sure is there more more I need one
more oh
hello talk to me are you oh you
[Music]
Trader I don't think I need any of these
cards thank you I was hoping for a hint
haven't gone downstairs oh [\h__\h]
okay haven't thought about going
downstairs to be
[Music]
honest brought down by scurvy it's real
it's real I'm scared it might take me
down
too one of these
days told you so don't be so don't be so
petty it's about life and death don't be
so
petty scurvy
[Music]
there was no
cure but does this
match this one does that
match does this
much no 18th
[Music]
century uh are they being that
realistic I guess there was no defil in
the in this in 17
whatever
uh so they tried keeping that person
alive with the fil relator is what
you're
saying and this guy got eaten by a
hungry dog but okay it even opens
automatically okay marvelous I believe
you have proven your W adequately are
you prepared no you will not defeat me
yeah wait wait wait wait let me look at
my
deck
uh you can open the Tombstones
downstairs what really but I think I'm
already
done
um I don't like the D girl I didn't
understand what it
did uh I do do like my
Hawk what do you think I should put
in missed Easter egg okay I'll
check you don't want more cards no not
really wait can I have more than
20 look at the bone costum
okay we have bone Heap tomb robber
Necromancer Dead Hand blah blah blah
broken no B
the Walkers ah here the these
ones but will I get up to six bones
perhaps I want to have far's pets
because it gives me a lot of blood when
I sacrifice it and does this mean it
stays in my hand I
forgot the does not perish does it mean
it stays in my
hand like it comes back into my hand
right I think
so it's expensive but you
know all right says on board ah right
amazing so when I play it once we're
already
happy the rest I don't care we can try
we can try to go with that one second
let me check downstairs
[Music]
again a gust of foul smelling air
Billows from the casket
[Music]
scary wait let's do something
here you have no
[Music]
offering oh that's
it wait what is that a reference
[Music]
to marous just marous I was beginning to
worry I would be the way behind those
tombstones forever lock down at the
mercy of a Challenger's wits until one
day discovered but no you prevailed and
now it's time to
battle W boss fight boss fight boss
fight let's
go my minions never truly die you
know new jeans also never dies let's go
new jeans newans let's see how you
fair oh I like this music
yeah so you start with bone Hound okay
okay mm that's fine that's
fine one attack well whatever I do you
will move to where I put the
sto it is what it is but you also have
lots of attack so I want to block
it two bones
oh [\h__\h] I can't really play anything
[\h__\h] wait when I die in this
battle uh what happens can I redo the
battle it's
over all
right you just get to retry okay
hopefully the C RNG gets reshuffled
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ch um it's not over
yet you die in real
life might need more fixing my deck is
not good enough for this but e
really B she will strike in the opponent
even if there is oh
[\h__\h] am I
dying Mar an opportunity to use my
Quin rip bone Hound oh no she's riding
his grave already this one will be back
h
transcends into higher what oh no oh no
oh
no okay what a rush you may try again
challenger but don't expect any less of
a
fight okay I changeed my dick help me
Chad how to make better dick
go to other places find more cards oh
you think I'm just not ready like I
don't even have good cards in here get
rid ofi okay sure I mean he didn't show
up in the first place but yeah
okay three blood four
blood we could bring the grizzly
though remover he's expensive you never
use
him fin out and pick a theme I'm fine
with picking the Blood Theme not the
bones but add some
skeletons
why do you want me to fight her with a
skeleton dick skeleton versus
Skeletons bone Heap and Tomb
[Music]
Raider two two robber you mean right pay
one bone to create a skeleton in your
hand
okay pay two bones to increase the power
and health of bone Heap by
one
okay but then I need more bones
also cuz otherwise I can't play those
cards until end
game then I'll be needing to do more
sacrificing but those cards don't
sacrifice
right you get both little time to worry
about it you can have more than 20 cards
ah
okay
[Music]
oops how do I get more bones by I know
by by sacrificing more but
like how will I do
that after attacking skill perishes also
SC owner
controls Four B ah when broken obal dies
four bones are water instead of one
oh so I can just put this out there as a
wall and then be rewarded with a couple
of
Bones
H when another creature you own dies it
is return to life and dies again
immediately oh that also brings more
bones
right creature your own dies return to
life and dies again in me that's that's
really that sounds dumb but basically it
just means I get double double bones for
a card
dying but is this card worth it maybe
this card is not worth it yeah cuz this
costs free
bones only that's only worth it when the
car that dies like this
one which brings four bones would then
bring eight bones Maybe
maybe cuz it's doubling that right but
then that's I don't know how to make
that
happen the Ice Cube guy is plus one bone
since it dies twice Ice Cube
guy I
guy guy a this
one uhhuh
yeah whatever I'll try like this and see
what happens or no wait ah actually ah
[\h__\h] let me double confirm lady I was
actually going to add more I should I
could have added more
squirrels okay well
[Music]
oh P to increase health of bone heat
okay well let's the I don't understand
does he not need anything to be
played but what how does this what is
this why you look mad I'm
determined he's free
okay a then I okay but I shouldn't play
him now cuz he'll just get
destroyed I should play him when I have
some bones available to upgrade
him well this is the same beginning
different hands go a little
bit damn it wait I already have two
bones but like I have these squirrels
but I can't sacrifice them if I don't
have
anything so but I I
could I could put one here to block his
damage and get a uh sacrifice that way
so right you can with the heam
oh oh thanks for the
raid yeah for now I'll just use them
like walls I
[Music]
guess I don't know is this doable thank
you for the raid first put bone card and
then squirrels because the dog will
follow
oh I mean this
dog well too late
you just played a card with an activated
Bill okay thank you I know the great
scribes instructions began to echo
through your mind activate it by
pressing the sigil like it's a button
okay but it will only work if you can
pay the cost yeah
sure bone Heap grow stronger there you
go bone Heap grow stronger again
but [\h__\h] I see I see I see I should have
played it so
that uh in the end that yeah whatever I
don't
know maybe this will still be
[Music]
okay that's now one will be back in no
time oh
ow I wish you would attack him directly
but that's okay ah [\h__\h] yeah
okay Oren pulls out a rabbit I could ah
maybe wait maybe I can do
this a but then I won't block that
bastard again but I can upgrade him
again ooh that's a cool card
[Music]
no and is what it is guys
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow I'm still
alive I'm still
alive ow ow ow ow
dead what are these batteries is it for
the magic deck I guess
so
[Music]
oh h
does that even make sense I guess
because I could place
it I could place it uh
here
no I get bones yeah bones oh wait I
forgot to upgrade but okay didn't need
in this case death by bone Heap oh my
bone heap's getting everybody he's
heaping those bones don't kill me I'm
still alive still
alive B he gr stronger okay we have a
hawk too uh wait wait I I know what to
do
oh [\h__\h] ah fine no problem I was uh no
it is problem I need another
sacrifice I have
a I have a hawk tool
ah I out Dam Dage them now okay good
then hopefully next round I have
something else to
sacrifice okay good
good ooh ooh
ah so plan is
to put a rabbit a stout sacrifice both
Place Raven
attack also get more bones I guess in
the process of doing
that can kill the bansi with the
sto I can't wait what oh oh right cuz
the St also are ah all
[Music]
right that's right whatever then we'll
do it like that upgrade one more
time here we
go I'm enjoying that bone Heap a
lot yeah kill it with fire
hello
Adder can't play you
guys that's all have to
do come on what is this stupid fight oh
finally he's not playing anything there
so that should be the end of him
right
yeah oh Yoo you're halfway there oh I'm
halfway there
oh living
[Music]
on living on my bone
Heap what comes next [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] rip
all your
cards do you miss them what [\h__\h] she
took my bone
Heap square right on a chair no she took
my bony what is it [\h__\h] I'll give them
back yeah after the battle you mean
right as Corpse [\h__\h] you bone he already
was a Oh what how does this how does
this affect
them yeah she did a board wipe no it was
so
upgraded oh no
doio wait but the sto doesn't cost any
more blood but was it always always 01 I
don't think it was always
01 you got the salmon to carry you now
okay it was one two right yeah salmon is
the way but it needs two blood so what
am I sacrificing bone Heap and stoed can
I do that
even okay
where should we place it what's a
strategically smart place to place
it cuz wherever I place it the bone
Hound will
go and then if I put it
where like but then it always moves of
course as well anyway you like will move
yeah but like do I want it to block one
of these upper ones for example but by
putting the bone Hound where it
goes rip bone Heap I really liked
him front of Banshee but
like you do I want it to be there after
my turn or before I don't even this is
too much brain work to do I'll just
place it
[Music]
um if I place it here it will go to the
left right it won't go all the way over
here what dire to the right no wait
maybe it will go
there not
sure it will go away there okay well
let's put it
here we'll see what
happens bone Hound finally [\h__\h]
dead ah it does move to the left but
just one space I was hoping it would go
here but okay
salmon emerges from the deep oh tomb
rber activate pay one bone to create a
skeleton in your
[Music]
hand or we work
towards the six bones
first he needs he can be played for free
he has two
health I I can I could have four
skeletons now immediately if I use all
of my
bones can play free on the left in front
of bench that was so
good
okay
one do should I get endless how many
should I get all of them cuz yeah they
do give
bones of course
at all okay before he dies we got to get
its full
potential
so I'm just going to fill up the
field ah should I play should I
sacrifice them and play an add or
so
yeah or the
bird HW Tu a time a [\h__\h] ah sorry I
accident I actually was going to play
the first
I accidentally pressed the the Bell oh
well it's
okay we're going to be
fine give me some more
skeletons
so here
Unos place you
here perhaps
maybe I was thinking maybe sacrificing
the tomb robber too now and getting the
adder out but it's okay GG
already oh what
really it only took seven this time I'm
confused
it Oh I thought it was somehow game over
suddenly even though you guys were
saying GG doomed Necromancer complete
the Temple of the Dead
aha you you really defeated me I was not
expecting that I know that uh it is your
mission to replace Ley but well between
you and I there will come an opportunity
to change your mind and I beg that you
spare me take these then go
interesting it's like she knows what's
going
on Ruby
Golem Sentry
drone the Walkers when the Walkers dies
four bones are awarded instead of one
cool no bone Heap and
Frankenstein now I guess my deck was
fine after all oh wait another
one mommy Lord free free costs eight
bones headless horse man is that 13
bones Airborne also oh five five wo at
the end of okay it moves to the
right
sheh Mommy Mommy Mommy
Lord damn battery low [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] hey it fixed itself
somehow I guess we're fine okay now that
I did that oh the bridge is fixed
they did want me to go there first
huh okay then now I'll go down here I
have a feeling this is where I want to
be cuz the top part looks like magic
don't want to be there what is
[Music]
this the note reads greetings if you are
reading this it must be because you wish
to challenge me oh oh this is the mage
to a card battle but in order to earn
that privilege you must first defeat my
free graduate students as for their
whereabouts that is for you to discover
sincerely
magnificus uh why doesn't this look well
this too does look like magic but this
up here look like I I can't explain it
shut
up so should we do this first o robot
will he work with sentries what is this
puzzle oh it's like the one in the
house I don't [\h__\h]
know
no am am I these
ones I
don't
no no time to BR for course yeah um
okay stay back
then
try H changing just one thing surely
doesn't do the trick what about this
three out of
five how about this three out of five
how about this threee out of five
bruh how about this one out of five
why wait what is I don't I don't even
know what the goal really is what is the
five five
attacks
uh two out of
five but
oh everything at the
bottom okay the lock cracked open the
drawer emerged from within the device
that contained two card
packs he received a techno card pack
techno
techno oh I got 6 DM's again let me
check
[Music]
so with
other
10 uh
[Music]
uh uh
anything you want to share with the CLA
um Santa Claus is very generous this
here she
no
[Music]
okay if you're Santa is that good for
you it's okay cuz it's not coming out of
my
[Laughter]
pocket the bgm it's so scary it's not
Christmasy at
all wow winning yeah basically I'm doing
I'm I'm I'm in the midst of uh arranging
a little bit of a
giveaway and it will
[Music]
it's kind of last minute cuz I had the
idea like last
night
um but if if you guys should let me just
say you guys should check out the Advent
calendar video the first one that comes
up
in five 4 and a half
hours
oh okay
um
ah
ah uh
sorry management buying in last minute
no no no um
Vite
why I just like the admin calendar in
general thank you that that's very very
nice of
you expensive giveaway yeah
surprisingly I M oh [\h__\h] Paul does your
stomach hurt how do you know a little
bit tiny bit Christmas nudes nudes
Christmas
nudes no but I will say I I got to give
him a little bit of credit uh management
um I asked if they at least just because
it's a hassle for me to like
arrange uh moving the like payment and
or organization of the URLs Etc again
they are continuing to pay for the
server hosting I think management so
they got that credit thank you I
appreciate that well that's very nice I
asked nicely hey guys can you still like
uh like I'll pay for the graphics and
everything but can you guys continue
paying for the server or and they were
like okay uh we'll look into it and then
they were like okay no problem send us
the
bill I appreciate it just because I
don't really want to bother with
it yeah
yipp so okay what are these cards
Factory
conduit empty spaces within a circuit
completed by Factory conduit spawn leap
Bots at the end of the onus turn o lead
speak MOX module when MOX module is on
the board it provides a green orange and
blue gem to its own it's the only thing
that's making this thing here colorful
meat bot is founded as free blood rather
than one blood when
sacrificed so in the other map that we
went to I because they gave me so many
bone cards I ended up using a bunch of
them against the bone lady so would it
be the smart thing to do to do the same
thing here like use a couple of
these blue energy cards as well or can I
continue with my bones and
my uh in my blood not really do as you
like okay I'm just wondering if I have a
chance at all what is this squirrel
ball at the end of the owner turn
squirrel ball will move in the direction
it will probably roll in the direction
scribed in the sigil and drop a squirrel
in there it's cute just a ball of
squirrels like they're fighting they're
fighting and that's why they like in a
in a fluffy ball rolling around punching
each other you get one battery charge
per turn yeah I noticed that but I don't
know if I want to bother with those new
cards now we just want to keep the same
deck uh if Mage Knight's owner controls
no MOX cards Mage Knight perishes okay
whatever I don't know man shut up I
don't need these cards oh another
one oh another scre ball gor Mage
activates pay two BS this is like the
same
oh and you pay bones
again but you do need a green triangle
to play
it wait green triangle
how
a
oh I just looked at the back of my head
and it looked
like either a crab or a jellyfish on my
head or or something like this looks
like a face to me and this looks like
ears and this looks like
feet like this
blob I was like why did my hair my my
head change I'm crap what's going on
here oh another card pack I feel like
the general just as they want you to
experiment with all the different decks
because they give you so many different
card decks but M so what the power of
green Mage is equal to the number of
green gems that the owner has on their
side of the
table but wait we don't need the
gourmage we can just do the same thing
with the the bone the guy the bone guy
that I had we don't need to build this
whole deck around
gourmage I'll just do what I did before
do you want to battle challenge me let's
see your deck wait are you the boss here
we Parts total lack of synergy this pile
really doesn't send a chance again do
you always say that look I'm trying to
finish up my cond with control list here
but the Bots there standing down the
line are trash get those workers to send
me something good tell them to throw
themselves on the line if necessary and
please have a decent deck by the time
you're done okay you're the boss here
huh okay that's a St oh yeah right
that's why he became like more and more
square and then the the bug became more
and more like a lady
right you're just selling [\h__\h] again
don't care total
misplay you don't know what you're
talking
about uh do I have to check this thing
out
here what is
this what is this riddle
if it works it
works two out of six two
now easy easy easy I
understand hello robot how you doing do
you want to battle me
what is it what do you want can't you
see that I'm I'm very busy here what
perre isn't happy with my output but I
am merely the inspector to put better
bots on the line I would need to uh just
who are you to be carrying orders from
po3 P3 would only trust someone with
some semblance of card game
skill I am very busy but I must know if
you are qualified to give me orders
[Music]
2 2
2 ear
I don't know what I'm doing I'm playing
very brain empty right now please
forgive me if I
die but this is W play style
now B BL empty B
bted what just happened oh yeah they
disappear all right don't kill my
thing I I'm not even looking out what
they do you guys must hate
me make make skeleton make more
skeleton should I place skeleton I place
skeleton why not make damage go
die maybe I should have looked at oh
[\h__\h] maybe I should have looked at when
everybody does I don't know it doesn't
matter they're just like whatever I just
don't have good cards right now
[Music]
bruh we're still good he's like uh lower
than me in terms of
health oh now we got
something uh needs free bones to play I
have free bones when Bergen Noble dies
four bones okay so I'll put you there as
a wall but
[Music]
you all would you just block it okay
okay so you will attack my oall very
good very good very well very well
indeed you're working on Instinct
exactly you understand please use your
brain b shut
up I'm using my instincts do you doubt
my
instincts I want to play Adder but no
space to play these both and I don't
want to get rid of anything that's
here I can still afford one more turn
without doing anything
right as I believe in the heart of
cards it will be fine guys oh they still
didn't get rid of anything on my field
what's going on oh cuz you don't attack
right you don't attack so nothing's
going to happen you're just a wall a
meaningless empty
wall oh [\h__\h] that's boring
they have no attack without the battery
ah
ah they I killed their battery like I
took their soul ripped it out and ate
[Music]
it you all have no attack I just got to
destroy that okay well then you're no
danger to me either so I can destroy my
wall because what good are you guys to
me now
and
you yeah four bones thank
you okay I shall place you perhaps
here and I'll place you here
go there we
go things are happening again thanks to
me thinking a little bit harder about my
actions for once what is this hand they
can't do
nothing
okay we're fine it's going well what
what is this deck deck is
[\h__\h] my deck is [\h__\h] guys it it is
true fact of the matter is my deck is
[\h__\h] but I got lots of
Bones oh dear you missed from po3 must
indeed be genuine you played well even
though you have a [\h__\h] deck good job as
I mentioned I am a mere inspector not an
engineer not a designer I cannot send
new Bots down the line but I I I can
send
myself I am proud to have served P free
what faul well met
stranger no what is is this like a
Sudoku kind of moment like out of Shame
like
bro I feel
bad it's my fault I made him feel like
[\h__\h] Mage
people don't like these cards they go
into the trash I saw goo stream you were
so cute love
you thank you come
on that's sweet thank you for watching I
hope you
subscribe probably you
did you know I had a a thought that
people will only understand if they
watched a bit of gusu and know this
K-pop
artist I wonder if anybody will be able
to understand I'm a fan of a cap up idol
a solo Idol who used to be in a group
her name is yenna y n a and I a while
ago I wanted to say this already but a
while ago I noticed gosu kind of reminds
me of Yen or Yen reminds me of go maybe
more like go reminds me of Yen like her
face even G is like 3D and yen is a real
person yeah Jo Yen but her face the the
like Vibe of her face is so cute and and
cute eyes cute cheek like I don't know
it reminds me of gosu and her energy and
I feel like if gosu sang toy y songs it
would fit so well yeah from I
one so I want to hear Go Go
[Music]
sing yeah or not even that song I
actually like her other songs
more I said hey I want to make you smile
[Music]
smile that song or so
go go please sing say
all I love her
songs
[Music]
smile just smile away cute I want to
sing her songs
too okay H bloop I take cards thank you
I I hope some I there's always like
Korean Clippers as soon as I mention
Go's name there's somebody clipping it I
hope somebody clips and translates that
and and go to go sees it and then sings
a y song for me I'm awaiting
it ooh what's going on
here ooh
math okay this is more challenging that
the than the previous ones but I can do
it if I put this here and it's on uh
minus one and then it's on zero and then
maybe plus one is on two three
okay isn't it like
this it was just in that order but I
still thought about it okay I didn't
brute force
it okay it's currently at four out of
five oh easy also isn't this also easy
it's just like this what's this
oh wait
oh
N I don't understand what this does it
blocks it
oh what how am I supposed to use that
one ah maybe
here no
yeah it breaks the cycle but do I even
want to use it I
mean I don't understand this
[Music]
one
oh wait is that seven out of five
oh Maga
then I replace this oh
what
sh I boosted them all
[Music]
help no I can't move the numbers that
are already there but I can put
something on top of
them minus one in the place of the
two and then like this or what or or
like
this or what or maybe like cover one of
these too
no you have no
[Music]
idea cut one and add the remaining two
to+ one eh what do you mean
plus one on the second
tile
you you me with the right solution and
the easy phrasing cuz sometimes people
write the right thing maybe but it's not
phrased in the way that I will
understand so you understand my
brain wow you cracked the code and you
cracked the
waa wait
wait wait still not work wait wait a
second why why why
why ah do I need another thing
here I need to put all of
them ah okay
maybe [\h__\h] what what do you mean I need
to [\h__\h] okay y let's let's re yeah let's
look into this
again m no I I still have faith in you
plus one blank blank zero cancel okay
wait wait wait plus
one blank blank
zero
cancel
ahuh oh because then the minus one
doesn't matter anymore cuz the cycle has
already been
closed oh hallelujah thank
you let me out ha
a what was that I didn't say anything we
are I I am the melter they sent me raw
materials and I well you can see how it
works let me out ah not another word out
of you we must have a card battle he's
tortured he wants to
die I will help
him buff conduit other creatures with
with in a circuit completed by Buff
conduit wait wait a second within a
circuit do you mean
like is there a thing like when you play
like just in the game that we just
played like when you place them next to
each other they like add to each other
and like create a a circle Cycles thingy
circuit
oh so when I break the one that is
giving
battery if that's a
thing plus one uh then oh my God
interesting
system but we shall continue to ignore
it and just brute force all way through
it we'll
see
um
interesting think
w02 so as long as they're not connected
they're going to stay with zero attack
power right
a right
door pull out a
rabbit could
play
you and could put you like somewhere
else there we go wow perfect first play
no oh they are connected oh even though
nothing's in between oh okay
Oh I thought they had to be next to each
other but this is like still connecting
I
see ah they will fill the middle to
connect them ah but they still have no
attack power so it's
okay I guess they will never have attack
power but they're giving the ones that
are in the middle of the attack power
no but yeah uh ah [\h__\h] yeah my bird will
attack
[Music]
not
ah give me those bones for
later a
wbit h he's already dead what I was
ready no boring I was ready to
no I want to St I'm I was getting into
it I was getting into
it
no
[Music]
no okay
sorry all Santa Claus business but yeah
looking good as a battle uh even though
kind of cut short by your Genius
abilities uh that not even you expected
to pull through now with that aside what
did you come to tell me po3 wishes for
better Bots for his scanner that is
difficult you see I melt the metal but I
cannot reprogram the stamping
machine uh there is a way to send at
least one new bot down the line no no no
yes be fre oh no this is so sad what's
going on why was she so manipulated by
himself
no no poor
guy this is just like care be no it's
not it's very
different minus three a minus 5 fre okay
wait wait wait I'll I'll figure this one
out we start with one here I'll just do
the map I'll do the map if I do the map
I think is doable 1 - 2 is minus
one minus another two is minus 3 minus
another two is- 5 yeah makes sense okay
so we'll just
[Music]
put huh I have hoped that that would
work h close
close
uh wait okay so one plus
one that's just the same thing why
doesn't that
[Music]
work here
eh [\h__\h]
it works whoa I did I had
it oh it wents free I I somehow thought
it wents up to five
again wait here I did have it I did
have why was I trying to calculate up to
five I don't know okay here at want five
we're currently at
zero um sure how about we start with
getting rid of this then we're already
at
free then we'll do plus one then we're
at four we'll do zero here then we're at
six and then we'll do a minus oh my God
I can do
math if it's so like visually presented
to
me that's much easier than math at
school I appreciate it I did it for
first try and wow you all must change
your opinions about my smartness now my
IQ there's another robot in here who I
will make them uh uh bamboozle himself o
mate I know what you're here for you're
asking me to take a dive yeah but I
can't accommodate yet mate I still uh
want to go watch Marin's concert after
all before I take a d
otherwise my life will be
incomplete we can do well anyway he
maybe even give yes something if you win
but I can't be taking a dive because I
still have a ticket for
concert
ooh he's a
card all
right we have the tomb robber on her
hand and the broken
orall but nothing to safy but he also is
not even playing anything okay
okay okay now what mate can't take me
eyes of me work here I'll give you this
uh what here take your back
what he didn't even
fight what why was he like oh I I can't
take my I I have to continue
working uh I can't jump into the water
and kill myself for you so let's just
duel and then we duel and he's like
sorry actually I Can't Take My Eyes of
work I can't duel so I guess I'll just
go die
after wait is he
staying what is he doing now off with
you me I need to concentrate oh wa oh is
that here is going to reward me big for
this one oh now you want to
fight off with
you is it because I didn't do anything
in my first
turn do I wait do I have to kill him
first
turn because I mean like maybe you could
have I don't
know look what he pulled out okay let me
check
where did he pull oh
this scar what what is that why is that
so oh that will go up will that go
up what who what is that so I I go
back follow
it do you think I can take it some where
at some
point I
know but what if I Miss I still here
should I wait for it wait wait
wait up here
now what happens if you do miss
it is it coming it's
coming
oo I see things in
it interesting things that I feel like
I've seen
before and it gets melted or not does it
get does it stay normal what
happened something happened but it's
still doing its corrupted thing I can't
take it can
I no okay so I guess we'll wait until it
arrives
it's taking so
long
but doesn't everything kind of look
different now oh never
mind are just the part and he gets put
together yeah where's my corrupted
one
hello did she do the fight in the
basement basement
I don't think so did I miss a
fight I had to pee my
dog bombastic side
eye do you want to rephrase that Rena
so should we talk uh now
or oh wait there's another one that I
didn't do yet huh cuz this one's open
all right we have something to do zero
out of
five it
[Music]
it what's
happening I don't
[Music]
know let's talk to him it passed him by
now the Bots haven't gotten much better
but you battled all of my workers and
you actually won except for the last one
give me that de
again it's still the same wow you beat
them with this
[\h__\h] all right maybe there are some
synergies that I missed n it's just me
it's just pure skill I can make a [\h__\h]
deck
great it's imitating a battle board I
know I know English is not my first
language sorry for the roast but it
sounded
funny you see those conveyor belts just
like my factory oh [\h__\h] what no why you
got it complicated like that n I'm duck
it
so my cards go onto your side I don't
want to give you my cards are you
crazy GG roast me all the time
too
G have
mercy give him squirrels for robots
I don't understand this door is tricky
but it's easy if you're careful if so if
it's on that side it will automatically
be his thing but it will come back to me
and his cards come to me
or I
guess oh no at the very least they add
to test your lane
[Music]
positioning brain
H she's not orange now fake waa yes yes
I also question my
today can already play my salmon wait a
second my salmon moves against the
current and doesn't my wait does my
salmon stop the flow if
I wait how it it doesn't jump over
anything right so doesn't my
salmon well we'll see it in action I
guess we'll see I'll carefully place you
here now I'm wondering if something is
in front of my
salmon it will also push that back right
so am I not com uh creating a traffic
jam oh it will turn around
oh okay it won't push so I do want to
have it more over
here wait so if the enemy has a card
here and my salmon is here and this
field is empty the enemy card will go to
this empty field
h no
what oh you see okay do I want to play
my bone Heap
now I could already upgrade it
twice not yet your salmon will flip
yeah we don't want our salmon to
flip not when it's not not done yet
roasting on one side grilling on one
side okay move to the
right it and when is this whole thing
going to
turn now okay see how that works okay
your
turn uh
M ah right it cost two bones for one
upgrade M ooh we got this one but it
will take a while until I can play
it my I get his meat bot next okay but
what does it really do it counted as
free blood rather than oh I should
sacrifice him when I get
him
uh May complete a circuit but provides
no effect uhuh in sector drone will
strike an opponent directly even if
there is a creature opposing
it when explode but dies the creature
opposing it as well as adjacent friendly
creatures are dealt
damage how do I deal with this I could
bring it over to my side like hope that
it doesn't die until it's on my side but
but it even hurts adjacent friendly
creatures
so don't hit it yeah I
[Music]
guess well we'll see I guess I don't
know if I should place my bone Heap now
maybe still
not CU I'm I'm still worried like what
will
happen will what well what would what
would he do if he gets my bone he
killing it on his side only loses one
yeah right now I guess
so might be ripped for the salmon you
take one damage give it for lat
okay well one one of his cards is
gone okay I have this thing
now
I I don't have a good card to make use
of the um blood that it would give me
now maybe next
round maybe next
round yeah I can wait to sacrifice I
still have I I have it for a while
longer after
all but I still don't know what I should
do now this turn
either he's going to kill me go the
robot
oh oh if I don't oh if I don't sack it
he'll kill
him okay then I might as well take it
no play the
St oh yeah
oh I don't
know wait
no no wait I couldn't stop that though I
couldn't have stopped
it I got I ain't got no control over my
salmon salmon do what the salmon want to
do
well we got tomb Rubber and Bone he
that's interesting P one bone to create
a skeleton in your
[Music]
hand let's get those
skeletons tomb rber seems good here
okay you can use it but he can't oh does
he not have any
bones
good I don't know I'm so so like
questioning should I put down a
skeleton after attacking it perishes so
as long as I put it here it will attack
and then go away and he won't have any
benefits of it so let's damage and then
disappear and I get my bone back so yeah
that's actually pretty good no ST
ch
um oh he has another one of
these that give me free blood but I
still don't have anything that I want to
use that
for um but I'll have it come over to my
side so I'll keep this spot EMP this
spot empty empty for
now I'll make more
skeletons and
go oh hey this boy I forgot this was on
my
side didn't realize
it so are you going there ow [\h__\h] yeah B
how how much until I
die save your bones
five three he needs 11 5 uhhuh
uhhuh
ooh okay I don't like this fight it's
too much thinking but okay
[Music]
um I
could uh place
[Music]
skeleton
again and
and well
yeah no need to overthink it
really my bone guy is leaving us now but
that's
okay thanks for protecting me
good boy he's such a good
boy wait can I even still push this
button when he's on the other side it it
blinks up but I'm guessing
not trigger bomb with Skelly oh no he's
got more bombs okay but it will kill my
tomb
robber
oh
well we already got a lot of skeletons
out of it wor your sacrifice
okay but I should have put skeleton here
too maybe
oopsie ooh big explosion
yeah
um okay okay what got what what he got
is this his last card when an opposing
creature is placed oppos opposite to
move to space okay uh
oh yeah that's fine wait I almost got
six but it doesn't really
matter oh but I don't want him to get
this bones will he get bones from that
if it's on his side when it
dies don't play anything else
what I'm just a
rip
oh I was I was actually Pro purposefully
I'm hoping that he attacks the broken
oall so that I uh get the
bones I could have gotten the Hound next
turn almost big brain FL
no if you did you would have lost
because skeletons would break uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh well we'll see we'll just
let it let the game do its thing run its
cause the skeletons did damage and my
obal is gone and I get the bones
wonderful that's what I was hoping that
it would
do uh okay what are all these [\h__\h]
cards wait you know what we make our
bone Heap super strong now we'll do that
now yeah yeah yeah is that the card we
just got so I'll put it here so I have
it for as long as possible although the
dog will move
there right side cart ah right side cart
last
okay
uh just place a squirrel afterwards
yeah
wait do I want something else
also I could uh
sacrifice this
guy and put
[Music]
down
you I'm going to put the opal here and
then put a squirrel like anywhere
afterwards yeah
and make it like super
strong okay it has four five
now
okay does that look
good looks looks good good looks pretty
good even now it will attack
directly upgrade One More Time 5 six
baby now I
[Music]
win all right
uh
victory victory oh wait second round oh
no how you going to change it don't wipe
my don't you dare wipe my car oh
scanners online which card to
scan just kidding obviously the one with
the no no what do you mean scan are you
taking
it oh he's changing the effect stat line
could be
better wait what are you doing you're
move he stole it wait but he can't use
it can he
he copied my strongest
card he didn't copy the Boost so yeah oh
oh
oh and I got his I got his Hound
now oh
boy
huh uh oops Yeah okay H yeah then I'll
just leave the field like that I
thing cuz I don't want to sacrifice
either of
these
H take a little bit of
damage ooh I
don't want him to get it can I we'll be
fine will'll be fine this is is this
enough yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
nice luck you had oh thank God thank God
that was close like he was one more
round found the away from getting my
super strong boy oo that worked out
well no Overkill it's okay oo got
him with that shitty deck I mean it's
not that shitty though is it it's okay
it could be a better deck but it's it's
uh used by a skillful mind a genius mind
bone Heap strong I guess you want your
ambition is to become the Scribe of
Beast that soft-minded stump you ought
to
reconsider no I don't know why why why
tell me more like explain yourself don't
just leave me hanging like
that no Cliffhanger
please well oh again battery low again
wait this time it turned off
[Music]
[Applause]
restarting B
fo wait what oh is that new footage
that's new footage
right I think I've just got to send
it to whom am may
concern it's a bit formal
hello there wait I forgot uh just to re
re remember because it's been a while
this is not us right we're not this guy
he's just
somebody who found all this stuff before
wait it is me
oh oh he is us okay well then okay good
exclamation point my name is Luke Carter
and I'm a fan of your colle You' ever
taken a look at my YouTube videos you
will know how appreciative I am of the
merch that you've sent me over the years
so it was a great surprise to learn that
there is a digital version of
inscription I think maybe one of my fans
pranked me and buried a copy in the
woods near my house upon further
research however I have not been able to
find any record of this game is this
some kind of elaborate
hoax interesting any trace of this game
is this some kind of elaborate hoax the
game doesn't seem like the work of a
prankster it at least appears
professionally made yeah both puzzled
and excited by this discovery any
information you can provide would be
much appreciated thank you love you
Carter okay good
enough how do you do
that I don't know how you do
that that he did it way louder than that
or is it that
though I'm I I can just do pops
quietly oh
oh
oh P your lips as do yeah I just did
that
now you press your teeth against your
inner lips make it sound louder mhm
you're just asking for a kiss ah you
scamed
me hey card Gamers I'm the lucky Carter
and
this well it's a bit of a strange video
um it's actually more of a question to
my audience as I've learned over the
years nobody knows card games better
than you guys do I'm hoping someone can
help me out here back seating
requested did anyone ever play an
inscription video game I did or hear
about it I'm talking about that vintage
one set card game I open packs for last
week
M I don't know what I'm allowed to say
he's like the way he acts and just
looked you could just replace
inscription with like a lady's name and
it sounds like he's just so in love and
like with this mysterious woman
Cinderella perhaps
and asking if anybody knows her because
he met her and she just disappeared at
midnight and oh my God like he looks so
just
Bewitched he wants her so
bad I don't want to get in any trouble
here
um I think I've got the only known copy
of the digital version of inst oh you
think you got the only known
filming myself playing it and uh you
think you're special it's weird guys uh
you're weird I don't want to get any hot
water by showing the footage but why
show it someone please prove me wrong
please tell me someone has a copy of
this game gek keeping online for days
and I cannot find a word I cannot
confirm or deny if I ever saw this game
before unless you show me what you
saw don't hide it I reached out to the
Publishers hoping maybe
get back to me but as a fall back I got
you beautiful viewers how do you know
I'm beautiful that's creeping me out can
you see my
webc that's it video today guys uh thank
you so much as always and um oh yeah uh
what the [\h__\h] is the
car why did it end
there why did it glitch
Mr Carter we have receiv ining a digital
of our
intellectualists comp to return US
computer frud AB [\h__\h] they're making
that [\h__\h] up considered stolen if it is
not returned to us stolen carefully the
what do you mean stolen when you say
such thing doesn't exist it can't be
stolen can
it
of theage at a local office you would
like to avoid taking legal action
doesn't exist but you must return it
yeah return software sus sincerely gamea
customer happiness
Department
sus what the [\h__\h] yeah right right I
know I agree indeed I'm with you bro
something's fishy super
fishy okay good
talk I think This Woman's actually from
gamea she came to my door yesterday and
I didn't answer this time I'm going to
record
it
what hi hi there creepy smile wait it's
again call it incription why do you know
our address bu a copy of it
somehow uh is that familiar no no no I
don't know anything about that
incription she looks so normal though no
I don't think
so really take your foot out of my door
right now you emailed us about it you
are right this game company freak outter
gmail.com yeah uh you know what that's
uh I am Luke Carter but that's not email
address really
because I've noticed because I've seen
your videos oh
a liar thanks for
watching close the door listen uh how do
you know where I live exactly yeah my
boss gave me your address and how did
you get past the side gate it's
locked okay luk um I'm going to give you
my business card and if you remember
anything anything at all feel free to
give me a
call okay we'll do is she hitting on us
now take
care maybe she doesn't care about the
game at all what the [\h__\h] she just wants
to you know hopefully hopefully
hopefully why is why so much
corruption hey there card Gamers I'm the
you're
looking spy upop man what
happened lucky Carter and this is
another pack opening video did you get
laid today I'm opening secrets of
legendaria oh different gameing for that
sweet sweet foil he has been
silenced he's sad he looks so depressed
he can't even open card packs anymore
[\h__\h] oh bro is he like I can't do this
[\h__\h] these cards I I can't look at any
other cards present description cards
anymore that's the one and only true
love I
have but I thought your channel was
about all kind of card games come on
stay true to yourself
well interesting
lore back to the
[Music]
game are you're not going to talk
anymore to me how did we how did we get
into watching those videos in the first
place also what's this thing about the
basement that you guys said also we
still need to finish this
one okay okay I can do this I I can
actually do it by not brute forcing it
you will see thank you for the
memberships you you um
he has two Health one damage I need to
do five damage to him in
total
right so this evens itself
out care a first your first oh my oh
that one's a
bomb
Oh that one's also bomb though
and this what is this though forign
damage isard
by oh but yeah and then it dies and then
makes it
Kaboom and this also makes Kaboom so
well but then okay wait what is it
[Music]
what I said I wasn't going to boo for
said but basically the cards right next
to each other and the opposing card
should die when it explodes
right just don't use your bomb
okay what about
this
no but this this and this card will die
by me attacking the bomb right
I don't
understand just don't let your bomb take
yeah I put it
down oh right I could move
theirs
uh left to right it goes left to right
oh in order you
mean
uh uh oh okay so two
two one
oh wait five damage to like just do five
damage in total even to cards or five
damage to the person
behind like direct
damage person face down okay
[Music]
ah two
three but what does this card do
you need enemy
bomb
bro I don't understand
whatever I don't need to
[Music]
understand it's whatever oh that one had
four and the obal
card now should I leave this one's done
right
the ah the bomb blew up the no sign
card I guess
[Music]
so think in order what happen in each
attack check left for glitched thing oh
true true interesting
[Music]
where
go what
point when
fall where
going what
thank
you it
just it it poof it
poof magician CH before I challenge you
let me see if I can improve my deck I I
don't want these stupid Warren anymore
why do I have five of these okay I'll
put
one one one just
[Music]
one when another creature you own dies
is return to alive and dies again
immediately ah what else should I put in
add more bone Heap yeah I was thinking
about that too but do I have enough like
[Music]
yeah I can like spread it out I mean I
mean do I have enough like bone output
[Music]
input 13 bones to
play Four bones are awarded
[Music]
no I don't know about these cards
n maybe I'll add H generally I think we
also would benefit
[Music]
from maybe another thing that costs
blood and does
damage yeah so I'm
thinking let's put
in another
Hawk maybe the Bears I was thinking
about the bear
too maybe is this too much a hawk and a
Grizzly I'll I'll we'll see but wait
that's still 19 out of 20
[Music]
maybe another Adder cuz I barely see the
adder but I do like the
adder 20 cards I'm happy with 20 cards
let's see how it goes so this
here
said uh kill my other dudes are they in
huh
huh a strange monacle you put it on
oh Sparkle the note reads greetings if
you read
[Music]
uhuh
wait that means something doesn't
it but
what ah never
mind so there's something like a
skull RI thank
you happy
birthday uh a wing another skull
so in that order
or oh
easy whoa
[Music]
ew
ew this is what happens to
you if you drink too
much energy drinks or the green the
green what's the green drink called
again what's the green Dr um that that
everybody loves in America Mountain de
yeah this happens if for your whole life
you only drink Mountain
Dew this is what you end up as a green
toxic oopsie jelly puddle sticky puddle
with a cute hat and a cute face you'll
keep your cute face oh wait that one
doesn't look so cute anymore so let's
try to not become like
[Music]
this the pain is
unbearable my organs are
melting you see
magnific
me go for my final exam I just need to
defeat one more Challenger then I will
earn my rightful
place my rightful place in the deck of
the b as one of his prized
cards nothing will stop
me except for me oh cute I like his
Battlefield it's so sparkly what a
beautiful night
sky what do you got the power of green
Mage is equal to the number of green
gems that the owner has on their side of
the table
uhhm while Emerald MO is on the board it
provides a green gem to his own so you
have one gem so all these have one power
right so you always have to have one of
these on there unless otherwise these
have no nothing
whoa mhm
thanks for the good
[Music]
play
attack no Bon he hello um give us a
moment I'm not sure I want to play do I
want to play you I'm not sure I want to
play you
yet power gone there we go oh he's got a
new one h
[Music]
okay all right now we can go zoomy zoom
zoom zoom ah kill it no kill
it
[Music]
ah kill
it K it yes good job o interesting
though if you unless if you keep on
providing the the energy
then that's an interesting way of
playing but you suck you're going to die
regardless at his Touch of death kills
instantly
yipp now it's team's worthless yeah he's
got no more energy so what are you going
to do now you ain't got no plan B either
it
seems sysy baka
I will destroy you I will be the end of
you I make it it's a skeleton I don't
know what to do with it now but uh
whatever we just continue attacking cuz
he's not even adding anything
new all right all right y y I could have
probably such a pot him mou shut
up did you write that AR did you did you
huh
betrayal no please please just tell the
master I passed he won't know the here
take this
bag
a I almost feel bad oh frog B frog I
haven't seen him in a while and he looks
so cute in that picture
in those low
pixels here I can open the door for you
again to the left to the
left was there anything else to open in
that like these chests can you open oh
you
[Music]
can no wait then let me go back to the
other room there was one there too
every deck I own and a pack to the
left
just everything I own in a pack to the
left there's my
salmon moving down the stream to kill
you when you
sleep my salmon doesn't just taste that
fine
uh it is so good your soul will mine
yeah when life gives you lemons then put
them on your salmon it just tastes best
yep
D salmon lemon
good eat food
yum okay ah no accident please I good
views what's going on in here the dummy
stares lifelessly back at
you oops sorry I didn't read the other
sentence but I guess we
fight we shall fight force Mage if a
creature would attack Force Mage it does
not ah
huh how do I kill
it either way
[Music]
h
webit
h wait no I want I should have played
the adder cuz does it does it die when I
attack with the add or does it still not
count as like does the blocking
overpower the
perishing or
does it does
okay the other want okay damn it damn
it
even that sucks okay
whatever two damage salmon moves to new
space salmon like these space salmon
attack
again salmon moves to new space salmon
like this
space
salmon salmon attack salmon move to this
space where salmon still attack oh what
fight don't
no I was going to show you my God play
moment
but you know what I was trying to do
right I was being
smart you
know the dummies hinges Creek back into
position and it returns to its lifeless
stare okay all right but
what what we fight again we fight again
uh I didn't want to lame no leave me
alone oh but wait you really don't do
[\h__\h] you're so in
character you you don't do anything oh I
can't you don't do anything
you don't you don't he's a training
dummy you need to kill the cards I have
to
huh what do
[\h__\h] I do I have to
or like does it give me anything for the
riddle he's is an anonymous actor for
sing a
character you don't have to okay good
thanks for clearing that
[Music]
up how do I solve this riddle though
well maybe the the answer is not here it
led me back to the
[Music]
beginning let's go
here it's just a [\h__\h] traitor
again that won't help
[Music]
me there's also the floor puzzle but you
can grind for foils
afterwards why would I grind for
foils Oh you mean this is the floor
puzzle is that what you're talking about
this thing here cuz I was thinking that
I have to do that to move on in this oh
right otherwise his door doesn't
open buy AO BOS he has
that is it
worth my monies do I have money wait I
do I have
money I guess we're trading are we
trading he doesn't have Oro
BOS dummy is is the
puzzle dummy is the
puzzle a [\h__\h] is it the the placement of
his
[Music]
card unless she has the AO I don't I
don't remember why why why why would we
want that anyway I I I don't understand
what
what okay I'll try to kill his cards
then
a so I do need to kill the cards
otherwise I'm not getting the solution
here but how will
I find out what this one is when I can't
get rid of this one
did it have
this poison can kill it
so
skull
oh
ah
push
wait and fly
skill push Wing skill push Wing skill
push Wing skill push Wing skill push
[Music]
Wing
wait go go go
go skill push Wing remember
chat I remember skill push ring there we
go there we go there we go es SK oh SK
skull skull push
Wing I don't know what's wrong with
me I mean I don't know if it's really in
that order though
because okay it was in that order cuz if
you killed them in a different order you
would have seen the signs in a different
order but okay ooh what's going on in
here a witch head on a
pike
[Music]
H
uh ju just just just just imagine you
are an ice cube slowly melting on a hot
pan oh I was only talking to myself the
pain of being ahead impaled on a spare
is well it is worth it of course
magnificus will award me the highest
honor I've will be the centerpiece and
the centipede of his
deck yeah we can make a centipede out of
you we just got to add some more heads
to your poke
stick uh what do you got something
interesting orange
gem
uh okay so I want to kill this one
first when we Goen par or Ruby MOX oh is
great in this
place if Mage Knight's owner controls no
MOX cards Mage Knight
perishes okay I want to take
down both of
these
[Music]
immediately I could have played the hawk
but the hawk won't really help me
at this moment not in the way I wanted
to
so we shall H let the stealth
[Music]
destroy
well maybe I should have killed the Ruby
Golem
first it is what it is wait oh what's
going on
never mind of course I totally
understand everything that is going on
completely I would like to replay that
cuz now also my cards aren't good I
don't want to play the
Hawks but I need to yeah like out damage
[Music]
him maybe I'll get something
better well well well I can block with
this at
least
mhm aha you come back to me
[Music]
now what's this MOX cards on the owner
side of the board gain one power uh oh
uhoh no no no no no
[Music]
no oh [\h__\h] and ah yeah no we're fine
we're fine we're fine we're fine T come
on
seven what why do I keep on getting the
same cars I have like pretty good
variety in my deck and I keep on getting
the Hawks and the squirrels and the strs
that's all I got so
[Music]
far
ah so yeah this one I killed one of
these and it created the Ruby mod
and then Ruby MOX gives uh him an orange
gem but now we'll kill that one
[Music]
too I guess you're winning for now
double hog for the win yeah but then
really should
I we can try that's six damage oh that's
already Overkill
okay I thought I didn't think you meant
it so l L Al I thought you were more
like you know spiritually double Hawk
for the win Hawk T
yeah perhaps that will not be Central to
this to his strategy I care not he can
use me as a jump blocker I have mastered
disappointment I have mastered
disappointment bro that's so sad me too
though me too take this
pack yippe cards I will never use
yippee I really need to like get to end
this soon I need to work on my
video go thank you
bye-bye ooh free
pieces the not R the top C is found by
The
[Music]
Grey hard of hearing or by those who
hear too
easily pale pale as an
impaled that's the only one I understand
so
[Music]
far oopsie why is she retro cuz the game
retro need to really think outside the
box for this one well let's think ins
inside the box for this one to get a
card a
single a single
rabbit single
rabbit wait a
second what do we have rabbit this is
the this the rabbit we got a rabbit in
the box that's one of the sigils I don't
know if it's the first one but it's
definitely one of them okay then in this
maybe means that I find the sigil by the
the impaled which I got to go back for
and then heart of hearing I
guess it's probably by the dummy cuz the
dummy don't check
again what me let me try
to I mean he had several sigils in his
[Music]
battle but the impaled is there any sign
here wait how do I get to the impaled
again oh I can't go back to those
anymore can I cuz those are like
[Music]
fights
uh clothes are only in that room
[Music]
go
okay let me
leave how do I
leave
I how do I go I want to go home
is this pale uh what this is just I
don't know let me out I can't think ah
thank you wait so we have a skrull and I
do still believe in the
[Music]
bunny all let me read this
again found by the
pale found by the heart of hearing or
those who don't hear too
easily found by the greedy
[Music]
greedy
greetings is this a hint does you said
only that room but that room connected
to this room
[Music]
so think outside the
box only that room okay okay
[Music]
okay uh is there anything else in these
Corners oh
it's another entrance to the
[Music]
skull a a door I can't open
you read
oh ah cuz normally it gives more than
just one card and so you reach in to get
more cuz I'm greedy and notice a Sigil
where the card used to be a
wing so the greedy
one uh wait what the top is the wing
and then maybe I'll just like try to
brute force it and
[Music]
say
solution jump
scare I didn't use my
bunny and I don't know why there was
that one
why I don't understand my solution
no
anyway stimulate that's just me stim
last Last At Last At Last At
Last At Last At Last
At
Last At Last
stimulation my test has been sensory
deprivation you
see to unlock the full potential of my
mind you see it's a luck now hear me
magnificus I
ready have to battle
okay oh he's suddenly square and a card
[Music]
he's got
sapphires we'll strike upon it
[Music]
directly if G fiend's owner controls no
MOX card Z perish okay simple I like it
yet I have nothing to
sacrifice but I got my
Grizzly well well well
okay your
turn
ow Square world time okay so as quickly
as possible I guess I shall
[Music]
kill
you will I survive another turn if I do
this yeah I should right
cuz oh but then he's moving down he's
replacing him basically very bad hand
indeed yeah I could I could bring out
the bone he I could have brought out the
bone Heap I could have I could have
sacrificed sto and Bone Heap to play a
hawk or so
[Music]
but
yeah H wait he perished before the new
mock came in okay okay okay I didn't
think it would work like that that's
good then well we're on times four
that's a problem though we need to we
need to come back with a lot of damage
now
[Music]
um and the problem is I can't block this
damage so that's one on
[Music]
me summon
Bird yeah
but should I get rid of the sto for it
or should I get rid of the sack for it
in combination with the
squirrel hwk Heap up hwk and Heap up hwk
and Heap up what uh to
have so you mean
like
this and I where should is there a good
place to put
[Music]
in maybe
here or maybe I should have put him here
no it doesn't matter cuz he will attack
the he will attack the opponent directly
and then I'll place this boy this bad
boy I'll put him right here and I'll
power him up and that will get rid of
the mock
oh but wait actually doing me a big
concern now [\h__\h] are we good I okay
we're good we're good I totally knew all
of this was going to happen yep yep yep
yep yep yep yep good good good because
that one also disappeared when the MOX
was gone no MOX no
power uh he's got another one coming up
but we're taking care of that one no
[Music]
worries I can play this but I can only
activate it once but we could put him
here I can just put him here he'll be
safe and then I'll put the
skeleton here for
fun
oh we're looking better on the damage
now
aha oh
oops do we want to upgrade our bone Heap
or do we want to summon another
skeleton you can use bones to summon the
bear
what what do you
mean Skelly and Boren
mhm uhhuh I see what you
mean you want me to sacrifice a
skeleton for the
Warren and then
no I mean you know I could
still like yeah I was thinking of that
too
no be
time what do you want me to
sacrifice now you can boost Heap all
right yeah we do have a bit more bones
now I could sacrifice like The Bunny The
HW and the Tom robber for the
grizzly I guess
but well
let's
close a wait wait wait
wait how about
this I could have even upgraded I forgot
to upgrade the no I could have done more
excess damage oh
no should have upgraded my tomb rber oh
well it's
fun that was
incredibly
stulting we are done here right I wish
to see the light again to to sing to
dance you wouldn't live
you they're all kind of insane in
here I'm worried I will become like
them please let me out of
here if I open the door you'll stop by
on the way back and let me out
right honestly I'd love to I want to see
what
you're capable of oh what's going on
here he looks like a Christmas tree
[Music]
let me read this the not reads dearest
grimora I believe PE Free's plot may go
far past the extent of a common power
grab indeed this great Transcendence
will have catastrophic and unpredictable
results the note is incomplete and ends
abruptly I urge you to
consider okay he's painting something
let's just talk to him oh he is kind of
a tree
[Music]
a you're here at last how do my pupils
Fair no matter there are far more
concerning issues at hand do you
understand the canvas that you have been
moven
into n you are the brush and the artist
moves you with a terrifying
Mastery my eye aches with premonition
the future is very very Grim first we
must
battle oh oh he's got a brush what's
what are you going to do with that
behold the brush Of The Scribe of
magics my pupil would die to be painted
by it and live forever as a card but
that is not the the full extent of its
[Music]
powers this one needs some
bleach hey what are you doing with my
Tom
robber [\h__\h] oh no you didn't did you
choose that
[Music]
randomly now for a bit of color oh you
replacing it with something else plus
what what one wait wait wait what are
you doing what SK stop SK scop scoop
hey he changing everything up my whole
hand every
turn
o what what am I supposed to do with a
ruby
MOX the striker then dealt a single
damage point the
striker oh yeah yeah okay mock cards on
the owner's side of the board G what am
I supposed to do with that
you little [\h__\h] get out of here stop
mocking me you're mocking
me [\h__\h]
you
what
a nine
[Music]
nine iax and enjoy the song it's really
good but he destroy my
deck so I'll destroy
his the the
the the you
know
[\h__\h] this card is now useless it's just
a wall for me cuz it doesn't do anything
I can play it for free and it has two
Health but I can't do anything else with
it I guess it's a
sacrifice yeah wait I could have played
this and the squirrel and played the
hawk oh
[Music]
well it attacks
back
[\h__\h] wa wait stop painting my
[\h__\h] my brain already hurts
[Music]
wait wait I forgot now the bird doesn't
fly
anymore which is kind of good in this
case but then I would have liked to
place it in front of this guy I know I
know I know I know I I I I I if I
realized that it was attacking directly
I would have placed it in front of him
I'm doing everything
wrong he's playing me like a
fiddle oh whatever I never I never was
able to make use of that original effect
anyway so do what you want I
guess well I can't play it
right oh
no oh no my
hwk no I don't need this no don't take
it away from me
I should have made a deck that uh like I
can use the moxes
for a
[Music]
[\h__\h] do I get bones when I Bonk
that I can't do
anything
I I almost complain this and then I
could sacrifice both to get the adder
but yeah no believe me you do not want
that
oh use magic carts or
die you going to redo you dick I don't
have time for this I still need to go to
the other wait oh no is this the last H
the last area almost the last how far am
I from finishing this act I want to
finish the act and then uh get to work
soon but I I still have time I my video
doesn't need that
much that much effort it's fine it's
fine it's fine you need to fight Ley
okay last are okay okay and then lushy
[Music]
okay kill me then just kill me
bro
really I don't want to play your stupid
cards
when I play when I put auto complete
does it use these
cards yes it does all right I'll do it
with your with your random deck without
looking any more into it but just try
should
okay oh
[Laughter]
no oh be
fine this will go well I already did
pretty well of the [\h__\h]
deck those Sig so
colorless oh you like the other one huh
a bit of paint
now gave me
forns oh you're keeping that one huh all
right all right uh
so when orange Mage perishes a ruby MOX
is created in this
place uh once Gorman just struck the
strike is then delt a single damage
point because of the forns yeah but you
need one green to be played you need one
orange to be
played right
and uh you can be played for free and
you give me an orange
[Music]
gem so I want to keep you on the board
as long as
possible and now I can place you but you
don't have any attack what does this do
um
it provides a green gem to its owner
also while it's on the board it provides
an orange gem so orange and green and
you don't need anything cool I'll place
you here now I
have orange and
green but none of these have any
attack
uh perhaps I can play him here because
he will be struck by the green Mage
right and then I'll Attack back like
that oh yeah and now you get attacked
back right yeah at least
something
oh um provides blue and provides
green yeah great but like what am my
I should have looked at what cards
they're putting into my
deck um give me a better card
please oh
no at least that one's
gone what are you
doing he's got at least one attack and
leaves a MOX in his
place he got one attack he's got one
attack he's got to use it
wisely uh if jami's owner controls no ah
well you do have a lot of
mocks uh wait wait
[Music]
wa card I need to kill this card I need
to kill this card but this is is it the
way
no and it won't kill my card
either Mama
Mia use Hammer I don't
[Music]
know just put this [\h__\h] here I don't
care
oh no what are you doing with my
interesting card that used to have an
interesting effect not anymore but now
it has Shutterbug when Shutterbug is
played you draw cards equal to the
amount of MOX cards on the your side of
the board I see but it needs five energy
so I can't play that e
yet ah this is so
stupid this is so stupid
this is so
[Music]
stupid I don't care kill
me um
what are you doing what hey hey hey ah o
o o o
[Music]
o you draw cards equal to the amount
which should I play the
gourmage I'm thinking of playing the
gourmage here
obviously at least I'm doing I'm giving
everybody some power
we got to fight
back we might be so
back you think so well you know the
thing is though he this one's hard to
take down and he's got one attack right
now but wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait before he attacks I will first kill
this one which takes away his attack
okay okay and then this one disappears
too yeah yeah oh yeah yeah wait yeah you
gone your attack is gone good good good
good good good good good we might be so
back
uh-huh uh-huh a rabbit is created in
your hand a rabbit is Define okay rabbit
rabbit rabbit don't need the rabbit but
uh here we'll put this one
here oh I got a field mice why is why
why are field mice in my deck
anyway okay okay
okay he's he's is he running out of
carts
we're so
bad yay let's
go summon the
mice mice have two attack ooh
two two attack but summon by killing
what what what do we not need we need
this um we might not need this
you guys are so controlling of
me all I ever say is because you put the
words into my
mouth now put moves into my mouth like
tell me what to actually do
here uh what
okay m shut up shut
up the mocks will die so sack it the go
Run's
Mo okay but I need to sack another one
ah these two right I I guess oh this one
is unsackable
oh okay I'll stack oh wait this one's
also
unsackable okay yeah it does say can't
be sacrificed all right I'm not doing
that I guess we're just um yeah H oops
no no no sorry
uh
attack
oh
if okay
uh stem Mage once stem Mage is struck
the striker is then dealt oh okay and
you will have one attack right because
of my gour
Mage so so yeah what oh oh it's some the
mo oh I see
okay I think I'll huh oh I don't have
orange oh [\h__\h]
I don't have
orange but this
one would work for
example just whatever does damage
whatever some mocks even the tiny one
damage I will take
it oh let me play the Oru
mock go just do whatever I don't care
but we need some Dam damage over
here wait wait wait I can't keep on
doing this I need damage oh okay or not
actually no no no no no we're fine we're
fine as long as we do enough direct
damage we're fine which we'll soon we'll
get
there oh and reset okay good good good
good what what are you going to do
now I must be slowing down with
h I may need to set my brush upon my own
cards once
again your own cards your own cards what
what what
what um whatever attack as long as I
have these cards I'm going to continue
attacking with them until you kill them
oh he really is using it on his own
cards
uh Ruby MOX is created in this place
uhhuh a ruby Mox
oh does this mean I only have two cards
left in my deck it's fine it's fine it's
fine GG
really uh what should I I can place uh
[Music]
you oh that's it already
Okay yippee
very well we have battled and now I may
speak you see my
eye it aches because it remembers it was
excited by none other than Lei The
Scribe of beasts and a beast he is
arrogant single-minded obsessed with
gaining power but he is far from the
worst scribe to become hergon
you see the ejection of my eyeball is
far from the worst thing that can happen
around here you must be especially aware
of oh oh oh oh
oh hey aware of what a
home glitch in The Matrix once again you
like my VA thank you I am after all a
VA so I should be good at
vaing mhm
[Music]
uh uhuh grap
Digger shall we change our deck I I wish
I could have saved the deck that I had
previously I just want to go back to
that
deck I don't want to keep this stupid
deck I want to give
me let's auto
complete uh
oh oh it mixed everything did
it I don't want this I don't oh no no no
it didn't really mix any it mostly went
with the no aut complete why okay let's
try to remember what I have I surely had
maybe two squirrels probably
more um I had uh bone Heap times two and
I had a to tomb Town robber a tomb
robber
M I had one of
these um I had one of these but I never
really ended up using it so let's leave
it I had a stout but we don't
necessarily need to bring that one how
about we bring the
bullfrog
[Music]
and one of
these two of
these one of these
two of these a
grizly
and Hawk
Hulk oh wait
oh just one R add more
srels how many did I have
before is six enough you ever use a
griet I I I it just barely it just it's
just never on my head
hand and when it's on my hand even then
I'm like kind of having troubl using it
but oh the other broken all ball you
mean I should have
both I
mean oh this one still gives me the
[Music]
four yeah sure
only need two
adders but I like them ah the pH no no I
said like even you know I never actually
got to use its effects it's kind of
sad cuz I always in even when I had lots
of Bones they were usually all pumped
into these two
[Music]
boys okay let's just see how it goes
with yeah one more squirrel
okay then let's go fight Lei hopefully
we can kill him and fight him easily
oh hey this
room what can I do
here
oh oh the great ccken great ccken
submerges itself during the opponent's
[Music]
turn you're not as good as I was hoping
you would be
cracking let's get
[Music]
cracking you
know I don't know why I'm thinking of
this now but I I had a a phone call with
my
besti like
yesterday
and she told me about you know her
studies and all that and then I I I I
remember
something I don't know why it didn't
come to me earlier I think it's because
recently I had this eye opening moment
on
Twitter that I am
Gus and I just need I need I realized I
need a Walter I need a
Walter and I actually have a Walter in
my BFF and I asked her yo girly did you
ever watch Breaking Bad and she said she
did not everything but she did so she
knows what I mean when I I say like I
ask her can you be my Walter
White cuz she actually I asked her like
would you be able to do the same things
with your knowledge as Walter White and
she's like yeah and I'm like uh can you
make can you make the blue stuff and
she's like well I could but I we would
need the
equipment that equipment is not really
you know that's that's
no no no no no she knows very much about
chemistry it's all a joke of course but
obviously I'm very straight edged and I
would never like that's insane but it's
funny because I am the chicken lady with
a big fast food Empire and my best
friend knows everything she needs to
know about
chemistry
hello it's right there so I I joked with
my friend I told her look yo we can make
Millions we could make millions she's
like yeah oh my God too bad we're both
very very we have just a too good of a
moral
compass so where do I fight Le back to
his house
huh I'm a chemist it really isn't that
difficult to cook well yeah I'm
sure probably really isn't what was with
you no fish no pass oh do I get a fish
after I kill
Lei I have salmon what else do you
want Oh you also have one of these
still five you
say this one makes it
perish how about we do this makes the
parish five you say
what is
this what do you mean
zero what do you
[Music]
mean
oh two
two
three five there you go yeah
ooh oh those are my kind of cards ooh
Ghost
Ship o
oh drop
skeletons I don't know do I want that
actually no maybe not necessarily I'm
fine with my current deck actually oh
another
one meman when an empty space would be
struck meman will move to that space to
receive the strike instead also M men
will block an opposing creature bearing
the airs
oh funny
though anything else you got here you
got the
safe numbers wait I mean there's numbers
outside oh [\h__\h] wrong
room interesting that uh I'm I I come
from this side cuz normally wasn't the
entrance
273 the entrance was
here but yeah
two seven free sounds easy a stinking
pile of meat is it
fish wait is it
[Music]
fish no fish no
pass do you want stinking pile of
meat give me some proof she's all right
maybe get her some food
[Music]
whoit there's something down there can I
go
there no there's some eyes opening there
his
dog where is his dog is that his
dog I can't I don't think I can go
there oh never mind oh there's the dog
took a picture of the dog why don't I
just tell the guy to go oh because uh he
doesn't want to open the path he's got
to protect the path huh well I'll be
darn that's my girl I'll let you pass me
and into Yonder Pond but dnab it first
we got a battle
oh uh Pokemon battle music
starts bam
bam I don't really remember how it goes
properly ah it's finally looking
relatively normal again in
here I missed this look this wooden look
you got a squirrel that's all you
got
really what you cooking with that
squirrel squirrel stew oh he's got a dog
now the dog that I just gave the stinky
meat
to well I'll just
continue oh he's already dead he's
already dead I wi you
win easy win fair fair you beat me like
a dog take this some say these cards are
better than
[Music]
gold really just seems like
a my baby my
baby my
baby my baby my baby my baby you came
back to me m
if only I could en chanted like like
make it more powerful I'll just replace
the oh G I guess I could do both 21
cards is still fine we don't need
bullfrog yeah right I guess it's
yeah but both are pretty strong well not
really but you know okay okay okay okay
like
this mantis my beloved fish oh that's a
big
fish oh I took picture of
fish place a photo of bait on the the
photo you think you'll react to a photo
B got to try that one but I'm not really
much of a
fisherman try it you like this bait
really a picture
a picture does the trick oh now I got a
picture of the pig fish oh okay I
thought I was going to fight the
fish that's not much of a
riddle Fish Fresh Fish good still must
beat oh
okay yeah oh o
o the crackos the Kraken in my neck he's
got salmon
H Hawk like salmon but Hawk Attack
fishermen to get more fish from his
bucket my beautiful my one and only how
am I going to get blood to get you out
there can I S I can uh no but I don't
have to no okay soon my beloved soon you
shall
shine and I shall take what is
mine give me a squirrel wonderful that's
exactly what I
wanted there goes my
beautiful attack three
times I love my mantis my baby my baby
once again he's working it's magic
[Music]
you beat your pants first to take thank
you another mantis perhaps no what
this the only thing we're still missing
to make oh this looks like that one game
is
um my
cat but here is Bonnie oh there's a trap
here
what game um it looks like um the one
game
o it looks like the one game that I
played with not
wacko uh the one with the the like where
uh you make a
cult and it's also
a uh not starve no no no Cult of lamb
yeah patches of dried blood crackled as
you Pride the chest open but two packs
were inside two
pack two
pack t packs was inside yeah let's go
tup
pack [\h__\h] mole wait the mole is
shiny what the [\h__\h] is I
can't is this a guy sitting on a guy
What's Happening Here
few players visit me here I sometimes
Ponder what my game play purpose
was don't worry it's
still like happening like your your
potential has yet to awaken properly do
I need to get the bunny to jump into the
uh bear
trap how do I do
that how do I
even can I place
this
bunny
push
what was here okay did it pass here well
now it's like just staying on the left
[Music]
o there you go oh
P somehow I didn't saw where this was
going I didn't
see bro you need
[Music]
pelts oh it is clear now that you wish
to know more what can I tell you I have
glimps the old data and I will speak
nothing of it as a
kindness what take my Pelt are you not
the Pelt person aren't you palting this
whatever thing
now wait I didn't pick it
up wait can I pick it up I can't pick it
up but what
now she's a to yeah okay okay well I I I
do realize that all these people we were
meeting they're all like
somehow in the can I go here no in the
game the Act One
game took a p I took a picture oh okay
well then let's yeah try to go to
Le yeah now come to think of it we have
the Pelt proof we have fishing proof and
we have yeah well this guy the one that
always like took my cards we have
something from him
to model overlay so pretty you think
so I see you have a photo of a pelt the
trader next door may desire it oh oh
really you have brought a pet I'm
pleased but another turn of the skinning
knife it's time to set another trap
I smell the hair's blood on
you oh you got a problem with
that seems like we're in
[Music]
trouble it looks like you used the same
photo from their IRL videos what no
their IRL videos are not
this this much like
retro anyway
[Music]
what my
fish my fish
so do everything that is needed and I
shall not need to do anything
else is it too early I don't care I
shall play you anyway my bone Heap grows
stronger and we already do free
damage
yipp he's in a safe place it's
okay salmon is safe also we're all
safe perhaps I shall keep the
srel but so what you do when an empty
space would be oh oh you'll move there
now huh
well whatever it's fine I'll deal with
you another frog has died today and
perished soon we will run other frogs in
this world you block an attack and kill
the he
does he's still
there salmon attack I got the grizzly
coyote I got the grizzly but uh cannot
play the
grizzly I think when he dies when a trap
dies it kills it
oh oh okay well that's all
right I'll block damage ah maybe
whatever I do want to block the damage
though it's
okay oh you moved there
oh oh he blocked both of the attacks I
see how it is now
a ah I wish I still had my screw
W sh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] am
I I'm not going to die
but I don't like
this guess I got to wait another turn
and then I can perhaps play a lot of
things ah goodbye you did good
work salmon
[Music]
G nothing nothing to
sacrifice
GG for me it's over
no I
no are you sure
no okay we try
[Music]
again do I even have to fight this guy
is it necessary to proceed
ah this is the same
hand this is the same hand no it's not
the same hand almost the same hand
similar I'll still use my
salmon
m m put one
here maybe I keep B
one hey place I don't want
[Music]
to oh
well will this be to my
detriment make another one
before you die put another one
down before you ah soon soon the Trap
will be completely
[Music]
gone a bone
Heap I don't know do I want
to I still make
skeleton still make a skeleton
can try and kill trap with skeleton
since yeah yeah yeah
yeah see it's okay skeleton is only
small price to play pay for such a good
play haha it
Rhymes okay I think this is fine right
yeah yeah that's good oh we got free
bones even I could do something
interesting
H I
could wait
yeah do you think this is a stupid play
but now I can upgrade it twice is what
I'm
thinking
uh yeah oh you would have gone with the
hawk I guess that would have worked too
if I sacrificed both and played the Hulk
but no my play was
cooler and the traa waits for the next
victim you've defeated the three of us
now le she awaits all right so it was
necessary shiny mantis
God but shiny mantis God not any
different huh from other mantis God
goodbye wait what do you sell actually
Ah that's what the the foils are
for my
baby what do I replace to put you in not
that I need to necessarily I know
but I think I want to
[Music]
why do you hate the Raven and the
adder Grizzly
yeah grizly can
go let's
go our perfect last addition to our
absolutely mid deck to finish you off
you had best at the unhanged perspector
a gormless angler and the enigmatic
Trapper you found yourself standing
before your ultimate match lashy scribe
of beasts your ambition is to defeat me
foolish even if by some odd luck you
defeat me now you will still need to
defeat me once more in the final Dell
and that is even more unlikely steal
yourself from my BAS will show you no
mercy only fangs I hope we can speedrun
this do not spare your creatures my
camera is waiting to capture them at the
moment of their demise capture the
moment and my beasts are
famished oh
so I can already play it do I want to
why not
right uh how about
you
kill the the
the this one first and the
go
nice or a B us man top deck top deck
snake
[Music]
uh
okay I can't do
anything I'll need a photo of that one
cl no no he's not really dead he comes
right back to my hand you don't
understand
no oh no so expensive oh my montis is
here a but I
can't I maybe maybe playing orbos right
away was not the play we'll see we'll
see okay okay this one can be sacrificed
right at least
I'll put you
here good
luck that helped a bit but my mantis
dies on away sh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] too many high
cost
yeah one will not
suffice I must save it up this is it not
we understand we understand you didn't
put in the second mantis oh I I wasn't
really I guess I
could uh sure yeah let's replace one of
the expensive
ones
with oh no never mind let's I do want
the adder at
least and
here one more cheap card one less
expensive dropped the
oal In This Very case it actually was
pretty useful let let me just you know
our top deck RNG might be very different
this
time oh needed for a
secret my my camera is Bo show me
something worthwhile mhm mhm okay oh
okay okay okay okay
should place it on the side so that my
mantis can go in one of the middle
paths play Both of Us in the same like
do they have to be on the field at the
same time I don't think
I do I maybe I do have to no already
dead
already I have them in my deck right now
right oh hey this is
okay I mean we're
living we're living on the uh on a life
on edge I don't know how to say it like
we literally have no cards but he's
already down to five which will change
now surely and he's taking it whatever
is he taking those pictures because he
will use those stats on his own cards in
the second phase by any
chance is that what he's going to do
no
comment please pick better positions
no that will
do only the first free ones
the depths of your creatures will form a
beautiful
Mosaic
huh oh look who's back not ready to
[Music]
attack that a good starting hand
terrible
positioning well tell me
me how to make
better should I still change my deck a
[Music]
bit or you think the deck is
fine you can win of the
[Music]
deck okay
yeah I could play one of these if I
sacrific these two I guess that's a bit
sad but uh
bad hand expensive
hand so you guys want to play botos
instead of the salmon
[Music]
huh maybe you won't like me putting it
there but I want to block the D like the
the more the superior damage
this a
to
now I shall play Tomb rber here to keep
him a bit safe make
skeleton make make skeleton make
skeleton kill skeleton kill
skeleton put
fish make damage
move hide take
damage come
back make
skeleton make
skeleton H think ah can kill all ofos
put
skeleton kill
kill um oh he gets
stronger okay
and okay so where do you want me to put
the the
bird cuz he blocks it right so here
right
ah can still put skeleton or even
you no I can't put you but I can put you
oh and I can make more skeleton make
skeleton
really
um
okay
good some people did not like
that still fine though we're still good
he's yet to kill a card of mine I
think could have could got him directly
oh it's fine it's fine it's
fine reset the spaghetti will you clear
my
field no you have something better
you're not going to take pictures of
them right we know did finish your death
card there wasn't enough death I hope
you don't mind but no what you don't
don't use those for
yourself he gave me Amal
gums okay okay he didn't do what I
thought he would
do he's got a [\h__\h] Grizzly lined up
and a [\h__\h]
moleman yeah these look like cats to me
doesn't look like emo gums at all meow
meow meow
meow
go go it's my
baby oh look at your bony
is it
over is it
over the great scribe was incredibly
basted far away a light enveloped a long
forgotten
Monument is it the end of act
two I'd appreciate it cuz I'm Running
Out of
Time avenge through it complete the
Temple of Beast yipp yippe you had
Triumph narrowly avoiding tooth and Claw
The Scribe of beasts Was
Defeated yeah this this
uh almost done one more thing it will be
okay one more fight that you were able
to defeat me Beggar's belief but now I
must yield to you my only regret is that
our battle was so brief indeed um didn't
even take any pictures
where are our memories in the shape of
Polaroids surely the summit of Victory
is made sweeter by more our
assent a great a great actually we share
this
opinion o wolf
CBS what else what else another shiny
mantis God so why was it getting
stronger is it because it was
shiny didn't say anything about that
we can replace the other uh un shiny
mantis with this one if we need
to oh stop what is that
what oh robot
Chan I had to see your face after you
lost you're just
so bad
it's no wonder we're back here again and
we would have been even sooner if the
disc wasn't lost H take a long look at
this face because you will never see it
again it's so perect that he shows up to
be so like anti bant in German we say
aty bad like uh what's what could you
compare it with in
English like suck at loser aty B it
doesn't it's just a sound but it
literally means suck it you
loser yeah cuz like he's the most salty
in act one and like you know he's the
most passionate about you know star
since the beginning and super passionate
about getting me through it and here he
is but you think you'll never see his
face again well you are wrong I guess
I'm done I'm done being your pet you
stinking Beast stinking
beast that's where the emphasis is
supposed to be
at I pushed it too far last time why
don't they see to live a beast as a
beast would be the noblest thing even so
lonely a creature as a sto what's what
keeps on showing up here like CU like a
little
[Music]
animal baby
baby oh squirrel okay makes sense now
what go back to the middle one
maybe zoom zoom
here
oh it is time Challenger choose describe
that you will replace I can
choose uh which one was
it this one
fo you have no idea what could have been
a carefully curated cycle of life and
death excitement Terror mystery that
gormless angler has once again failed me
I suspect that I know which scribe best
of
me of course PE free the synthetic freak
knows nothing of our hisry of of
Aesthetics monster I liked you better as
a
sto
oh so he was a sto before being a robot
interesting filthy old Beast I'll never
be your sto
again now let's play you and
me H wasn't I supposed to if anything
play the uh play against lashy again bro
you're supposed to battle the Scribe
that you picked but uh like a powered up
version for the
finale uh this is going to be
different hey this is not what I
expected but okay we got our mantis in
the beginning very nice very nice
indeed I could have played the hawk
first
also but I do some good damage here
right
away I'll just leave this here oh it's
the corupt the [\h__\h] no don't place it in
front of my
mantis I've got to give it to that
treger not as useless as I thought no
what is that what is
it what's it do
[Music]
oh
uh it's a good draw like I'm almost
thinking yeah but no I don't want to
yeah almost making sacking the
[Music]
Mantis
but yeah I guess I could cuz it does
good
damage if I put it like
here already next round yeah
okay what is
happening that that
tiet what the [\h__\h] is
happening chill w w w w w w w w w w wo
wo woah wo wo wo
wo
wo wao
wa who the [\h__\h] ended Mak it
then act two
complete allow feel free to gain control
of inscription
oh are we happy about that him
controlling po3
you remind me of something like
that some musician
thingy you done
ging we can
start good now we can
end not sure guys what is dead mouse
never seen that before I think whoa oh
this is partopia and once great
technical Paradise it's ruled over by
four uh Uber Bots that's right and
you've got to get out there and beat
them why to perform the great
Transcendence of course doesn't matter
what the means you want it
okay wait
what
no what
I'm I'm
handcuff to the desk bro get up no we've
got transcending
to you remind me of Victor from
[Music]
Arcane or or Walter or Gus from like
instead of transcending we've got
cooking to do yeah actually that's Gus
cuz he's basically keeping our Walter
captive
basically Walter from
Arcane wait wait is there a Walter in
Arcane but I can close the game now
right it will just bring me back here
when I open it
again I
hope good next time we play act
free oops not that way now you are
free from me playing this
game yippee good job took a bit longer
than I expected perhaps also longer than
you guys
[Music]
expected
oh okay okay okay
okay cars are making act three yay thank
you next time we're going to learn how
the robot deck works
do I have
to yeah we did Yap a bit in the
beginning about the Adent calendar and
about Singapore and we read a whole
interview
so it's true bit short of anything
really all right we forgot to unlock the
secret room would that have been with
the
oballs only robots now robot deck are
pretty op I guess it makes sense cuz
we're facing this robots Stout Stout now
that somehow I don't know why he thinks
he needs to hold me prisoner now what is
his
[Music]
issue 40 minutes what do you mean 40
minutes it's been 4 hours and F Oh you
mean 40 minutes was me stalling in the
beginning you mean yeah yeah yeah yeah
perhaps how does it feel to be in the
usual I'm not in the usual
room I have free will and I can leave
whenever I have the power I closed the
game didn't I
H and I still have the cards in my
hand the Jimmy cards and look at
them look who is really
imprisoned it is not
me it is you
okay now uh should I undo this effect
because I don't even have a room that
fits this
effect I shall undo it
then I become orange again
taada what was I over this pretty
oh yeah right I was blushing this whole
time I I feel like I'm
glowing
beautifully I mean I still have
the chmatic aberation I kind of like it
you
know add a little bit of an
oomph I'm so pretty
so
[Music]
pretty okay I will go
to ah my office my office has
the winter stuff right
now uh uh
wait copy paste
Myself by the way I mean can you tell
the I think you should be able to tell
the difference just by um not so much
the tracking and all that but the the
color filters basically that are on can
you tell oops that I'm a chair that this
is different than the the last time when
I used my 3D
model this is this is
uh this is the one that I revealed as my
3D
3.0 a while
ago this has the blend shapes the other
one also has the blend shapes but it's
made by different people so I think it
looks a bit different
H blurry your blurry below the neck oh
yeah it's because of my chromatic stuff
you're not like
it
okay I take it
away did you not like
it did you not like
it I liked it
though man I'm so disappointed
no
[\h__\h] what do you mean
onion nothing's onion about me
here I am in
fact I am but a Christmas ornament
that's just for
me let's be
here all
right
wait I make a few
[Music]
more I don't need your guys's help of
the Christmas
ornaments no need thans though
this one's
wrong all right guys I'm going to read
the super chats from today's
stream well we need some music
[Music]
uh what did I name the ones that I
downloaded
recently sort
by why why does it not have sort by
[Music]
new sort by
who
[\h__\h] what do you mean what nothing was
here nothing weird what what what
[Music]
perfect perfect eerie
music let's read super chats
[Music]
everybody are you feeling
uncomfortable don't worry about
it do you want to me in my original
shape don't worry about
it I I am fine the way I
am I just wanted to be more like you
round friend
change because you're so
beautiful you like spheres because you
are a sphere believe
me trust me
[Music]
you're
welcome and
ball I am
ball you like
ball
[Music]
yeah super
chats Doug
Hood thank you for two
pinkies so generous
W laughed when I sent a small donor
during Fallout due to wallet pain only
for me to send a rainbow the next day mm
she did she did no worries Wawa I got
paid the day I sent the Rainbow Oh what
a
relief I did some kfp pole dancing and
got some nice tips maybe next you should
do sphere
dancing I even sang a little song while
I danced rotisserie meet that's
underneath the lamp light 9 five move
your mouths and start to chew chicken
and a drink tonight give me that pole
get me spinning stick it right through
[Music]
me what's that
from it
seems as if you have manipulated
an existing songs
lyrics foreigners like to
manipulate to me you are a
foreigner makes
[Music]
sense it was a beautiful song though
even though I write it like a poem
because I don't know the melody thank
you Doug hood for your generous
donation I am relieved of your financial
status
I am an image
manipulation
really I don't think
so I am who I am I am
[Music]
ball Jacob 47 D Doug Hood
D no you're too late you're too late
Doug Hood your kiss cannot be
transferred I know you feel guilty for
taking Jacob's number one super chat but
this k be done it is against the rules
it is illegal no no we cannot bend the
rules like this it is
unusual manipulation of the rules no
no I cannot tolerate it
denied the guilt shall destroy
[Music]
you just for now I hope you feel better
afterwards ticket monkey thank you for
the the
pinky just wanted to say I hope you and
kfp had a wonderful day today and that
bod semi bod gang loves you and always
will love
you I am so glad to hear that it seems
as if you have to V quite often I miss
you come back to me my chicken ball Jed
monkey should I call you monkey ball I
guess Monkey Ball sounds
familiar orb of Wawa what is your
wisdom my
wisdom shall I spell it out for
you
okay are you ready write it down write
it down are you ready
h
o
l
e
n minus
a
d
v
e
[Music]
uh yeah thank you take it monkey for
your donation I hope Vault gang is
somewhere out there and sees this and
feels
unsettled
concerningly
worried fro fro thank you for the red
super chat waah waah so in Italian we
see we say AR no wait what I wanted to
say is in Italian it's Amor
oh I was watching the VOD oh hey VOD
gang never forget the
something or else Italians won't
understand you it it doesn't show
up the orb cannot perceive your Square
it is only a square the orb hates the
square it doesn't show up here maybe if
I used to
lier love the Wawa our wonderful funny
and amazing Phoenix we all love and
appreciate oh really you love me and yet
you seem to have more love for the
square it says here Amora Mo
Square you
seem like you want to deceive
me
traitor
traitor oh this one okay perhaps I was
wrong because that shapes an orb in a
way in the middle the hole the hand
shape of the Italians I
see just this once I
guess I shall trust
you with your
intentions thank you froo
Jim Tracy thank you for the red super
chat I can't believe this is my fourth
birthday in kfp even ever closer to soup
chicken
status or is it Ramen now H I think it
is ramen but for real it's been a ton of
fun and I wouldn't trade the time spent
with you and KP for anything love you
ateno you are going to make me
blush can a morb blush what can an orb
blush can an or blush
thank you so much for your generous
donation and for continuing your
subscription with
kfp to one day reach Enlightenment AKA
Ramen
status thank you Tim Tracy unto many
more
[Music]
years it's moring time
yes I am the one who EV invented
[Music]
death I am moring at this very moment
can't you
see jackan
[Music]
Soul Edgar thank you so much glad you
enjoyed I think it would have been even
greater if I could have performed as an
orb but I have been
denied delin
squared let's move
on the Mad kitten
D Ro
thank you
than ooh I see oh
yummy delicious slave Honolulu dun very
lazy King D oh thank you for watching
I'm glad
people watched my performance at
Singapore AFA Hol life stage 24 World
Tour s
what jtm
D thank you
no you did great it was all right
macaroni King
D ah there is a bug that prevents the
calendar from being seen correctly in
Safari for anyone who uses it
mainly H that is because Safari is
unbasic because Chrome is in the shape
of an orb
kto fixed it why is he a follower of the
non
orbs I thought it was a
statement towards my
greatness Firefox May indeed be greater
because it is an orange
orb
yeah well we can talk about that and
discuss it another time I am on a
mission to provide
for the website we are talking about so
let's continue
space
waterfall V faction D for the pinky
hello master of potty talk potty talk is
below
me I am an
orb a beautiful
mysterious magnificent orb Divine
even potty
talk I do not
engage in potty talk thank you Tanaka
from kfp Dan shut
[Music]
up botom
FR LC La than thank you thank you Tanaka
from kfp than
Quantum twin
spark M for the red super chat hi Ki
another year another birthday I'm so
happy to be a part of kfp I've seen a
lot of positive growth in my life over
these past years but it's always nice to
see a Ki stream on my timeline have a
great
stream but your usage of the word but is
confusing
[Music]
me but I guess in the end you're still
saying
that my Divine oress has led you to live
a better life which I am very very glad
about I hope this continues for you only
in the best ways as long as you stay
loyal to the great
orb
M thank
you I hope you come back
again to offer your
offerings I meant it's like a comfort
that it still the same please don't hurt
me I cannot hurt you until you are
unless you are
paper as an orb I am not only scared of
squares but also papers who often come
in the shame shape of squares I cannot
speak it makes me
nervous do you understand it is a rock
paper scissors
joke did you get
it it's or humor
[Music]
indeed okay continuing
you get it now
good I continue
to better the lives of
my
suborbit
wow wow that you must admit that was
pretty
good if I really was a vtuber orb then
my fandom would be called sub
orance and you are yeah orbiters at the
same time I suppose
oh I even got a laugh out of the Grumpy
One great VOR
bir you still laughed at it even though
you didn't understand you seem
brainwashed which is great you were on
the right path anyway thank you R and S
virtuous varment happy 30th birthday
congratulations thank you for your Super
Chat 30 you are are in
demand I'm sure your life will be great
even
greater now and
[Music]
onwards let us go let us
go metal
[Music]
bar be
careful not that it hits you on your way
out the metal
bar duck I would recommend ducking J D
thank you root toar D I shall now
refresh to see more of your
offerings and then I Shall Perish for
today vanish I mean not perish just
vanish oh that was funny for a moment I
looked over to OBS and saw nothing
sitting on the chair and I thought this
whole time you weren't looking at
anything but here I am on the tree
everything is
fine of course according to
K thank
you that is me indeed space waterfall
than action
it what are you talking about hands off
don't you dare eat
me Cruz tun Brian cro Dragon tun
dragones never mind something weird a
glitch in my brain
perhaps I don't know where I was going
with that
one Steph sings than oh I guess I
already answered your question it was a
good question or are you a different
wait was that question the same question
but from a different person must I give
you another
[Music]
wisdom do you do you require enough
wisdom
yes okay this wisdom is a little bit
[Music]
long are you
ready okay v i i t e r a m e
n period C O M
slash c o l l e c t i o n s
slash k f
p
wow that
felt good to
say this random combination of words
wait we are not done yet minus
xus v i t e minus r a m e
n that is the end of my
[Music]
wisdom oops oh my
God no no everything is okay I am
fine you don't know what just almost
[Music]
PL
I'm
I accidentally almost played KDA more
cuz I had the tab
open and clicked on
it uh back to Super chats where was it
where am I
here where was I a chibi disciple thank
you
what
[Music]
fine fine
then do what you need to do I know you
will come back once you have
realized your
mistakes the gamer Creed than Misty than
thank you
I am happy don't worry G
than fright screw thank you for the red
super chat oh great or Wawa tree please
would you tell me your wisdom you see
today is my fourth birthday with Wawa
and kfp I am not sure what I could do to
celebrate my mind has grinded to a halt
you see so please illuminate my mind
with knowledge oh great
tree why don't you use
any periods in your sentence it's all
right I guess anyway yes happy
[Music]
birthday wisdoms I have too many to
share perhaps I shall sing for
[Music]
you happy
birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe
happy birthday in your pants
CH happy birthday to
you
congratulations you are still far from
your greatest
[Music]
form but you will get there one day you
can be an orb too
[Music]
are you even wearing shoes and
pants maybe the song was not appropriate
but I hope you'd like
it singing to me is quite
foreign moas
NOA a package of my
balls
inconceivable unknown
d i now will vanish goodbye I
have orb things to attend
to ball
things I must
go goodbye and good luck don't worry
don't forget about the first W uh wisdom
I gave you
[Music]
today ouch
ouch
ouch I'm
scared catch me please I am the last one
you must catch me kfp make sure to catch
me what will happen when I'm
gone catch me please are you
ready 3 2
ouch
[Music]
I was lying on the floor fainted what
happened oh my stream is ending oh okay
uh I guess I didn't say in German we say
in a in I
guess man weird I have no memories of
the past 15 minutes
H oh
well y I have no time
[Music]