[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
i hear a helicopter
surprise
hello
oh god it's getting louder
oh did someone put a door there
that wasn't me someone
okay
um
someone put a door there to protect me
how nice
uh
off to a good start yeah
that was maybe a
jump scare rta
never been jump scared that fast before
damn
can i
go away
i was still so dark
how does this work i've never had like
an automatic door before that's cool
though
okay
wow
sunrise
hey everybody
[Music]
i wanna
play some rest today but
uh i don't know if we can
if we're gonna do anything interesting
because well
i looked up a few things like like in
our arrest
some people reported certain npcs not
being
um
there
where they should be
it's interesting um i don't know
uh
what exactly we could do but we'll find
out i guess well i'm gonna make myself
big like this i want to make the screen
big this time
but also i guess we're gonna like
yeah yeah military tunnel i heard is
empty and has a [\h__\h] ton of rare loot
that you normally
wouldn't get unless you you know
oopsie
unless you actually
you know properly rate the tunnel now i
have never raided anything before like
never
fought anything properly so that's the
reason why i'm kind of like what the
[\h__\h] am i supposed to do
um
i guess at this place
i just like
cool it's easy to get some cool stuff
but there's like no
you know there's no rewarding feeling
you know what i mean
like
uh
yeah i was i was hoping to
and do some cool stuff here and then i
heard that
or read
that in an oil rig i don't know is it
this thing here
and it's really [\h__\h] far away anyway
but apparently here
you um
like there are npcs
but if you try to call the boss
the helicopter will
stop at the top and never send the boss
i don't know what exactly that means but
apparently that doesn't work either
[Music]
and then there's another
oil ring
i don't know if it was this one or
the other way around uh
ah this is the large oil like yeah the
large oil ring
apparently
too difficult because
um there's like
the the npc respawn is crazy there like
after 15 minutes everything respawns
apparently which is apparently not good
but yeah in any case apparently the oil
rigs are supposed to be rated with
groups anyway
so i don't know much about
this game just yet
uh but do you guys have any ideas of
like in terms of fighting
what we could do like we could go to the
military tunnel and pick up some weapons
but then
what do we do is there anything i can
do alone
do you guys know
fight the tank what
the tank what tank
killing the tank
what what tank
there's a tank in the snow area
like like a you know like a tenkanashi
kiwawa like a like a moving tank
like a military tank
the patrol's the launch site uh
need rockets and grenades to take that
down
damn
besides that
anything else realistic
any idea
otherwise you know i would just be
building some [\h__\h] but
arctic research base
a dome i could climb down
wow that sounds so exciting
that sounds so exciting oh my god
i'm sorry it's not your fault but
um
my motivation is skill i was so
motivated at the end of the last season
but now i'm like
um
what about like this kind of island is
there is this dangerous this place is
this listening station what is that
what kind of place is that
yeah yeah i'm going to put on some music
give me a second
nobody been there yet
i was thinking maybe there's like some
repetitive features
throughout rest maps in general
[Music]
station dracula's no pc there
cali and id girls checked on that island
aha then if there's no empty season
what
what else
i didn't go diving yet yeah that would
be
interesting but like what's there to see
anyway when you go
i'm so sorry guys there's like
i'm i'm trying to find uh
reasons to play this today
desperately
i'm sorry
underwater lab
okay what is that is that like can i
fight people
uh
apparently there's two other people
online i guess but um
that's what the game said
uh
yeah a car would be nice
is she streaming rest right now
is she streaming it or how do you know
oh she's streaming
senpai nanny
how long has you been streaming
probably not that long right because i'm
guessing nobody was streaming when efe
was um live
one hour remember oh members only
remembers only rest
oh oh then uh
i guess
that would be like membership
content leaking
if i
were to do anything with her or if she
even told me what she's doing i didn't
know a rest was allowed for members only
okay interesting well she's not
answering me anyway she probably didn't
see it
but uh let me show you
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] was this also here last
time piccolo showed it
i i remembered this but
i don't is that out of stone now
i don't remember it
did she work even more on it
is she like you know she enjoyed it so
much that she decided to
oh oh dear
that she decided to you know make it
part of her own base
because it turned out to be actually
pretty interesting and and good to
protect yourself you know since we can't
according to the rules we can't put that
many traps and and guns and everything
uh around our base anymore
but then instead what you're gonna do
well my thought was
make it difficult to reach your base in
the first place
is that
is that uh
that that's still wood no i'm not sure
the ground is uh stone
the stairs are stoned
holy [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
it what this looks like something hot on
my belt
i never ever expected them asuki and
piccola to put so much
effort into this
what
wait a second
has it been improved so you don't have
to jump uh around anymore
because i remember when piccolo said i
showed it on her stream like
three days ago
maybe
maximum three days ago you had once once
you got to a certain you know like a
level here the end of the uh stairs you
jump because there was a gap and then
you jumped onto the next stairs because
you can't make them so long you have to
have some
ground in between and then continue
building apparently
what the hell
oh yeah authorize as i go by okay
i'm surprised you can like just do that
you don't have to give people a key or
so
a little bit dangerous though like here
without a fence
but at least you know uh air comes
through
damn
what on earth wait i wanted to put on
some music just give me a second
before we continue this
i'm i'm shook as no more pakor yeah what
i thought they were done helping me
who improved this even further i wonder
who it was
because
let me tell you one thing one second um
music music music music music music
oh for now
[Music]
okay you like jazz
so
actually
um you know this happened to started
during my 12 hour marathon and then i
had to dip out pretty quickly um and
they continued building and then after
words
uh i messaged them
each of them piccolo senpai and azuki
snapper i was like thank you so much for
helping me out sorry that it was so
weird and then
um
asaki senpai answered
uh
um uh
sorry
um
sorry dad it got it got difficult after
a while so sorry that we couldn't finish
it and pickled out
um has an elevator so
maybe she will give it to you you know
she it sounds like judging by what pekka
sent by then wrote to me
um that she built it to the
as far as she could to the top
um
i feel like azuki dipped out before and
then pick would have finished it on that
day but then i don't know who
who made it
like even better who improved it to this
stage
this was not here before
[Music]
so i think you really can't get any
higher than this with like
you know
the levels
so then they tried
from what i can tell
ah
try to
on it
[Music]
tried to like
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh
build some other ways of getting up
there okay that works oh
where do they get all these but
there's like a million [\h__\h] stones
where did they get so many stones oh
oh how nice this chair here you can just
look at your surroundings today the
weather is kind of [\h__\h]
thank you uh sweet skittle
that's nice
what what
[Music]
i feel like
whoever continued this
saw it as their own child at this point
and was like
this is my baby now
it doesn't belong to kiara anymore
i'm gonna put everything i have into
this
what the [\h__\h]
you can't tell me that this was mummy
continuing as we uh talked about having
a house together
right she would have told me
she would have told me she would have
told me
what the [\h__\h]
how how how do you even carry so many
materials so many stones i was like
looking around for stones and i was
having really really really lot of
trouble to find anything
[Music]
unbelievable oh i got a good view of a
big widow's house
[Music]
what on earth
her island has stone spawns
oh and then here is
wait is that like um
an item itself on its own
i'm confused or is that something you
can oh
what
this is this is peculiar logistics
i think this is peculiar logistics
what
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] this is the highest point
someone can get on this map at this
point
how how how high are we going
[Laughter]
this is this why did she
why did she build so much
what
[Music]
sorry i had to look several times
because i thought i was seeing things
oh
oh oh
wait how do i get
what
now let me get up there just one time
i don't want to like fall over the tip
[Music]
there we
go oh my god
i can't look at i can't do a 360.
oh
this is kind of scary now
this is pretty scary
you would you would just invite someone
to the very top here and then
there's any kind of weapon that makes
people like
that that you can push people with if
you just push them down there and their
kill
yeah basically the mission is try to
reach the top
[Music]
[Laughter]
i mean it's not so difficult though
it just takes a while
there's no no
traps and [\h__\h]
that's
that's crazy i want to fly yeah
tony not it i wonder i have in my
inventory i guess i can just pick it up
again but um
yeah i'll just i'll just pick it up
again
oh
[Music]
all right
vape jump
kobe
[Music]
that would be hard to pick up
[\h__\h] wait wait
i didn't leave i didn't land at
[Laughter]
i'm tumbling down
oh
[Music]
maybe she left a message no
where's my body
tower of death
i think
it might be
um at the top of the stairs
like on the roof of the stairs
what what
how does she have so much time anyway
[Music]
does she have nothing to do
[Laughter]
what when
how why
[Music]
now honestly this is not a build between
me and mummy anymore this is a build
of well i'm not even included at this
point i didn't do [\h__\h] i just had the
idea
ah
[Music]
this is not my home
you can go now buddy
that was um
a disappointing jump i'll do one more
oh
not like that not like that not from
there
oh
how
now is this just
going to be used as a
really
unnecessary watchtower
or will we try to
use this as a battle
[Music]
um ground
i want the weather to improve though
[Music]
better weather would be good should i
just jump from here because if i jump
from there i think i'll just fall on top
of this or
if i jump to that side i should maybe
land on
uh
a good spot at the very bottom wait
[Music]
wait
we can get a helicopter to fly to the
top faster maybe
i don't know what i'm talking about
[Music]
people might try to shoot this tower
down at the very end huh
[Music]
damn
i i wish there was a vault of hair
building this because i kind of want to
see how long it took her and what she
was thinking while doing it
all right uh
uh-huh
if i jump down over there i might land
on the very bottom maybe
okay
i guess this is just what we're doing in
this stream just kidding we'll lose some
other stuff too hopefully i was thinking
of of now
building a house
on top of the stone because as far as i
knew by the last time i checked up on
this i even logged in myself it was only
the stairs
going up to the relative top but they
were also still made out of wood
and uh it didn't look as
like
wow
amazing as it does now
is that is that a
thingy um
over there in the middle is that a
hot air balloon
anyway let's do a flip
three
two
one
oh no
i wanna do a sick jump
i need a ramp or something god damn it
i'm floating though she will fall down
once she dies we'll see her body
tumbling down i think yep yep yep yep
detailed stats
[Music]
oh
interesting
well uh
hello oh yeah oh wait huh
[Music]
ah there we go i have a countdown a
timer
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was i know it's not an impressive
jump i want to do an impressive jump
god damn it
[Music]
i i don't understand why pakora got so
so into this so passionate about this
what what
what
[Music]
wait i mean
this is this must be new i would have
noticed last time
oh wait my body my body
[Music]
so it should be on the other side now
i think
i'm going to
[Music]
oh this is how you get a lot of stones
just keep on killing yourself i mean
it's it's rocks i guess
is rock
wait can you make a stone with several
rocks or a wrap with several stones
[Music]
yes
i think i got it all um
second one what did i say
a rock of several stones
look there's a wait we need to we need
to get that to work and then fly it up
to the top
how about that
unless it already works
check the note a note
[Music]
where did the note come from
i think this is outdated
[Music]
because
there's no no name or so but it says
uh
she she
built it until the limit
[Music]
uh and then
what's actually buying english again
assumes like something for a place for
the foot
and then here it says connect it and i
continue it and connect it with the
stone but that's already done that's why
i think
it's outdated
[Music]
okay
i want to use this
and fly to the top
these things do they spawn i i don't
no do they despawn if you have fuel
inside and if you don't then maybe they
do
they do uh
despawn i mean
[Music]
oh i need cloth too
they decay unless prepared
oh my corn my corn is dead
oh man wait that's new oh there's mint
i also it's like it it's like
[Music]
i'm being treated so nicely
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait
that was that was mine that was mine
that stairs but there's nothing inside
ho ho ho ho ho
wait wait
wait that's new
it's like we're sharing this place now i
don't live with mumei i live with
pekuran natsuki senpai
most things here are mine though most
things
wait
[Music]
is there a note here too
[Applause]
a good survival use this
it says
uh the building has been complete the
construction has been completed payment
uh yeah good survival so
but what am i what am i supposed to pay
with
[Music]
what
with my body
canada
daniel
what's the payment
what's the payment though
sheesh
677 days
[Music]
okay what i want to do
i'm going to do
a thing
i want to
i i just need some cloth and uh some
fuel but that's by far not enough fuel
right
how do you make fuel again
a bill we have an unclear bill
very unclear
[Music]
oh my you're sad
animal fat i need to go hunting i don't
have any of that
i i have yet to really do anything at
all in this game
but
they left me some weapons
very sweet
[Music]
i'll take one
all right then i would uh leave this
here until i have more fuel more animal
fat
[Music]
i will you know if it really comes to
another battle like that i will pay by
protecting pekora and azuki senpai at
all costs
they i didn't
[Music]
they did they used so many of their own
resources i didn't provide anything
[Music]
like nothing
my house also was um
a lot better uh
in the previous season but this is my
second time i've logged into the game
basically
this is only the second time
[Music]
so um you know
uh let me just put some stuff
in here
whatever
what is this again oh flair oh yeah
light it up at the top
okay
we'll go hunting some animals if we find
someone
[Music]
else
when i'm done streaming today i'll i'll
write a message to both of them and ask
them like who
did that like
who did all this
who
and why and how
i have so many questions
oh sh
okay i need like a sniper gun maybe so i
can snipe people from the top
ah i can snipe all the people who try to
reach pekoras island but before i do
that i get rid of all of this
and then fly with my whole air balloon
to the top
so the only ones who can reach me if
they notice where the shooting is coming
from if they notice in the first place
is someone would need a helicopter or
something
to reach my place to kill me
you know
or just make an elevator no but we don't
we don't want to we don't we we don't we
want to make it impossible for others to
reach the top ten but getting rid of all
this
feels really uh difficult too
maybe just like i guess it would work if
we just let it decay i guess
like um
i put a bag at the top
let take everything out of the tcs let
it decay
[Music]
practice aim yo my aim is actually
fairly decent
especially when i can just snipe in
peace
and don't need to
think too much
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay now let's try to find some animals
need some fuel
i guess i'll go towards the
towards the
convenience store
it's a ways to make it no no we won't we
won't let the top despawn but you know
at the end everything despawns anyway
like because the server gets reset so
might as well just go to the very top
all all alone
and protect people
oh low grade fuel thank you soon that's
exactly what i need
[Music]
uh i need fuel fuel fuel what's this
someone left the boxes here
for what
purpose
they get
damn
i'm still
like i feel i feel bad
[Laughter]
i feel bad
that use pump jack nearby for fuel what
i don't know how that works i never did
that before where would i use a pump
jack where
[Music]
ah mount what is this
oh a piece
a little piece of a car
let's call amelia watson car repair
services
earlier near the building near mining
outpost what was that
huh
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
i set it free
oh dear
is that
if it's locked does that mean
this was somebody's car
wow that's so rude
sam
some of you guys sometimes don't realize
realize how rude you guys sound right
you don't realize right
some of you guys
[Music]
this is my second [\h__\h] stream in this
season
okay and overall
even if you combine the others
it's not been
that long
[Music]
these these are growing naturally right
i need some animals there's like nothing
nothing here
[Music]
uh
i
there's it's not a rule to turn on
members chat and
i mean in that case it wouldn't even
have helped so
uh
i don't really think
oh what is this
rechargeable battery
maybe i can research them oh [\h__\h] sorry
large animal spawn on the north side
what
why only in the north
[Music]
where is that
i said a car
i should buy a car
from watson how much is it
i would imagine it to be pretty
expensive although could even try to fix
this one
[Music]
500-700
i don't have that much yet
i'm like maybe 400 maybe
[Music]
but at this point
i might be able
to build my own car soon wait two of
those two of those
i i also know the recipes
[Music]
or i think all the carp what is this
a helmet
oh
that looks so stupid
[Music]
my view has been obstructed
cute
totally kill 10 out of 10 helmet
[Music]
so much loot here yeah what the hell a
sword
don't really need this stuff
i didn't know there was so much loot
here
splitter
uh i was looking for animals but okay
[Music]
oh nice
made from a bunch of other crap
you say it just the way it is huh
[Music]
this doesn't stack does it oopsie
oh it does
oh
sick
large furnace let's go
that also doesn't stack god damn it
ah god damn it
i'm gonna get hot
[Music]
where am i right now
oh
i heard
[Music]
m2
oh this thing
oh i was it was left in my
in my home
[Music]
very
kindly so i shall take it wait
this is also a pretty impressive
construction
what is this
a place for a car oh damn actually oh
wait is this thomas
the building style is hmm
[Music]
is this all cars
in there
uh or horses i think i heard a horse
sound
yeah
huh
wait does did she also build at the top
of
the stone
oh
what
[Music]
but ah
hers is not so easily accessible because
i guess you have to go through this gate
first and then yeah we could do the same
[Music]
we could do the same like make something
so that uh you can't just casually walk
up there
anyway you guys said north of the map
but it's
real
the very north
what do you mean the very north i
already have like ah i need to commit to
um
[Music]
i need to commit to just uh not picking
up any items until i'm at
where i want to go to
[Music]
okay
but i still have like barely nothing in
terms of materials and items in this
season
ah so i don't need to
i suggest a dome
for fuel
okay
we'll go afterwards why is there like
uh why do you know why why do you
suggest a fuel how
how do you know i can get lots of stuff
there
[Music]
red oil barrels
there's lots of red oilers
[Music]
whoa
is there enemies there
[Music]
i always wonder when i play this game
there's always like something
on my screen
is that uh loot dropping huh
[Music]
didn't realize how different this map is
yeah
i like the previous one more
this feels so
hmm
wait who who said this
nenety also said this it feels like you
are all we're all on matsuri senpai's uh
chest dancing
dancing around yeah yeah wait now let me
go to the recycle thing first
i saw a clip
where she was mentioning that
she's right
she's not wrong
[Music]
okay
all right let's recycle
splitter i probably already know how to
make that and then we'll keep this
[Music]
i'll keep that but now
i wanted to build a house at the top but
now there's already like
something up there
it protects pretty well
but i don't like that there's the sight
is so bad with the
pump jack nearby
still space
it's there but like now now this usage
is not really
it doesn't feel like home
it feels like destruction
and power
you know what i mean
i'll try to research that
[Music]
it might have enough full
keep
i'll that the hammer too
[Music]
amen would be very happy
i wonder who besides specula bought a
car
from ame yet
she's pretty it's pretty smart of her to
like in the beginning right away collect
a million of cars and then sell them
like that for scraps
mikko and porka oh
[Music]
whoa
but see i could actually make my own car
i could and i want to i kind of wanna
anyway let me look at my scraps though
oh
514.
[Music]
not bad
let's leave this hammer here what do i
what i needed
this you guys say do you guys talk about
this pump jack like is this something i
can build
pump check
no
i thought it was like something it goes
like
[Music]
100 c4 for a car
holy [\h__\h]
metal horse looking thing
[Music]
what
where where where where where
pump jack doco
pop check oh wait pump check compound
will it
how do i use that
that thing
how how do you use that do that let's go
and water
[Music]
do i need to bring something
oh wait i didn't know how to like get on
top of this
[Music]
oh i thought that would hurt me
huh
why is it empty
[Music]
oh the red ones
i've never noticed
oh and they spawn
in these kind of places oh wait there's
an opening here
anyway another adult
drop me some more
[Music]
barbed wire immunity yeah what's up with
that what i'm invincible
why is this
ah
what
can i put something in there and then
turn it on and
[Music]
fuel storage
huh
i put in fuel to get more fuel
[Music]
start engine
which one
ah crude oil because they turn it into
low-grade fuel
[Music]
maybe
oh it's moving
[Music]
i think i turned it on
but where does it come out
[Music]
oh
is it moving now
[Music]
it looked like it was moving
oh it was just light effects
it was just the light
[Music]
no it's moving
that's the output
oh
wait oh i put it into the blue one
i don't need i don't know
[Music]
it will take a while really
i put
86 in there
[Music]
but you guys said this would be more
effective than killing animals huh at
least if there's like no freaking
animals here in the first place
okay i'll check out this place too the
dome
when i come back i want all of my fuel
to be there eh
what
but i already started it what do you
mean
[Music]
it needs fuel
but i want fuel
are you saying it will give me more fuel
[Music]
right now
it makes more than it uses okay i would
hope so
oh
wait it comes out as crude oil though
which can be refined okay
[Music]
actually they respond so fast here what
respawn insane
[Music]
okay then i need like a refinery huh
do i have the recipe for that
[Music]
let me check
need to sneeze
[Music]
ah
did you guys watch luna senpai's and eof
his empire eyes 3d reveal um
we're finally at the hardware
[Music]
bunk oil
yeah yeah i thought the
two reveals were quite different
when i simply focused more on like
singing
what'd i come here for
ah recipe
and even for senpai did some cute
drawing was really cute like uh with the
gimmick you know her whole thing is like
being an alien artist
ah
small oil refinery see i can make it i
need 250 low grade fuel
but by the time i got this the air
balloon will be despawned
[Music]
is it even still there
okay i'll make it i'll make it
250 low grade fuel 500 metal fragments
200 wood
[Music]
wait but
no you said by the hardboard but the
hardboard
which hardware
is
where
like some specific place
or we just go to the dome
dome has refineries huh
don't have refineries
okay you know in the last um
play-through
last season i had
a lot of
encounters i guess with um animals and
therefore
i had more than enough animal fat
and then more than enough low-grade fuel
never was a problem now that's a problem
for me i need some wood oh
i'll take some from
from the house because it's more than
enough
do i need a suit
is it a fancy place huh
is this a husband's
arctic
trains radiation for cold protection
okay that won't work i need uh
i need a has
and has a suit
under the dome is safe
interesting
what do i even i don't think i ever saw
the yeah
wait i could make it
tarp
sewing kit high quality metal
[Music]
i actually have all of that
[\h__\h] i'm sorry i'm so sorry
wait i need five times
can i make a tarp
[Music]
how to make type
is tarpa spawning item only
look
i have an insane tower now
it's
uh
incredibly
incredible
i have a suit
apple sells hazmat suit
i don't see you soon 125 scraps
aina can i borrow her has my suit
can i have a husband
[Music]
arctic but oh i thought it meant no okay
okay no never mind right now i thought
it means when it says trades i thought
it means
it won't protect you from
the
huh
it won't protect you from the
radiation because it will only protect
you from
the cold instead
it gives some radiation protection oh
okay
well then i'll i'll take that
[Music]
thanks though
thank you
actually i was going to talk a little
bit about eofy and muna senpai
3d
reveal showcase thingy
eofy made me cry
almost i was crying you know
what won't this make me feel super hot
won't this make me feel incredibly hot
[Music]
okay don't have to wear it now okay
all right uh
[Music]
i'm just doing this for this stupid
balloon
yeah she she sang a song i thought first
i thought it was an original but then i
looked it up and i saw it was a cover
uh a japanese song about is it gone
it's [\h__\h] gone
guys whole idea why i was doing this in
the first place
ah i'll find another one
and i'll take this horse
[Music]
[\h__\h] satsuga
yeah she was um she said one thing she
wanted to do when um
she becomes
3d
she said she wanted to do sign language
so she did a
um like a song that was about that
yeah and it was really sweet
the whole idea of like
signing someone a song because they
can't hear it it's just so
um
[Music]
oh man my kokoro was broken off
it hit me right in the fields yeah
i was that was pretty sweet
i was sleeping back there
yeah
surprisingly
many cool
forts were built
somehow and i'm playing less in the
season than i thought i would um
unfortunately
[Music]
anyway
and then um
was really cool
yuffie was like cute honestly it was
cool
and then this i wonder where at least
senpai will be
tomorrow
although if he said by most of the
things she said i couldn't understand
uh no well i guess i could it was like
mostly
japanese and
uh indonesian
uh but like what i was like what's going
on but it was still so cute her cuteness
overcame everything her interaction with
sora zamboa was cute and buena senbai
came in
and they were like where's my piggy bank
i lost my piggy bank as like an
old joke right
oh wooden sign
all right will it hurt me if i go in
there
let's see
it's already too hot
oh
i don't feel the radiation yet oh
look at those
yeah this is still luna's piggy bank but
it was so sweet sweet when muna came in
because um
the way muna and eof interacted it
really
gave me this feeling like these girls
they've been hanging out a lot together
in real life huh
like they know each other well that's
the vibe i got
so
they were giggling so much even though i
didn't understand indonesian the tt
came across
oh wait
[Music]
never saw this before
oh
nice
nice nice nice nice
yeah they're so close not only the first
gen generally all of them they always
feel so close
um
but they definitely have way more
opportunities to meet each other than
ian does you know i do envy them for
that same with japanese girls like they
can meet whenever they want
naka
[Music]
if i want to meet anyone
anyone i have to fly at least for 12
hours
either to the japanese side or to the
uh
american side or if i want to fly
to australia i never looked up how long
a flight takes but probably around the
same time and yeah
[Music]
it's way too far everything i mean but
even then
even america they don't even the
american girls don't
and a girls i guess they don't even meet
up much either
because even within america i guess it's
just not
not that simple
i guess
[Music]
yeah
make a eu branch well you know oh
there's another one oh someone left
their wood in here
i could split my
thingy
i could split it
[Music]
never went to the dome before in the
previous season because i thought it was
a dangerous scary place
huh
the more you know
i mean let me take like
of this and throw it up there
jago said they want to expand an eu when
the hell did he say that
[Music]
when did he say that and who says who
says he was serious about it
i don't believe it i don't buy it
[Music]
interview for the crunchy con
uh-huh fifth anniversary
but you know isn't that just like you
know when when girls
uh whole life girls collab and they say
oh let's collab and then nothing happens
you know isn't that like kind of the
same thing
oh yeah let's go out nothing happens
and
i'm not the only one yo i i try okay i
tried
what the [\h__\h]
that's
huge but i am actually um planning
a uh
i started planning
another big collab um
a mogu's collab for next week who knows
why why am i playing planning it now of
all times
[Music]
among us
i already have like
some some interested people but for some
reason they're all indonesian
for some reason they're all indonesian
interesting
uh i wanted some of them to be able to
participate anyway that's why i
oh there's another one
oh that's why i am
i'm planning it to be at a time where
indonesian members could
also participate even though it's a bit
late
[Music]
yeah
i have a feeling it might just be me and
indonesian girls
oh
[Music]
didn't i put something in there did i
already take but there's not even any
wait did i not ah no i didn't i wanted
to
i want i wanted to but i forgot
there you go i didn't put it in
so confused
when what's at the top
if you go up what's there is there
radiation
[Music]
is there like good loot or
loot
we should go to the military tunnel
later even though there's no npcs there
and that [\h__\h] sucks but i'm gonna go
anywhere and get some weapons
okay so i'm guessing here
maybe
radiation see
oh
so far so far we're good
maybe there's no radiation at all here
i need to suit
all right
[Music]
oh it doesn't even feel hot
what's
that
[Music]
wait i need to go to the top that was
not the path to the top coco
can you get to the top
[Music]
pop up
yeah anyway actually there will be two
big collabs one next week one is planned
by me
and one's uh planned by amer
not worms another one where i am
planning to participate
what did i miss did i miss the place to
go
on up
[Music]
there you go up
the big pipe
[Music]
big pipe
ah
this
it's not that big
or do i follow it
[Music]
near the free pipes
free
one
sorry everything looks like a pipe to me
here
let me
run around here a little bit
maybe i'll find something
um
oh yeah hold up i'm planning
i wanted to do whole talk this week but
then
yeah
it didn't work out but then now i'm
planning holotalk for
for next week
and
there's just so many scheduling issues i
guess and and discussion like
communication is late
[Music]
uh so
yeah
the ah this one maybe
the studio is more or less ready though
oh no now it's getting dark
we can go diving
oh [\h__\h]
still you're more or less ready now i
just need
oh
wait maybe there
no
[Music]
i just need a guest
but i don't want to skip too much
forward you know and go for
some two new generations before i i get
you know some others done that i should
have been done with
[Music]
um
yep
[Music]
oh fun
oh god that's scary yeah
like one
[Music]
what is this
a kayak nice
cute
oh
where next
yeah
extreme popcorn
yeah this is where the radiation would
set uh-huh
[Music]
whoa
i know some people like to do this as a
hobby
like go to
like lost places they call them last
places
and do some pakur
oh dear
hey walk
up
i've infiltrated a lost place before
actually
wait that's where it came from
that's where it came from
oh maybe
there that one
i did yeah but i mean not alone
and i had a reason
not just i didn't just do it for
the sake of doing it
yeah [\h__\h] i wanted to use it as a
as a location
[Music]
hey
not there
okay
so yeah
[Music]
but i'm like
i'm i'm a very
scaredy cat scared he's an easy to scare
kind of person i never mind it's here
like i got really nervous
about going there
yeah
hey that's scary
oh that was so scary that was so scary
i wanna fall
[Music]
my mouse my mouse tilted a little bit to
the side that was so scary holy [\h__\h]
ah
quiet
i'm gonna [\h__\h] kill someone i swear
to god stop stop it
stop scaring me
[Music]
the night is um opening up though now
right
it's getting brighter now i hope
dude
[Music]
yeah
am i at the top oh
i'm at the top i think almost almost
almost almost almost
[Music]
so far only like the typical crate still
only the typical stuff is it over there
i came from there right
[Music]
bad i can't see [\h__\h]
me in it
gotta be careful because i can't see
[\h__\h] oh a telephone a telephone
but i need electricity too right
i think i would need electricity for
that
oh is it up here
sheesh that is hard without
maybe does this have some light
no if it was with e to activate it then
it doesn't have any light
we're almost there we're almost there
f
key
ah never mind it has
it has a flashlight nice
and
wait what if there's nothing up there
oh no there's always something huh
eh it's just the normal stuff
hey i thought it would be something more
special
[Music]
no oh there's some air drop here
drop air air drop drop here sometimes
oh
i should put a sleeping bag here
[Music]
uh
military great good great
sometimes
[Music]
okay let's go back to my horsey
at least i did it once
at least i can say
i have climbed up
this thing before
now
i did it i did it
ikaya
oh another wooden sign
oh god
okay going back
careful
my fuel dad says yeah yeah i remember
remember
wait what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] beautiful
oh this place again
oh that's good this is easy this is easy
[Music]
also like there's um
a place like this oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
a place like that
hmm
[Laughter]
okay
well
i'll be rb
i'll be right back
that's the fast way to the bottom yeah
[\h__\h] hell
yeah let me die already
oh my god oh nice timing helicopter was
just
just coming
okay what was i think
there's a
place like um that
but that's actually
like not really a lost place it's like
um
[Music]
it's
i would assume that a lost place means
that you're
normally lost places you're not
not um
really allowed to go in
but
in uh close to dusseldorf remember the
place where dokumi was
close to dusseldorf there's another city
forgot what the name was
but
i went there before and they have like
this huge
like near automata style
lost place which is not really a lost
place because in this case
um
they
even though they don't use the structure
anymore
uh
it's just like there for i guess like
people climb but to the top for like
sightseeing kind of like a hiking
but it's not a
not a not a mountain
yeah yeah yeah
it's not really abandoned no no like the
i guess
they kind of
kept it there for because it's really
sick like really cool way bigger than
the place we just were in in the game
actually way bigger than that and it
really looks like it's from nero
automata
so cool
i saw that person
i'm gonna kill him when i'm on my way
back
[Music]
considered a ruin because it's not
ruined at all it's actually in a really
good condition it's just not used
anymore
yeah lunch of spark
uh
no wait no no no no no
[Music]
let me look it up on my phone
because we totally have time for this
um
okay sorry lancers park
look it up if you can type down what i
just said even though you don't speak
german then you're a genius i i can
imagine that would be difficult land
shafts park dewey
lord
google that and look at it it's really
cool it's um
it's like an industrial
park
yeah
[Music]
last time i
or the last last time i went there
uh
there were some there was a naked lady
too
having a photo shoot
like really naked
really naked
having a nude photo shoot
oh do go on
yeah people either like go up there with
like
school trips or just
no school trips which is private and
whatever just for hiking just to see
what there is as a tourist and some
people go there to take photos
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
and during dokomi
since it's so close oh [\h__\h] i need food
since it since it's so close
like cosplayers go there too
i've seen like near automata cosplayers
right there
it looks like this but a million times
bigger
and more interesting structures even
although i guess it doesn't have like a
big ball
in the middle like that
[Music]
where's my body
oh where's my body on the other side
[Music]
i think it would have taken us almost
the same amount of time
[Music]
if we would have just walked down
do i need charcoal for anything
at all
[Music]
is that me
oh it's me
my body is gone
[Music]
i'm starving i know doesn't have food
what do you expect me to do
gunpowder oh okay okay then i'll take it
oh [\h__\h] i'm eating too much
[Music]
i'm alive
i'm alive let's see if my horse is still
there as well
[Music]
got telephone
stop calling me
the
[Music]
where's didn't leave it
nothing left there am i blind i don't
see an axe
i don't see my axe
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] i dropped it when i
uh but i didn't drop anything else
do you only drop the one thing that
you're holding
damn that's strong
that's surprisingly strong
stop calling stop calling
me
[Music]
we're still not done with that what
and now i have all this fuel but for
unfold there's no
there's no hot air balloon can i build
one
i would say even if i did
the materials would be insane but i'm
guessing i
can't this kind of archived hmm
yes
this will be archived
ah a man would maybe need it
i want i still want to find a [\h__\h]
air balloon i want to find it
i will find one we'll go around with the
with the horse we'll take the horse to
go to the
military tunnel
and on the way maybe we'll find a hot
air balloon hopefully
hopefully at least they're easy to spot
because they're so big
yeah
[Music]
should i just leave this
here
it's pretty fast but um
[Music]
wait wait okay
a thousand fuel yeah
damn
i've got fuel for days
[Music]
are you safe
mercy be safe don't go away i need you
you're part of my plan now like a petrol
station
if i really have that much left over i
can i guess i can sell
like i never made a shop before in the
game
that's something i could try to learn as
well
[Music]
literal oil baron
nobody else that's what i thought too
that normally like there were so many
shops uh in the last season but did
anyone really use the the shops
besides now the car the car shop i think
is
pretty cool
especially for the people who don't have
car parts recipes
that one makes sense to me
i want that one
i see value in
oh c4 c4 shop okay okay okay okay that
one maybe two yeah yeah
i could make c4
i know the recipe for it
carefully guesting
no one wants that probably i'm sure that
people
can get gas like
a fuel relatively easily
yeah
cars are more important because the map
is bigger
true
i guess so
wait oh we're done we're done
okay
i'm going
home
letting
leaving everything and my home and then
gonna go look for an air balloon
and gonna go look for some weapons
okay uh home is where the
tower is
[Music]
oh i'm better at doing this freestyle
stuff in german
pretty good only the germans are
laughing now
ah german freestyle
it's easier for me to find rhyming words
in german that's for sure or like any
interesting words that make sense in a
sentence at all
in such a short amount of time where you
have to think fast
yeah
that's that's why if we ever do
the
you know the
rapping contest
i would
not want to be a participant
especially under pressure it's even
worse than
german
gangster rap i [\h__\h] hate german
gangster rep so much oh my god when i
was younger
when i was going to school and [\h__\h]
everybody was listening to all these
[\h__\h] german gangster rap artists
and it's just the most disgusting kind
of play i'm so sorry for people who like
it but
you're not very cultured in my opinion
if you like it because the lyrics are
like
just ridiculous i feel like they're
worse than an english rap
it's so like
brain [\h__\h] like you don't have a brain
the lyrics okay i'm really roasting it
but
i'm i'm sorry but oh god some of the
lyrics i've heard in these songs are
like the worst thing i've ever heard in
my whole life
anyway i have a horse now you will stay
here right as long as there's food
[Music]
let me drop some more then
person i don't know
[Music]
i don't know
english gangster that's quite a feat
well it's just also like
maybe it's because i can speak german
but um
for me
the way they also like wrap it is really
cringe to me
[Music]
the way they rap you know and it's hard
to say german pronunciation and [\h__\h]
there's like this this um you know the
capital of
of germany is berlin and berlin has a
very
[Music]
uh in very cool
accent
berlin people
but then in combination with rap i feel
like it's really
cringe
[Laughter]
when they wrap like like these really
intimidating lyrics it's really cringe
to me i'm so sorry okay i'm so sorry
it's like
it's victor mutter
it's so [\h__\h] cringy
just hearing myself saying that i don't
know maybe it's for for english-speaking
people maybe they hear his english rap
the same way but this is just
when i when i as a german speaking
person hear that
[Music]
it's all
it's like why do you do this with our
language it hurts my heart
and what i said is i
i will
your mom
but in in this like dial accent it's
just
so [\h__\h] cringe anyway
[Laughter]
[Music]
there's a lot of people who like that
german wrap so i should i should not
condem it that much now the question is
do i want to bring all of my fuel in
case i find um
a hot air balloon maybe just a little
bit
maybe even less
god damn it
[Music]
yeah i mean i'm sure there's lyrics like
that in english rap as well but i guess
it's just more cringe to me because it's
german
yeah
anyway let's put this in here
[Music]
do i still need this
oh i know this is a [\h__\h] mess i it
was supposed to not be messy
i wasn't supposed to be like this
[Music]
okay we are going to
i'm going to recycle this
recycle this
keep this
[Music]
keep this recycle
keep uh
keep
recycle
wait
keep
oh
[Laughter]
well i guess we'll keep this might be
useful in the future
keep keep
recycle recycle
don't really need it but keep
keep keep
[Music]
okay
nice
[Music]
okay
oh need to drink some water oh my god
keep the tech trash oh you need that for
crafting explosives oh okay okay
i don't mind keeping it either
okay
i just heard that they're really good
for scraps or for or for the electrical
thingies whatever i don't know they're
good for something so next we're gonna
go grab some weapons
some free weapons free to take
it's too simple so it's not exciting but
oh well at least i can look at the area
in in
in peace without being
disrupted by npcs and then maybe if i if
if i play another season
then we can go in and hope that there's
npcs next time
[Music]
free weapons yeah
no actually
like anya anya brought it up she noticed
and she was like yo it's kind of like um
easily explode
what do i spy with my little eye i think
that was a hot air balloon
good eye kiwamo okay
on oh it's really close
it's really close to reflect
should we fly this home first
don't i need like um some cloth to
repair it too though
horse is in j17
oh no it works oh god let's see
taking off
[Music]
i i i know how to steer it guys
i've done this before have you guys not
seen when i took iris on the ride
i know exactly how to steer this [\h__\h]
it just takes a little bit of trial and
error
no
i'll that's not circles i'll come back
i'll come back
and die
well that was that was because of iris
shhh
[Music]
now we're going in the right direction
we turn it off for a little bit
[Music]
and then we turn it on again it's that
easy guys you guys are such amateurs
saying that you can't steer it of course
you can you guys are never oh
you guys are never gonna be professional
hot air balloon
uh
drivers
yeah
understand
if you don't
if you don't let your dreams come true
of course it's not gonna work you have
to believe in yourself see how easy this
is so i live
uh
yeah believe in yourself just do it
just do it
[Music]
oh perfect yeah nice curve nice curve
house is there
you need to have patience for this thing
here
patience is the key
ah sheesh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i should have brought um
a
who's that
over there
should have brought
a sleeping bag with me
oh i could just land on piccolo's island
there's a gift it's a present
and uh
i'll try to land it on my
tower first but can i even get that high
[Music]
come on circle please
does it get any higher than this
i mean
it should be fine it should be fine
[Music]
but the question is how
exact
can we land it how how
how much can we nail it you know
[Music]
very close that one sounds close
i have a feeling we're gonna get pretty
far away again
uh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it's tricky very tricky
yeah phoenix flying a hot air balloon
i like hot things i like flying things
[Music]
i think by the way
returning to the topic of german rappers
you might know some
you guys
i think like for an example for that
kind of gags to rip would be like
bushido and sido but those are the old
ones there's like newer ones what are
the other ones called again
yes
he's probably like 60 by now 60
60 years old i i feel like he might be
that old by now
[Music]
aya aligator
wasn't that the austrian one there was
akulega
kulega
the names
uh hurts myself mine too
oh thank god i'm i'm not gonna be like
really um hated for this here
which one was the german one at the
austrian one
there was one like where where are we
one one austrian one
let's try to keep up with the germans
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
what happens when you bunk uh-huh
uh-huh
this happens
okay at least you don't fall to the
ground i mean oh oh look what it's doing
interesting
oh
it's like hugging the the mountain
how cute
what's it
it's so tinted
oh [\h__\h] we're running out of fuel oh
it's stuck
oh [\h__\h] i'm running out but at least
it's really close
uh
[Music]
there
okay let go let it go
just let it go
how much did i put in like 50 in the
beginning
or less more 500 300
[Music]
it's so stuck
[\h__\h]
professional hot air balloon flyer kiwa
yes i did it i let it uh go again
yeah
i thought we were stuck forever
the burp has nested no
no
[Music]
i like how it's staying so close to the
mountain now though
got skills okay okay now go high go high
go high go up up
[Music]
that might be
a good approach anyway
in the end it just makes circles anyway
[Music]
fuel
i'm out of fuel we're falling
but we're falling perfectly
right next to the house
all according to kikaku
i need to save my house and my horse
so if i put fuel
in there then it won't despawn i hope
just a little bit so no one uses it to
fly away you know
[Music]
fuel enough being repaired oh
repair okay
with cloth right glove
[Music]
and a hammer
and then i just bonk it right
it has been prepared
[Music]
we now own a hot air balloon but i don't
want anyone to steal it i hope no one
will steal it
ah okay next door
next
let me leave these things
here for now
i'm gonna go
the horse i hope the horse is still
there it was in j17
a day's time
i'm actually keeping my
oh my god
so [\h__\h] scary actually keeping my hot
air balloon this time
that really hurt
cactus attack
oh is that a shooting star
did you guys see that
that was a shooting star
[Music]
so pretty
oh shoot look
you see that is that the shooting star
oh no wait isn't that just
oh
i know what it is
it's lit
it's just it's just the light the thingy
nevermind ah this is the light tower
uh
ah i thought it was a really sick
shooting star
[Music]
do you guys want to know what i'm
drinking right now
[Music]
trust me
it's something good
yeah
i'm drinking self-made
[Music]
that had to be because it's part of the
um commercial for that drink
[Laughter]
oh is that a deer is that a bear or no
could it perhaps be
oh an actual deer wait where's my horse
is that my horse
oh i real i was like what are the
antlers looks like a deer but no that
must be my horse because my horse was
here
that rant
that's right oh
[Music]
that gun goes up when you
shoot
[Music]
this knife is nice
all right
continuing
recoil
anyway i wanted to tell you about the
drink
um so i'm doodla nice poop horse
or doodler is um
it's it's um
it's a austrian
uh
uh carbonated herbal
soft drink
and it's special because
of the combination of words that i just
said because that's
a carbine carbonated herbal soft drink
that's not really normal
and second of all because it's from
austria and things normally don't come
from austria
whoa
[Music]
i didn't realize
okay i'm coming back and let me just
bring my
ah
i need to
grab my suit i didn't think it would be
here okay
well we're fast with the horse and i
have a story to tell you anyway
yeah
um so
it's in the soft drink you know we sell
it
you should shoot those for some meat
[Music]
nice
good shot
[Music]
and they sell it in bottles and cans
that's why i was asking on twitter but
then i remembered
then i remembered they don't only sell
it in bottles and cans they also sell it
i mean well that's also bottle but they
sell
a syrup
to make it yourself at home
in a big plastic bottle and that's not
carbonated so i think the chances of it
like you know exploding would be lower
and with the syrup you can make way more
of it than with just one bottle
it's not um
like i'm drinking it right now it's not
i i would say of course not as
amazing as a fresh
freshly opened bottle
um
but
let's see
what's
but it's it actually it really gets
super close to the real deal to the real
thing
i'm gonna eat the food
no
[Music]
explosion
so
instead of buying the carbonated bottle
i
bought two
two bottles of the syrup one for me to
test it out to make sure if i should
really send this to bails
or
not if it's not good enough but i think
it's pretty good i'm drinking it now
it's pretty good
yeah i am
[Music]
one for me one for her and unopened one
of course
[Music]
so my plan oopsie
is to send her the snack box soon i'm
sorry i didn't do it until now but
i'm going to send it so i actually
and this is um way more than i expected
but actually i spent
[Music]
60 euro which is like 60 bucks
on
snacks
for bales
and you know shipping will be
i think quite expensive too
so this whole thing will be like i think
a hundred bucks
100 bucks
worth
of a box
but i you know i didn't want it too
cheap out i wanted to get as much many
things as possible and then i was
surprised i was standing in the
supermarket i was thinking oh i will
have to mix in a lot of like german
german things german snacks because we
don't have if we don't have that much
but then
i actually
i think the snacks that i got are like
80 90 percent
austrian
and then i put some rita spots in there
and milka
that's i think german or white milka i'm
not sure about milka but you know how to
include milka
but the rest is uh
the rest is very austrian
i'm very surprised that i could find
something oh wait there isn't wait
that's that's not an npc who is that
hello who are you
daddy don't shoot me no please don't
shoot me
oh hello
[Music]
it's me what are you doing what are you
doing
i was waiting for the crates
oh i came here for the crates too though
shall we share
sorry i just took the last one you
[\h__\h] kiss you're the next one if you
want
you can have the next one
no no no i'm not ah [\h__\h] stream
sniper man took all my crates
[Music]
you are sleep snapping at this very
moment
[Music]
in the background
i shouldn't have paused
we would have heard my plan and you
would have known where are you you would
have known to not take my crate just
kidding it's fine
i'll explore a little bit where is she
[Music]
npcs right
uh no it's empty
[Music]
wayne you need to show me your house i i
don't know where it is
later later you can show me
i don't know where your house is either
okay
i'll take a try to like
watch your stream to like pinpoint the
locations but i couldn't
uh see i tried to do the same thing
when you first did your rest stream i
was like i want to surprise her so i
waited for you to show the map but yeah
it was difficult
very difficult
oh hi
[Music]
i'm sorry
some squats there's a dead bear that i
just killed i don't know if it despawned
though oh well a dead bear well oh thank
you
sweet
so where's the where's the entrance in
this place
[Music]
oh so the crate spawns here
here oh
and then
yeah wait i'm good
i thought this was a tunnel i thought
there were more crates like more stuff
[Music]
there's more stuff and then there's
stuff that require keyboard
oh
what what key cards which color
[Music]
oh
oh oh
oh no oh i'm fine
but um
nice
normally oh look normally i would be
npcs here i don't think it would be a
place to play music
[Music]
well i wanted some npcs here
where's the loot
[Music]
i thought i would be playing alone today
it's nice to to not be alone at all like
completely
oh berries
[Music]
oh what is this
i think like
confused in here but i recycled mine
oopsie hey a fuse what what happens if
you put it there chad do you know elena
do you know
i have no idea i've never been here like
doing
oh
there's a lot of cool stuff here
like overpowered stuff
it powers the keycard reader huh
where's the cool stuff
[Music]
okay
it's so cool to hear your voice like
this
[Music]
it really feels like we're in a tunnel
together
wow so scary dude
[Music]
what sparks this spike stream spike
first time i went here i didn't have a i
didn't have a flashlight
oh you should come here with a
flashlight without a flashlight you
shouldn't come here at all
[Music]
i think i saw
someone conquered this place in season
two
and there were actual enemies wait do
you still need the hazmat or no
uh i think so
i mean i oh i mean i'm i'm wearing it
right now so yeah i think you need it
here that's what i'm saying but um i
have the the the
warm heads
[Music]
there's nothing here
okay
but if you go there there should be
something but let me check because
but that was like 15 minutes
like half an hour ago
oh yeah look the loots are here
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
what did you take
did you take the rocket
no no i didn't
i took a c4 what do you want
i use it to explode
no i can make my own c4
oh
i know how to make c4
are we going deeper are we going back
right now i'm confused
um
[Music]
oh we can go even deeper
wow
there's
there's not much deeper on and what what
kind of car i saw a green one next to my
house
is that not the right one
[Music]
i never did
that you need green and blue i think you
need a blue one
[Music]
why are you not sleeping right now
okay i guess that's so pretty early yeah
so business oh disney
oh
did you watch your fees bye 3d stream
today
i'm going to watch it all but i only
saw the drawing parts
that was cute
[Music]
i could understand but the other one i
had no idea what they were drawing
[Music]
um
yeah i usually save that for bedtime
oh oh um yeah just like my streaming i
have a separate streaming room now oh oh
yeah you talked about that i thought you
you meant you moved into a different
apartment or so
streaming room now separate from your
room where you sleep you mean
yes yes oh
[Music]
i could not do that
but
that's the main reason i yeah you just
have to move this room because you know
you have to try like i don't know
ignoring them or so like something must
you must be able to teach them somehow
to be there but still be like good and
and quiet because my cats they they stay
they just sleep when they come in into
my room while i'm streaming they just
sleep
that's it
normally
sometimes they meow a little bit there's
too much
there's too much sometimes they just
[Music]
well in the end it's your decision if
you have the the cruel
heart
to let your animals stay outside of your
room and look at them while they're
crying yelling for their mommy
then that's your problem
oh there's a bandage you don't want this
i need i need
oh
where did it go
there's some more oh thank you
uh
my daughters
i didn't even have to teach them manners
and they still have them
what a good life
okay good life
man
[Music]
this [\h__\h] is boring let's go somewhere
else let's go somewhere else
i'm sure i show a show i can't help you
i'll show you guys
and then i can fly you somewhere because
i have a hot air balloon ready to go at
any time
don't worry i have a lot of fuel wait
how do you use this again
here we go
yeah
let's meet at the crates crate place
okay
see you guys
i'm always lucky there's always someone
usually it's reina or ahmed but there's
always someone to be with me
ah
[Music]
not all alone i would have been fine
though you know i had no expectations
no expectations at all
okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] loud
girl giving me a [\h__\h] heart attack
where's my horse
where is it where am i i have like no
direction sense
[Music]
i was was there a recycler in here
no but now i think i know where
i am horses up here maybe
is that my horse no
that's my horse
she's like
retainer
[Music]
all right
follow me oh wait do we wait do we have
the same horse maybe but this is for
different
probably the same
nice matching horses
beautiful horse
[Music]
she's making music she's my radio
so elena do you know
do you know
oh are you too far do you know anything
that we can raid together where there's
actual npcs
there's the oil rig i don't have a
sniper though so i'm not very confident
oh
i thought there would be like actual
useful weapons uh in the military tunnel
so that would have helped but wait is
this your house
no
oh yeah what no
yeah i am i am
we can build we can build you a sniper
maybe
sorry we can build you a gun maybe a
good one i have some
recipes the boat if you snipe them
because on the on the last floor or the
top floor there's so many um
you know the the scientists with the
black armor
there's no idea what you're talking
about i've never did anything like that
before
oh okay okay okay
so i guess uh i think it wouldn't it
would be nice to have a sniper so we can
like take them out
um take most of them out from uh far
away and then just fight them head-on
when there's like only like super few of
them okay okay otherwise it'll be really
tough i don't i only have this um
this what what is this what is this
thing here m2 for a rifle machine gun i
have a machine gun but it's pretty good
oh
[Music]
yeah
see this is my hot air balloon and this
is um up there and this is my yeah all
of this is mine the mountain is mine
[Music]
what yeah what is this do you want to
try going out i have a big tower
because um i i
some reason i got both asuki and pekora
senpai to
build me
a [\h__\h] fortress
can i put a sleeping bag here yeah
sure
if i die
oh wait you can put it and then you can
authorize me to use it
oh can you come in because i don't have
permission i don't know how to give you
permission oh you have electricity
that's so fancy what the heck wait i
have electricity oh
electricity oh does that mean that's
electricity yeah
oh my god the pressure plate
[Laughter]
i know it's so cool
[Music]
it's kind of like the other game where
you have pressure and the other game
michael i don't have permission to play
stuff here so i think i'd have to like
live somewhere can you touch the tc so
said i'll make it easy
i'll make a tc next to oe what for real
yeah for us just authorized yeah
a mile oh shoot what that's so cool
ah
it's okay i won't like i will i will
like steal stuff from your house don't
worry oh it's okay i i honestly i
deserve nothing here anyway i didn't do
[\h__\h]
i'll show you the top come come with me
come with me
so
all of this
was built by azuki samba and pick a
azuki senpai and pick what i sent but
just because
i wanted to get up to the top and i
tried building it myself but it didn't
quite work out that well
and then i was like uh i saw i saw azeki
simple and pickles online i was like can
you guys like do you guys have any idea
how i could do this and then they were
like leave it to us and
shortly after this structure was placed
here
they did way more than i thought they
would do
[Laughter]
it's insane thank god
insane what is this wouldn't it be funny
if you accidentally like fell downstairs
oh that would be so funny yes
yes
wouldn't it be funny if you accidentally
fell down stairs
i guess that would be pretty funny
pretty funny right yeah no
but it goes up way higher
oh did you just
[Music]
anyway
come come
this way what what
here it gets a bit more complicated
need to do some jumps cause you can't i
think you can't build any higher than
that with the stairs
in one set at least i don't know yes
this is my watch tower so i can stalk
pecora simply
because she lives there in that
in that island right
oh this is a very normal
[Laughter]
bones see gotta be careful here there's
no fences
[Music]
better
there's the chair wow oh it's not over
yet it gets even higher
this way
[Music]
yeah i know right
it's peculiar style
this is like the shooting floor i guess
yeah
nice you have your own shooting floor
that's kind of yeah i can snipe people
from this
i probably shouldn't be showing you you
better
now that i'm showing you this you must
be on my side if there's another battle
at the end and i don't know if you're
going to participate but in that case
you will have to you know since i let
you in listen i have a sleeping bag in
your house i can't go oh i'm gonna be
we're gonna be allies
oh there we go
yeah wait allies now don't betray me
whoever side i am on you're on that side
i'm stuck
maybe now i was stuck
oh the weather is way better the view is
way better now can you open the door
please hi
thank you oh are you not able to open
them okay
um yeah i was stuck so i closed it and
then i wasn't able to open it ah i guess
only maybe i can do it yeah
oh i don't oh
[Music]
can i like get a longer
field of view we will field whatever uh
in the settings because otherwise you
can see this from here there is no way
you can you can probably see my tiny
house by the way
fishing house i want to see i never
fished before
[Music]
yeah nice it's the ugly house the better
house is by the junkyard it's pretty far
though also i wanted to know what this
is chad tell me
what is that
is that eyes of the outpost wow this is
so cool
the outpost in the water was way cooler
the season two well this is the first
time seeing the gas station and the
stupid supermarket right across each
other
you know
right in front of my eyes oh
wait you didn't you didn't go there
before
oh no i i mostly live on the left side
of the map oh
okay do you think it's actually like
probably why we never meet for us two to
go to the oil rig or is it a little bit
too ambitious
[Music]
um to be honest uh because the last time
i went with anna and i we
each like took out a lot of people
what i just found a note that i didn't
see until now
stick last time please you can recover
him from season two spider failure
he says with this you must protect
piccola
uh because you failed in season two
protecting me
oh oh because you are i know what you
did yeah
wait let me see
oh
all right easy easy i just need to
improve the settings so i can actually
see [\h__\h] because no
nice
eel
that's exactly what i was thinking
so you could do
this is exactly what i needed in order
to protect her a [\h__\h] ton of ammo too
okay dana you cannot tell anyone about
this tower okay
[Music]
no one is allowed to know because i need
to shoot snipe down everyone who's
trying to reach her island at the end
okay
[Music]
oh okay my sniping towel don't tell
anyone otherwise i will have to break up
with you
oh sure okay
[Music]
i want to go down break up with me
together
[Music]
air balloon ride
how many fuel do you have enough
more than enough plenty okay i i uh made
it my mission to get a [\h__\h] ton of fuel
for the hot air balloon beforehand so
don't worry i got like a thousand
all right
be careful
this way
don't fall down
don't you have like an elevator or
something
i i could build one i have the recipe
maybe
in the future
[Music]
are you complaining
i was asking out of curiosity
i understand now i think what piccolo
wanted as a gratitude just the
protection which i will give i will try
i have no idea
just go down and then down follow the
stairs
the final piece of the puzzle
the note
all the notes
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna hold my stop oh i can practice
with reina
i'm gonna have her run around at the
bottom and i try to shoot her
uh
anyway
of course only with your permission
milady
[Music]
shut
oh we're actually doing it oh cool
but then
um
i don't know
i was going to take you on a ride
but
i want to see the
draw is it draw distance
draw what's draw distance right
wait i want i want that too
what
in graphics yeah i wanted to see more
draw this sentence mine's already maxed
out what what
i had it like extremely long it's
already like on the right
let me drop a distance 2500
shadow distance one oh
[Music]
i don't see a difference what's graphics
quality does that
make a difference
graphics oh yeah i could probably up
that a little bit too oh
it won't go higher and there we go
render scale
oh [\h__\h] my game
oh there we go
oh oh it's oh
it's not it's not answering
[Music]
oh dear
that's loading it
that maybe looks a bit prettier than
before
i don't know about the render distance
anyway
your whole band i have a guitar
i'm gonna bring my guitar
um
can you tell me on the map where your
your house is
[Music]
what
oh
so
so far up there oh in the junkyard
[Music]
it's like so [\h__\h] dark in here let me
finally place some
lamps
i only have one
okay
that and i'm gonna recycle really
quickly
[Music]
there's a recycler in the junkyard but
if you want to do it nearby um
no there's one here
actually
beware of polar bears
oh
[Music]
pull our bears
you have polar bears over there
[Music]
oh i'll keep that
m
i have four pieces that i don't need
nothing happens when you stand on the
recycler i thought like there would be
damage
ah they should add some
something there
spice things up yeah spicy
[Music]
almost done almost done oh there we go
i'm done
[Music]
i will place a table make this place
actually look like i'm living here i
guess
i guess i guess i'm living here now
it wasn't really the plan this was just
supposed to be temporary but you know my
only my sole purpose of life in this
game now is protecting piccolo
up at the blush tower at the top of it
that's my sole purpose guys
this is my
this one is my horse
oh
what about
difficult to tell apart your horse is
the one by the hot air balloon right
um yeah i think so i would say so i
would assume so
[Music]
you're not are you like able to eat
though
here there's ah maybe there's no food
left
no there is okay all right get into the
get into the hot air balloon please okay
fine
okay it's so dark okay i'm gonna feed my
horse first because i care about it okay
hey eat
he's so stupid that's okay it's so dark
okay let's go
have you ever
been in the hot air balloon before and
rust
and breast uh
couldn't drive it well so i gave up oh i
can i'm really good at this so leave it
to me
[Music]
yeah
just enjoy the scenery
the beautiful scenery i'll i'll have to
it will take a little while but i'll get
there eventually
i need to go this way okay okay then
um
we are at wow
it will find itself eventually
where are we going
to your place
though i guess we could even go to the
oil rig with the how do people normally
go to the oil rig with a boat
oh
[\h__\h] this mountain is in the way
oh well can you go to the hot air
balloon and then just like drop grenades
and stuff like that oh i think that was
like pretty resource intensive i wonder
i think it would make sense to just get
yourself a helicopter then because this
thing is hard to control
i guess so yeah
yeah yeah
are we are we
wasn't paying attention wait where is he
okay yeah you have to keep on turning it
on and off and on and on
[Music]
ah it's trying to have a guitar um
wait how do you
okay
what's a pen flute
pack float cute
and we're fine we're fine
[Music]
again
you're like from zelda
because it wastes so much fuel
that sounds like zelda
[Music]
please play the root center i mean i'm
out because i made useless musical
instruments you know what
we we are going to go
by horse this is gonna take too much
time
uh that's the thing i hire balloons like
you love a lot of fuel yeah
at least you got a little bit of the
experience
[Music]
there we go need to learn how to aim
with this thing
yes
okay
gonna pick up the horse it's better that
way anyway because i'm scared about
horses to be spawning while we're gone
[Music]
yeah
how what does i have yeah
[Music]
ah mounting horses
let's go
now i will follow you instead
and you lead the way
okay oh pumpkin yeah shoot more give it
to the horse
i'm gonna mark my house well i should
know the way mostly
let's go i follow you
damn how can i ride the horse when i are
you with my higher balloon being there
yeah
it's fine
okay
wow oh this is a pretty good place you
have pumpkins you have um yeah in your
backyard yeah and i'm close to the water
so i can catch water
[Music]
um did i invite you to team um i didn't
see an invite
hold on let me um
okay there we go
[Music]
and where is it how do i get it
um um um a tab tab you usually have your
inventory and then
are we in a team now
no
[Music]
i'm in a team with myself
bottom left well i don't see everything
on the screen somehow
[Music]
there's like a supply drop opposite of
where we're going if you turn that way
southeast
yes
ah in the dome my inventory is full
though
am i even serious
that's like dropping
[Music]
okay oh wait do you have a team do you
have a team because i have
okay yeah i don't i'm without the team
now
i want the crate
i don't have it
[Music]
okay
there's one in the dome
[Music]
did you kill him
i want to kill him
[Music]
can i shoot that fire
hey is it elena
[Music]
yeah only useless [\h__\h]
yeah yeah yeah the signs by the road
at least something
okay
[Music]
okay back to the horses
eh is that explosive ammo i don't know
what that ammo is
he's killing you
my screen
okay well we'll have to cut it a little
bit then
there you go you won't even notice it's
cut
oh which one is your voice
uh my horse is this one okay
do you know where it is where's the air
supply
yes
i know follow me follow me
you still have that awkward delay in in
the game when i talk to people
awkward
the european thing
oh there it is what's
i don't even know what exclusive ammo is
but eh
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] boring
sorry oh what that's the crate
oh it's not marked on the mountain not
the mom i took i only took pistol
bullets cool
i'll take wow
wait how do you find this if
that's what i found uh in season two and
i was like i don't know
why it was there because it wasn't
marked on the map i guess it was like
one of those
but elena there's one more at the dome
is this your horse
i don't know
one of those is
nice helm bro thank you let me put it on
you can't see [\h__\h] come on i know we're
using the same horse doesn't matter no
you can't see it
okay come on
one more crate one more crate
i saw it falling but i just assumed it
was the one at the dome and then i just
went that way and we're lucky that i
just jumped off because of the
scientists
damn
[Music]
oh i went today for the first time too
you need a hazmat suit for radiation as
well
after we get the crate i want to go to
your place you show me
i wonder if it's at the very top
we have to do some parkour if we need to
go to the very top for it
i'm gonna assume it is
oh no
i don't think there's a recycler here
but don't worry i'll take all the items
gladly
[Music]
it feels like you've you you played
already more than me in this season
[Music]
from what i can tell
oh
[Music]
there's a wolf hunting a bear over there
yes
ah here this is where i made it like a
thousand
oils
shook it here we go um
don't fall you gotta you have to be good
at this if you want to get to the tap
try harder
all right what's this way right this way
this way
[Music]
my momentum
i just criticized reyna for falling down
but
i'm not better
hey wait here
no
[Music]
where owl
i'll figure it out i've i've went to the
top before i haven't got um
there's like another side of set of
stairs there
yeah
oh yeah that's that's where that's where
we have to go
yes
do a good jump over the side did you see
how i did it
[Music]
oh wait uh we have to jump over here no
no no no come back come back
oh you're looking at something else why
come back
oh i'm looking at something else
[Music]
didn't see this gosh
they're up here
you can jump from there yeah
and now i need to
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] oh oh oh thank god i fell down
again
what happened are you okay i fell down i
need healing
no no i'm not dead i wouldn't be
wouldn't be able to talk to you if i was
if you ever hear me suddenly being quiet
or exactly you don't hear me then then
that means i'm dead
[Music]
okay okay okay
i got food i just need healing items but
i'm fine i'm fine
maybe healing item healing item doper
[Music]
there's another crate down there
a fridge
do you need a fridge
okay
i mean i also just use it without
without electricity just because
a piece of furniture you know looks nice
this layout is pretty fixed
oh okay curious
curious what kind of
house you built this time
[Music]
my house
i don't know if you could even consider
it a house okay you have to be careful
here
i'm so scary
[Music]
skills
oops
i'm dying
uh
take
don't take care of my body
take care i don't know where it is where
is it
i don't see it
i'll just go get the crate
i think she died oh yeah she's dead
she dead
let's hope i don't
follow the same
um
destiny
i'm so scared to jinx myself
[Music]
on
yes and i just found one
uh
yeah yes but don't worry i
almost
got the loot
i will be down in a sec
she says she didn't want the loot anyway
oh she didn't need it
so i'll take it
gladly
[Music]
but wait don't i have to activate it up
there and ah it takes 15.
[Music]
go all the way to the top activate it
and then wait 15 minutes what
oh that one is way more mendocin
annoying bothersome than the one
in season
two sheesh
okay
started
15 minutes i mean i guess i can come
back i'm not gonna wait up here for 15
minutes am
i am i
am i
how many pcs again
[Music]
uh should i go down
it takes me to takes me like five
minutes to get up again but oh well
um
chatting time
[Music]
okay
satsudan time
okay i have some zatsudan topics
i'm so smart that i prepared that's not
topics
maybe try coming up after all
okay let me see my phone
oh i hear a helicopter
oh
with a hide inside at least
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh i see it's over there
before it shoots me
i'm scared
is this safe
they think it will see me
i guess if i just put down uh
this stuff i should be safe
okay
okay so i was saying
i was gonna say i was gonna talk about
let's see
did you guys see
sims 4.
apparently it's gonna become free to
play
next month
which i did not like hearing that
because i already spent so much money on
buying sims and all its extra games only
the base game though only the base game
yeah the
um the packs to make the game bigger
are still gonna be
only for exchange of money but that's
still pretty cool and fairy for someone
who didn't get the game yet but
it makes me very salty when games do
that like fall guys as well right fall
guys used to be a pay to play and now
it's free to play right
kind of
makes me mad
i don't like that when games that i'm
paid for suddenly i'm free to play
but
if you think about it sims 4
let's see
sims 4.
i think you said by wrote to me
ah
[Music]
yeah she says she's watching the stream
anyway i was saying i wanted to check
sims 4
released
in 2014
that is eight years ago
and people are saying
the fact that they are making also this
has never happened before in the history
of sims i think the fact that they're
making it free to play
seems like they want uh they're gonna
announce the release of sims 5 soon then
oh hi
which is exciting i can't come um
i can't come up cause i need hazmat i
have one i found one i can drop it to
the floor and hope you you you get it
[Music]
is that ah that's you that dot is here
wait i'll throw it from
[Music]
a it from here maybe
more
wait
dana can you hear me
can you hear me
[Music]
i'm dropping one down here
oh it's falling down
[Music]
[Laughter]
means you're coming up here you're gonna
die
it should be fine
nina that's not safe
i know you crazy
also be careful helicopter is coming
it seems fine
that's like insane guys there hasn't
been a new sims
game since sims 4 since 2014 it's
actually crazy
actually crazy guys
that's like really exciting
to you
this is
did you find your body
[Music]
you need to find your body
i know if she's hearing me
[Music]
no she's alive i think as long as that
mark
there is green the p
and she's alive i think
i need to call it an island meeting
uh
see my body tell me where it is
okay
i i didn't see it before though
maybe when she like
fell like when she died it dropped like
my body dropped so it should be
somewhere on the ground
the first body though i think she didn't
die again
also if you don't take everything that's
in these things
do they just never
[Music]
uh despawn
because then i should probably empty
them
yeah yeah yeah that's what i'm thinking
too in october they're probably gonna
release info on sims 5
which is really [\h__\h] exciting i'm i'm
ready
i'm ready for a new sims game but i'm
really curious to how it's gonna like
visually look like because if you
compare
sims 1 sims 2 sims 3 sims 4
the graphic
the graphic style
has changed quite a bit okay am i making
it down safely this time actually
like not not the graphics cell but like
the art style like it it's it has on it
it's been like pretty
like comical
comic style before and then it went a
little bit more realistic but not really
and you know it's interesting i want to
know what they're going for next i i
think sims will never try to look
like realistic you know which is good it
should it should not look realistic but
i also i don't want it to look like um
like disney
style i don't think
that that's the way to go either
[Music]
oh hi
nina
no
you just fall down again
[Music]
you're not good yeah oh god yes she died
wait i can try to help you right wait
wait don't die
you're really bad at this
she's like orange i think that means she
needs help
oh
i almost killed myself for you
how do i help you oh i can loot you
how does one i guess she's already dead
it's too late is it too late
[Laughter]
[Music]
on it i came to rescue her and she's
just dead
this girl is not making a good
experience on this date huh
[Music]
all right where could her if her body
drops to the ground then
[Music]
i don't know
let's find it
the first body although the first body
maybe is gone by now it looks at corpses
it's too late
i mean i thought she was you know when
you die you're at that stage first where
somebody can help you i thought it was
that
my date's done let's go
[Music]
yeah it will be a backpack right i'm
also trying to look for her back but
wait she
she fell pretty early on and then i
looked down and didn't see anything but
where exactly was that spot
[Music]
oh
maybe like here
[Music]
at least now she would have an empty
inventory
oh lena
[Music]
is that her
how do you know
ah she's on her way
she's
he's really not
like
you know and seems
since we're talking about sins and sins
when you have a party or a date or so
there will be like certain things you
have to accomplish during that time to
make it a good experience
and if you don't do anything it's gonna
be a shitty party or shitty experience
or shitty date and the the sim will then
be kind of disappointed that it was so
shitty
and i think right now
nina is not having the the best
experience
grades away yeah see you
somewhere after this she died
[Music]
like
no
now it's getting [\h__\h] dark again
don't like it
[Music]
well maybe maybe she doesn't have
anything so important anyway but it was
before you enter
wasn't it like
maybe wait was down
here
[Music]
no i remember looking down and i just
saw this like greeny greeny stuff
she died after the jump after
which jump
this one
nah she made that one
this is not a jump
[Music]
no i guess i we did go inside
once
never mind
she died outside but oh said
no that's just that okay
well i feel like right now 15 minutes
have passed what do you guys think
i'll try to go up ah maybe somewhere
here
let's hope i don't die
yeah that feels familiar
[Music]
uh here here
ah
oh the hazmat suit
[Music]
throw you a hazmat suit i see you
i see you i throw it down okay try to
look where it falls it should be just
wait no no please no cause um
i won't be able to find
okay um i i i think the crate should be
ready now i'll go get it
okay i'm scared now i'll [\h__\h] up
probably because i'm nervous
okay i'm fine i'm fine
okay
getting really good at this
nailed it
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and then here
[Music]
oh there's never oh
well that's too difficult i feel like i
oh hi letting me some food
yes
wait how do i get to you
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that's a difficult jump again
foreign
[Music]
oh my god
what oh she died again are you dying
[Laughter]
just stay where you are i'll go get the
crate
you didn't hear that probably
mata
[Laughter]
yeah
i feel like she is
she's very very um
[Music]
what's the word
what's the right porn today
it's the only word i can think of right
now
mary porn
pom pom
keeps on dying all the time
way way why are you
such a little pond issue
is my crate ready
[Music]
is it ready
it's ready
[Music]
that looks something like some nice
stuff let me get rid of the useless
things
don't need to wrap a body
a camera cctv
[Music]
assault rifle looks cute
oh yeah yeah yeah
maybe get rid of
the hammer can remake that one easily
what is this
a thompson
mp5 what's mp5
stack it
oh you can stack that wait
oh
an aiming model
i don't think i'll be using that but
oops
[Music]
ah i want to recycle them but
i don't need this
[Music]
for the module
yeah i don't think i'll be using it
yeah i would think normally you wouldn't
be able to stack it but we made
something stackable that you normally
can't against the club
okay
i got it
later coming down
coming down
[Music]
now we go check out elena's house
i didn't die a single time guys
i need to find my body which one
which one
the first one
oh
[Music]
okay
i'll try to see
if i can find it too
so
it should be
somewhere in this area outside right
[Music]
before this
but then it definitely fell down
[Music]
so i looked
up
was it here
[Music]
or before
i think it was before
my [\h__\h] heart every time i do this my
kind okay
[Music]
but did you see something guys
did you see something
it definitely fell to the ground you
just have to inspect the ground or
somewhere in between if it's like bugged
somewhere
below that part
below i can't go lower than this oh you
mean like
it should i mean if it fell down then it
probably would be like around the three
pipes
scared
let's see
right
shouldn't it be there
i feel like it should be there at least
we know roughly where it would be like
where that place is above
i think i should ramp i've replicated
the jump several times but i just didn't
die ha ha
[Music]
we'll get it
i had a bridge
oh
wait i never went down here
yeah
it's okay when you can just camp a few
crates
[Music]
what did you have
what exactly did you have because c4
right you took one c4 i think
[Music]
okay
only winter if guns mats oh dana you
shouldn't travel
with so much stuff in your bags
okay
oh wait
i see a bag but
that's uh
a different dead body but we said it
should be around here right
[Music]
oh it's not here
great lena there's a crate coming
[Music]
maybe that one has some good stuff for
you
i think she's listening to the stream by
the way
even though she doesn't she's not close
but i think she's listening in the
stream
[Music]
on the pillar
oh yes
i have extra at home i'm pretty sure or
i can make one for you i don't need this
one take it take it where are you
[Music]
go go
ah here come come here come here okay
[Music]
i'm meeting you oh thank you
thank you i'm gonna i'm gonna try to
like look for it again okay
we
should see
[Music]
my eyes on the price baby
you can go check the uh
you can go check the crate if you want i
can
we can meet up
i yeah maybe i'll look a little bit
though i'm looking i'm looking
[Music]
it's not on this concrete block
not that i can tell
[Music]
it would it still and you guys saw it
you guys actually saw it
[Music]
later they saw it though in the chat
um
[Music]
yeah you guys talking about the old one
because i already checked that one out
the old one with the stone dead one
right take out this
oh you didn't mean yeah did you not mean
that one
up on the pill there's so many pillows
[Music]
gotta get good out
it's there
oh
there
[Music]
yes
i mean i hope it's the right one uh is
it like wait wait wait wait wait i swear
wow nice stuff you got there i can't
pick it up though nina because i have a
full inventory too but if you um jump
and down from from hold on jump from
right there
trying to fight me i'm like
huh it's this um
this where are you
uh after the
after the
the free tubes it's like right at the
beginning and then you jump down like
um
[Music]
tubes where what is that the wait okay
let's meet at the ground let's meet at
the ground come come come come at the
very bottom
[Music]
i'll teach you how to get there where
are you down there okay okay okay
from here
going huh
uh-huh
here you go you have to go so i can show
you
yeah
over here
oh
and then down here
yeah
[Music]
oh
i fell here oh my god
i think your back continued falling down
here you didn't even fall that far
yeah
i don't know oh
[Music]
yeah i would come back for that stuff
too
[Music]
nice i'm glad we got it in the end thank
you but now that's your view on you know
i know what you need no it's okay we
should go to your house to store that
stuff safely because i wanted to see
your house anyway
okay
go horsey
i need to drink water
oh well
oh i have one yeah
i will take your water give you water
thank you
nice i don't need all of it just a
couple sips bang oops thank you
where are the horses
[Music]
horsey john
yeah
i hope they didn't do spawn
around there because we came she's
clocking the other way
because i think i am
yeah make sure to find the body of your
dad's partner after they died
um it will improve your relationship
with your partner in case your partner
was able to revive which is
totally a realistic thing that can
happen i think our horses are gone
[Music]
um
ah i'll never mind
hey
yeah it was the other one
okay i will follow you to your home now
go go okay
um we're going to go um
somewhere all the way up here oh man
i got some important stuff
or something
there's like a shop there if you see at
the map actually
it's after that my home if we go a
little bit uh uh west first then we can
stop at my home and i can at least leave
my things
because on the way oh sure sure yeah if
we go that way it's on the way okay
yeah
yeah i don't know let's go up this stuff
[Music]
do you know that um anime i think it's
also a manga shirokuma cafe
[Music]
very cute i watched like when it came
out and watched like a few episodes yeah
long time ago
oh maybe i should make a sleeping bag
yeah
yeah somewhere in my home i'll make a
sleeping bag for your home
don't slow down
hurry up have you been feeding your
horse pumpkin
uh meat but uh since we left home i
guess it didn't eat anything
come on
[Music]
we'll check it hope it's got action are
you kidding it has no action at all
please don't get your hopes up
it's just one of those cute
like slow
slow living kind of animes
really comfy one yeah
all right let's get the horse in
position
you need that food
yeah that's okay
do i have something to recycle
the pc and got some stuff okay okay
let's be fast let's be fast let's be
fast
i feel like in these three and a half
hours i
barely did anything meaningful
[Laughter]
oh well
it's fine
i'll keep that for the war
[Music]
should i recycle this so keep it
i'll keep it for researching maybe
[Music]
okay you guys say i did stuff okay if
you think that was productive then i
i'll leave you to that opinion
if you guys want to think that way i'll
gladly take that oh hello
okay i'm ready ready to go just need to
drop some things off
revenge yeah that was a nice surprise
that elena showed up out of nowhere i'm
lucky
so lucky that there's some
actually
addicted
rest players that are online at any
given time
[Music]
i wonder i don't think i'll be needing
oh i hear music
i don't think i'll be needing the
armor or the hazmat suit
if
[Music]
ah i don't need it i have another one
you can keep it if you wanna okay then
okay
[Music]
what a [\h__\h] mess in here
so are these explosives which these are
the ah those are explosive
[Music]
i need normal ammo
oh well
guys i'm not planning on using it much
more today
okay
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i will off screen sort out all of this
[Music]
hi shin guys
okay
i am ready
oh shoot i forgot i think
my thompson oh well whatever what's with
your pumps in
what happened uh it's all right i can
just like i have another one at home no
because like i was holding the thumbs in
so obviously it wasn't in the bag uh
that one fell off whatever
yeah probably just
i have extra i have extra no no big deal
okay let's go next door go next
so next go next
and yeah that happened to me too but
thankfully i had something not so
important in my hands
sorry i thought i could jump off the
horse like in minecraft again
did you press facebook
[Music]
i wonder where the crates dropped
somewhere here
must have been somewhere there
maybe i'll go look looking for it after
ah
there hasn't been one there in a while
actually i think ever since
oops ever since uh we were there and you
took it i don't think it respawned there
yeah i took like two
oh oops yeah
[Music]
wait stupid horse
okay okay it respawned really quickly
and then it stopped spawning
damn
why
take me home
to your place oh
if we follow the if we follow the road
um
i never mind i was going to say like
there's a temporary house but it doesn't
have any boxes anyways ah so now i wanna
see your main house
[Music]
what's your game of the year
your favorite game this year
my favorite game is either somnium files
the second game
what makes it so great
that i really really like
um so the very first game i really
really like it a lot is basically like a
you know typical detective murder
mystery thing but with a twist you like
those kind of things um
these games are my favorite
oh nice i'm happy you found a nice game
again can we take a left here i think
no i'm so dumb
oh three okay
wait
oh [\h__\h]
okay now
sorry horse i wanted to i wanted to be
cool and cut the sign
my favorite game this year is tunic by
the way i recommend it
my favorite game this year is tunic
[Music]
yeah it's so
good
yeah
i really like it
oh
he's not shooting us i guess because i
don't have the weapon in my hand
where are
we this area looks much nicer because
[\h__\h] the desert man it's so depressing
green stuff is where it's at what
this is this area is way prettier
yeah i wanted to make a house like
around the desert area too but i felt
like i would be depressed oh i don't
know yeah i only did it there because
i'mma recommended it for living and i
was like okay
and then i was lucky because pakoda
lives right there as well
yeah she has a point
nice car
cute
see my house is nothing impressive so
you know
don't make it happen step up your game
what the [\h__\h]
wait a second hello who's this
oh
where is you
no
oh
diana oh
she's not streaming right
hello i don't have voice chat on huh
oh
yeah you look like an npc maybe
he's an npc
judging
hello ah oh she sounds so sleepy
hello
[Music]
what are you guys doing uh sightseeing
oh
oh okay excited to see she's gonna look
at my house and you know she was already
like yo whose house is that so cool and
i'm like yeah i might have something
like that
oh okay what are you doing
it's like trying to grind
i was like grinding for stones and woods
um
i got plenty of those thanks to piccolo
and azuki senpai
anyway
good luck yeah just keep going and yes
yeah uh really i think i i i will just
follow you i want to know your place
dude it's there
where
you want to come with
oh we're already dead there you see that
thing with like with like the inflatable
pool on top you have an inflatable pool
[Music]
ah
dude it's here
dude it's right here
okay uh i think i should have gotten
from the right side of them
let me try to go from
here
dude dude oh the bear
oh should we kill it
it's not good for the environment
to kill the little remaining polar bears
right
not good for the animal
whatever
okay horsester
pool
cool a pool
elena i saw your i saw the bear
the bear the polar bear
should i kill it
[Music]
national embarrassment it's a national
no [\h__\h] way
there it is but that's really oh you
could go skiing here if not all the
[\h__\h] snow is melted
too bad this would be a nice slope like
a really nice slope
skinny eyes
this would be a nice slope
[Music]
oh it's running
i failed my mission
but you know what i wanted that to
happen i wanted it to survive but
in this world we need to challenge each
other
yeah you're naked now why are you so
naked is that your switch yeah this is a
bear park basically
yeah
nice but
it's swimsuit
thank you
everybody in russ has this kind of butt
i think but thank you still
this is my house it has nothing it's
just it's a house
sleep outside
i live like this i'm sorry
what
wait
these are furnaces wait why why why
on like why
why why because it's compact
oh my god wow this is where i live
cleaner
what the [\h__\h]
it does the job
you were like building something nice
together with me i i i
i'm gonna steal your things i'm going to
steal your things
oh nice hat
oh my nice hand
oh
[Music]
i just wanted to i just wanted to build
something like like this i guess this is
not that of like a normal not even
efficient it's not even efficient
why
let's go to the pool
[Music]
don't make fun of it it's not like
everyone lifts this can make like a big
house
yeah but like the eh
[Music]
like i get it
[Laughter]
oh that's so cute oh my god oh that's so
cute
look at this
you yeah go very far with this
you can't really
you can't really i recently expanded
this one so that's why the pool side is
this big
oh i don't know i want to make like a
real leisure house with like a pool and
stuff but i don't know if i wanna it's
already like the second half of the
season yeah
yeah
i'm also doing way less than i expected
in this season i wanted to do more but
oh well kind of loose lost my
motivation mostly
you guys swim
yeah go swim swim
yeah
[Music]
drop down here oh
i i respawn here
so it's like when i wake up it's like
rise and shine
your place is
ridiculous elena
it's ridiculous
what do you mean ridiculous what do you
mean why are you gonna build me a better
house and show me how it's done oh wait
you didn't get your own house it's shut
up i did i didn't build the house as
like a starting point but then well i
mean
yeah
[Music]
yeah what
[Laughter]
[Music]
i the thing is um so i was just gonna
ask for help for the stairs but then
they built so much and then i was just
gonna build something on the top but
then piccolo built a whole tower at the
top now there's no space for me to build
so
yeah it was more than i expected oh well
[Music]
good tower yeah
um if you want to uh if you want to put
a sleeping bag
here
i forgot
i forgot i uh
i can make you a sleeping bag i like to
be honest really i don't have any cloth
with me now
it's a hemp
[Music]
did you just say that's so cute
the she has to like authorize the tc man
then she can access everything huh
yeah i didn't i didn't authorize myself
though i think
i i
[Music]
this place is ridiculous it's absolutely
ridiculous this is ridiculous it's
ridiculous
it's already triggering me now
oops
it's triggering me what do you mean
triggering
that's [\h__\h] triggering me can't get
through
are you okay look at it
i'm sorry sorry sorry
[\h__\h] glitching through the door
unbelievable
okay can you can you um can you
authorize yourself oh i will try yes i
did i did i did did i
oh
it doesn't work
no i can't
probably because
this thing this triangle is in the way
maybe that's why
because i can't actually open it i don't
know if you would normally open it but
you lost it i guess you just locked it
can you crouch
yeah but yeah i locked it
um what can i do with the log
excuse me
please maybe i wouldn't have to move if
your place wasn't so [\h__\h] tiny
there i unlocked
[Music]
you can put so much stuff in there
why can't you put
fertilizer
into the tc i thought you can only put
in materials that the house needs for
not decaying
really well if you want to sleep the
only place is outside
well where's mine where's my sleeping
bag
what the [\h__\h] oh yeah
what's happening right now i think maybe
kyle's trying to turn your house down
stop touring the house touring
i'm looking out of here i don't see
anything
[Music]
oh
i don't know i'm gonna sleep if anything
i'll sleep outside
open open up i can't open the doors
open open
can you give me the sleeping bag please
[Music]
be sure
i i gave you
thank you thank you
thank you okay
[Music]
it's a pvp game and i've yet to
experience barely any pvp so excuse me
for trying to shoot someone
we need some action well do you want to
change that
[Laughter]
shopping training yeah yeah so we're
chopping the trees that are in
lana's territory stairs yeah if i could
only go upstairs you want to see
use the ladder yeah okay
sleep while looking at the stars
there you go that's mine now that's
actually kind of quiet
too oh you can you can like put it like
oh okay
[Music]
you sleep
you wake up and you can't immediately
take a bath
[Applause]
[Music]
what's happening what's happening there
what's happening
[Music]
where is anya
where does she live
yeah
good question
anya who are you talking
to who is she talking to
who is this
is this built by someone or is this
generated by the game
this is by the game right
[Music]
a junkyard here
what
damn
this place is big
[Music]
actually i might go looking for the
other crate
if i can find it okay now
i'm gonna leave you now
[Music]
unless you wanna still follow me but i'm
gonna go looking for another crate
yeah
because your voice starts um it's
starting to glitch you know that
you know
oh proximity chat your voice is
glitching on my end yeah and robot
lena thanks for keeping me company love
you
too
[Music]
you too good night
oh yes me
[Music]
i'm gonna go grab my horse
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] i love you
how dare you
i dare you i'm bleeding
and you're laughing you're just laughing
[Music]
she's just giggling
be careful
[Music]
ah getting the pvp going now
i came for peace
peace peace five versus fine
and not pvp
y forces five p p mean
wait is this pvp people versus uh
phoenix i killed her i did
what
then
she sponsored
[Music]
wait why is she green now why is she
green what does that mean
so i think kaila doesn't know what
happened let's not tell her
murder
bye-bye have fun
[Music]
i did i didn't think i i thought i
missed the whole time
it only looked like i was missing to me
tonight
damn i mean i do have explosive munition
maybe that makes it go boom
even stronger
[Laughter]
i wasn't even trying that hard
but this gun is difficult with the
recoil
pretty difficult
anyway where am i going
i am
sorry
[Music]
but we were just talking about you know
also she started shooting she started
she started
i think i think i remember she started
it
right
[Music]
she will beat the crap out of me next
time heart emoji
oh so sweet so
teddy all the love do you feel the whole
the love
[Music]
it's just so
moving
it hurts to keep my my pinky on the
shift button continuously
i wish there was like a like a lock on
you know like the
wait did i just lock it on
no
or maybe did i it just stops after a
while when it's like
a moment oh and we've been so nice so
helpful
goddammit
that would have been really helpful but
you can deliver it to me if you ever
pass my my grounds again you can deliver
it to my home
gladly i'll take it
yeah i guess i could remap it but
whatever
stop shooting bastard or i will kill you
i swear to god
they're all out for death
they all want to die they choose
what
is that
stuff
[Music]
this
dealership
racing car ah i highly doubt it's a
legit racing car
if i would buy that would i be highly
disappointed or what
i have a feeling i would
scam
i call it skim
okay here we are at my place but i want
to go even further and i don't have that
much stuff in my inventory so i think i
can
i can go
i wanna
see if oh wait there's actually also
crate in the dome again but there
there should be one around there that
area too oh hello
is that who is that
[Music]
she told me to go to sleep i said it's 9
pm here girl
[Music]
watching
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
a peaceful random meeting yeah what
should i shoot her
i told her to sleep but
i don't know what she's doing
[Music]
she's tea bagging me would you call this
tea bagging only when i'm dead
damn
intimidating
oh my my
my
what
she's good at oh there you go
bye bye
okay okay let's go get the crate i don't
know what she's doing but i guess she's
not going for the crate because she was
going the other way
all righty my crate
my crate
that was kinda the same pie
[Music]
mm-hmm
a certain dominance
i didn't feel so dominated
i need to try harder canada senpai
oh oh dear
see that one doesn't shoot me is it
because i don't have the weapon upon
probably
all right so somewhere here i think
there could be a crate unless somebody
already took it but i feel like i was
like
i'm not not not here i thought it was
here already but i feel like i was on
the dome and looking in that that
direction and it looked like it was like
dropping around there what do you guys
think
would that do you guys remember would
you think it was rather close or really
really far
didn't look that far
[Music]
east
yeah i think so too
i think i was looking east
good morning from europe
oh come on not again it's not warning me
i wonder if that's the same person as
last time
it's not morning time
[Music]
you can't see engage at all
yeah there you go now you see all
everything
just in case you were so curious
it was the whole interaction was
basically uh
hello
why are you awake and she's like i
should ask the same question to you and
then i was like well it's [\h__\h] 9 p.m
here of course i'm awake
and then she's like oh let's see and
then i'm like what are you doing and she
said she said
uh i i was
coming to hang out or play
but
it kind of implied that she was coming
to
europe
so then i was like oh everybody says
that but nobody's actually coming
so i don't believe you
yeah that was basically the interaction
yeah
okay
we can we can go up to uh maybe we go up
to that one first
because that one needs 15 minutes anyway
yeah not me mama is in europe i need to
ask her like i think like at the moment
she probably wants to
you know find
her place and
and like you know
just
[Music]
how to say what's the word einstein
pendant
sadly and that's the word yeah oh
ah forgot my
[\h__\h] where's husband horse
oh that's not my horse
i don't have the hazmat suit oh oh god
damn it
[Music]
okay let's try to find the other thing
first
yeah she'll be there for quite some time
so i think there's enough time for us to
meet up
and i think it might not necessarily be
in austria maybe we'll just meet in any
country that she was interested in
visiting and
feels like
would be nice to have someone
around
i mean i don't speak
french or spanish or whatever but
i think
i think it would still make you feel oh
i think i saw it
more
more relieved is that it
was that close
[Music]
i at least have the european attitude
you know
so i know my way around somehow
uh-huh
another thumpson
that's some good stuff
nice
that was easy
was that really the one huh
okay
then
[Music]
maybe
i go
back for the hazmat suit and we go here
one more time and then let's go get the
crate but it takes 15 minutes
[Music]
keep the pipe for what
european attitude no i mean like you
know the european way of thinking
and used to being in europe i've been to
paris before i've been to spain
like
you know
i said hot air balloon
okay you know what whatever i'll go back
and then we'll end it there i think it's
been four hours and i need to read super
chats
and then i want to cook
i need to cook today
i'm gonna cook some chicken
with um
cashew
cashew nut
sauce
yes
rice
cashew nuts
sauce apparently
[Music]
which is an interesting sauce but yeah
that's the recipe
yummy
and then tomorrow
tomorrow is the release of my new song
in the music video i am planning
um to have the mv reveal
uh
i might i probably will do it at 4 pm
because
i think it's gonna be like
um
a midnight release for every country
again and 4 p.m that's
no wait no wait 5 p.m i'll do it at 5 00
pm my time because that's probably
when it releases in japanese music
services you know because it then it
will be midnight in japan
here
yeah and then so you guys won't be able
to stream it yet but at least the music
video will be out and then whenever it's
midnight in your country
that's when you should be able to stream
the song
in spotify amazon music wherever it's
been a long time since my last
music video drop my last
music drop i really need to go to the
isle meeting i'm like
bursting
i'm about to burst
i have so much to say to my manager
[Music]
oh oh it's running out of stamina we're
almost there we're almost there why
almost there horsey
are we [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah i'm excited i finally want to show
you my new song it's been so long
it wasn't supposed to take this long but
yeah
and there's so many crates here
[Music]
bursting with excitement
totally yes
yes
[Music]
that's not my place right
my place
there there i can't
i need to go
[Music]
sniping that dude
from the very top
i will try that
you guys think i can see him from there
i think so
[Music]
i'm going to try i want to try it i'm
going to try i'm going to try
[Music]
it will be a good test although this one
won't run around like crazy but i think
i think this will be
interesting
ah
[Applause]
okay
okay horse
you eat
enjoy
good job
let me get up there
[Music]
no no
just let me go let me go
[Music]
i'm fine i'm i'm i'm going to be fine
i'm really good at um
holding in my idol meetings
really good
[Music]
okay almost there
more stairs
endless stairs yes
[Music]
can't believe piccolo senpai put so much
effort into this
because
she took my my idea seriously that i
thought if i put a tower up there i can
watch her and protect her
[Music]
once she heard that she's like you know
what this this will benefit me greatly
so i shall help you to benefit me
for the bigger cause the greater course
[Music]
okay
question is
can i see
[Music]
what's going on there
i think it was like somewhere here
oh
oh okay i can i can see some stuff
[Music]
i feel like he should be like there
i know wait oh
nice
[Music]
oh record
you won't be able to shoot me there
idiot
where is he there
so i have to aim lower
[Music]
did i hit him oh was that a hit
oh [\h__\h]
higher okay
he's looking for me
[Music]
ah
there we go nice it was beautiful
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
okay
so we will do
that plenty full
when
we have to protect piccola
[Music]
okay i might as well just stay here
uh well i mean now i don't think anyone
will really try to mess around with this
but um
[Music]
before
before the big war if it happens again
that's when we have to protect
this place
uh sleeping back here to respawn yeah
that would be nice anyway i'll just stay
here now
[Music]
i will go for idle meeting and then i'll
see you guys to read some super chats
okay
you're welcome to stay
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah thanks for watching so far
thank you soon tomorrow is um
a new music video new new song release
do you and
i was thinking of doing a stream on the
german channel later but
i'll think about it
bye-bye see you later
[Music]
food
me
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
hello
yellow
[Music]
very cute
was like
in the bathroom with me
she was like sniffing something
not me just some there were some clothes
on the ground
there was like um
some kind of bug i think some tiny baby
bug
and
trunks was like really really really
really really carefully
like sniffing the ground trying to get
close to the bug i think
now they were in front of the washing
machine because i just watched them have
to hang them up
and uh yeah she was sniffing
[Music]
she was flinching at every sound and
every movement and then i
i found it funny so i just made like a
breathing laughing noise like
[Music]
you know just like that
and even at that she flinched like crazy
[Music]
so cute she's so scary the cat such a
scared cat
are you cats block hunters yeah like
they
they play around with them but they
don't actually
it depends on the bug sometimes they try
to eat them
but they never properly eat them
unfortunately they just like start
munching and then leave them there while
they're
suffering
we brush my hand against something to
make him jump what are you doing on
purpose on your
cat
my especially chunkers is like extra
careful and always so scared of
everything
ah
but
i have to say i'm really happy
um with my cat's sleeping position at
the moment i have to i have to report
because it makes me really happy you
know they always after
like
two weeks or so they always kind of like
change their favorite sleeping position
and you know i think i told you guys for
chunkers
i got her a new box and at first she
seemed to like it but then she ditched
it very really quickly and was just
always sleeping
on
the ground
right
next to the bed
right next to my head basically
just right down there
her her body was touching the bed but
she wouldn't come up anymore she
wouldn't sleep on the bed so i'm like
girl why
do you sleep up here with me and this
movie was also like i don't know where
the hell's movie was nah nice movie was
sleeping on the bed though i think
but then after a while i got rid of the
extra box
and now
smoovie sleeps
right on my head side where the box used
to be
which is for me crazy because movie
would never sleep that close to me ever
before
but now she's always right next to my
head
always
and chunkers is also back up on the bed
she now likes to sleep like
around my hips
or so
um so i always first when i fall asleep
i turn sideways to cuddle with junkie
finally she lets me cuddle with her
while falling asleep
and somewhere after like two or three
hours i wake up and i'm like why am i
sideways on the bed
and trunks is gone and then i roll back
into the normal position and this movie
is there and i cuddle this movie
and then sometime after five hours i
wake up again and i see both chunky and
smoothy on the bed
so happy
so much to cuddle with so much floof i
don't even know where to start
[Music]
ah so happy uh
yeah there's so much love
oh
yeah um
so much purring too
you know purring is healing
oh no no no i don't think i roll around
a lot not at all i never
do that so i also don't roll on top of
my cats thankfully
oh [\h__\h] do you guys remember where i
stopped reading
i don't remember the number
did anyone write it down
[Music]
which one
one dog
[Music]
yeah there's numbers yeah yeah yeah if i
read it in hololyzer
which is really helpful
[Music]
oh a six hour mark ah yeah i said oh
we're halfway through so let's end it
but didn't i go even a bit further like
6 30 or so
[Music]
ah there's some there's some gesundheit
super chats there are those
the moon dog is here
[Music]
that's yeah 5 17.
nice
oh yeah that that could be
[Music]
i feel like i've read it until i saw a
red one and i was like
let's end it here
i have 17.
[Music]
ah oh what i already clicked around i
don't know if i unmarked something by
accident it was definitely around here
and i remember
going quickly over the sneeze jets um
all right
um
endless
danke soon for the red super chat
happy anniversary kiana thanks for the
varied
and frequent content looking forward to
continuing to tune into your streams in
the year ahead thank you
did i read this one i wonder
maybe i did if not that's fine too
it's fine
i'll continue doing my best
endless thank you for supporting me
[Music]
nice to see a name that i don't see it
so much no more in the super chat those
thank you very much
also i'm gonna put up just the thumbnail
i guess
i'm gonna put it
here
[Music]
okay
tanaka thank you for the rest of the
chat they all doubted her they said she
was just a small fry in the fast food
world but two years later cafe isn't
going anywhere tremble fast with rivals
because we're not gonna kick the bucket
anytime soon
even from the deepest deep fryer the
phoenix always rises
thank you
very inspiring very motivating tanaka
yeah that one sounds very
fresh i didn't read that one before
definitely
yay
[Music]
biggest fast food company one day one
day
thank you tanaka for believing in our
purpose
[Music]
thank you for the rainbow
congratulations on two years of kicking
the kicking good times there might have
been ups and downs but what matters is
that you are now in front of us
chimpkins more beautiful than ever cuter
than ever more attractive than ever oh
feels kind of a waste for not coming
across your channel much earlier or even
watching your debut i started my whole
life journey sort of with hatchima oh
was it around the time where
she was doing all these like story
videos i wonder
maybe that's what got you
hooked
um when council debuted then i then did
i started watching more of hollow ian
sanna and bay caught my attention back
then oh
eventually my youtube started to be
flooded with more halloween clips i
think somehow i have a natural
attraction to aussies
yeah hatsumasana bay and then me
interesting
gradually a funny orange burp attracted
my attention more for clips it was last
year on her henry stigma stream that i
decided to be reborn as an egg
i can remember back then i was like oh
my god this bird is so funny i'm signing
myself up
as we're deciding my oh she only made up
this year
damn
i it felt like you were around longer
hmm
to be continued like in the aleca soon
all right it's time for me to sleep have
lectures in a few hours time oh
oh thank you wow it took you quite a
while to get to
your favorite streamer
even though you were like
around me
by watching other whole life members for
quite some time but then finally you
found me
nice
it took you a while but you're there you
darren that's all that counts thank you
so much open the link
[Music]
it is it is also funny you went from
hatama to sana and bae and then to me
then watching that aussie
collab that we did
[Music]
must have been
very nice because it's all the girls
that you liked
all of them
[Music]
perfect
the perfect combination
that's him i wasn't really playing i
mean she was for most of the game
thankfully it only happened around the
end and she thought she was playing so
she still was kind of involved we
thought she was playing she thought she
was playing
so in the end you know
[Music]
yeah
it's fun it's fun
very very induction
[Music]
burning noodles thank you for the devil
super chat red one yesterday i left your
stream promising that i'll be around
till next year
later that i had to leave to help a
friend
evacuate cause of fire warnings on you
damn
long foot short i just wanted to say
thank you guys and the cats behind the
curtain
even in this time of chaos you still
make a smile cat behind the curtain
does that mean does that mean the person
behind kiara
like me
i'm kiana
is that a saying
does that mean
the person behind it
oh
what do you mean the actual cats
well i'm the cat
or the staff
[Music]
in any case you're thanking someone
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
you're saying you you promised that
you'll be around till next year well i
hope that's not like a
like a
maximum
but at least i'll have you for a long
time i hope
thank you for the support
yay
i hope that the fire warning turned out
to be nothing
in particular be careful
[Music]
i'm a cat
hmm i could be
[Music]
thank you burning noodles a kiss
thanks for the pinky happy two years
tantra i can't believe it's already been
two years since you graced us with your
fiery energy and warm vibes you keep
amazing me all
with all your hard work towards your 3d
concert collabs and creative stream
ideas keep it up thank you
i wish i had more
creative stream ideas and i wish they
were you know like super easy
to make it happen i wish i could snap my
fingers and have 10 people at my
disposal to collab with me or work for
me or whatever
at any given time
[Music]
it's not always that easy and some
things take more work than other things
yeah but yeah stuff like iron beads
thank you i thought that was really cute
too and the hollow bags
i want to do holo bags again at some
point
yeah the book club will take a while
just for the simple fact that take that
we need time to read a book
[Music]
but i'll make it happen
yeah snack boxes too yeah yeah actually
i'm still owed two boxes that should
have arrived a while ago
i don't know where the hell they went
i mean
you need to check with them
maybe there was a tracking number i need
to check where they went there should be
two more boxes though
i think
[Music]
but
yeah after that the subscription is over
and i'll either look for a different
subscription or
i'll just end that series here and try
to replace it with something else
although it was a it was a nice series
i i would like to continue it
[Music]
but i look for a different service first
yeah maybe i can even get sponsored you
know
buy some company
i know there are a lot of these
companies but um this one at least was
you know german speaking in germany so
it was easy to receive and all that
snack box
monthly
[Music]
books
international snack grade box
that's just japanese i need like
everything oh snack crate a monthly box
from around the world
website looks fine
[Music]
ah
oh your first snack adventure you can
choose and the next one will be a
surprise
but yeah the problem is if i use a
different
service the chances of it overlapping
are higher like overlapping with a
country that i already did
are higher than if i just go with the
same one again because the same service
would try to not overlap
too much within like two years at least
i would say
[Music]
but i will look into it maybe maybe we
can even like um if i ask them to
sponsor me maybe we can even like um try
to sort it out so that they sent me a
box that
i didn't like from a country i didn't
look into yet
if they have the option to choose anyway
then there should be several ones at
their disposal i would assume
[Music]
oh but
i just thought of a problem but never
mind i'll look into it another time
anyway thank you rosaline thank you
thank you for sharing your feedback and
your love
golden boomi thank you
thank you for the red super chat
dear tend to happy anniversary in my oc
i will continue watching every stream
buy every merch really support you in
every chance i have glory to kfp viva la
quina also don't forget to buy food
thank you i already i had i had a lot of
food i think uh during the stream ah but
you mean like
i guess i wanted to order food uh
before the stream ended i ended up not
doing that because i
i just ate some
some
noodles
some instant noodles from my storage
yeah
was not the best dinner but
at that point i was like whatever
yeah the contents still have potential
to continue i mean the snack box i agree
i think so too i wanna there's still so
many countries
um
[Music]
yeah anyway thank you john mold
no need to get every merch but
i think if you don't get it you'll also
regret it so
yeah
you do you if you want to get all of it
you're welcome to do so
what about kinder country don't worry i
can get kinder country at any time
thankfully
entirety thank you for the rent of the
chat another one this time you're
serving me some coffee
thank you i don't drink coffee but but i
could
use that
a lot of times i'm
i'm thinking of forcing myself to start
becoming a coffee drinker
maybe now that i'm
more adult and my taste buds have
changed maybe now i'm more receptive to
it
maybe it's worth a try
maybe starting with like a really really
really sweet one i like the smell of it
you know but not the taste
it happened with me too
i only can drink mochas
[Music]
with the chocolate right it's with
chocolate
[Music]
i
don't get addicted
what's g fuel
try a cafe latte
yeah yeah
i think that
i would definitely prefer that over like
a pure coffee
[Music]
we we definitely have really good coffee
in austria we have a coffee culture
[Music]
oh guys
it's totally random but
i saw
japan
come here
[Music]
i saw
i saw japan
is um
apparently
i don't want to get my hopes up too high
because they
they
like to get your hopes up like that but
i saw that japan
opened or is opening
borders for tourists
who are also
not going with any travel company
in october
until now was guided to but just like
yesterday i saw the news that the plan
is
that you can go as an individual tourist
without a guided tour without a tourist
company if
if that information was 100 correct that
means
as a tourist i could already go
and tbh
work visa
is possible too
[Music]
but
you know for going with all of myth more
planning is needed but i'm wondering
should i just go alone
and like you know
before because who knows how many more
times it's gonna be delayed i just go
alone and like hang a little bit with
people there
[Music]
like ahead of time and
just chillax have a meet meet nineteen
and everyone
maybe
i know
i'm thinking a little bit about it
[Music]
i i first want to make sure that it's
really true but i already
saw one of my friends
saw the news and already booked a flight
ticket because they're cheap right now
apparently
because people you know haven't been
booking flight tickets to japan for a
while so they're really cheap
[Music]
i i
i want to go
i
um i definitely want to be in japan
during november and december for a
specific reason one reason in november
is um
there's a tales of
collaboration with yomi londo
it's like a theme park in japan and
they're doing a collaboration i kind of
want to check it out
[Laughter]
yeah and then another reason december i
want to go to komike komi market because
i haven't been in a long long long long
long time
[Music]
so
i'll think about it
i'll see what happens and what what our
plans are in general
[Music]
i might um do it relatively
spontaneously
[Music]
yeah
anyway
i already told gemma about it she was
like oh yeah
[Music]
oh
oh oh she's turning around she's leaving
she
took a few steps oh no she's coming back
she's indecisive
it's okay i have to focus on super chats
anyway
i just want to tell you guys that you
may have seen it anyway
things change all the time so honestly
it's not really reliable but so far
it's just been getting better and better
and opening up more and more rather than
go like opening up and closing again and
opening up and closing again
so
that's pretty hopeful
[Music]
it's kind of unreal because i wasn't
able to go for such a long time that
now seeing it it feels like
can't be true i'm like so used to the
fact that i can't go japan
and like coping so much with that fact
because like we really wanted to go and
it's been delayed a million times
you know for the 3d and debut
delayed a million times
so i was
i accepted it
i was like okay i'll go to other places
then if you don't want to have me i'll
go to other places
[Music]
if only it would have been in time for
tokyo game show that would have been so
cool because i really wanted to see
tokyo game show
ah
[Music]
oh well anyway continuing
uh tai chi here's the case what
be our waters
[Music]
oh my god we're getting close to the end
zero look thank you oh for the rest of
the chat kinda late for the stream but i
still want to congratulate you attention
on your second anniversary keep it up
tanto you managed to achieve a lot of
things you wanted to do within two years
so i believe kp will be able to dominate
the world soon and we too is our
training
yeah but then you guys have to play aoe
too as well
and otherwise it's just training for me
and you guys are just backseating
um but thank you
you've also been around for a long time
it's nice to see you're still there
thank you so much
[Music]
please continue
enjoying and supporting hiwa content
yeah
really happy to see like oldies
still being here
[Music]
you're my watching hawaiian
european orgies
thank you
european bro let's go
[Music]
let's go
i'm an oldie but mostly a lurker that's
fine like thank you
hi junkie you're here again you can't
decide where you want to go huh
i touched her tail and then she flopped
on the ground demanding belly ribs but i
can't i can't now
no
crispy naked
thank you for the rainbow oh what is
that the profile picture looks cute
that's me right
yeah thank you for these two wonderful
years of you i may not be around as much
but just knowing that you are here
brings me joy i love you i really do
really
may we continue to be graced by your
beautiful voice strong presence and fun
antics for a long time to come
thank you
very sweet but
yeah you're not indeed not around much
because
your name
your name is not so
burned into my brain
but thanks for saying hi and supporting
me on such an important day
and the belly
[Music]
what are showing doing
oh my god
she's making out with
with a t-shirt on the ground
she's needing it what the [\h__\h]
she doesn't need so often this movie is
the needer in the family
the the cookie maker
oh my god what
that t-shirt is like totally normal
uh
cloth fabric i don't know why she likes
it so much
what's going on
no
no wait never okay i see why
wait is that my swimsuit
why did i put it here
oh it's because of the pool
the pool water yeah
um i think she
i mean it it's it's i washed it though i
don't smell i don't smell the pool water
but generally like she has a thing for
this kind of like you know the the
fabric that um
swimsuits are made out of
like stuff like that she does like yeah
and also generally like kind of like a
pool water smell or any kind of plastic
kind of smell
or or or texture
yeah
i you watch your swimsuit left here on
the ground
i think it fell down because i have my
um
currently i have my clove
clothing line hanger thingy in this room
i think it fell down
no i took it away from her now she's
like what the [\h__\h] am i supposed to do
now
yeah claw chlorine
she likes it
[Music]
yeah yeah don't worry she just was
kneading it's just not it's not like
she's bathing in it
[Music]
anyway thank you streaky clutch
thanks for the pinky attention i just
clicked on stage one heart mode with you
in the whole cure thank you
actually like i see so many people
saying they're clearing stages with the
new kiwawa
and someone wrote on twitter i think in
japanese like
um
after clearing with kiara i tried
clearing with other characters and i
can't anymore like hard mode i can't
clear it with anyone but kiana anymore
[Music]
apparently
i can imagine that in the heart mode
the 15 seconds of
uh revival
is
very useful
i could only be stationed with kiana at
first
yeah i really should give it a go too
[Music]
with halo and kiwa i forgot again what
halo does but i need to look into it
no don't nerf me again
i was nerfed before let me enjoy my
strong
powerful
op life please
[Music]
no nerf please no no no thank you no
i'm coming for you if you nerf my
character again you know who you are
yeah
anyway
sanji shone thanks for the pinky it's
already been two years if only my mind
could keep up with all the times we've
spent together same tbh
and if i wasn't such an airhead then
maybe i could find the right words to
express my gratitude for you i love you
kiara unconditionally
oh
i love you too
that's so sweet the word unconditionally
means
so much
on its own
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you i have a
really
uh
lose brain as well
memories are hard to keep but
yeah
just the knowledge that we've spent two
years together alone is also precious
[Music]
i can't believe that uh we have been
here for almost every day for so long
happy 2-year anniversary oh you're one
of those people who are here almost
every day
that's insane thank you so much
i appreciate the effort
even though you're a lurker
you still try to be here as much as
possible thank you so much
[Music]
also pinky thank you
happy 2 year quinoa bursary since the
beginning i've watched you grow so much
becoming more powerful with each day
kfp is truly a wonderful community
you've cultivated and even if i can't
comment much these days no i'm always
rooting for you
thank you
why can't you comment much because
you're watching the vlog
probably right
that's okay thank you for trying to keep
up and watching my streams
even after such a long time i'm glad to
know you're still here
down kitchen watching while working
thank you too
hiding you from my bus
yes hide me it's our little secret
thank you campy and everybody else as
well thank you soon
live and called on donkey shoe and
randall sans thank you soon skye thank
you 10 out of 12 let's go
flat people thanks for the red super
chat
confession time initially i didn't
recognize you as the incredibly
committed talented and entertaining
phoenix lady that you are
luckily i have now achieved kfp
enlightenment and can hopefully serve as
a helpful chimpkin during the third year
of your journey thank you only but for
alice
kind problem
english
compliment this is
well
i'm saying i i i'm assuming this person
is german speaking i was i was saying
once
once someone made an opinion about you
it's really really really really hard to
change that person's opinion
um
to even make that person consider
that they could be wrong with their
opinion
or that something has changed
so the fact alone that
you changed your opinion and i was able
to you know do that and you you did that
that's already quite impressive and i
appreciate that
and very important to me that some
people
give me a chance and you know
change their mind about me so
it means very much to me thank you
you're welcome to be here and you're
welcome to support me
in this third year of hollow life
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
thank you soon
[Music]
i was german i was saying something in
german
congratulations as a fan seeing you and
your content style content evolve has
been one incredibly fulfilling journey
so far i already can't wait to see what
adventures your our favorite cutest
shiniest meanings gets out to next
thank you
i
i'm not sure
what awaits us
in the coming year but certain things
are certain to me because i don't want
them to be
any later i i want to achieve certain
things and even even though it might
take time and it might get delayed so
don't get your hopes up guys i wouldn't
want to do certain things like a concert
kibaba only concert
at an actual venue
and it might only be one venue depending
on what possibilities i'm given but then
you guys have to travel yoroshiku
or watch the online stream whatever but
that's still so far so far far far far
far in the distance
i have yet to really hear anything back
concerning that topic so
yeah
i'm basically standing in the waiting
line
uh
[Music]
i will make it happen i hope so
ah
that would be amazing but it would also
make me really nervous if
if it's really just me you know
if people will show up
that's like
ah
you know third fest was incredible but
doesn't mean that all these people were
here for me obviously obviously not
so when it comes to kiwawa only concert
that's way way way way more concerning
especially because it's so difficult to
get
like
such a
such um
spread audience into one place
but you've done it before a little bit
for dokomi and i'm assuming that if it's
only concert a full concert
that more people would make the effort
i would hope so hi
you're here again
[Music]
no come here
i'll pick you up if you get close to my
feet again
i'm ready
i want something to cuddle come here
thank you guys
oh
okay she's coming back
she's coming
back once i stand up for my chair she's
gonna run away
she's trying to get me to chase her
[Music]
so careful
i tackled her
[Music]
i tackled
her she was
she was trying to escape
[Music]
she ran immediately the moment i got up
i tackled her and stopped her in her
tracks
[Music]
isn't that what you wanted
so now she's she's
in my
on my lap
[Music]
let's see where was i
oh
oh yeah bruno thank you
[Music]
still sending super chats what the hell
titan
what the hell
thank you
that's that's at the very end already
well well well
[Music]
oh god
yeah i'm not sure if
if tai chi has any money left for food
oh dear
no escape no no
no oh
[Music]
okay i'll let you go now bye bye bye bye
bye bye
[Music]
junior of londor these past two years
have been genuinely amazing a big thank
you for being the cute sweet passionate
intelligent talented phoenix beachwood
idol that you are you're always the
highlight of my day
i'm always here for you my oc and i hope
you know that i love you so much
i know i love you too thank you
ah
baby very sweet loyal canadian chicken
thank you for supporting me
from
the country of maple leaf
thank you
don't have
that many kfps were presenting me there
but
you're you're a big maple leaf chicken
thank you soon
thank you
[Music]
tastes like maple syrup this chicken
weird
the way i bathe
with um gravy you probably bathe in
maple syrup
[Music]
i'm canadian
hello canadian
hello canadian i'm kiara
[Music]
both cats are in the room waiting for me
to end the stream but i'm not gonna end
yet no no
no no
[Music]
nice one good one
i know very funny i love everyone
[Music]
that's my girl yeah high five
clap
[Music]
if your throat hurts thank you
but that's so awkward happy second
anniversary yeah thank you for being
such a hard working talented amazingly
genuine person thank you for watching
thank you
it was indeed
um some really good 12 hours of you guys
i really enjoyed it um
we do it
every month every week
to be honest but then it wouldn't be so
special anymore
then i couldn't call it a marathon
um but we'll definitely do it again yeah
maybe for 1.5 million but
that will take a long time
[Music]
we just reached 1.41 and that took like
an eternity
very slow
[Music]
next marathon 1.5 or
or 3 years anniversary or birthday
whichever comes first let's see
[Music]
ah
thank you though blue thanks for being
so considerate too
very sweet
very kind
thank you shin blue you're a sweetheart
[Music]
typical jrpg finale yeah we might
accidentally get a 12 hour stream when i
play
whatever pokemon riser
zeldzelda whatever
any of those games fire emblem fire and
play
those gonna be some long streams again
[Music]
yeah yeah cause the finale was 11 hours
i think was i pretty exhausted at the
end i feel like
i might have been very exhausted so
exhausted that i don't remember a single
thing
[Music]
yeah i'm excited for the new fire emblem
because like the previous one we played
it was my first entry to the series and
it got me hooked and i wanted to play
more but
you know
um a long game like that don't really
have time for that in my private time it
would have to be a streaming game and
you know so now we have something new
finally
[Music]
i hope it's gonna be good
three houses was really really great
[Music]
really really liked that one
oh i did not watch the yakuza 8 trailer
i just know about the announcements but
i didn't watch any trailers
oopsie
more touchy banana no [\h__\h] touchy banana
wait
that banana ended up being good i forgot
[Music]
was weird i think but then that's banana
was good right yeah yeah okay
sorry touchy banana
sorry
again something shut up that's a spoiler
don't say that
i mean to other people you know who
didn't play at the end
i don't know for some reason have a few
bad memories of him because he was weird
but
i guess he was fine
[Music]
for the red super chat i know i'm very
bad before it's especially especially
with english i'm very sorry for that
so keep it short and just say thanks for
the two years you're incredible because
you are
that's
the best medal ever i feel like you
could have said that in english and
without you i would be so lost thanks
for giving me a reason to keep existing
well i said
this the other day when i was reading
super chats i think
i appreciate it but
i shouldn't be the only reason the only
source of happiness in your life
yeah you need to find something else
anyone who feels like this
needs an extra source of happiness in
your life i mean
i'm really
really happy that people watch me so
much those people
who love me so much spend so much time
with me and watch all my streams and all
that
but it's not
healthy
if
like you know i'm the only source of
your happiness
because
what if that's taken away from you what
are you gonna do
[Music]
you can't just fall apart
just because of that like
if you can't function without me then
that's a problem
yeah and that's reality
it's for your own good really
anyone who feels like this towards me
it's for your own good i'm not saying to
leave me i want you to watch me as much
as possible all of you guys watch kiwawa
every day
um
but yeah you need to find a balance and
something
something to make you happy
[Music]
yeah it's true that's true in the end
it's just you know for the sake of your
your health
yeah
i'm trying to also find something else
as i said a trench is trying to find a
new hobby i was looking up um
places where i can
ride a horse
learn how to ride a horse from scratch
again
it's a bit difficult but
looking for something
trying to find something
some people only teach others apparently
when you have your own horse already
and then others are like mostly for
children and school groups and so on
need to look deeper maybe horse riding
is not the best option maybe i need to
explore some other options too because
horse riding
is quite exclusive
[Music]
that's geographers
i could buy a horse but then like i
don't know i don't want to buy a horse
but i don't know yet how committed i'll
be to it
[Music]
um
i look around a bit more
[Music]
and i know someone i have an
acquaintance who owns a horse and rides
really well but
um
she can't just teach me
because
actually you need like some kind of
license basically because if there's an
accident then you're [\h__\h]
and also she has no time but even if she
had time she couldn't really teach me
it's unfortunate because that would have
been like the best option
[Music]
oh well
uh continuing spanking duncan
for also read super chat ooh there's a
lot of red super chats coming up
congratulations on two years of
wonderfully entertaining streams i know
the katos
and i always look forward to our time
with kiwawa and we'll continue to ah
okay i read that wrong i know the katos
and i always look forward to our time of
quinoa and we'll continue doing so today
small cattle has been watching you with
me ah
cute
i love that you and yukito katos
watching kiwawa
i wonder if they like react to my voice
or if they
like by hearing me for such a long time
or if they're like whatever
i don't hear [\h__\h] unless it's my owner's
voice
or something in reality they do
really
what if i do this
[Music]
they react
did they look here
because my cats always react to that
big cat just look at the screen hello
wait wait i know what to do
this is for your cat
i'll go
i'll go here
i need
i need something
small
uh-huh
i have like a
cursor
or like a dot
dot png
i guess that works
i'm gonna be a laser pointer
okay
tell me if she sees it
meow
is she following this
wow
now
[Music]
is it working
spanking time
oh
cat nose print right on it really it
worked oh my god
probably needs to be down here for her
to reach it but what if it's up here oh
can't reach it
too
[Applause]
and cat
oh no my monitor
attack attack cat attack
and circle
what the heck is going i'm doing fan
service for a cat okay for a viewer's
cat
this is important
because my smoothie would react to this
movie would react but chunkers would not
i know that for a fact
i'm not
any cats in the chat yo what's up i'm
doing this for you
[Laughter]
okay at some point they lose interest
though
i hope i hope uh your cat enjoyed this
hi
[Music]
my screen was attacked oh my god really
oh my god big success
my cats are going nuts for this really
they did
[Music]
oh yeah cat's eating good today but
honestly i mean there's definitely
videos like that on youtube
definitely on like apps on on ipads and
[\h__\h]
but sometimes like
even when it's not as clear as this my
cat will still focus on something on the
screen when it's like a relatively
simple
layout where most things are
relatively still but one one small thing
that's easy to focus on moves around she
will like look at it
like also i think um when i was watching
some sims 4
uh playthroughs i think she liked
focusing on that [\h__\h] because she
like sims 4 and not much is going on on
the screen but you see the mouse moving
around and it's pretty easy for the cat
to focus on that
so she liked watching those hmm
i got the cat audience nailed down here
i know what they want i know what they
want
you know exactly what they want to see
this is the kind of fan service that i
like
uh
anyway i'll get back
back to the unimportant things just
kidding
[Music]
oh cats smashing the like button and the
tv screens
gaining subs from cats all over the
world
number one reach over
biggest audience in my youtube stats
cats
next one will be catnip and new swords
your swimsuits you're just asking for
that for yourself huh aren't ya
you're using that as an excuse now
because of the cat liking it when
reality you want it too
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see what you're doing yeah can't fool
me
it was worth a try
a nice new outfit what
what do you mean
new outfit
[Music]
you new here
you're near here
i was rushed today was
decent
[Music]
was fine
gta was more fun
we'll play gta again next week
[Music]
ah the orange dots out of it ah
anyway thanks frankenheim
skydiving for the pinky
of 11
i love tantrum i'm gonna stay to the end
oh my god
incredible skye thank you for staying
for the uh for from the beginning to the
end noise good job
almost there
uh it says it's like a 10 hours now here
my super chats
some guy thank you for the random chat
flawsy william if this isn't the correct
german translation of happy anniversary
my family will be so irritated they're
german and i use school to translate no
i think with like
um
important phrases like that especially
if they're short
you normally
you can't go wrong
yeah that actually was 100 correct so
don't worry about it all good
thank you
thank you thank you
anniversary
there is not
many things in my life
besides whole life
that
like i celebrate an anniversary of
honestly like nothing besides like
birthdays
[Music]
i don't think there's anything else
so it's nice to have something
[Music]
yeah i think that's normal um
no i have like
a relationship
or you're married
you know
or if you
i don't know any kind of job i guess but
yeah anyway
it hurts
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you some guy
also interesting your family is german
but you you never learned german huh you
have to um subscribe to my german
channel
to learn some german there go
go go how the [\h__\h] did you not do it yet
if you didn't do it yet i'm sure you did
it already right right right right
um
right
some guy are you in the chat
[Music]
it would be
something that you could make your
parents very very proud with if you
someday show up and speak some decent
conversational german with them
they'll be like
holy [\h__\h]
after all
you might really be my son
i am so proud of you
[Music]
you never spoke german to us like this
before
you might just really be my son
i accept you now
it's pretty harsh i don't know i know
how harsh your family is but if you in
some way need to make your family proud
of you then this would maybe be a good
idea
this would be a way to start
that project
anyways it's probably it's hitting too
deep at this point
uh anyway oh it's at one seven six
dancing for the rest of the chat click
[Music]
[Applause]
by
[Music]
happy second and a very sweet mama yay
thank you for being such an inspiring
lovely and kind idol for all the press
and the future amazing songs wonderful
amazing wonderful gaming adventures
breathtaking cat elkis and concerts a
little
there's chicken emote there a little
humor rhyme chicken rhyme
little
chick
rhyme
little bird rhyme
is that supposed to mean something like
a replace a word
i don't get that one
[Music]
bird brain rhyme that's supposed to be a
rhyme where's the rhyme
oh it's coming now oh
it's following after that sorry sorry
sorry
[Laughter]
time flies when you are having fun all
thanks to kiwawa oh number one working
tirelessly for kfp to smile tensioning
wrapping chihuahua freestyle yeah
streaming and entertaining all day long
always giving us a new burger song
wawa is amazing delightful cute a true
empress her rain absolute
oh
cheese oh hi tuckers even chocolates
came to hear that because that was
amazing
[Music]
wow that was on fire
sick
bars
[Music]
damn all the bars in my city are closing
down because that was just
you dropped them all
oh my god
thank you i liked that one
i felt the the passion and the soul and
the rhythm and everything
[Music]
thank you so much
mwah you got talent
could almost join my rap uh contest
[Music]
bearded phantom thank you shooting van
von nevudan kitchen brandon duncation
maxi king duncan random guide
skye
sending the last 12 out of 12 but this
is just the 11th hour sky
you kind of did something wrong there i
was thinking that since the beginning
yeah
you sensed the 12th one at the 11th hour
something went wrong there
some hole in your logic
the start of the 12th hour well i mean
no
it should be at the end of the 12 hour
ah you sent a thirteen in the end okay
and says i will be the 12 hours
endurance stream survivor hashtag will
cast a yoke thank you i believe in your
survival
yes
i believe
[Music]
well
you probably
could even survive a 24 hour stream
could you could you ah
would you do it for me skye
surely show me would you maybe not maybe
that's crazy without sleeping 24 hours
[Music]
only an insane chicken would do that for
me
without sleep challenge accepted oh dear
but i didn't even accept the challenge
yet
i could do it really of course really
i wouldn't yeah that's fine that's
totally fine that's totally
understandable
i wouldn't
um
i would not stay awake for 24 hours for
dom tendul
no
so
i wouldn't really do that for anyone
anymore
um
i don't think so
[Music]
so you guys love me more than
anyone i've ever loved
you guys love me more than anyone i've
ever loved what the [\h__\h]
for piccola no
no i wouldn't do it for background
no
[Music]
i won't do it for anyone
maybe for my cats
maybe for my cats if my cats were in
like the emergency station in the
hospital
um
at the at like the the brink of losing
your life
for 24 hours i would do i would stay
awake for them
[Music]
i would do it for them
cats
[Music]
i don't wanna think about that [\h__\h] that
no
[Music]
this got dark okay continuing
ellie smith thanks for the pinkie love
you can i here's another year after
phoenix yeah with kiwawa every year is
the year of the phoenix
thank you ali smith i hope
this year of the phoenix will bring you
much more luck
and success and happiness thank you very
much
hd
[Music]
dino lord jacob thank you for the right
super chat
happy second anniversary kiana you are
amazing and bring everyone so much joy
with your streams hope your hard work
brings you more of your dreams come true
thank you for getting me through my days
and as i have a job now i won't be able
to watch much more now
what the [\h__\h]
oh
you have to watch my vlogs then
please
please you can't just disappear no no
no no at least bring a replacement
someone else
you have to get someone else into the
rabbit hole instead okay do you have any
friends who don't have a job
then they have time go go
tell them about kiwawa if you have to go
somewhere then your duty is to bring me
a replacement
it's that simple
i think i it makes sense
[Music]
tdp thank you for the pinky first pink
super ever happy two year anniversary
thank you for all the joy and
inspiration you have brought to us all
you worked so hard and it doesn't go
unnoticed here's another year of the
phoenix yeah thank you
[Music]
thank you soon for
acknowledging and recognizing my efforts
feels nice man
thank you so much
another year of the phoenix
yay
three years four years five years how
long can we go huh
endurance
not just for 12 hours but also for 12
years question mark
i'll do my best
thank you for being part of it yeah
right thank you lori perots
[Music]
oh
anniversary congratulations thank you
for always being by our side after our
debut i'm happy just being with you i
wish you continued happiness in the
future kia is the best
no you how do i say no you
in korean
thank you for being so sweet dave you've
also been around for a while thank you
for staying with kiwawa
i hope you're enjoying
all my content
even if there might be some
problems to understand no you oh do you
or do you do you do you want to listen
to my new song
do you
[Music]
do you yes
yes
thank you
all right i'll play it now
[Music]
just kidding
but we'll play that it's cute
hi
oh she sits
she sat
you actually got me
don't you don't you know does that sound
like kpop well maybe not in your world
it doesn't my world this is kpop okay
[Music]
oh my god they never end
okay this is like the last hour of super
chats but there's like a lot of boom
i think i'm gonna end it here six five
three
six five free at mh ziggy
[Music]
i'm gonna end it here i think
yeah
my throat hurts
but
last hour yeah i think i think i can
turn on super chats again after
this stream
it's not too bad
[Music]
this is not to be clear this is not my
new song
[Music]
i guess i'm gonna cook now
ah i don't wanna i don't feel like
cooking man maybe i'll just make pizza
and cook tomorrow
i don't feel like
[Music]
maybe tomorrow
yeah this is the problem after a long
stream i'm just not failing i'll think
about it i'll take a little break and
then maybe i'll i've i get my
motivation back
maybe if dom tando uploaded a new
nuzlocke video
maybe
he did
okay
maybe i'll cook
nice
[Music]
content
it sucks though because he's not a
streamer so he uploads only like 30
minute episodes per day
[Music]
but he does it like twice a day
motivated no not so much but i'll try to
motivate myself
[Music]
yeah the old-school way yeah i mean
sometimes he streams but i don't i never
really catch them also i
i skipped a lot
anyway
yeah bite-sized content
i i honestly sometimes i feel like you
know that's maybe the more comfortable
way
because you can take
more breaks in between don't have to
talk so much in in like a long
amount of time
uh
but yeah i'm a streamer
i
am a streamer
but for a while i was considering that
to be maybe the way to go for my german
channel
honestly it might really be the way to
go because if i
let's say i do like 30 minutes of
content per
three days maybe
that
could be subtitled
but it's quite the commitment
like instead of clips
doing
subtitle 30 minute videos but um
[Music]
who
i talk a lot you know
but then i mean sometime from german to
english so that you guys can also watch
it the video itself would be in german
but it would be subtle to english that's
the idea
rather than streaming
because subtitling a whole like five
hour stream
but subtitling like little bites of
content
30 minutes per every three days seems
relatively reasonable
[Music]
and then you guys could watch it too
with understanding it could even use it
for practice if the subtitles are
accurate then you know it's like anime
it's like anime but it just lets you
look anime because i'm anime
but it's not japanese english it's
german to english
damn anime has changed man
[Music]
woo
but i don't know if it's like worth it
because you know i have to pay the
person who subtitles it and
i feel like you know obviously like it
would totally be deserved to get some
payment for that
a decent amount
but doing it so often
30 minutes every three days
it might get pretty costly
why not translate yourself because
that's a [\h__\h] and a work i hate
subtitling i've like tried it before in
like video editing but i hate subtitling
so much especially 30 minutes is like oh
like the softwares i've used so far are
not really like made ideally for
subtitling
[Music]
maybe i should ask like how
how the
whole life
subtitlers that we have
in-house do it
[Music]
because they do they don't do it the way
i tried to do it before they do it like
properly how subtitles work the most
efficiently
honestly if
if community uh subs would still be a
thing i could just stream and lend hope
for you guys some some of you guys to
take up the job and then do it you know
just because you want to
that would be easy
but for whatever reason youtube got rid
of the
function of having community
submitted subtitles
that used to be a thing
already ancient history yeah already
[Music]
yeah they removed it long time ago
already
[Music]
i think like videos that already had it
already
like already submitted
subtitles they're still there but you
can't do like new ones
it were until they planned to move their
shows onto youtube what they would have
relied on fans subtitles
to be submitted
that was their plan that's not a good
plan
even though i'm i'm saying i want to use
that plan but
well i think in general for like a big
anime company it's not uh not the ideal
plan
[Music]
i think i think it would be a good idea
if it if there's like a
if i get a decent pricing
i'll think about it
[Music]
so i still don't 100 know where to go
with that channel
we'll test out the waters how about that
and now i will go
i will go now
and it's saturday tomorrow
tomorrow
music video at 5 00 pm kiwawa time which
is in 18 hours or so 18 hours 24 minutes
18 hours 24 minutes
sorry junkers she's like behind me sorry
that i have to scream you know i have to
hype up the people
[Music]
i think i'm gonna put up the reservation
soon
before i go to sleep
and then
originally my plan was to stream on the
german channel tomorrow but since i
still have the clip ready i might just
upload the clip
[Music]
then no stream
maybe i stream maybe i stream tomorrow
[Music]
i was thinking even if i do a stream it
will be a few hours after the
music video
yeah
but for now i'll just uh put up the
reservation
i don't have a thumbnail yet
but i want to choose a thumbnail
that doesn't give away too much
just the one from the teaser maybe the
ending scene
yeah i think i might go for that
[Music]
with some pizza
no i
i would eat the pizza while watching
something but
i'm so excited finally [\h__\h] finally
oh
finally
[Music]
it's been over a [\h__\h] year
ah
oh for a [\h__\h] year
um it's about time
okay
and in germany selfies and guys my
throat hurt
bye-bye love you
anticipate to be my favorite
i think
it's very different from like hinotoli
and heart challenger
low-key similar to sparks
but uh fevernight also very different
it's it's hard for me to say
it's my favorite because they're all
very different
but it's definitely up there and it
might be my favorite it's hard to tell
cancer no no okay i'm going bye-bye
[Music]
i
you
[Music]
i'll be doing
do
[Music]
you