[Music]
Kogoma wa Kogomao
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone, Komakoma Komasaa,
15 years old, Times Tago from 2015  Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
What was it like trying to do it? I wonder if it's changed. It's
just right, ah, it's
just right. It's not loud anymore, right? It's just
right. This time it feels good. This time, it's too low.
There are some sesame oils out there who are saying things like, "This is
just right."
It's a majority vote, so I'll leave it at that.So
today is the
first collaboration live broadcast on YouTube.Hey
everyone, there
have been a lot of people waiting for a few days now.  I
thought it wasn't quite yet,
but I'm so happy to see so many good kids.This
time, I've invited three guests.However, I
previously recruited V Goma for Goma XX and Tokoro.  These are the
three people who contributed to a project called VTuber Friends.In the
first stream, I introduced Haneru and Hiara,
and in the second stream, I introduced Cheri-chan,
so I said, ``I haven't seen that yet.''
For those of you who are interested,
please check it out! It's
been
almost two months since Sagomasa became a vtuber.  The months have flown by so fast! I
had my first press conference on October 25th, and the next day I
streamed it live for the first time in 2D, and that Saturday I
appeared at a virtual Shibuya event.  and 3D  I'm going to
spread the word and sing Love Machine, and
in November, I'll be invited to appear at the virtual idol festival L3
6. Recently, I've been dancing,
posting videos, and
starting a membership.
Seriously, a lot of things have happened to me.I'm
such a new vtuber V piece,
but from now on, I
want to do many more things with Neko, and I
want to ask my friends and seniors about various things.
That's why I
wanted to have a normal conversation
with you, but I'm hoping we can talk a lot today and get to know each other,
so I'd like to invite these three people right away.
Is everyone okay? Well then, I
'm calling you Kihara-chan, Chiri-chan
Kucho-
chan Yay, it's real everyone. I'm so
happy, so real. Good
evening, I can hear Kogomakochin's voice.
Kogomakogoma
Now, I
'd like to start by asking everyone to introduce themselves.
Well, first of all, I'd like to introduce myself, Kira-chan. Yes,
thank you very much. I'm from
Hololive English.
By the way, I'll be broadcasting in English, basically in English.
However, my native language is German, and I
also speak Japanese.Actually, I've been a fan of Kanae Haplo for about 14 years, and I've
loved her for a long time.Thank you for inviting me.Thank
you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy that you're a Salon Pro. Yay,
no, no, thank you again.
Okay, then next time. I'm
Haneru. I'm Inaba from 7 Sync. I'm Haneru. I call
myself a vtuber1 idol. I
call myself an otaku female idol otaku.
Oh, hello! I've always
loved Hello! Pro, too, and that's the debut of that guy. Excuse
me, is that Goto-san okay? Hey, Goma-chan's Goto-chan.  I've
been rooting for Mr. Goto from Kaugu-chan since the day he made his debut. Yeah, that's
amazing, but he's still
15 years old, so he might not understand,
but I wonder what that Goto-san is.
Yes, when I went to that live show, I
was watching it from the 10th row or less from quite a while ago.Yes, I may
not know it yet,
but I was watching it from the 9th row from the front even on the last day.  the
last day of the day
I don't know, but that's right. When will it be the last day?
I don't know when it will be the last day. I don't know, but when will the last day be?
That
means that something is going on. Yes, yes,
yes, yes, I heard the last red diary. Yes, I
heard it right in front of the red diary.
Something amazing happened.  This is what I'm talking about
Well, I'm happy Neho-chan, but hello
hello. I'm so happy. That's it. That's it. Chiri-san.
Hello, my name is Chiri Katari from DoTribe. The fact that I was invited here means that
of course Cheri also said hello and said, ``I love that amazing person.
''  [Music]
Thank you for all the trouble.
So this turned into a fan meeting.
Or maybe it's a
fan meeting. Yes, I know
Kia and Mochi-chan too.
Even among all the Vtubers, I'm especially
happy about Hello Tani. It's a
strange feeling. I'm
so happy, Hello Pro.
Three of my favorite people are here, but there's
still a long way to go. I'm also a little
excited.  I have a project waiting for me, so I
'm going to talk about it a lot.Well
then, I'd like to go to the project corner right away.It's
called Vtuber.
Secrets Oh yeah, but this project is a
newcomer to the vtubers, V Koma, who
is both a friend and a seasoned senior, is
participating, so
we're going to ask him to tell us about the secrets and secrets of how to live as a vtuber.  Yeah,
yeah, I'll tell you. I'll tell you anything. Are you okay? Don't
worry about your studies. Are you okay? Are you
okay? Well then, I
'd like to get to the first question right away.
First of all, the first thing is how I started being a vtuber.I see,
I see.Goma
must have been that 15-year-old.V
Goma has been sucked into my smartphone since 2001, and
for some reason,
suddenly became a vtuber.  That's what it feels like.
But yeah, yeah, I think there must be some other reason for Kiara-chan,
Haneru-chan, and Kachiri-chan, and I
want to know why. I see.
That kind of feeling is okay.Yes,
yes, then let's start with Mr. Hanel.Okay,
well, I'm just a self-centered rabbit,
but the world of sake is extremely high quality, and it's extremely
high quality.To my grandmother, I
came to this world because I wanted to go to high school.  The story is that I want to
earn a lot of money and go to high school as a grandma,
but in reality, yes.  I was
scouted by that Vtuber, and he
asked me what I wanted to do.I
love that third-rate Pom Pom Plink,
and as I said earlier, I
really love female idols.I've always
been one.  I said I'd
join if I could perform with that girl's idol, Pompompurin-kun, and my
current agency said they'd let me,
so I joined here.I guess
that's what's on that shoulder.It
looks like bread.  Are
they like Pom Pom-san
? This is actually
a dog that I have. It's a
cute dog, right? It's a poodle. That's right, it's a
poodle. That's right. It
's not bread. Goma-chan is always bread.
As I said, this is a poodle
. I don't know if it's a poodle or not,
but I thought it was a delicious-looking poodle, and it was so
big that I could eat it, but it was actually...
Well, it's coming true right now. I
'm really happy that it's coming true.
Thank you very much. Oh, I see. I wonder if
everyone at Sesame Oil is listening too. Ah,
listen, listen, listen, don't listen, I'm happy. I
can't see you saying that.  Wow, it's amazing that it came true.
Oh, my dream came true. Oh, it's so
good. I wonder where all the old settings went.
[Laughs] It's
true, it's true.
Yeah, but it might be fun to go back to that setting someday
. Yeah, maybe I'll go back.
Let's use it when it's convenient, when it's convenient
. Okay, okay, next time, Chiri-
san. Chiri-san.  At that
time, I entered that game in 2017 or 2018,
but around that time, a game called PUBG was
popular, and I was playing PU, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, 10 hits.  It
's a game that
Chieri plays, and I can say that I got really hooked on it for the first time.When I was playing an erotic
game,
maybe Chieri
got into a mood that she wasn't very good at, and oh, she
got carried away.  When I was thinking that I wanted to do a live
broadcast, I came across a stream from a senior at my agency,
and I
thought maybe if Chiri is so cute, I could do it too, so I
got into that mood and started doing it.That's great.  I see, you
love games.
That's right. What have you been playing lately?
Lately, I've
been playing Dead by Daylight. I've been playing Dead by Daylight.  That
's right.
I really tried that challenge, but it's
difficult. That one is difficult, difficult, difficult. Next
time. If you have a chance, please try it together. I'm
glad you did it. I'm so happy.
Is Goma-chan okay with horror games?
Horror games that don't seem like horror games
are fine. I see.
[Music]
Let's play it. I'm so
happy. Thank you.
Thank you. Finally, Ejaa, Kia-san,
please tell us how you got started. Yes, I used to
watch a lot of Hololive.  Around 2020, I had been
watching it quite a bit since the beginning of 2020, and I was watching it as a fan,
but at that time I was staying in Japan for a little while
on a one-year test visa,
but since I came to Japan.  I guess it's
safe to say that since the coronavirus started, I wasn't
able to do anything I wanted to do.I
couldn't work at that time,
so instead I was watching Vtubers' streams all the time,
and about half a year later, I
started playing Hololive English for the first time.
There was an audition, and
up until that point, I had no intention of becoming a vtuber,
but since there was an audition, I
thought it would be a good fit for the skills I had been honing, so to be honest, I decided to do something else.
Since then, I
've been doing it since September 2020. What's more, the way
Kia speaks, her
pronunciation is like Deathbythe,
and it's amazing.  I
wonder if I'm good at Japanese.
I've been speaking Japanese a lot lately.  I'm
not very good at English,
but I'm only 15 years old, so I'm still 15 years old.  I could
n't read Coffee, so I called her Kealgia.
Lugia, are you okay? I can't help it. I'll tell you
everything in English.
Wow, that's amazing, even if I go abroad with this.
If you teach me, I'll
probably be able to improve my English skills and be able to have a conversation with the store staff.If that
doesn't work, I'll come with you.When A-
chan comes, I'll talk to Kira-chan about everything.  It's
okay to receive it, just leave it to me.I'll
protect you very much.Wow, that's amazing.It's
kind of reassuring.The trigger was also amazing.Everyone
had their own
reasons.
So,
let's move on to the next topic.Okay, next
is here.What is the current VTuber industry like?
Ah, what is the current VTuber industry like?Well,
what is it like now?Do you
know the history of VTubers?  For someone like me who doesn't have
a lot of experience, I would like to
ask you to tell me about how you became a vtuber.
I really wanted to know something about it.Yes,
yes, it's history.Yes,
it's history, so who does it start from?
Yes, who does it start from?Who does it start from?This is definitely the best.
If you're cool, please give it a try.In the early
days, there were a lot of vtubers who focused on videos,
but on the other hand, now they mainly stream,
which is a big difference.
Personally, I think the good thing about live streaming is that it's
normal, yeah, feel
free to do it for a long time,
and that you can interact with fans.
There may be an image these days of people doing a lot of live streaming. Yes, there are a lot of them. In the past, there were a lot of people who
watched videos. I guess it's hard to say what kind of videos are interesting.
Wow, that's difficult.  Is
n't it better to be a Vtuber and the Emperor
? Oh, it
seems kind of difficult. I wonder if V Sesame can do it. It's okay. It's
okay. I can
do it. It's okay. Yeah, it's kind of like the beginning of the point of view. It
's like the four of us.  There are
five people who were active from the beginning, especially when vtubers were just starting out, and they're called emperors.  There's a
girl called Cyber Girl Shiro-chan, and
Nesonoko is also one of the four heavenly kings.
Yeah, the amazing people are already the beginnings of the Emperor. That's
right. They're
amazing seniors, aren't they? They're called vtubers.
But what are they?  It seems like there are five of us,
but that's what people say. It's
not just four people. It's an eternal mystery. It's an eternal mystery. We
're here. For some reason, it's always been that way. Well, it's just three of us.  There
was also a possibility of becoming one of the Four Heavenly Kings.Is that
true?There must have
been five of them.Yes, I
see.Heh,
I also have a point.
As far as I can tell, I
think the vtuber industry originally started in Japan, but
even before Hololive English was
created, there were a few people who spoke English here and there.  There
were vtubers, but ever
since Hololive English was created, a
huge community has formed around the world,
and it has become common for
vtubers to be invited as guests at anime events overseas.
So,
I often appear on the show,
and yes, it has already become popular overseas.
Yes, yes, it is true, but it is true
that the international vtuber.  The
comment section is international, that
's true. It's an
image of a lot of people from all over the world getting really excited about something. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, wawa world,
wawa
wawa.
That
's what the word "virtual YouTuber" means.
Yeah, that's true.  After all,
when we and others had just debuted, we
were just YouTubers.As the
term goes, we were virtual YouTubers.  My main
activity was to be active, but even now I
'm more of a virtual talent than a virtual YouTuber.It's
amazing.I've appeared on TV, I've
appeared in various media, and
yes, when I think about it, I'm already a virtual
YouTuber.
More and more people are now referring to them as virtual talents,
yes, that's true,
because they sing on TV and whatnot.  I'm
not saying that kind of comment, but I've
been thinking about how great it is to do narrations lately, and live shows
too. Like Bugoma-chan, there are live shows like that, too. Yes,
that's true.  Wow, it
makes me feel like I've learned some history.That being said, let's move on to the next one.I'd
like to go to the third place.
Chie Chie V's wisdom for overcoming the rough waves of the rough VTU
VTU bar meeting I would like to tell
everyone who was running through the rough waves in the first round that they
have to be careful in their daily activities and that they
must take care of this.  So, I would like you to give Goma a little bit of that.Yes, I
see.Yes, I see that it is very important.Well,
let's start with Chiri-san.Well, the
distribution activities are quite on the spot.  Things
change, but the things that are
important to me are the most important thing right now.It
's mental.It's about managing your mental health.It's about managing your mental health.It's like
dealing with a lot of different people,
hearing people's voices, and so on.So,
mental care is really important.
That's what I was thinking,
but I'm a [ __ ], so even if I say something small, I'll
get sick easily.Oh, I feel like I said something unnecessary.Wow, I
wish I had said it this way.
That's because I get sick, and also because my
fans look at me more than I do, and they
become sensitive to even the smallest things, so I
always manage my mental well-being so that I don't feel sluggish, and I'm
full of energy.  I wish I could see her.I do
n't know if she's done yet.Are
there any things or items that could help Eki-chan's mental recovery?I'd like to
do a lot of shopping, and I'd like to
stream something that would be good for her.  There's something
about watching other people's streams that makes me realize that
everyone is doing their best, and I
feel like I can go back to my basics.Or
rather, I guess it's important to never forget my basics.I see,
but that's kind of amazing.  I
feel like I
get it, but
when I think about things like I'm having a hard time or feeling tired, I end up wanting to
buy a lot of things, like buying some clothes, etc.  I
know, I know, I might end up doing whatever I want, but when I see other
people singing and doing things like that, I
feel like they're trying their best.Maybe it's the same thing.The sight of someone
trying so hard is amazing, it gives me power.
It's going to be, it's going to be, it's going to be, everyone's going to be
like that. I'm sure it's going to be like that. Yeah, I'm
happy to be with you. I'm happy.
So, next, let's go to Chiara-san. Let's take a look.
Well, I'm basically basic.  There
are a lot of game streams, but I
'm careful to create not only games, but also all kinds of content that I think will be interesting.For
example, I'll be comparing sweets from all over the world,
cooking streams, and whenever I go to Japan.
Basically, I can't do a lot of off-collaborations because
I'm in Austria, and I
go on a trip and stream on the spot.For
example, if I stream from the beach in Morib, it's different
from Morib.
The beach is amazing.Actually, I'm going to the beach next month next month.  I
hope to be able to do something unique and unique in my own way.There are so many
different things that I enjoy most about traveling.It feels
like I'm taking on a challenge and it's amazing.I
was really surprised.Maldives  I
really want to go to the
Maldives.The beaches of the Maldives are really beautiful.I
guess they are really beautiful.There
are a lot of Hamon couples, but there are
some honeymoon couples among them.  A
couple of mosquitoes who thought it was a crab were
cute and thought they could catch a lot of cute mosquitoes.
Yeah, it does seem like there are a lot of people out there who are hams,
but there's a
friend of mine who is a streamer among them, so they
might have thought we were a couple,
but yeah, that's not true.  That's why I
think it's so much fun and there are so many different ways to stream it.Finally, I
'd like to ask Mr. Neeru.I
might be on a slightly different route,
but I don't think I'm too tied down to being a vtuber.
I see
Yes, I think the good thing about becoming a VTuber is that you
can do more things because you're a VTuber.I
see.It's better not to do this
because you're a VTuber.I've thought a lot that if you do this because you're a VTuber, it won't work.
On the other hand, if you
become a vtuber, you'll be able to do
more things that you can't do anymore, and your activities will
become narrower.I see.
Even though the history is quite bad, it's only been 7 years, or
about 7 or 8 years, so I
think it's still in a period of growth, so I
think it will continue to change more and more in the future.  Yeah, now that I
think about it, I don't think it's okay to be a VTuber
so you have to adhere to certain settings.For
example,
when I debuted, I didn't really
post pictures of my food or anything like that.  There are people who
say things like, ``It's not good,'' or it's like, ``Real photos aren't good.'' Also, people say that it's not good because it shows the real thing, not the virtual one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Nowadays, I'm posting quite a lot of photos, and I'm
holding real events,
but I'm also thinking about the difference between virtual and real.
Vtubers from both sides have also appeared,
so
I think it would be better if things just keep evolving
and keep evolving.  It seems like
V has evolved a lot, but that
's true. That's right, V Goma-chan.
In fact, from our point of view, the legendary
idol Gonaki
became a Vtuber, which was unthinkable in the past.
Thank you for saying that because I didn't have it.It's amazing, but I don't like it because it's not possible.Thank you for saying that.With the
existence of Sumatako V Goma-chan,
I think that Vtubers are one step above the rest of the world.  I'm thinking, ah, yeah,
no, I have to try hard. Let's have
fun. Let's have a lot of fun.
Yes, it's beautiful, it's beautiful. Well
then, I'd like to move on to the next theme.
There are a lot of themes today, so next time.
Yes, this is the theme of the Shijiri Senpai
Experience Group.I would like to hear about the stories of the seniors who
became Vtubers and
did things like this, but
in the first place,
there is such a thing as Shiri.  What do you think?
There are some things you can learn even if you just sit back and relax.
What do you think? Mr. Kia, oh, I
've probably done a lot of things that I've done wrong.
I have done this many times to spread the word about new clothes,
but when I spread books, it
's quite a big event.
Sometimes, when there were
so many people coming, the
YouTube chat
became so heavy that the streaming stopped, and
so did my computer, and it never got better, so I couldn't do that part,
so it was very difficult.
That's when I got really sick, and I
cried a lot.That
's why I'm not very good at computers.I end up doing a lot of things,
but
then I found a lot of good stuff, and my
YouTube chats didn't become that heavy.  I
found an app like this, and now I
have to fix the mistakes I made,
but it's normal to make mistakes.  It
was tough because I wasn't active, but
since then, I haven't failed in trying to spread new wins,
so I've been successful.Everything was great.What I've
learned is because I'm a good person.  It feels like they're being put to good use,
right? Well, I guess that's
true, but maybe that's actually a good thing in a way.
Yeah, yeah, it's
better not to do it.
Well, now that I think about it, I can think of it like that. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
wondering if this is going to turn into a song.
Of course, it's okay, I'm glad it's an orchestra.
Next time, please, Mr. Cheeri.  Yes,
Cheeri is also many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many.
Then, around March, my poop, throat, and nose often
go bad, but
that coincided with my appearance as a guest at a convention, and I heard a
ridiculous voice that made me
think it was the teacher Chieri.  And
since it's a character like Cheri,
Capi would have to do something like this, but I'm also worried about the people who are
like Capi, who doesn't look like her at all anymore.
Well, that's what I did,
but if you break your throat once, you
won't be able to do any work if you're a Vtuber or something,
so you're probably an idol.  It's
frustrating that I can't do that.
Yes, Sesame also has hay fever, so it's really bad. Ah, I have hay fever, so
I feel like I
have to take medicine during the hay fever season.  I'm
sure things are progressing and I'll be hearing about the medicine soon, so I'm sure. Did you
get hay fever? Has the medicine
changed? It's not changed, it's weird. It's
not changed, it's progressing.
It seems like it's progressing in terms of amount.  Yeah,
yeah, I'm scared that I'll have to rely on medical help from now on,
so that's right.I'm scared that it's
coming in three or two months, no, no, no, it's
spring in my dreams, so oh, I'm scared, I'm scared.I
sleep in bed with a runny nose every day.  especially
Well, that's scary
. I haven't taken any precautions.
So in the end, Neru-san,
please. I
don't really think it's that bad, but it's
really amazing. Is it true? Haru, I'm so cute.
However,
if I may say so, Goma-chan also receives fan art from
me, and I
often receive illustrations
for her as well.  I
often like and retweet them,
but one day,
someone was drawing a naughty illustration of me, and I
thought it would be okay if I liked it, even though I can't retweet it.  I didn't care what I wanted, so I
hit the like button, and
then a little while later, I was
called to the office, and I was so scared.
Thinking  I was
in a meeting room where the president was sitting, and I asked him what it was, and
he said, ``What is this?''
I clicked the like button on my smartphone.I was
shown an illustration of it, and I thought, ``I like this.''  I
shouldn't have pushed her, right? She'd get really angry, and the
president of the edemaa would say, ``
Well, yeah, there are some of my fans who
don't want to see those naughty Cannel illustrations,'' after all.
yes  I
was told in my heart that I shouldn't say thank you and don't give a like because if I gave a nice comment, it
might hurt my fans.I see.  I see. I kind
of liked it too. That's right. Thank you for everything you wrote. It
was really nice to hear what you just said. It's
scary to be called out like that. It makes me tremble
. Oh, I'm
retweeting a naughty illustration on Hololive.  There are many people who do
Well, I don't know. It
seems that Lime doesn't get angry or get angry. I
see.
Well, I don't do it. It's a little
difficult,
but in
the end, you can do whatever you want. Maybe it's different depending on the place.  I
guess I pressed it at first, but then I got hit again and I pressed this one too.I pressed this one too and it showed me everything, and it wasn't the first time I did it, so no color came out.It's true that my account account was hacked.  hand
But now, I'll do that next time.
Hacking. It
might be a good thing even if I get hacked. Well, it's not me. It
was interesting and interesting. Well,
there's more, so I'd like to go to this one. The
next one is this one. I'm
continuing to be a vtuber.  I'm glad I did
that, but today I learned that
being a vtuber is more difficult than I thought, and
that it's better to do things that way.
However, I believe that the reason why you continue to be a vtuber is
because something good will happen to you all.So, I
wish I could hear stories that make you feel glad that you continued to do so.Hello, Chieri-san.  Well, that's
all I can say, but I guess that
means I've met a lot of people, like friends who are vtubers,
but I've also met some fans, and I've
said good morning.  I've
already had so many people say
good morning to me, and when I said good night, they
said good night and said I can't sleep, and they
took care of me.I thought it was a great thing, and it's true that I
don't play games very well.  Even
though I'm complaining, please look at me like that.
But I think it's love. So I'm glad that I can continue to
receive such love from so many people and feel happy.
It's true  I
appreciate it every day. Thank you. I'm sure
love is really powerful, and it's a good thing. I
think so too, so I'm happy. That's the
same thing with the people who watch Sesame Bra. I
understand.
Well, Kira-san,
there are a lot of things, but for example, I
think you were talking about your fans just now,
but I think I was able to create a strong bond with my fans.
Every time I perform at an event, we have a one-on-one
meet and greet, and
I appear on the screen in one room,
but I see the fan in person
right in front of me.  You can have a conversation right in front of me, right in front of me. Yeah, that's
amazing. At that time, people tell me all sorts of
stories about themselves,
like how their lives have changed because of Chiara.  more healthy thanks to you  I feel like I've
become a new person, I've made a lot of new friends,
and I'm tired of my old job,
so I quit my job
and found a better job.It's amazing.Some people
say that they were influenced by me, but I
can't believe it.  I can't
say it, but it's because I've been told so much that it
makes me feel that way.Also, there
were a few times when Kia appeared in front of people like that even before she went on a live show.  At that time, there were probably 0 people.
When I appeared in front of a single audience, I felt really
depressed, thinking that no one would see me,
but when I went to Hololive, I was amazed to be
able to dance in front of thousands of people in a place like Makuhari Mess.
Being able to dance has really
changed my life, and I'm
really moved by the fact that so many people have come to see my performance,
and
being able to support my family is also great.
No, no, no, no, there are certainly more. There are so many.
There are so many. I'm so glad I
did that. I'm really glad I did that. Of all the
things I think about, the one thing I think in common is the feeling that I have to share
with all of my fans.  It's kind of like a
connection or something like that.When I
say it in a big way, it
feels like love.Yes, it really feels like that.Then, Haru-san,
please.Yes,
I have a lot of them, too.
First of all, it's a very strange and gratifying thing to be able to do something that I love and
then find that my fans are happy because I did that job.
As I said earlier, I
said that I love you, Pompurin, and Pompurin
kept saying that he liked me, and then we got to
do a lot of work together, and
even though my dreams came true.  Fans too  They're
happy with me, right?
For example, I really
like mahjong, but when I said that I've always loved mahjong,
it turned into a job, and
I was happy to have that job.  I also
hope that my fans will be happy. There are so
many things that I want to do, like my favorite sweets, my favorite meat, my favorite throat lozenges, and so on.  The
things I love become my work,
and I think it's really great that all of my fans are happy with it.Well, that's what it's
all about.Love
is love.  Really, it's love,
no, it's true, I still have it, but the other one is me.Unlike that
V Goma-chan or Chiara-
chan, I've really been amazing since my school days.  I
was kind of like a nerd who studied all the time, but I didn't
really talk to people very
often, and I wasn't very good at showing up.But when I
started becoming a vtuber,  The
fact that they were a little quiet, quiet, or did nothing but study
turns into a character,
and there are people who empathize with them.In everyday
life, it's amazing how gorgeous people are.  I've
always had the feeling that people who are cute and have a good butt are treated like this,
but after becoming a vtuber,
the otaku character has
become one with the character, and people can sympathize with them.  And
that
really changed my life somehow.
Yeah, I see. It really feels like there's
a lot of demand for people in today's world.  It
's such a joy to be able to naturally utilize what you're good at. That's right. Through vtubers, I realized that no matter what kind of person you are, everyone has their own
good points and people can empathize with you. I see.
Good things happen like this, I
thought. Well, it's almost time, but the next
theme is the last one. Yes, it's the last one. Well, it
's
early, so let's move on to the next theme.
Masue, I don't think V is better than me next time,
senpai. I'd like some advice on what I should do as a Vtuber in the future, so please.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes, I'll
stream karaoke.  I want you to
do karaoke, I want you to do it.I want you to
do it.I
want to hear it.I want to see it.Do you all like singing?I
love Dora's songs, so let's all
sing together next time.  I
want to do it, I want to do it, I sing it, it's Yume Yume, I
want to do it too.I thought it would be fun if everyone could
do it.I want to have a karaoke stream where these four people sing only songs from idols like Haplo.
So let's try it out now,
if I say, oh, what's the future of Japan? I'll
try to do it.
That's fine. Let's
do it. It might be the future of Japan.
Okay, then please lie down, okay? Can I go? Yes,
those sesame oils who are listening, please do that too.
32 The future of Japan is
wai, but karaoke streaming looks fun, isn't it
? It's awesome.  It might be
nice if we could do something to prevent that delay.
Thank you Neki-san. I
'm looking forward to the separate distribution, which might be good. Is there anything else I can do?
Please dance with me. Is this also a Hello! Project
tie-in? I don't have a Hello!Polo tie-in song, but Hello!
If we could dance and sing together, I might as well just die. No, I do
n't care if we dance to a Kiara-chan song or something.  I'm Kamoneya
Sakae. I
want to do it. Let's do it in 3D. I
want to do it.
[Applause]
[Music]
No, it's amazing. It looks like it's going to be exciting.
Thank you for making me realize what the future holds.It's a
good thing, so that's my
condolences to the vtuber.Thank you very much.How
was it?
That's amazing.I think I learned a lot more today.
At the beginning, you said that you love Hello!Pro,
so it was really fun to be able to collaborate with you like this.I'm so
happy.Thank
you very much again.Thank
you very much.That
's it.  here
Well, I
'd like to make an announcement, but to all of you,
if you have something to announce, I'd like you to do it first.What do you think
? It's
okay.It's okay, please go ahead and do it.V
Goma-chan.  I'm so curious about the announcement of ``Ai
? Okay? Well, let's go.
'' The announcement of ``Itadakimasue'' can be found here.On
Sunday, February 4, 2024, in Tokyo.
Goto Maki Live & Talk Tour will be held at Otemachi Mitsui Hall
Live &
Talk 2024 Macaron Wagon, which is not a tour.
Hey, if that company is open every day and there's
no vacancy, I'd like you to come, so I
'd ask you to take paid time now and let the company know that you're prepared to take that day off.  Hey
Three cars will appear on the Virtual Festival 2024 on Saturday, February 25th, 2024. It's
like this.
Look carefully, Haneru-chan is here. Yo
Homa-chan, that's right. I'm here too.
Together, together, together.  Okay, let's do some live
together and make it exciting. Let's do our best together. Let's
do our best. No, I'm really looking forward to it. That's
why I'd like to thank everyone again today.
Thank you very much for coming,
thank you very much, thank you very much.
Thanks to all of you, my
understanding of vtubers has
deepened, and I decided to try again.
Is it okay if I ask each of you for your impressions? Well then, first of all, Chiara,
please. Yes, I've been around 14 years now.
If I told you that I would be able to do a collaboration like this, I don't think you would have believed me.
But yeah, I'm basically broadcasting for English,
and I've
been explaining a lot of things about
Mr.  That's amazing. Thank you for
saying that. I'm glad. I
think you probably understand, so I'll continue to
explain things properly and spread the word about V-koma. I'm so
happy.
Thank you very much for today. It was fun.
What should I do? Haneru-chan,
please. Thank you very much for inviting me today.
Thank you very much for inviting me today. Thank you very much for inviting me today. I've
been saying Maki Goto is the idol I've always respected ever since my debut.  I was
talking to a fan about how I wanted to do a collaboration with Maki-san.
Even when that 38-year-old Go started YouTube, I was
making a fuss about it for quite a while. Yeah, yeah, yeah, really.
I love you and have respected you for a long time,
but I thought it was so strange and honorable that someone I respected so much became V-Goma-chan, and I was the one teaching them this kind of thing about vtubers.  I've
loved you so much for so long, it's been great,
thank you so much. Thank you for coming. Thank you very much. I'm so
happy that you're already here.
Maki-san, it's wonderful that you're already here, so please
continue to exist like this for the rest of your life.
Thank you very much, yes.  Keep going and
keep going
[Music]
Last
but not least, Mr. Chiri, when I first
called out to him, I
asked my manager over and over again if it was okay.  I
spent an hour talking with Haneru-chan and Kia-chan, and I thought it was amazing.In the
announcement just now, there was a photo of Donteneko.
At that moment, reality hit me all at once,
and I was
really, really excited.But I learned a lot myself, and
thank you for the wonderful opportunity.I'm
grateful for the bond that Goma-chan made.Thank
you very much.  Thank you very much for your
time. Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you
very much. Thank you very much to everyone at Sesame Oil. It's a good day for me to
do a live broadcast this year.  but
In closing, I would like to say hello to all of you and
to everyone at Sesame Oil for the new year. So,
thank you again.
And
bye bye bye bye, bye, Nemo. Good luck.
Bye
bye bye, bye.
[Music]
By
A