[Music]
so
good
morning
ohayo gozaimasu
asano kuji hondas it is 9 30 am
over here
i'm actually already pretty awake
because i woke up
half an hour ago for the
for the premiere of my remakes of hino30
of one of the three remixes yeah this
was announced off stream so i didn't
even get to hype you guys up yet
i know
the astrophysics remix yeah yeah yeah
yeah
it's like a synthwave 8-bit
kind of thing
uh
really really dope i really really
really really really really love that
one
um
and i i i think uh it it shows
it um it
it shows uh hinatori in a very different
style and this is basically what i'm
going for
uh for this particular project aka
hino21
[Music]
itself pretty so cute i really missed
mamaloni's art
um i wanted to see
more maloney art for quite some time
[Music]
um
very pretty
this is a project that uh i was really
really really excited about uh because
especially because um it's it's uh
well
the i i chose these
creators i chose these producers because
and they all have a very individual
style to them
and that is very very specific and
special to them so
yeah so astrophysics has this like synth
wave style which i absolutely love
synthwave 80s 8-bit stuff like that
um lone alpha is like more
fluffy
and and
um
cute
and
it's a bit difficult to describe that
one
but but it's like a more girly um
and chill version of hinotorii and
spoiler alert and then there will be a
redshift and i think a lot of you guys
have heard redshift's work before for
example for uh leina's remix
of
king for example
um
and redshift is really really really
talented too
they do like some really
badass remixes as well
and yeah so look forward to that
one please they will be coming out
throughout the day the first one came
out half an hour ago and the restaurant
will be scattered the
the stream reservations are up the one
from redshift had to be uh changed
because something had to be changed in
the video last minute uh but yeah all
the reservations are up so please don't
miss them they're so good
i know
[Music]
i thought it was really funny though
that when the astrophysics remix started
when the countdown started you guys were
like oh this is already so cool
i mean i guess it didn't really look
like a countdown because there was no
timer until the very last 10 seconds and
it was a two minute timer you guys were
so bamboozled
i chose a fitting uh countdown i looked
for the countdowns that they have
available they have like 10 countdowns
or so
and i chose the one that is kind of
suitable for the style and you guys got
something what the hell
[Laughter]
account
is
you can choose them yeah you can and you
can also choose how how long you want it
to be but if you don't choose anything
then it will be like default and
yeah so that's what probably most people
still do they don't take a close look at
the countdowns
yeah yeah there are quite a few uh count
different contents the concert
ah this one should be
live because they're performing also in
the in a concert hall
um
yes
they will be performing in a tokyo dome
shitty hall
tokidome city hall which is um
uh
we talked about this before uh
it's a
show it's a
inside
life
uh hall with a capacity of around 3 000
people by standing but i don't think
they're gonna let in three thousand
people because of you know the obvious
reason
unless something has
changed since guatemala senpai's concert
and what am i saying
no it's not tokyo dome it's not tokyo
dome it's tokyo dome city hall it's like
a different live house live
hall that is uh
uh
probably close to it that's probably why
they call it tokyo dome
um
yeah yeah three thousand but maybe
they'll just put in i don't know two
thousand four thousand five hundred
ratio
uh i don't know because uh at vata miss
empire's concert uh a little while ago
um
they uh they also didn't uh put in all
the people
if they wanted to fill up tokyo dome
which is by the way not three thousand
so uh but uh it is uh fifty five
thousand that's a whole
1.0
uh 55 000 capacity i think they they
could definitely
fill it up if they wanted to if they
tried
yes yes yes but uh
they chose a smaller
smaller
[Music]
place to perform in uh venue um
regulations and stuff
um
apparently in tokyo they're doing a
baseball right now so
that's why it wasn't available
of course we totally could have done it
in tokyo dome but they're doing baseball
okay it's occupied
try again next time
let me open the chat on the side
uh i think that will probably be
30 minutes of free
footage again
uh
i think maybe on nico nico
if
if anything or is there a youtube stream
as well
i did not look that up uh
but as as far as i can
say from experience
uh oh yeah i need to open it up i didn't
open it up yet i need to change the low
light latency yeah yeah um
yeah
there is on youtube okay so guys for the
broken you can watch 30 minutes with us
uh on youtube does someone have the link
manager sean do you have the link
i think manager sound may be sleeping
maybe
um
uh uh there it is there it is it's right
on my uh
subscription box
all right
uh 30 minutes free
there we go
i will pin that comment
uh
yeah you guys should watch it
go watch it also the rules as per usual
screenshots uh are okay you can upload
screenshots to social media and you can
also write your thoughts and everything
uh and on social media um they have a
hashtag which is in japanese but it's
holy right with san casey first live
and
uh recording or mirroring the stream or
uploading it illegally is
okay now let me try to open
the stream on my side also look look at
my pen lights
dakuma made them
island this is a really confusing title
for me
fun fun because in japanese it ends up
being the same fun fun
fun fun
fun fun fun
hands a bit small
you're small
your hands are small
i think they gotta go a little bit more
here yes yes
[Music]
okay watch live
god i'm good with that one
yes
[Music]
oh god i think we had this last time how
did i fix it
oh god i i opened it in a different
browser didn't i
did i
it's so laggy for me
we had that before why how did i fix it
fixed it
oh no do i have to log in on
edge
it's helpful
it's not
uh shut up i don't want you to use you
as my main browser shut up
okay
oh
i'm logged in already thank you nice
okay so we can stop it here
and let's open
on on edge
wait it's super pixely what's going on
okay now now i have it on low latency
mode chi and moto de
okay seems fine now why does it
keep on lagging on chrome for me but not
on edge
so
japan bros who couldn't go to the actual
concert for the chilling at home
game
[Music]
[Laughter]
yo japanese bros who couldn't go to the
actual concert i'm so sorry for you it's
actually a normal working day
in japan and you know how japanese
people can't take their uh they can't
take a vacation day that easily
yes
[Music]
um
yeah
oh
they could say they have a c thing they
probably want proof though
[Applause]
[Music]
think about the millions
lucio cute
oh my god penguins was so cute
i forgot what i was talking about
i'm lagging you should try a different
browser i had the same problem
yeah i love hearing
cute
[Music]
oh
oh my god
i'm sorry lucia gum england
hi
no no
no
they're just uh
telling you guys all the rules of the
of the concert
also rules for the people are actually
there like don't don't disturb anyone
with your pen lights
and if you if someone cannot follow the
rules you might get kicked out or the
concert might even be stopped that's why
i was like no
no no
no
okay
[Music]
me
i will be translating the mc parts for
you guys or at least i'll try
if they don't speak too fast
hi
yes
oh my god it's happening
virtually live it's happening happy
mario
eight minutes
[Music]
high
da yeah even though i only slept like i
don't know five and a half hours
i am so hyped up
hey
[Music]
this this part is so long isn't it
oh where's the sexy bean
montage
i forgot all the licks
[Music]
oh this song is just not fair it's it's
too good
[Music]
are they already trending number one on
twitter
worldwide apparently
oh my god 70 000 tweets let's go
let's go
30 minutes live for free here
i'm tweeting something
i only listened to it once turns out i
only listened to it once so i don't
really remember
it
what are you listening to right now
listen to the link above in the pinned
comments this is 30 minutes free concert
and afterwards you got to get a ticket
or you should get the ticket right now
if you plan on getting a ticket anyway
and then watch it together with us
[Laughter]
but the instrumental is nice
hmm
gotta enjoy the instrumental
how do i get the ticket go to the
description of this stream
it's literally all there you can get a
ticket on spawn or you can get the
ticket on nico nico if you go to spawn
you can change the language to english
if it's japanese
uh quickly go go go buy buy buy it now
but you need a credit card if you're
going to get it on spawn i think that's
the only way to pay for it on spawn
for nico nico i think you can also use
other means
go quick be quick now be quick three
minutes left go go go go
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay i i i got some
okay i i guess managing son just uh sent
me pictures because managing son is
there
the pictures obviously
oh
oh my god that's so cool
ina
it looks like
it looks like they are
let me look at this closer are they uh
keeping seats in between
open
i think
uh
actually maybe not on it no yes they are
except
except when i guess when people are like
coming together then they don't
need to do it kekko
seki
yeah when you're in grips you don't have
to leave a seat open i suppose
where are the no soggies why are you
guys not putting rabbit ears on your
head
[Music]
are you guys not putting bunny ears on
put on bunny ears
hey let's go
it's starting it's starting it's
starting
[Music]
i'm so excited i'm too excited i'm too
excited
oh sponsored by kfp
uh
uh dr peppa
document what's your favorite drink
she's asking
earl grey tea for lucia
oh
everybody says uruguay which means is
there a sponsorship
say sponsorship
or channel
they're like all right what did we come
here for
oh party game
ah
they're going to dive into the game or
something
what happened to the earl grey
what happened with the earl grey
sponsorship
laughs
oh
okay they wanna uh they wanna do a
cheers on their concert
they're having like a little before
party i guess
eating food drinking stuff
oh
hello
who this
new phone who it
is oh did the board came talk to them
oh oh
oh and they're like oh we're getting
we're getting sucked in
who's his voice
is the first song
hey
[Music]
oh
you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
be
[Music]
foreign
oh
the people
the audience
they're so calm i think they have to
i think they have to become let's
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
i will not chill the f out this is a
[\h__\h] closet let's go
this is how you're supposed to behave
for the concert
get your [\h__\h] arms up here
[Laughter]
[Music]
i can't hear her i just see her meowing
at me okay now i can maybe hear oh now
she's she's left she left
[Laughter]
this is like okay you good
my boss arms fell off let's go
oh
the trees
oh man
the trees look funny in the back
where are the mizuki's where are the
mizugi's bikini swimsuits le please
please
where
oh
no who is this
did they
hire
a voice actor for this
i don't mean by
listen listen
okay yeah they just said
they got thrown into a different world
she's like what is this fantasy oh it's
kind of weird that we say it because
we're whole life fantasy
oh
she's like don't you notice the
important thing
there's a ferry and there's an ocean
oh let's sing together
what song
something related to that
hot limit
oh
isn't that sora senpai's new song
[Applause]
oh wait it's a cover
oh my god that's why it sounds familiar
oh my god i i
i
beach stage
don't fall into the water girls
[Music]
who
i
[Music]
looks great
what just happened
yeah
yeah yeah wave at me i'm here i'm here
are suffocating in water let's go
wait what's the word for that
drowning in water
[Laughter]
hi
[Applause]
cute
[Music]
oh my god
oh nice pose
she's like how was that pickle
she's saying i got i'm getting really
hot right now
oh
she says she got a an interesting
feeling from the audience when she was
singing
oh
she wants you guys to show your
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
hey
hi
um
[Music]
there
let's go
[Music]
she's so cute
ahoy
oh
[Music]
please
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
is she like really far from the island
no no slow ship
okay
[Music]
m
mata
[Music]
ah
where is
[Music]
let's go
oh my god
oh
there's like there i feel it there must
be an audience you guys should sing too
it's like they're trying to
get out of this world by uh
you know
by
getting
supported by the audience i guess
is the theory
oh okay
trio
ah
they're singing uh
that beautiful song
cute
hanayamata
hi
oh it's just so cute
[Music]
i hi
hi hi
oh that dude was vibing
oh
[Music]
so what so what
this is fantasy whole life fantasy
um
i'm gonna jump into that water right now
oh man
[Music]
they're even like going from the ground
into the sky so the
cherry blossoms
are coming out of the sand
yeah
whole life fantasy this is what you get
hey eh
wow magic
[Laughter]
[Music]
the song is so pretty i love it
so
hi
[Music]
it's a catchy song right
try not to rip your arms out too much
oh they got hustling
my arms
adorable
[Music]
booty
booty touch
they hired someone
but i like the voice it's like an anime
voice typical
no no no no
yeah
you guys are so sure
i am a hundred percent we are fans i am
if it's not
then
you shall go into dogesa for claiming
this is ayami senpai and saying you're
sure because you're a fan
the joke
the japanese fans think you're wrong
okay anyway
she's like we're in the wrong in the
different dimension but we're still
watching you guys
and we need your support and your cheers
in order to get out of here
yay yay
what should we do exactly
okay i will explain it to you girls
let's go into the forest girls
okay let's do it
all the forest
it's been a long time
all right yeah you're an elf in elf
oh i will check i will greet her parents
they won't be here
oh
free free part is over now
imagination gang
come come come in now
let's go
over there
it will only get better from here on
bye bye free gang hello imagination gang
wow
russia do you understand
i understand
interesting
this means that
oh we have to perform in three different
spots of this
of this island in order to get out of
here
there are different rules depending on
the place
oh they're gonna throw dice and there's
from one to six there's uh the numbers
on the dice
oh they have to clear the forest first
this is the doki doki no mori
okay
okay okay okay um
[Laughter]
oh
okay so the the quest is to
uh get everyone into the same pose
and they have to do it until they do get
the same pose
okay everyone do a sexy pose and it must
be the same
are they allowed to discuss it like that
though
she's like we should do we should do
martin's pose okay okay
okay
they're closing their eyes
or not
eh
ah
annoying
no evidence doing something else which
is also money's pose
yeah it's
they don't all have the same pose
they gotta do it again
um well yeah i guess that's sexy
that's maybe sexier hmm
oh yeah
oh yeah right mine did a different one
too
oh
me i'm so busy to screech out go on
twitter they'll be posting screenshots
there
i'm too busy
i sort of
sorry imagination gang but you gotta go
by my words and the screenshots on
twitter
okay they're giving me another try the
next topic is
oh
fairy poses
i am a fairy is the topic
what's the favorite pose how do you do a
fairy pose
okay
pose
yeah i would have done something like
that too with the wings with the hands
to the side
yeah i think just russia is doing
something different
oh only lucia is doing something else
no no no no
no
let's see
get out of here
okay three times the charm yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
they're probably going to do one where
they reach out with one hand
she says there's only like what it says
there's only one
pose that you could could do
which which one
oh
what what what are they gonna do
hand of the chest hand reaching out yeah
that's they do that a lot
yes some some of them got it some of
them got the memo
russia is doing something else marine is
doing something else
lucia is losing her balance
[Music]
get your [\h__\h] together girls you need to
get out of this world come back into the
streaming world
wow oh
that's very cool pose for their
essential
sanchez is hard to see anyway because
her hands are always covered up
you're making us jealous go on twitter
i'm sure there's a lot of screenshots if
you go to the hashtag then i think a lot
of people will be posting um
pictures on the hashtag
it's currently number one trending so
just go on the number one trending
uh hashtag and go through uh the newest
ones or the pictures
yes
hold on you're on camera man dude there
you go go on go on their twitters
okay so they didn't get it the third
time either
dulcinendal
next topic
mata
okay
[Music]
i think they're going to use noida
senpai's previous pose as a reference
why is the only noise doing something
else
ah she's chasing she changed she she
wasn't done yet
she wasn't done yet it was one whole
movement
sorry i'm just stating facts here
okay apparently that one went through
oh wait no one more topic baseball
okay you gotta get this one right
i think there is one
pose
the one where you wait
for
for the ball come on
yeah cute yeah cute yeah cute
this is the the fifth one so i guess
fifth time is the charm
lucia
foreign
is like throwing the ball and the other
ones are trying to hit it with their
bats and then for the eyes doing
something completely different
what is she doing ah catching it ah
oh come on i want one so obvious it's
gonna be the one who who hits it with
the bat the batter
[Music]
nick okay sixth time is the show
shannon's really throwing it
oh ghost
oh
i guess like your hands in the front
uh
oh
[Music]
bucket
no bunny
the six six times they gotta get it
right now
okay ready
well some feet are different but the
hands are generally yeah
ma
[Laughter]
why why is one leg up how is that ghosty
[Music]
they're like this is our bond yeah
oh connection
success
oh
to celebrate the success they're gonna
sing
oh
piccolo gonna sing
revolution
[Music]
oh what other stones are that supposed
to be no sakes
is
oh
cat
[Music]
oh that little dance
yeah that hand twirling cute
[Music]
hi
oh
oh my god
okay
[Music]
is
hey
me
[Music]
i
cut
next up lucia
is gonna throw the dice
one and no five
five go go go go
do 50 squats together
all five
eh oh no
no yeah yeah yeah
one person fifty or one person ten
i think one person ten
[Music]
come on lucia she first was like uh no
problem he's easy and now she falls down
oh someone else has to do more than
okay
uh seven eight eight
she's not doing it properly
eh she's gonna go deeper
[Music]
18 19 20. okay but that was not deep
enough
[Laughter]
gonna make me proud right
oh piccolo
next
that's that's not a squat well i'm not
free i did
two guys okay ten ten squats please put
pick on that
share some cute bunny squats
[Music]
hey
if it's push-ups i would understand but
squats are fairly easy
oh noel's gonna save this group right
ninja ichi they're like did she really
even do one
[Laughter]
twenty two oh
25 26 27
28 29 oh
[Laughter]
seven
eight
nine
ten
oh wait you gotta do ten more oh my god
oh oh my god those are some erotic booty
squats
but at least she's doing it properly
compared to the others
oh she got sexy boying
bling bling squats
noel saves the day
they reached 50.
damn i gotta buy it now yeah
go get those nolan squads
[Laughter]
oh russia is gonna sing
the forest suits here
morning
cute
song is called koi
oh
oh they're doing purple and and green
pen lights oh
i want to see the audience a bit more
they showed them way more with vitamins
concert but i guess it's because
the
the stages are so immersive
they don't want to show the audience too
much
but i want to see them more
yeah they're kind of watching a movie
butterflies
ah the ar stage thing they don't have it
oh
all right i don't have that invisible
screen ah
[Music]
maybe maybe at the end who knows
maybe they at the end they they are able
to
get out of the isekai
and they roll the screen onto the middle
of the stage
maybe maybe spoiler spoiler
kawaii
very cute calm song that fits lucia
you
do
[Music]
she's like thank you for watching
next stop foreign
is it going to be smiling go
oh no god saves the girls
what song was that
let's go for this and
god save the girls oh life june is it a
vocaloid song
livestream is a vocaloid producer
ah
hi
oh
she got out of the forest what happened
with the forest
wow
big
the big void i love it
it looks so pretty
[Music]
pretty yo her legs
ashika no jin sayori nagai her legs are
longer than my lifetime
oh we're back we're back
which really means something i'm eternal
hey
[Music]
cute
i really love this singing voice
ah
honestly i have to say um
out of the third gen
or even out of whole
has one of life
favorite most favorite designs
he's
i told her that
i told her that even though she recently
only wears her casual outfit i told her
that i love her
main outfit so much
the whole design i love it it's so good
um
[Music]
hi
hi hi hi hi
i
[Music]
good job cameraman i i i i i i i
[Laughter]
nice
noel quietly was like i love you
tayden
i want someone to say that to me
they cleared the forest
fairy froze the dice and gets a six
what
[Laughter]
okay the rule is to get
many many uh uh praisings and and and
compliments
oh
no one says she has the perfect song for
this occasion
[Music]
yay
oh she says she's doing her best singing
and dancing so she wants to get lots of
phrases now
[Music]
okay
cute
[Music]
oh
jiggle jiggle jiggly
[Music]
papa
cute
yeah
okay
eat me some
okay okay
both kind of things
i thought it was the only one
[Music]
oh
cute
actually i've never heard this song
before i didn't
know this song i'm sorry
meow meow meow
bone
ah
no i'm cute
no beautiful
no sweet
no pretty
she wants more praises
more compliments
wow
[Music]
yay twitter has got a weird trending
subtitle and what is it
what is it
is it five widows got teleported into a
is that guy
okay different area oh
oh they're in the water
oh
here apparently they do it a little bit
differently oh
oh
okay they're gonna be interacting with
the audience with me
hmm
hijacking this concert
twitter what the hell are you doing
applause
[Music]
reyna must be confused as well
oh it's my concert now
the hell
oh they're calling out for the second
floor now
first there's a third floor
oh
yay comment down
oh where did the fairy go
oh
oh the fairy can't be here so she's just
talking to them from the
from the sky
sorry i'm just doing japanese
oh she's gonna check if everyone can do
the the right color
oh
i forgot the name of the color in
english
[Laughter]
baby blue sky blue light blue
lucia color next up
so i needed to fix my chat because uh it
kind of stopped
pickle blue
okay fixed
free
color
red orange orange
wow it looks like the
like the whole venue is on fire
no
[Music]
[Laughter]
a sexy red
oh someone touched her butt oh
oh
they're gonna ask the audience question
and now everyone shows their pen lights
according to the answers
uh
men are blue girls are red what there's
so many girls here
really
she's like oh i'm surprised but i'm so
happy that there's so many girls of
course i'm happy that there's men too
oh
pointed out that piccolo was forgetting
something oh was she forgetting her
introduction
that's like i'm getting help
[Music]
oh
apple or pear
um i would actually go for a pear
[Music]
oh
wow so many pears
nice i'm surprised there's not so many
apples actually
now she's scared honey honjin
i know penguin loves apple dough
she says it's not good to fight
both are good
oh they're gonna talk about the stuff
that was in the collab cafe
if you guys don't know they had a
collaboration uh time limited cafe
that is themed after this concert i
think it's probably still going on
somewhere in tokyo
where they have like
food and drinks that are themed after
the concert and after the girls
oh oh oh piccolo is gonna do her thing
she's apologizing already
oh she wants to do the wave oh good good
job good idea yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh
go down
wait where's my mouse
[Music]
and up and down
okay okay i'm ready
okay from dead side to dead side
where am i dough where am i
[Music]
oh i'm back back back back
oh wait you guys are too fast you girls
are too fast wait wait wait
maybe there's a lag
nice wave
nice with
[Laughter]
i wanna do that too
you see i'm gonna read some comments
foreign
no i just said that because the comments
are being read the people in the real
audience are just leaning back and
chilling
oh oh this just says everyone put on
their the colors of their oc
oh
it's calling out someone who's not
energetic
i want to see the show again
no
no they're gonna do a pose together
with the audience a pose that you can do
with your upper
body health as well
hold your money balls
oh
the girls got it right oh in the
audience there's some different ones
i was thinking of that too uh
hi
bunny ears
and bunny
she's asking if you guys saw this stream
from northern senpai answering 100
questions
oh who would you like to become if you
could change bodies with someone for one
day
oh who does the audience think piccolo
would like to become
oh they're guessing it most of them are
guessing marin
oh
wait so is it correct
it wasn't correct
they're gonna do
a chair together
yay
oh
apparently they succeeded
they succeeded
oh we're going to the different area
again i like this area though they're
not going to sing in this area
i like this area it's very mystical
magical
where are we going
what
okay okay okay
energetic hill
exciting hill
it's pretty
okay
they're gonna sing
[Music]
oh wait oh wait foreign
vibing hell yeah
rapping
[Music]
whoa
okay
[Music]
oh
i like this song it's so high energy
it still has this japanese vibe to it
[Laughter]
pagoda
[Music]
you
mama
[Music]
hey
something's rising
and it's not my arms this time
[Laughter]
it's so cute it's like her love it's
perfect
[Music]
wow i like this place
i like this stage maybe the most
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey
body part is so addicting
[Music]
wonderful
let's sing together let's sing together
and manny's like i need a break
are you not gonna sing with me
[Music]
uh
maddie get up
oh they're gonna sing together a song
that they always wanted to sing together
i know that that's really old
[Music]
oh
yes she sings the male party
maybe me and kelly should sing this
[Music]
i love her male part voice
gosh marin
honey
[Music]
you
oh
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
[Music]
ah
mm-hmm
[Music]
da
oh
right
[Music]
hmm
i shogaim
[Music]
oh my god it's so scary what if the what
if that huge rock drops on them
okay okay we're good
it just exploded
the rock the floating huge rock above
them just exploded
so i see
my instincts
yeah before it drops on them i guess
it's better to just explode above them
[Music]
oh i look i like those harmonies
super smash brothers stage
but i was like oh you two had a
connection huh after all and they're
like yeah we had it
all along
oh whoa wow
oh
so when
no where is bakery
no
she's like
at the end we should sing all together
it's five but it's not over yet right
where's my pekko down brain
where is my peculiar brain
peculiar
right no she already got her solo are
you telling me she's not going to sing
it
okay this is beautiful but still i'm mad
um
why
this is good too
are they did they stand up
they stood up i think
the audience
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
hey
um
i
laughs
[Music]
let's
go hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
she says oh we completed our missions it
sounds like
oh they're going back to the real world
oh
the fairy seems a little bit unsure if
it's gonna work out or not so russia was
like are you good
oy
it's gonna fail isn't it
it's a guy forever
hey
raid zero
let's go
hey
[Laughter]
i like these new protagonists
oh it's a sad farewell with the fairy
don't be sad it's gonna be fine
you'll go back to the real world and
forget everything that happened here
what we're even gonna forget about you
yes
this is a special time
oh no lonely no i don't want to forget
they apparently really really bonded
with the fairy in this time
fairy says if you sing you'll feel me in
your heart oh
teddy
there's no time
so you have to go back
oh
time to go back
[Laughter]
you're getting sucked in again
oh yeah
okay
was it all in for their head
for their imagination
for the imagination
wait jonga jungkook
instead of jengar
maybe if they look at the image on the
screen right next to them maybe they
remember
foreign
[Music]
hey
oh
hold it
um
[Music]
hi
music
[Music]
not at all
i don't know the lyrics of the second
part
[Music]
they really dug out an old classic uh
vocaloid song there
[Music]
i love this song
and it really fits the end of the
concert
has the right uh atmosphere music
music hey
hey
[Music]
music
foreign
[Music]
keep on grooving
keep on growing
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
no need for angkor
oh this is the credit song
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
what is this
i like it
this isn't original
pekka pickle
yeah yeah
it's a song about all kinds of meat
oh my god this is cute
oh
that means here
[Applause]
box
go
hi
oh
drink uh order coming up by bakura
oh are they still hungry
i like this part oh
oh kokosuki
[Applause]
a
[Music]
coin
i love this generation
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks for the meal
what a song
but wait uncle
i'm going to die uncle
no eh can i get an encoder it says finn
um
they don't even give us a chance i think
hi smoovie how did you know the concert
is over
yeah yum yum
hi
[Music]
what's that
meow
it's apparently really over
oh
it's really over right yeah it's over
what
[Music]
okay okay here i i need to get back into
the whole live
member uh uh uh point of view and not
the fan point of view because i'm
um
i'm very much looking at this from a fan
point of view
[Laughter]
ah see i was really really really really
happy that uh virgin
is having a concert so i'm i'm happy
that it happened
yes yes yes
[Laughter]
you know
i will sing it give me a moment to
prepare
to celebrate i will sing picoram brain
[Music]
pick i definitely have like the
remix maybe this one this one
gotta go from my audio stuff
yeah yeah this is it this is it
okay
no no no no okay okay so
i'll raise this a little bit more get
the lyrics the lyrics uh
guys i need you to do some uncle uh
cheering called
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't see my chat uh
moving where's my uncle
uncle
uncle yes
when my when my child moves again i will
i will do my thing
okay i'll say it on obvious i said an
obvious i'm good
okay
please listen
from my senpai
i am doing an encore because they didn't
do one
to make all of us happy and satisfied
please listen pick around our brain i
haven't sang this one in a while yeah
bye
[Music]
is
yes
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
um
i
[Music]
time
[Applause]
if you get no anchor you do it yourself
[Music]
ah
thank you thank you thank you
i
[Music]
please listen
to
my new
is this is not planned
[Music]
has not been to do the concert but since
we're all excited and hyped up right now
he know 30.
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
me
tell me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
is
uh
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
i've been trying
is
[Music]
could you tell me please
tell me i can hear it clearly tell me
[Music]
i promise i will
find you
[Music]
hey
i should have put on these glasses
earlier
it's very fitting
thank you thank you again
sorry it's a little bit uh
and i just felt like getting an encore
felt a little bit short so what is some
uncle thank you for listening
um i will
celebrate these um remixes together uh
tomorrow in its own stream so look
forward to that there will be another
uncle another remix coming out in
six hours from now
you can see it as an encore i guess
if i were to say my
my uh
my feelings about my feedback about this
concert well i think they definitely
tried something new by
um implementing this whole
fantasy theme and rather than having it
all be only on like a basic stage they
really put a lot of work into the 3d
stages and each each um place had like a
theme like and everything looked so
magical and stuff yep
no
yeah i like the stages especially um the
last one on the hill or or even even the
simple ones where fudaya was suddenly in
the void sky even dad it looked magical
also the forest was very fitting to
lucia senpai i think
um
and you know the song choices i'm gonna
be honest uh i felt like maybe
some some songs were missing there
but still like there were other songs
that i was really happy about like suki
kirai and and mr music for example uh
[Music]
is just a song that always
always is so freaking exciting
yeah
i love it
yeah smile and go
got it
i thought they would get a bit a bit
more a few more solos because they
didn't really sing uh
a couple songs yeah i i listened to
smiling go just before the stream to
prepare for it
like
so i think there must be a reason for
this
maybe
hmm
maybe they thought
because people already listened to the
original songs they want to try
and saying something else
that is more unexpected
yeah ahoy and neuters original as well
but
hmm
[Music]
seeing all the originals here right now
i don't know how to sing smile and go
yet but i'll try to prepare it for the
next karaoke
as well yo
well well well but okay i mean there are
still some songs that i was really
excited about so that's okay
eh
what oh oh the fairy was voiced by you
sasahara
there we go where are all the super
confident imf fans that were like i'm
sure this is i am a senpai i'm a fan of
her i'm 100 sure this is 100 i am a
senpai where are these people get out
here now
get out there and explain yourself are
you really so sure about your oshie
oh
my god
i know it i know it's not her it didn't
sound like her it sounded like like some
i think i heard that voice before in an
anime though so it must be a
professional uh say you must be a
professional voice actor for animes
because you suck sahara let me look it
up
whoa japanese voice actress
who's affiliated with i'm enterprise oh
she's been in
let me see
she's been in dakashikashi oh
uh
what else is there
um
it's couldn't john i didn't watch that
so i don't really know it oh she's been
in
wait
what do i know dr stone
hmm
i don't know many of these
ah
um
i really liked how they did a lot of
cute choreographies for the concert and
they definitely practiced a lot to put
that together i also like the the mini
games in between the mc parts because
that's honestly okay i'm going to say
something really positive here that's
something that i thought
was maybe a little bit lacking in other
concerts where the mcs
felt a little bit stale but for for this
concert um it felt much more
like exciting and and like they were
really having fun and was more original
um
the little games they did the challenges
in order to get out of the
uh second or different dimension
so whoever thought of all of these games
good job good job
i like the theme and they had they had a
whole story throughout the concert so it
was indeed someone said it in the chat
it was indeed kind of like watching a
movie
um mixed like i guess like a musical
almost a movie with some songs in
between so whether that's good or not
it's like i think individual choice but
uh it's it's different and
i guess yeah you you they wanted to have
it be an experience like a movie a
little bit with a storyline from
beginning to the end with a introduction
and with a happy ending and all that and
with a side character that we've never
heard of before
um
musical drama
like an idol idol musical
yeah yeah yeah
kind of fitting for a generation that's
all about fantasy
i want another third gen concert though
i want part two
i want more virgin is so amazing i want
them to be in tokyo dome next time not
tokyo dumb city hall that's
tokyo
tokyo dome let's go virgin let's go
[Music]
yes
i'm asking for more
mo
so uh actually i woke up really early
for this i'm going to be honest i want
to go back to sleep
i will read the super chats uh in the
next stream uh we have a stream tomorrow
where i'll be celebrating the one-year
anniversary for hinotoni and celebrating
thanksgiving and i think we'll have more
than enough time to read super chats
[Music]
and and all the other first gen fans who
came by to enjoy this together with me
[Music]
it's it's i think i said this with uh
concert as well i think but it's
actually
maybe
almost even more fun to watch it at home
because here i can cheer
here i can dance here i can be loud
uh
and you can't do that in the in the
concert hall i mean there's other things
that have been in the concert hall the
whole atmosphere you can't get that at
home quite that much
i don't know
i think the concert really showed
everyone's
charms
so that's my
that's my feedback yeah
cute made me like the girls even more
and it made me
re-re-charge my love for fertigen
yeah
jordan
[Music]
okay then yeah i will see you guys
tomorrow please uh until tomorrow
there's gonna be two more
premieres of my remixes so
no time to rest except for me i'm gonna
take a nap
[Music]
thank you guys for watching and in
germany
[Music]
thank you
yes yes we'll go back to sleep
[Music]
this will be i'll be right there
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
you