[Music]
thank you
I don't wanna
dance
[Music]
let's go
don't go
[Music]
back
let's go
[Music]
back
who goes
[Music]
hello hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
I hope everything went well now
live English and
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
holy lordy oh yeah well we have Gabbert
here today to present to you a new
feature that just was updated in Among
Us the home alive
[Music]
[Applause]
and Japan this these streams are not
sponsored but we just really want to
show you something good look at
everything
[Music]
yeah look at that wow wow look at those
snazzy amazing
hello we asked everyone to introduce
themselves and they can also show off
their sexy outfit while they're
introducing themselves
no we might get kicked out of the room
eventually but let's just start oh let's
start with
hello everybody
uh number one detective I'm naked
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
she will have some sick outfits some
sick drip right yeah yeah yeah
okay below um we have Anya at least in
the Discord so anyone introduce yourself
please hello everyone I'm shirakamian
today nice to meet you guys
in the nation hello
hi
okay next we have Clio primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not here but guess what also my
mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi
streaming in 480p which to be honest
[Music]
swag As a sheriff let's party
clips of you guys every once in a while
who is also with Amelia one of the
selected people you can get the outfits
of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now yes
[Music]
foreign
now you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
I love it there are many sharklings
around
this one's right here right next to you
is cool please introduce yourself or are
you Gouda
who is you who is you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah
[Music]
oh my God
it's crazy
[Music]
I don't know it seems like an imposter
she's wearing the whole outfit it has to
be
suspicious
all right whatever it's close enough to
Calliope
and then we have Muna who is also part
of the people whose outfit you can get
in the game
hi everyone I am Moana from Whole Life
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
you're wearing your own hair yes
[Music]
I feel like right now I'm I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
um I'm doing a touring love in the Among
Us
hi
[Music]
I'm Amazed
yeah
chocolate ice cream ice cream we're
working on it right Mommy
[Music]
who are you going for what outfit do you
want
whatever is the closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right and then
we have a baby
yeah
from the whole life ID today I'm
cosplaying as sexy naked money
[Music]
[Applause]
was so good what the heck that was
really good she was here
okay and then we have Zetta
hello hello I am I will be the second
today
[Music]
oh my God yeah
at least the organizer of today's event
the sponsor of today's event
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay that is so funny
I just like
hi
hello oh that was funny that was Lenny
no it's funny
oh good nice can you guys hear me hello
yay
okay awesome and then let's let's re
introduce
thank you thank you
a really sexy combination of marine and
pecora you look at that
so cool
looking good I can also do like a music
I can do so much I can do this but
anyways
[Music]
and I will now change the world settings
we will have everything included we'll
have scientists uh just in case you
don't know the scientists can see the
vitals at any time no not any time well
there's a countdown but you can see if
someone's dead before finding the body
and then we have the engineer engineer
can uh is a crewmate who can jump into
the vents so you can maybe with that I
got that a lot in practice yeah or you
can maybe find some other imposters
because of that might be healthy eating
in the vents oh no yeah
spicy for YouTube
very spicy and now we have the guardian
angel which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
and we have last but not least the shape
shifter this one is that that calls for
a lot of
fights
[Music]
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think wow that was
Anya oh my God
two onions
but just so you know all of these rolls
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it might happen to you now
let's see yeah
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
thank you
everybody
oh okay
[Music]
okay uh
oh here
okay we can choose
I'm gonna
doing everything that I could I'm a good
I'm a good girl one tomato tomato
oh
wait I had to put it on the okay
all right oh where is it where is it
where is it
it's a far away
it looks like Lego somewhere away
oh they look like little the lights the
like is up guys the likes the likes is
the likes itself do that wait where
where can I where can I
do oh here I am
wait that is not that is not the light
where's the lights location
s
already
[Music]
[Applause]
Kiara's gone real quick that was fast um
[Music]
where was the body Armory yeah
[Applause]
tasks
Kelly songs
I was in the shower I have no idea in
the lounge now I was in the Gap room
doing something electrical and I think
all I was in the room with her oh
[Music]
um
I mean Phoenix tastes good right
that sounds so soft
[Music]
like uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory but that was the
beginning I was in the guest room when
it was fun out well
well you know I
didn't anybody want to
wanna I have no idea you can you can uh
if if you are you were telling me that
um I was in a Armory you can ask uh gura
because I saw Guru also in uh nearby
there in the kitchen
I was passing by yeah
[Music]
I'm gonna choose only
um
okay I'm gonna Skip and see how it goes
oh really
voting time is too fast
I feel like 14 times too fast hey what
up what up
what is this a fashion design what
should I do oh I couldn't Jam
okay how's Japan senpai
what half the pants
you asking my pants
oh it was Japan
I just realized it's stupid okay
I'm going hunting and going up
where is it
oh it's going wait the hell
okay
wait it's it slammed me to a different
place again
okay
what is this oh
zero four seven four seven
um I need to go there
how can I go down
how can I go
Oh that girl is in my head
wait
what is this oh
I need to go do it
I do this I'm going to the shower don't
look at
wait what
okay
oh okay
okay how can I do this uh that was
impossible scary
oh I got to the lodge
how can I get in oh there
wait
huh
oh my God come on man oh my God is that
is dead
it was like a kitchen a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maurice and fight we were
nearby Electrical uh going through the
viewing deck I was with a roommate and
Kelly Senpai I mean I I was uh uh I
passed by I passed by I think it was
Watson or and
and gura in records yeah
I can I say that last time I saw zado
they were in the main hall with hobo
Cobo
you know
I I was I was listening about global
because uh she she telling me on the
previous one it was me well I definitely
like far away from the kitchen and now
[Music]
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobo
yeah
so any last words
was like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh see herself like like just
what she said and then after that I go
up
are you sure about that oh well I think
this is for you before right near the
lounge that was beginning though that
was the very beginning
after that I go up
go up
up after killing her you mean
I'm just going to Cobo we have like we
have little short time uh choose uh
who's you're gonna
have enough information yeah I have no
idea
foreign
wait what is it
oh okay freaks
okay hi
I still need to fix the toilet though
okay
toilet is clean now
we got a lot of things now
where should we go now electrical
electrical
[Music]
nice and then
um
hello hello
the One Direction
going down me going down we're going
down hey what's this queen hello hello
hello wait how how can I upload okay
Builder
[Music]
okay that's insane Watson is dead uh I
found the body
yeah oh
um I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like
and doing things and then I walk out and
Watson's dead body is there
Watson if you were entering the front of
the ship you would have passed Watson
how did you not see her well I don't
really pass I want to say I passed gura
and I went up
we people people didn't
I asked you not to stab me baby oh okay
I'm not gonna point fingers at you
immediately I just want to know what
your Alibi is
no no I'm not I just want to know what
your Alibi is because I Watson left and
then you came in and I walked past you
and Watson's dead bodies on the ground I
just want to know what that's about
why you remember so much Kelly I'm I'm
just surprised I don't know all right
now listen here's the deal so the amount
of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
it was like no time at all you would
have passed her I just I just want to
remind you that we have 10 seconds left
so I think if if you don't have Alibi
I'm gonna Choose You may I'm sorry I
have to vote for a movie I just really
believe it
I don't know I don't think you're
listening to me I don't know the uh it
might be movement actually I have no
idea
I have no idea
oh
it was moving
it was Mommy
nice nice
yeah
I know it I know it it's nice for sure
[Music]
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately
[Laughter]
thanks I think Kelly you should go for
it Amelia wants some detective outfit
yeah
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yeah
let's go
oh let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God okay
hi
[Music]
okay
because we have to clean clean
thank you
[Music]
am I talking on
I don't know how I don't know how to do
it
hello
just doing my tasks yeah there's
electric stuff to do
like in
I'm not gonna say that
senpai
[Music]
oh
I thought you so you don't get caught hi
you're not gonna hurt me right
who's gonna who's gonna why there's a
lot of people we usually safe okay
there's a lot of people in the shower
I hear something weird
really
hello how how do how do we do it
what is that
I don't know how to do it not the
outside
joke man what oh that's only okay
where
that was crazy so I don't know the map
super well but I left the shower so I
put away all of the washcloths from the
shower yeah and I turned right and I
went down that long hallway and found
Ollie's body right in the middle of
there but I didn't see anyone coming
down
[Music]
so like above the shower house above the
shower archives to the right yeah all
the way to the archives
who was there who was there that you
that you that you remember
well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower um also Rana could have
killed me and she did pretty close I
think the girl was in the shower as well
but she like went down to the left
room with Cobo I was thinking uh do we
have like a like a delay of the of the
of the kill because because if if it's
really if it's raining if she already
killed only probably she cannot kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so like
I feel like
she was trying to tell me a joke and
then I ran away from her oh yeah
[Laughter]
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
[Music]
why are you cussing me out huh no I just
like saying uh so call is saying that
you are nearby the the place I just like
thinking oh it's true I'm true
I saw him in a senpai in the middle-ish
or on the left side
oh okay okay then
that is so funny what is that Holy
wait that is so scary
yeah okay Spider-Man actors wrote
what is this oh
it's a good taste everyone
so wild saying myself here hello hello
I'm following hello
oh
hello goodbye I think we go to the same
direction
[Laughter]
I don't want to do calms because I can't
like literally I'm just gonna I can't do
this one I will do it leave it to me I
have to wait um
safe you fix it yeah
I'll be away
full's put away
and they have to put away the pistols
[Music]
wait how do we do it
cannot move
because I'm not gonna move
oh
[Music]
um
where where it's going to
get it
ding ding
don't worry you
oh my God where
no no no no no no no
oh
[Music]
nobody else
Kiara I was with you and we confirmed
each other as Alibi yeah
below the main hall or something
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room
I saw you at the right side of the map
going up yeah sure because I was doing
tests at the cargo bay you know there's
the top oh okay cool we
thank you
so
um
so you from the cargo bay you you go you
went up and then tried to go I'll
explain my route I went cargo bay uh for
the you know small thing and then I went
to the showers because you know that
those are a two-part tasks after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts and kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so you
found me yeah I think I think I I felt
it's so rainy but like I think it feels
good but Reina went past me and it was
the best voice
and I was like I went like what what
oh how is that possible interesting
is
something so
um
[Music]
oh wait
I'm gonna
I don't know
it's raining with Zetta voice
oh okay
oh my God
[Music]
we don't want to talk
oh
hey
oh oh no no no no no no no no no go away
please don't kill me what do you mean by
that
[Music]
what
wait what was wrong
what you came from this side because
like yeah I just like we let's go from
this I go go from this and then we meet
in here right now
[Music]
[Applause]
we were we were met in here and you're
going that way I'm going down
what happened I don't know whatever I
mean maybe not but it was kind of weird
you came from somewhere right you know
no I wouldn't be wouldn't be foreign
[Music]
wait where should I go
where should I go and then go here hi hi
yes
ding
there is nothing in here
all right on in my tasks hello hello
[Music]
oh
Michelle
going up what is that
um
[Music]
the four of us again yeah it's four of
us
anybody
making my girl oh hi
send me back what where where
[Music]
when I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical task and I ran into it
raining and mummy
um
that's uh technically that's I I keep
thinking why I think these three a two
Row in the back is always you guys
always spots sounds about rainy why yeah
right now and this time rainy too
what why is so much rain in everybody
[Music]
huh it wasn't me it wasn't even me
reporting I don't know where the body is
this time the one who are reporting is
Google
yeah
shifters don't forget shapeshifters what
about medical guys
where was it
wait I want to ask uh Arena where
I'm at Medical I came from cargo bay
Uma was like going from bottom oh yeah
yeah I saw her in the cargo bag
and where was the body I literally have
no idea
for a little bit but then I was down by
electrical like down the ladder that's
where I was coming up when it was
reported
I don't know why
I'm so serious why see I want to ask why
is Mermaid so always so afraid of me or
is she just afraid of everybody in
general oh yeah I was thinking the same
here's me oh my voted for me last time
wait so do we have an answer where the
body was I missed it yeah where's
where's the body was I was gonna see the
body both the body and the bathroom
I don't know what should I choose
um um I don't know sorry I don't know
what should I choose
oh no
now we just need to reject one more oh
my God one more one more one more
I was oh that this is the bridge this is
the braids
[Music]
oh cool down Gouda
wait what is this not a
lot of the UAE that yeah
huh
what why are you ready
on the left what
what Luna I just saw you saw you on the
right really
oh
hello
[Music]
why uh uh up there
I I was I was in the cockpit
ah
shoot like me okay
[Music]
ding
hey bro
where oh
[Music]
it definitely wasn't raining then I
thought it was her maybe uh I found her
body in the kitchen but I saw no one
else around I I I heard I heard rainy so
doppelganger of me
so yeah
of me
so I don't know who it is so somebody
was pretending to be you yeah only
running from Luna but maybe it wasn't
Luna Muna oh wait who yeah I saw I saw
you too I mean Muna is like oh whatever
it was with Rena for a while so I'm not
not this time but I was with her often
enough wait was that the previous run
I'm mixing I can't remember yeah
yeah it might have been last game when I
was alive was it I ran into combo combo
was sounding very scared though so I'm
always we have to vote for someone oh
that was killing someone scary is that
it but with Como I was like for a while
together she could have killed me she
didn't so I think she's fine
but but she didn't kill me neither
so I have a feeling that
but then I but then I think it might be
I got a doppelganger so I I don't know I
don't know I just wanna because last
time Muna is with arena in the weapons
like it's oh right what so where was in
the weapon where is that close I haven't
I haven't go I haven't go to the Armory
can anyone vouch for Ahmed and say like
she's safe I was with Gouda and I didn't
kill her
nothing about Kobo though because
I don't know
who wants to come sit with me while I
clean them it's really that was an
engine
oil is an engine
who's not finishing the task
bye bye bye
push
electricity
the electricity is down somehow
yeah
I don't know what's happened
first I think I still had
hi Mona hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
laughs
oh
then we're still there
yeah but very quiet
oh you wow
wow
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me it's pretty hard to
watch yeah it was really hard to watch I
was barely doing nothing you need to do
and then I saw something I wasn't
supposed to see he just killed me on the
spot
I'm sorry I'm sorry
wait hold on I'm gonna
I'm gonna go away
hi okay
nice I got faces even if I buy some
clothes so bad like
early in the game
no evidence
[Music]
no maybe it's not her
Detroit
[Music]
question because I heard you in the in
the selection screen where you choose
where to go next I heard you say
something that sounded like something
I felt like you might have been acting
was that what you were doing
um
let's go all right so you were like
aware that we would hear you and you
were on purpose saying something that
only a crewmate would say
[Music]
let's go
oh my God are we waiting for Muna right
now I'm back yeah I'm back already
[Music]
let's go let's go
Ollie congratulations
hmm not here
oh
ding ding ding
ah okay
pretty milky but Jiggy
onion hurt
hello I have a gun
me too
Armory
oops
what is it the is the lights the lights
off the lights off
what is this what
oh are you viewing files
that's these are killed so nicely
what
happened
where where
the location of the map
press tab then you will know um
I I saw I so rainy I saw rainy uh going
to the Armory and the kitchen when when
I want to go to engine room so I don't
know what I see from cockpit or main
hall
yeah so we'll cost each other in the
kitchen and I'm from the communications
Armory kitchen I saw viewing that alien
Guru yeah yeah it was
we kind of passed by each other oh yeah
why is it always me what you guys have
against me yeah
yeah yeah
and Calum was in the shower I saw her I
saw her in the shower but then she went
away to the left side I think
she went to the left side so she was you
know she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't
I
[Music]
went up
no I went I didn't see you go up
what is this
what is this one okay don't Point things
I'm skipping I'm skipping
I'm gonna vote for Zetta because
that's varies
[Music]
somehow
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't
I don't think
no one was addicted
[Music]
hi hello
doing my task let's go
let's go down here
all right
and we're going up
okay going up up up up up up up up up
I love it I love how they put my hair
like that
okay fixing the shower
oh okay
okay oh
spicy spicy
[Music]
heck
hello what is this please don't do
anything I'm just I'm just a little guy
if I killed two minutes would be right
here and you know yeah right
oh
oh it's from the other side dang it
I can go
don't hurt no
always advice taking a dump in the next
bathroom
where is it
the lights is
the lights the lights is off
not this one why a kid
I can't find the lights
where's the light should be
here
dang it dang it okay
wait
oh wait what
[Laughter]
no oh my God there's a lot
Anya's dead
What the freaking
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else serves us here huh okay
um
where's the where's the body where's the
body first
or showers oh no wait what showers
these are
like you're out though let's wear out a
day where
um the last time the last time I went
near the shower and main hall is I saw
only
Ahmed and I think I think
Anya with anyone I think
no no I didn't see I just did yeah
is she alone in the
huh we're outside then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zetta
what what the question
you've been silent lately why do you
have any alibi
yeah
she's innocent yeah listen to me I am
always sus when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm uh nuts so keep
that in mind now you're sassing me which
means I'm a crewmate it's always like
this it's not gonna work are you sure
about that why
the why aren't you providing an
alibi instead of Defending yourself huh
I was only the secluded room where like
she would have killed me I would kill
her
I'm gonna skip I don't know Skip because
I don't know yeah I don't know I'm just
gonna Escape
hi
[Music]
I trust you I trust you too let's fit
the where's the light oh this is the
light okay okay
nice
thank you
let's fix it
yes
scary I'm scared of them
I'm going here
all the lights in in somewhere not there
you know
it's in here okay what is it
how can it how can it how can I do the
task oh
oh wait um okay uh
this and this okay that's just complete
I just like this off again God damn it
here I'm not here
[Music]
why are you killing me
why are you killing me Zeta I will
haunch
it's Zetta for sure I'm voting no really
oh really
okay
you found a body three
yeah because I just happen to be a
detective who's really good at spotting
bodies
let's say some scary things but I don't
know man Randy could I have killed you
or would I have it's an idea if I was
with you and in that room for like over
30 seconds
I don't know uh you want me to be honest
um what you said was oh just kidding I
was just waiting for my cool down yeah
but I was already in the room doing this
house
it wasn't always jokes
[Music]
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jada
no
no no but I mean I can give us I said
I'm running away from the body well
Raina and I were both up in the room
like in the meeting room and then as I
went down the whole time and then we saw
Zeta pass us and in that hallway
[Music]
yeah I saw Cobo take the little elevator
I'm going to put that up for now yeah
[Music]
30 seconds 30 seconds
[Applause]
who
I would have reset it but maybe it's
wrong
it's not me
it is
I'm gonna do my toes
finish it so
that was pretty funny when
hey
oh my God
okay
guys at all now I'm searching for
someone
who I'm gonna go sit Who is the
Who is the
um
where is it oh no no she's getting ready
to kill me who is hurting me
[Music]
[Applause]
I am here
[Music]
following any of you
I don't know
anymore
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
come on
oh no oh no
oh man I'm in here
I miss fishing a lot somehow oh sorry
sorry sorry
I keep pressing the wrong buttons
I don't how long does it last for fast
wait look what I don't like
what it's probably doing anything
[Music]
um
[Applause]
thing
separated
[Music]
foreign
oh sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place just because
because we want to develop you off yes
let's believe it's not me
um
[Music]
oh bye bye
no
[Music]
now where should we go
hi
we're both hello hello hello hello hello
hello hello
[Music]
can cream it here or is it only only the
The Imposter
I think only the unboxing here I'm sure
it's cool I'm
I'm recording
sheet
um
hello this is watchable okay hello
what is that Cobalt you can hear me all
right
you're still alive wait what did she do
I thought it was but I don't know
I don't know I have no idea too
um why is no one pressing I'm just
follow
[Music]
ing Cobo
where are you going oh you're fixing the
line
um
we could win
[Music]
yeah I finished my test
so who isn't finishing because we could
I have
yeah
wait so wasn't that a senpai
is Kara oh okay
[Music]
I like Cara why Cara is scared
it's Coco
[Music]
I done all my tasks
um
probably
[Music]
why
please
[Applause]
we both was a gun too
[Music]
it was it was global
I got I got killed by Vera nice good job
team nice Hustle
[Applause]
[Music]
but to be honest Army was so spot on
um
it's kind of funny not gonna lie yeah
I'm so scared yeah
that's just her personality it's not
that she's the Imposter that's just her
personality
[Music]
and I was like doubting myself don't
believe me
I believe you
okay
yeah yeah sure sure
[Music]
ah
hi oh I think it was weird I'm sorry I
can't do it in an audience
oh the leather glove is two doors down
oh this one
wait this is just a regular where does
this
shall we
oh what's this
I was dirty
I'm dirty so
you guys you guys watching me showering
okay
chocolate ax hi
hello
I want to ride
I miss you
I still have no idea where's the like
yeah
yeah right the lights are down here
there's more than one oh okay so there's
more than one
I don't know where the order is I'm
going up
it might be oh yeah wait it was
huh
it's not here
oh my God
whoa
what
I want you guys
watch her die where
okay okay
um
she said please you want to be killed
all right movie we'll give you some more
time to get some kills mama you want to
be cute
are you you want to be killed or or
Kiara Kira just uh go to mumei so if she
was the first one
again
what yeah I mean yeah sure people get
killed I mean you'll suffocate oh I want
to watch me get like you know beheaded
or whatever okay then I'll I'll grab
your way she have my little roommate I
will give you until the next meeting and
then all right all right this combo
wanna talk about it because she reported
sorry yeah oh yeah yeah where was the
body where did you find the body Cobble
I found the body in front of
Communications between Communications
and communication and I was oh I was uh
communication right again communication
I don't think I'm left side
[Music]
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
we'll give you until the next meeting
as many people as you can
[Music]
oh my God
no one was addicted
right now
hello hello
wait where is it
sit around here
is it done already
I think it's done already
you are
I'm cooking build a burger yeah
yo
you guys like your Tomatoes I'm a
palazzo tomatoes
nice it's really quick though and then
I'm gonna go to electrical
let's put an outfit by the way it looks
good on you thank you
[Music]
all right
no one has killed me yet
yeah you want to be together with me
wait where is it yeah sure I think I'm
gonna go with this
uh fixing the light
I have no idea where July this oh it's
already done bye oh
[Music]
yeah and and they they didn't kill me at
all the body was pretty quick to get an
alibi there huh
wait what wait who found which body
though there's three bodies right I
found zeta's body in cargo bay and it
wasn't there a moment ago I think but
the lights hard to tell
um so I I have a meeting room at the
very top
I have an an alibi for for only and gura
because I saw them and we were we were
near the kitchen first and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
we were from from Kitchen go to
electrical
so
what is what's uh what is
why and also why I want to us and also
why Kiara is not screaming at all
usually when when she was the crew man
she always she always screams whatever
she met someone
sure about that
yeah what the
I I've been I've been I've been uh
watching all of you guys
um you know
Sound by on the previous uh previous
games where Kiara Kiara really loves to
scream when I ever met anyone when she
was a grandma I was scared that's
because exactly that's because you're
scared and now you're getting you're and
now so far you didn't show that you are
scared do you have an alibi no it's
because I didn't see anything probably
that's because you're the size one
remember because only the whole time no
no no last minute I don't know the last
minute okay yeah
I'm scared for my life I don't know how
to trust anymore yeah
oh God okay
I think a couple of minutes in the
future I'm probably gonna get killed
hi oh you already did it yeah already I
just saw Ollie and she was going the
opposite way of the electrical light so
fast
all right
um
here I guess going up
hello Ollie hello
if she's screaming like I don't think
she's the sauce one
um
[Music]
going down
ah
awesome costume
[Music]
hi
I'm stuck
okay let's go
thank you wait I have to go in here uh
me too I had to upload the data
okay
wait the light the light is off
voice
ah
all right
I hate it
everything is close
read the electrical thingy
I need to fix this one okay thank you
huh
why did this just go out again
what I hear I hear scream
roses
here's my top yeah
are your thoughts done
your thoughts done
I mean you're you're nonsense right
uh where should I go next
maybe maybe I should
where is it where is it where is it
where is it
uh where's the worst it was it
we're going up going up going up okay
[Music]
did she see it did she see it I hope she
helped you see it oh this is it
Christmas yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai going
towards where Ollie was and that was the
last time I saw her
no
no wait wait wait
[Applause]
first emergency button everybody
it really went to check if anyone's
dead or you're the last one left and you
want to try to vote people out
also not saying anything yeah yeah I
didn't know
what is it called what are they called
imposter it's one consumers
why'd you call a meeting what the heck
I'm a senpai yeah
I thought it was over you know what yeah
I'm done with my task anyways so like
maybe I can just go chat with the girls
so you guys can vote me on because
that's what you guys want
to talk with the ghosts the imposters
oh
[Music]
Steve
[Applause]
shingles
[Music]
no so Zetta who killed you
ah
[Music]
I got killed like hobo
yeah it was Cobo
uh fine
well well well
why is only not the fan okay
pressing his
dang it
what should I do
ignore your task
s
[Music]
we're done with my tasks oh man uh
hmm
you guys I'm so happy what is that weird
who's breathing Ollie why are you not
defense yourself
dang it
oh my gosh
one step further from winning
every time that Kobo is the Imposter
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo
I just love how awesome
she saw the crime scene rent goes to the
emergency meeting and then Ahmed Changes
Everything by sussing the innocent yeah
yeah
[Music]
nice yeah nice I'm fully me now
um I never get imposter why
well guess we have a lot of things to do
fixing the electricity what is this
hmm
it's like something people were hoping
for what
oh there is like a number
oh sometimes sometimes there is there is
sometimes miracles happen
um
foreign
[Music]
were all like it's like a dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report I clicked report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there
okay the lights were out
at electrical
where where I was at electrical I have
my thoughts in there I was at the bottom
right I was at the bottom
I was at the bottom in the middle I
I didn't so I did it
[Music]
did you finish the towel the towel no I
didn't finish picking them up I thought
I did but it wouldn't let me put them
inside of the hamper thing so I still
have to grab a couple towels
because I was in the electrical I saw I
was in the electrical I was in the
middle I was in the middle bottom and
see that he was in the bottom but I
didn't see anyone no no
fans nearby
well I guess he could say that rainy's
body tasted delicious hey turkeys am I
right oh gosh
too much all right I'm going to call
again I need to fix this things
going back to the electricity
well we we went to we went to what
also we we go to four now
where's he
hi hi
five six
seven okay
finish
and oh we got another one
guys guys guys guys guys guys
I I I pass uh on Ollie's I pass on
Ollie's uh in the in the electrical I
was doing my electrical and then and
then after that she's going up and then
I saw I saw
kali's body in the electrical when I'm
doing the uh I ran into Ollie after that
and she was saying and I quote sure hope
he said I am you're right really yeah
right I was listening about Ollie the
first time the first time only said that
she was an electrical but I didn't see
it and then the second time you know we
we had to teleport first right and then
after that he said you know I'm an
electrical I find you and after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie passed by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
body and the last time myself
body I just couldn't resist to him
I
wish your partner good luck Ollie
whoever was with you whoever was
actually can do this alone
gotta be careful the next one might be
same gen Bond
[Music]
is it actually Ollie
well I think it's only because this is
us
I think she would defend herself more
than she would defend herself more if it
wasn't her yeah she will defend herself
if it wasn't her but she just like
admitted
she sounded like something
my bioli
oh no no wait
where where
you're going up
I'm on my way one five okay I'll go next
time okay
all right
yeah I stopped
I'm gonna go to The Fault
let's go
um
going here
where
oh yeah
I just saw her like a second ago running
away from the alarm like she finished
the alarm and then she walked to the
right side towards the records launch
Etc
buddy
the body
the body records
I was in Maine Hall going to showers and
then passed by and then contact I
checked like around the showers and then
I go up a bit and there's Anya's body
there are you saying so so the last time
you saw probably Zetta
yeah yeah but I was asking me again
so I was coming from the left side
uh-huh
come on come on we need we need fast
fast
Shape Shifter accessed here you are
uncomfortable we don't know for sure but
it could be we don't know for sure I
don't know I don't know but okay but
she's she's like she's like uh you know
when she tried to do her Alibi she's
just like kinking thinking for like a
long time
because I
what if
I would have done it was then that who
was like thinking right Cara voted
really fast
[Music]
because we know it's not ourselves I'm
is voting for me again isn't she
evidence
say the last time
instead of just like when she's doing
her album just she thinking for a while
I think she was thinking for her alibi
what is it is it correct
oh yeah yes
good job I did nothing but good job
I didn't even have like 10 seconds of
gameplay
[Applause]
you guys figured it out heck yeah Yay
good job
[Music]
that was a great job
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay is there anyone who didn't get
imposters
[Music]
yeah
I like doing my past
you know this game is like never end I
feel like I want to play it until I got
a another imposter
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know it's too late
for me it's me it's fine because
because good morning
I've already already took my nap so I'm
still I'm still fine if you want to get
going yeah
[Music]
okay okay
one more one more or less okay
[Music]
thank you so much
oh no
me too I didn't get it
is it already close oh it's fine
it's not the location
because she does
[Music]
right now
you make a mistake
Carlson by really planning her tactics
right now
you wouldn't be able to conceive
yeah
trying
to
learn
where guys
self report huh there's a shape
oh come on give her
give her it's come on
true I mean I don't want to talk anymore
[Music]
holy crap it was yeah it was in the
hallways it wasn't a mean Hall actually
um yeah main hall I yeah so uh I was I
was I actually uh saw her through the
showers I went to electrical a little
bit then I went back to the main hall
and guess this I actually met another
Ollie so if you guys said anything like
oh my God no there was actually a
doppelganger and I actually met her she
was chasing me down
no no listen you sure chasing me down
and you know what even if
even if I fly I mean the task easier I
believe you though okay
I think I think I think I'm gonna skip
because I don't know
um yeah I don't know oh yeah
she's desperate yeah she just like
desperates so much herself and whenever
she tries to defend herself always just
like very very desperate oh yeah
asleep
oh my God
what happened
[Music]
yeah
um
oh yeah
I got stuck
go ahead and go down yeah I can go down
I can't go everywhere it'll be like I'm
gonna go everywhere
[Music]
um
everything just like kill you and not
say anything stuck
where should I go
I will like searching for you know uh
you cannot find anything
huh
wait
uh uh lights off
wait there's a body here where is that
ah right here
what up
oh did you find it
[Music]
yeah hold me look at the pretty name
plate I want it I mean I have I have an
alibi
you know so I was I was on the first I
wasn't security we drain it if if I was
impossible I've been I've been with
Renee uh for like a couple of seconds
I'm not killing her at all so if and
then I got to to the main hall cool down
I passed at least girl like girls were
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something
and then there was also Zetta or
something but there was like a bunch of
people there
I think yeah I feel like Yeah I wanted
to show a magic that's a lot I mean like
I'm not accusing anybody I'm just
telling what I saw okay I mean yeah I
mean
[Music]
yeah but the thing is I don't know Anya
Anya was also there but Anya's also
there but girls also dead I don't know
hmm
I I don't know I don't know neither
because it's alive muna's alive I'd
always say anything I don't know I don't
know because everything will be used
against me because because I was I was
on the main hall before I was in the
main hall I have a tax in the main hall
I have a toss in the main hall and then
I want to go and I want to go to the
records to do another toss and then I
saw Watson okay it's a tie yeah I
reported the body
uh Yara says
safety
hmm
[Music]
the name oh this is not the place
where is the where's the electricity
where's the electricity
is this this one is this one I think
it's this one
hi
oh where wait
oh it's already done
okay
oh ah
because I'm gonna try to kill you
[Music]
oh where is it okay
I'm locking myself stupid
foreign
[Music]
okay
hmm
where is it
where is what
and then Luna please don't kill me wait
wait wait
oh okay oh yeah I have the braces
I had to press
in a while so moon has alone upstairs by
the way oh no she's no longer alone what
oh lights
lights lights where's the light
oh it's not these
whenever
I want to say
hmm it's Kobo
oh why
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gura
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
sort of electrical to
as if she's doing that task but it takes
one second and she waited one minute
there believe me trust me bro I don't
have any proof of her I will I will vow
because the only thing the only thing
that's like for me suspicious is that uh
she's she's being like awfully quiet
yeah she hasn't really said anything up
until like in the discussion at all do
you have a defense for yourself yeah do
you have a defense for yourself like why
are you so quiet or you know I'm always
quiet from the beginning
what if I really do my task in
electrical I mean why mommy I'm gonna be
so that aggressive
I did it right after you too and I know
it takes one second I'm just I'm just
gonna say Ollie and Watson are always
together
yeah yes okay I'm gonna fold stories
yeah
thank you for believing me okay I try I
try to believe I tried I try to believe
bye bye Kobo
I don't think I was getting injected
[Music]
on with Mata so I don't know what should
I do
oh Muna please don't kill me I know
you're the Imposter what I mean I can
follow you all day long and you wouldn't
get killed me
ah
no why should I do it every toss is
already clicked on
hey
where is it where is the electricity
where's the electricity
uh
where's electricity
those aren't lights
oh we're nothing bye
[Music]
okay that's really easy
yeah
prostrate
what happened to cherishing bye we're
not invite again
hmm
okay wait wait look
respawn
okay I opened it
[Music]
he was a fixer okay
the others
[Music]
wait wait wait wait
I guess so
yeah did you just come back from killing
someone
no I passed you guys
what where was that where was it
okay okay
in the cargo bay and she was about to
vent because she's she thinks she's cool
um and then I saw a red body
I just saw Moonah it must be Muna it's
Monada don't you see that um I was from
the Gap room and I passed by when you
are fixing the electricity and I go to
the shower and then I go to records
again
okay I was in shower it was earlier I I
saw I saw I saw I think it was Kiara and
then Zeta is from the shower too and we
passed by yeah right okay
then who is
where where is where is the location of
the body
I don't know what do you think no but
it's um in the cargo bay between the
door of medical to Cargo Bay Reyna and
Zeta which way were you guys going
through the showers like to the left or
towards the right no I was with Keith I
was with you
was with me we came from the top to the
bottom from like the other way or you
saw her going with you I saw her I
didn't see her at all what
literally I saw I saw like um I was in a
break I was in a break and I go to the
Gap room and then I got to do the record
I go down I saw Zeta and then Kiara and
then uh Zeta and Kiara I think there
goes some of them going to the up to go
into the record and then after so after
that I saw
it
no let's think of again if it's not Mona
then it's Zeta and she's just faking
being an
engineering I mean you always say it's
mean
I don't know
would say your brain cannot handle that
kind of skill
we will see we'll see if the game ends
now okay if it doesn't end in the center
no it's not I think I somehow think it's
Zeta
well that was a good game
oh that was a good game I I'm I'm really
bad I'm really bad at being Foster
his little height
it's so hot
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys you guys like playing group
like you guys going to two two groups so
I just like yeah which one should I
follow yeah that was so hard that was so
hard I think that made it difficult for
you yeah it's made me difficult
during the meeting was actually really
scary
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm sorry I had to that's pretty good
I'm so proud oh my God okay
a great a great round
excellent ice cream strawberries
I want to continue playing I don't wanna
you know yeah I think we had to end now
we don't even need to play on stream to
be honest just together
[Music]
50 pounds
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah it was pretty fun I won and it
passed around and then won all the
crewmate rounds or pretty much all of
them so it's you know pretty good day
pretty good game thank you for inviting
me Kiara thank you for setting it up uh
yeah thank you guys for playing thank
you for always sussing me even though
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I text you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
it's cold
outside
[Music]
next we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
um
to be crewmate I don't like playing
imposter anyway so I had a good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your boy that's fine just let it be
like and then everyone killed you
earlier
whenever you like explain something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like it sounded so convincing and you
were not lying yeah bullshitting us I
just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
tasks and I love doing tasks so it was
fun thanks for the invite here I'm doing
tasks I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damnedest best teammate that I possibly
could
agree honestly I was relieved I I was
scared to see what happens if it's like
especially like shapeshifter you're
killing all of you oh
my God that's terrifying I wanted to be
thank God I really want to be a safe
shifter I haven't got that
[Music]
can you give us a statement about your
actions today how many times have
imposter
a lot three times
it's like something in these collabs
there's always like one person who gets
it all the time yeah I only got it quite
a bit too right yeah
I want to say sorry for
for uh
um being posted together with me because
I cannot
um I don't know why but a playlist room
like uh there's
maybe pretty sure
yeah yeah yeah
sure so I'm not that like I felt that
you you seem very impressed
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good execute yeah I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia it's so easy but
um I don't know that's fine you can
always use that as the excuse me why is
that with the JP no English please
Japanese sorry you truly did yeah
you're really good yeah
yeah
and then we have
who gets us so many times even
[Laughter]
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I'm
actually says
Ali's just messing around but nah
was I was thinking whatever you like
yeah doing uh
um
[Music]
oh no
oh no am I getting Robin again that is
am I getting like 500 5 000 yeah
I actually want to thank your Senpai
especially because uh organizing these
source of collab
well all the most utmost respect thank
you for accommodating all of them
hey Kiara thank you
[Music]
oh movies
yeah I
didn't hear anyone
why I suddenly didn't hear anyone
legend wait what
um
what
[Music]
let's do it
I cannot hear any
it's who's talking permanent crewmates
oh thank you so much it was so much fun
I got a few imposters and then a little
uh two or three I don't remember yeah it
was it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you Kiara
said bye for host bring it and I want to
apologize because my stream died six
times
oh my
I don't know I just hold up
it is good yeah
you're pretty good
I think Zetta killed me more than any
other member I'm gonna remember that
[Music]
nope
the game
hey
wait
hello
[Music]
I cannot hear us looking at here or
anything
it's like an idea running one
okay there's a problem in the in the
talk not from Discord I taught them to
you know talking in Discord but
let me try
hello I cannot talk in the in the in the
better clearly somehow
I don't know if you guys hear my voice
or not
yeah so I cannot hear anyone in the
better career yeah we're here now okay
okay
it's okay
um
[Music]
yay congrats thank you congratulations
I have fun uh actually uh the first time
I'm doing uh the to become an imposter
with I mean it's really fun
because because I miss the one that I'm
I'm usually afraid of whenever I become
an imposter because she always does
everyone
[Music]
if I make it a list it's probably I'm a
Kiara and then Kali is the one who can
like talk a lot that make me you know
sweet Sala so that's usually the person
that I am
I'm a sheriff yeah
[Music]
I'm the sheriff hey what was that
surprise there
um well anyway we can just talk in here
yeah we can talk in here yeah wow we're
done anyway I think I got to hear from
everybody
I'm glad that we all came together for
another big Enid collab I think the last
one was Mario
yeah
a year ago
but maybe since there's a lot of people
we can we can try it again sometime soon
[Music]
to watch our streams today tonight thank
you
I'm having so much fun
thank you yeah and I really don't have
anything else to say besides good job
everybody hope you had fun and yeah see
you again soon sometime yeah everyone
see you soon
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]