[Music]
why to s
oh so
[Music]
one two say no
Dre
[Music]
one two say no
oh 1 two say no
[Music]
p
got
mining contrary to popular belief it is
5 a.m. I not in Japan
Kyla good
morning good
morning oh
hi a lot of people don't know but I'm
awake at this time anyway oh man yes
thank you thank you well I'm awake at
this time anyway I usually go to sleep
at
like 6
7ish and was I was going to have a clab
with while in the morning anyway so I'm
kind of like awake for so
hello but but we were supposed to WR and
I was supposed to have a a
um a this collab she was scky
so I was like well I started practicing
cuz I was like I wanted to get to know
the
game um I wanted to get to know the game
anyway before the actual race and I was
like why don't I just stream
this I was like I was playing the game I
was laying at the controls and I was
like if I'm going to be awake and like
practicing why as might as well just
stream this anyway so
oh okay well I guess I'll stream it good
morning good morning yes we are
practicing I set a course a compet zon
uh for the race later today at like 700
p.m. it is 5 a.m. now good morning
everybody surprise be stream I was like
yeah I'm in to practice I'm going be
practicing anyone might as well stream
it so here I am what see my
car
wait my car it's uh it's Beil
car it's Beil car it is a
Ferrari
8488 dt3 I did not pick my own car they
chose the car for me
so this is B
car I don't know what a
Ferrari 488 is but I am the Zoomer yes I
also did not pick that title they just
gave me the title the Zoomer so
H thanks
stop yeah so that's this is my this is
the be people
car the Zoomer I made it 818 because B
bab it looks nice is it anyway I'm going
to learn how to drive we're going to
practice I just going
to practice ice BS for a little bit I
don't know how long this stream is a
it's so loud hey hey
hey how do I
huh who was that was that the radio guy
turn the radio guy
down you let's just turn the whole
thing down a little bit
is it still
loud is it good
now
what oh hold on a little bit a little
bit you know what the bad thing is I
can't listen to
[Music]
my oh you know what okay okay okay I'm
going to I'm going to get
my earbuds and plug my earbud
to my phone so I can
play my
music in my ear while I
drive let you get it get
earbud because I want to listen to cuz I
wanted to practi I I do better with
music so I was like motivating music in
my ear you know so I'm going to go get
my earbuds Kyla distract my chat KY
distract them ky ky ky I'm be right
KY e
okay
now I have my earbud in so now I can
play my own music in the background
while we v
v so I will be motivated cuz I always
play better music in my ear racing games
especially how are you doing everybody
good morning were you sleeping or are
you like are you like people I never see
because it's is is good hours for you
who are you who are
you good
morning are you are you DST T are you EU
are you my regular viewers who are you
good
morning they oh hi oh
let's see first song I want
to yeah
okay
let's
a like that
maybe this
better oh jeez
okay it's it's still kind of loud wait
is it still still kind of loud is it
good for you is it good is it still kind
of loud still a little loud
okay well that's why cuz I cancelled
it okay is this
better wait what
that
better wait why did Master go back to
what okay hold
on
better better
better
now okay it's still it's still loud
okay may make it like 20
okay
25 how a it
[Music]
okay too bad you can't hear what I'm
jamming out
[Music]
to light light
uh uh
[Music]
uh oh the controls are wow
okay H okay don't go through the okay I
see okay controllers are
[Music]
funny it's not Mario Kart okay this is
go this is a
[Music]
go
ah aha
[Music]
okay oh and then you go slow you go slow
you go slow you go slow you go slow you
go slow and then you go fast you go fast
like this you go
fast you go fast you go fast you go fast
[Music]
[Applause]
e oh
okay oh that's a turn not to turn
okay my
BL
myn
FR
day for
[Music]
my oh oh that's a big turn okay we got
to we got to we got to the turns okay we
got to slow down for the turns I see I
see I see I see I see I see
okay use the mini map oh yeah the mini
map is over there you can predict uh you
can predict
the the thing I
see okay you slow down and then you turn
and then you wait until you turn and
then you go fast and then you follow the
green
line and you follow the green the
green light
you go slow here and then you slow down
and then you turn first and then you go
and then you go and then you
[Music]
go o it had to slow down so I'm
breaking oh and then I go okay
wa is at time and then oh that's a big
one that's a big that's a big one okay I
got to remember that that's a big one in
the map you have to look at the map
okay okay slow down slow down slow down
slow down
go PA
big Dang Dang for
[Music]
my this is a sharp
turn okay like
that go B go go B
go how do you do
it how do you do it
[Music]
oh I go fast now I go fast now I go fast
I go slower
and then I go okay I go fast I go fast
now I go fast fast y go fast go
faster I go
a and I go
okay I
go okay
and wa that okay oh oh okay okay where
we go here we go
good turning good
turning that that was a big oh okay
there's a corner coming up there's a
corner so I should slow
down and take this corner
slow and go and now go
like like that okay like that like that
like that
okay okay here's another turn slow down
slow down I then go
fast Slow Down slow down slow down slow
down go go go go go go go go go go go go
go slow down again cuz it t to slow down
and then you do this and then you go go
and then you turn and then you go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go
go oh how
[Music]
exhilarating
okay
okay h
nice oh and now I go fast fast fast fast
fast faster faster
no the what did you
say huh what what did you
[Applause]
say faster okay
faster
oh oh it's said to slow down
it's time to swall
okay if I yell the turn will turn
[Music]
more it's like drifted I don't know how
I did
that I I breaked a little late oh no I
went outside the line it got mad the
time got mad at me it turned
red no oh I made I've messed up I've
done a thing I oops wait is that a
shortcut is that
legal my time went faster is that
[Music]
legal you get a Time penalty a
[Applause]
[Music]
paneline
okay oh you got to go like real slow
right
here I you go fast here fast if it's a
straight line just press it and you if
you straight line you press it but
here's a turn coming up so I better
break
and then go slow around this one and
then there's another turn over here so
we got to
break break
okay no go go go go go go go go go go go
f
[Music]
s okay can I can I do a lap without it
getting mad at me the time can I do a
can I do a lap without the time turning
red let's let's find
out slow slow slow slower Slow Down slow
down go
go oh hey
ha okay we go f but there's a turn
coming up there's a turn coming up so
let's go and go
slow and go fast go fast go fast go back
up go back up speed go back up speed
okay there's another turn there's
another
[Music]
turn
Okay that was a little it feels like a
little too
slow okay turn
oh hey not bad not bad not bad not
bad and now we go fast but there's
another turn so let's slow
down follow the guidelines laid out for
me that's very nice if they have these I
[Music]
guidelines man the CL is Mak it go so
slow though
but I can't take the shortcut or it'll
make me penalize you'll get mad
at slow slow slow down slow down slow
down okay go go go go go gradually
gradually go there's another turn here
so don't go fast yet okay now go now go
go
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I did it I did around with with it
not okay okay chat
Sensei how am I doing let's go over
let's go over how how how am I doing so
far he good I'm doing
good Prett not bad any tips chat
sense you need practice well yeah I just
started I literally downloaded it like
an hour ago
you're slowing too much on some turns
okay how do you drift what's the buttons
to
drift e on
[Music]
break you don't you don't drift in this
game oh should we try a race let's try R
uh with with
uh I think it's
this what's a hot
lb no which one's the MPC
one what's a hot
stick quick waste
okay uh sure 10 10 minutes let's do 5
minutes first let's do 5 minutes cuz we
just starting
out opponent
skill 80% is the weakest 100 is the
strongest let's make them weak
first five minut is like too L let's
let's make them weak first
okay we'll do 10
minutes I want to keep doing silver
Stone because when I logged into the
server uh the H live racing server it
was it was set to Silverstone so I have
an inkling that it's going to be the map
for the race so we're going to we're
going to keep doing silver Stone plus it
says silver Stone which is bble which is
which is bble
so let's I have well why would they set
that to as the practice map if they
don't set it as the race map right so
let's try
it I'm B Co
going double file
okay what does that
[Music]
mean I follow the
line wait I forgot my music
stop oh good wait bar the light is
exactly 10 minutes long so this
what
o wait excuse
me let's let's going on
light oh go go go
[Applause]
I'm going okay I'm going I'm going am I
[Music]
[Applause]
first oh no oh no oh
no
no I still first
[Music]
[Applause]
are they too
easy where did everyone go I did a bad
thing and I'm still
hurt or maybe I just took a really good
[Music]
shortcut where is
everybody I will your time panalty oh
I'm
cheating I'm
sorry these
turn okay
[Music]
okay let's
focus how do I slow down but not slow I
how do I slow down and turn but not slow
down and turn so much that it's too
slow I cloud in
isol half thr what is throttle
me my
name b in
flame throttle is what throttle is
huh half gas what's half gas there's a
half guys
[Music]
chasing oh
[Applause]
god wow I've made so many mistakes but
I'm still first you're going to kill us
no you're you're safe in my
car it's safe in here no crashing has
happen
yet you will not blare in my car
[Music]
oh these turs these turs are so sharp
these
the okay hold on I will focus
to let me walk
in okay gas gas gas gas break break
throttle throttle whatever that means oh
the turn is too tury the turn is too the
turn is too turny I'm
I too fast I'm going too fast break more
before turn okay okay
[Music]
like that like that like that like that
like this like this I did
it like that like that like that like
that yes
okay and now I go gas gas
gas oh someone's on my tail someone's on
my tail
get off my
[Music]
[Applause]
SS okay not bad not bad not bad not bad
not
bad Slow Down slow down go go go go go
go go
go we're halfway through not over yet
halfway over halfway
someone's still on my six we need to
lose
though sorry I died for a
second I forgot I was dying I messed up
this the shortcut went
this
[Applause]
[Music]
got no
T even though it's tempting cuz that
seems like a pretty good shortcut to
me a
nice turn nice turn nice turn nice
turn what do you think they'll put
penalties on during the actual
race or are we allowed to take cheap
shortcuts like that
it's cheating okay I will be I will play
legit I will play
[Music]
legit What happens if I run out of gas
in the middle of a r do I need the pit
stop thing how do you do that
[Music]
I passed
[Applause]
it ah
oh I tried to turn my music up but I
accidentally turned my phone off well
now I don't have music what is
[Music]
Focus okay focus no music just
focus this is so
slow I have to slow down so much for
this
[Music]
one but this but going slow in a race
doesn't make
sense use your blue shell I don't think
there's
blue
slide okay straight line go go go go
go I think I made the PC is too easy I
made mistakes but they're they're still
losing I feel too good about myself
that's
bad I need to feel bad about myself so I
can get better out of
yeah we're just warming up I know
I'm still learning how to
play right you just the last lap is
final lap okay
let's
[Music]
is what's wrong walk in for this even
though I'm pretty well into the lead it
could change at any time so
[Music]
FAS fast okay turn this one this is a
this is a this is a turn this is oh
there it's double turn it's double turn
it's double turn it's double turn I'm
going too slow though I it's too slow
it's too slow go faster faster
faster too
[Music]
slow I wasn't too slow that was good
oh oh this is also a double turn
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go the there's the Finish Line the
Finish Line I see it I see
it excellent job M B1 water race well
done well managed bring it back home I
want
oh uh
yay why am I dressed like an
Eva
[Music]
Dy
yay W it was too easy
get in the
[Music]
car
okay any any tips tats s
say any any any any tip oh replay oops
oops I messed up I forgot
wait hold on I got to not be
siny how do I how do I customize
myself
aha oh
why you up so early I'm always up this
early I'm just you just don't know cuz
I'm not on stream or social media but
I'm always up there
Sor doing homework this is my homework
to learn how to play this oh this one's
cool
I'm not in
Japan where's USA I'm not in Japan yet
ooh ooh oh I like the shininess but this
one
uh no shy
this is the colors that it came
with ew you can see the reflection of
the person if it's
no
byebye glossy
metallic glossy pastel
glossy
carving hold
on what purple am I I'm like
uh wa wait what purple am I huh
312 where is
nah 304 oh that's that's a little too
dark maybe like a 318
317 H what color even
is ooh
Chrome let's get chromed
up why does it zoom out when I do
that what if I make this
pink no
I want to I'm going to I'm going to
practice ooh
I want to be
Edy is not too blue uh
he 322
left okay I don't want to spend too much
time we got to
practice you go much faster by being
okay I'll make my gloves at least red
okay so we have the the Orcs
thing the Orcs thing the gloves we have
some red on the how do
I there the gloves are at least red so
now that work believe we go
fast
okay uh um what do we do
now what are we doing how do we what
should we do what what what do we do p
what
oh party difficulty
[Music]
mpy can I play with you
guys well hold on we should we should we
should practice first maybe we make
85 and then 85 maybe we up at 85
90 oh yeah I should be humbled
okay let's
try wait my music my music my music my
music uh
turn this
up okay I got a automatic playlist going
on
okay uh uh uh uh guess what song be
always listening to Let's
guess stay
[Music]
what's going
on light light
why why car on the right clear on the
right rules of
[Music]
nature wait wait you're going wait wait
for
me I
why he's going too
fast this guy is trying to pass
me car on the right clear on the
[Music]
right I'm
so oh hey
oh Rules of
[Music]
Nature a
o on the left wait hey hey what why hey
that's rude why'd you pass
me why do you do
[Music]
that oh
God car on the left clear on the left
oh
oh dang
[Music]
it car on the right excuse me on the
right winnable okay winnable I believe
you car
C on the
left I am certainly getting humbled now
that I up the
[Music]
difficulty hey hey hey hey hey hey oh
what did you do why did you do that
you're
rued why' you do
[Music]
that this is a RAC there's no mercy so I
can attack people
[Music]
too
oh car on the right clear on the
right car on the left C on the left
excuse me excuse me please please
[Music]
excuse hey hey can we can we can you
move can you move
[Music]
TI driving on the track out okay I'm
focused I'm not reading chat
[Music]
anymore oh I'm off the
track I need to hide you guys when the
actual race happen is that okay
when when the eyes are race but I need
to like put you guys away
something so I don't get
[Music]
[Applause]
tempted oh I can I can catch up WI a all
right if I just halfway through Drive
[Music]
it's actually over no it's not actually
over what am I listening to YouTube what
did you redirect me to it's cool but
wait what car on the right clear on the
right
oh I got distracted by the
song s
[Music]
guys whatever I'm listening to this is
cool car on the
right clear on the
right car on the
right uh is it's uh it's rock metal type
music there's a why is it playing cod in
the
background oh the music
video I'm getting distracted wait I'm
getting distracted by the
No No
[Music]
[Applause]
Way dang
it can you guys move
[Music]
car on the right C on the
right Collision penalty oh s cut
shortcut shortcut shortcut shortcut
shortcut car on the left clear on the
left
car on the left car on the left what am
I supposed to do about it what am I
supposed to do about
it get wrecked
br oh it's night time now oh why it
night time
[Music]
it turned it turned
dark no matter I play better in the
darkness
anyway car on the right clear on the
right
[Music]
all right man leader on the final lap
the leader on the final lap what lap is
[Music]
it am I not breaking soon
enough oh shortcut shortcut shortcut
shortcut oh
[Music]
I I messed up I tried to shortcut but
it oh
hey waa the song I'm Listening to
whatever this song is just told me to
keep an eye on the road Thank You song
[Applause]
okayy I'm locked in slow down slow down
slow down slow down slow down go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
[Applause]
Slow Down slow down this is a turn this
is a turn slow slow slow slow slow W the
B just blasted in my ear okay anyway go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
why am I 21st place when did that happen
can the NPCs start making mistakes
please
no wait why are there fireworks
[Music]
[Applause]
I will not finish last I will not finish
last I will not finish
L I didn't finish last the you could
bring the car back
oh wa we don't have to we don't have to
review the
the we don't have to review the Replay
for this one all right you know what I'm
going to do I'm going to do my locked in
pose which is I will can you still hear
me like this I will sit back on my chair
and pretend not
care can you still hear me like
this okay all place is L okay maybe I
can't lean don't
[Music]
can I leave now let me
leave let me
leave I don't want to see my stream let
me
[Music]
leave
okay we're going to try one more
time for this but I'm going to try to do
better
okay oh let's review P
Sensei what what what do I need
Improvement
on try taking no shortcuts okay I will
try
this this time I will try to take no
shortcuts that it I don't have to be in
first but no shortcut
no
shortcut
yeah
okay stay double F eyes on the road no
eyes on Pebbles excuse
me why why why are you guys
here not why do I why am I starting
behind
everyone I don't want to start behind
everyone light give it all you can
ah car on the left this is hard because
everybody here okay hold
on okay
[Music]
guys car on the left excuse me
okay no
shortcut how am I supposed to get ahead
if I start behind everybody
[Music]
ah you're in the
way
okay I will just have to get good huh
stay on the track stay on the
track
ah excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse
me I'm going excuse
me no shortcuts
ah no
shortcuts like that like that okay play
[Music]
clean now we go fast there's a turn
coming up
catch up catch
up get back here car on the right no no
[Music]
no hey there's a big gap between me six
Place car on the right no clear on the
right
[Music]
no oh hey turn sharp turn we go slow and
then we go fast now
[Music]
okay keep the speed here I it's a big
turn I can keep my
speed wait I'm sorry I did it I still
have a cheater I see
it I F K
you I I I I failed I failed I failed I
can't I can't I can't I can't I have to
I have to do it
properly okay let's try it
again my right
can't be taken
away let's try this again
no if I can get no cheating
then I will play multiplayer with you
guys stay in double
file no hitting wait am I want to hit
people is that like a thing that I
should or shouldn't do should I hit
people or not the question avoid hitting
no hitting no hit oh okay no
[Music]
hitting please don't oh absolutely not
okay let's say Mario Kart
[Applause]
but what about now they're they're all
in the way they're all in the way what
how do I they're all in the way they're
all they're all in the
[Music]
way everyone's in the way
car on the left clear on the left
they're
[Music]
all look for gaps
okay okay let's FOC on driving
good don't hit any
[Music]
but excuse me excuse me excuse me what
if they hit me though that's not fair
don't hit me
[Music]
a I think I break too late for that on
Excuse excuse me excuse me excuse me you
mother be you I beep you beep you beep
you beep you beep you beep you be be be
be excuse
[Music]
me no buom he bumped me first
like okay clear on the left
[Music]
yeah let's sue them I'll sue you if you
Bonk me I'll sue I'll sue you for all
your
[Music]
[Applause]
money oh the turning the turning is very
old turn
okay I'm still on the track though I've
stayed on the track that's
good there it turn coming up break
break
go don't lose speed we need
that slow down
here go through this carefully okay
now
go not bad too
slow over breing is bad
[Music]
too but the turns are to so tight power
on the right excuse me excuse me excuse
me excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse
me thank
you to the slow as bed don't look at
CH
fight hey hey no tappy no tappy no tap
happy I tap
you okay we're go
[Music]
fast no okay I won't touch him I won't
touch him like you said I won't I won't
touch him I won't touch I won't touch
him I W he touched me on the left clear
on the left we are halfway through not
over
yet dang
it this signs in my
[Music]
eyes
oh oh I I don't cheat I'm not I'm not a
cheater okay there we
go I did I didn't cheat there you happy
[Music]
hey I see you trying to pass me don't
you
[Music]
don't
hey
[Music]
hey he pass me car on the left clear on
the left
[Music]
H I guess the map's real important
huh let you no turns are coming
[Music]
out keep an eye on okay let's practice
reading m
at the same time as
driving okay look straight
go car on the right no oh sorry I forgot
about the no tapping thing oh I oh sorry
that's it's against my nature you see my
nature is violet oh I'm so
sorry I'm not cheating I'm going around
oh I'm so oh so something has happened I
don't know what has happened
[Music]
wa Focus drive good focus on Drive
[Applause]
good this is
a and this is a turn
this way oh okay I kind of
kept on the
[Music]
map play Big turn big turn big turn hey
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey that's hey hey what are you doing
hey hey why you pushing me don't push
why that's R final give it all you
can no that's illegal go to
jail ah I
died it's okay the race almost almost
over I will just play with my eyes
closed why don't things how
happening excuse me I'm playing with my
eyes closed I'm so
sorry
no I was doing so I was being
[Music]
consistent yellow flager head what
hiding
yellow flag
ahead
oh what happened to that
guy what happened to me what's happening
to
me
W that's not cheating that's
H okay this is a turn this is a turn
watch the map don't get
[Music]
flustered it sure is different when
there's other cars on the road
huh everything I knew to right out the
window
[Music]
nether has finished race the leader has
finished the
race
dang oh pretty fireworks at least I wish
those were for me
[Music]
oi oi nice turn
[Applause]
all right Che flag good job the best you
could I'll bring the car
[Music]
back racing is intense
okay can I not be put in the back of the
map this
time can I be put like where first place
is you can starting
position oh
[Laughter]
one okay let's start at one and let's
see how long I can
maintain one
four why
four stay in double
[Music]
file oh
well Bo is not
bad
not not cheating not
cheating good luck everybody let's have
a clean race
no
TI No
smacky
[Music]
we okay
ah okay keep going keep going keep going
keep going keep
going
[Music]
going a i
oh sorry I'm too
slow no
cheating no
T let's just try to keep up with the
people in the front
[Music]
okay keep up keep going keep up keep up
keep up keep up keep
up we knew now
[Music]
turn turn turn turn turn turn go
okay keep your
[Music]
place keep me place keep me
pleas H nice okay hey no passing why
that's rude how do you do that anyway
tell me how' you do
that
[Music]
ah how how do you go faster than the
person in front of
you why am I slower I'm going so
fast got on the right
[Music]
hey what a slip
stream excuse me excuse exuse me that's
Rong
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
ah
you ah
[Music]
what why am I in 24
a I was in
24 okay let's try
again I guess if I if I sword cut
wait hold on hold file
don't break while you turn the car
okay
one okay I start at
one and I'm going to make it
85 what this wait I what the slip
stream what's a slip stream by the way
is when a car behind you has no Air drag
to slow them down so they gain speed
because of less Air drag if you get
directly behind a car people
you
oh you drive behind the car oh
okay go behind another car went and
straight
okay don't break while turning just
don't accelerate but what if the break
is or what if the turn is really really
sharp break
earlier right before
turn hey no slip
streaming no slip scaming
[Music]
no slip
streaming no slip
streaming stop
that car on the left dang
it clear on the
left no slip
[Applause]
streaming oh I I I I oh I I'm sorry I'm
so sorry about that I I I'll I'll do
better next
[Music]
S I went back on the path though I
didn't do full shortcut I went back on
the
[Music]
path okay I have to break way sooner
that's my fault I have to break away so
break way
sooner mini map okay break way sooner
mini map break way sooner mini map
tech mini map break sooner on
turn green light give me green
[Music]
light don't accelerate on turns either
oh that was
[Music]
night well that was
night I'm going too fast here slow down
a bit
okay now
[Music]
go okay slow down here break sooner
break sooner break sooner
okay there's going to be a sharp turn
break
sooner I'm breaking too much but
whatever no slip
streaming okay we made the turn now we
made the
turn wa
[Music]
okay let's let's gently go here let's
gentle gentle dentle
okay don't pass
me I'll beat you up
[Music]
the turn was too much excuse me
no I going to slip stream you I will
coming back come back here I will
slipstream you come here come here come
here I'll get you I'll get you mark my
words come here come here come back hey
come here I'm on his
tail okay okay I'm getting closer I'm
getting closer to you I'm getting closer
there's a turn coming
[Music]
up I'm getting even closer to you bro
I'm keeping
up wait for
me
[Music]
my ah nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
come here come back come
back come
on
okay turn coming up
[Music]
he wait a second I'm catching up to you
I'm catching up to you slip
stream slip
stream fter slip of the race man good
job thanks
man get behind you get behind you
was so close come
back we are halfway through keep pushing
halfway through okay I'm keeping up with
that guy
it actually nice having first CU it's
kind
of
[Music]
okay focus
no SLI
stream car on the left clear on the left
yeah this is exhilarating
nice turn nice
[Music]
turn nice turn nice turn okay
okay good turn
car on the
left you mother beep beep and beep beep
you I was doing so well why' you do that
now I miss don't wait wait don't wait
wait wait focus focus focus focus focus
focus keep
focusing I lost my focus and
I
had car on the left clear on the
left car on the left clear on the
left what
those turns man that's what it'll get
you okay hold we're
holding excuse me excuse me excuse me
we're supposed supposed to go slow here
it's a turn you stupid you stupid on the
left you're stupid you're St stupid
you're
[Music]
stupid we're supposed to go slow here
too
[Music]
dumy okay the leader is on the final L
now give it all you can okay I give it
all I
can I'm on the final lap now too
[Music]
[Applause]
hey sharp turn
coming nice and
easy hey didn't lose that much that time
also sharp turn
coming no I'll end
you okay
[Music]
okay sharp turn here sharp turn here
watch
out watch out another sharp turn just go
just go just focus on the turn focus on
the turn focus on the turn then go
faster go faster go fast go fast then go
faster then go faster
okay ooh
bouncy big turn here big turn here start
two break start two
break start two break break turn break
turn break turn break turn break turn
turn turn turn turn go go go go go turn
break break turn go and keep turning and
keep breaking and go go and go go we big
turn and then go and then go and then go
and then go and then go
go excellent
job bring it back home safely
I'm
[Music]
B hey I'm made the
party we did also we didn't shortcut I
don't think did we shortcut I don't
think
so yeah my arms across h
did I did I do better this time also if
you're wondering I'm using a controller
I don't have a steering
[Music]
wheel nice prce we are so place
how do I play with you guys is is this
going to be really bad if I play with
you guys am I going to like be in super
super
last
um delete this quick join
is
that just click
join you wouldn't
why no do not quck doing it possible to
make a ru
open empty
server where is the server that says
people come in this room
these all look very
daunting oh yeah my pain go crazy
huh is this all
DP I think there's racing etiquette
too oh this is EU huh because it's 7
a.m. how do I create a room
can I make one
M let me hide screen just in case and
aha there's one server
that's zero drivers
and 45
ping can we invade This
Server is that is is that is
that okay I want to fire your server
real quick this
person oh it's
DLC
oh
man hold on
well I don't want to ra someone's
server if if uh play with EB or is she
playing
uh what what what's he
doing how you how you
multiplayer I wonder let me tag
something actually
I don't want to
impose let me check my
to my brain is a little slow cuz it's 7
[Music]
a.m. okay uh
uhuh okay for
[Music]
now for now oh where it go where the
game
go let me keep
P look let me let me actually go back to
practice
and practice those
turns I think that is my what's a career
move that is my weakness is
[Music]
turning ooh okay that that is bad if I
if
I okay so we got we got to not we got
to what we got a delay green light green
light don't do whatever I just did just
there small movement
[Music]
okay I'm doing this course because I
think this is the course for the race
that we're doing
today okay don't go too fast here
a don't go too fast here don't go too
fast here I'm going too fast look I'm
going too fast and then I went on the
grass that's bad okay restart
that don't go don't go to the
five too fast to breaks lightly okay no
[Music]
okay
wait don't
go top
break smooth turn tap
break smooth nice
okay and now go forward
please yes okay
nice stay on the
track there's a big sharp term coming
up I'm I'm over break now I think I'm a
little too slow we got to prevent that
time that was smooth but that was
slow all break is fine there okay break
then
turn okay break then
turn
ah break then turn break then turn break
then turn break then
turn
ah break then
[Music]
a oh
okay here's another turn coming up wait
then turn I'm going too fast again
though a the numbers got mad at me they
turned
red the numbers they got mad at me
oh okay they're not mad at me anymore I
got a second
chance break then turn break then
[Music]
turn okay there's a we there's a weave
here it's okay I survived it
I survived it I survived it
[Music]
not break that turn break that turn
now
throttle out of the turn you accelerate
out of the turn there's the things you
break now you turn
now you slightly throttle slightly
slightly slightly slightly slightly
go not
bad we made it I'm doing it
[Music]
oh I think I broke
too too
late but still made the turn no
cheating no cheating
nice and
smooth we okay smooth smooth that was
smooth that was
smooth that was smooth
okay now we
no how can I tell that I when I'm over
breaking
[Music]
when you're too slow
ooh
smooth smooth
[Music]
turn
oh maybe a little over break there but
that's a scary turn so it's
fine okay get back get back in the road
the numbers got mad at
me it got
mad a too much oh it got mad at me again
[Music]
oh it really wants me when when when the
things change color it I should listen
to it huh
[Music]
yeah okay listen to the
lines I will listen I will look at the
colors and
[Music]
listen do I have a dream car
uh that is a good question I haven't
really thought about cars too much cuz I
don't really drive so I don't really see
the the point of having a dream
car uh it' be cool to have a bbo mobile
though like a Bat Mobile but beo
[Music]
oh tight turn tight
turn now I just got to learn how to
drive while reading
chat wait turn coming up can't reat cuz
there is a turn okay now I
can I well I think I would drive a small
car cuz small people
so I would like to drive a small Bey
P H break then
[Music]
turn curent coming up watch
out nice and smooth now go
nice and smooth go go go go go go go go
go go go
go
[Music]
yeah the fastest La so far oh that was
my fastest lap so far
[Music]
[Applause]
whatow way
slow down okay now turn smooth
now throttle throttle throttle n
okay I getting used to
it I'm not in Japan stop gas why did KY
keep why is is ky gu sliding me to she's
she she's helping the meme grow dang
it ah I looked away
[Music]
well
okay now I am going to I Tad
Sensei how am I doing Tad
s you're actually doing well I'm proud
are you am I actually doing well or are
you just saying
that and
improving improving for real okay learn
social distance you need to learn how to
gas early oh you know what I'm going to
do I'm going to go back
to Quick race I'm going to start at like
position 10 and I'm going to my goal is
to is
to
um end
up above 10
yeah what's okay what's a half throttle
someone tell me what does that
mean what is it half the
bottle half hold the trigger
halfway not fully pressing it okay
yeah my throttle is on the right
trigger going double
file press it lightly okay I'm pressing
it
lightly I'm lightly
pressing oh they have no cision
[Music]
green light go go go go go go excuse me
car on the left left wow how did I do
that
[Music]
wow
I I cheating I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I'm a cheater I'm a cheater I'm
[Music]
sorry okay it's on half throttle now
half half throttle go
throttle car on the right
I saw
hey meanie look you made me cheat now
look what you
did look what you
did what
your okay no cheating no cheating no
cheating
oh sorry I'm a little slow right now but
I'll go faster I'll go faster right now
so don't don't you do it don't you do it
don't don't you do it don't don't do it
I will beat you up you
Mr yeah that's what I
thought okay eyes on the road
Dental turn half throttle here Dental
turn Dental turn half throttle half
throttle half throttle half throttle
Full Throttle Full Throttle oh that's
where the term Full Throttle comes from
[Music]
oh I understand now
okay I'm getting some
distance now it's time to close the
distance watch out
over this this one's difficult keep it
half throttle keep it half throttle
break a little bit half throttle half
throttle half throttle now Full
Throttle
okay wait for me I'm coming
I want to catch up to
you we slow down here and now we
go we start to slow down
[Music]
here there we
go I'm still not good at the really
really sharp turns but oh
hello
hello thank
you thank you for the
raain we're
[Music]
practicing practicing well let's have a
good race out there
today
okay hello yeah I'm practicing
[Music]
okay break and then turn and then turn
and then ah and then turn and then turn
and then turn and then go and then go
and then break and then turn and then
half throttle half throttle half
throttle Full Throttle okay I'm
remembering I'm remembering I'm learning
I'm learning things
we're we're keeping
consistent okay Full Throttle okay
there's a turn break turn turn smooth
smooth smooth smooth smooth smooth okay
[Music]
go okay another turn keep it
smooth half throttle maybe half throttle
keep it half keep it half make sure you
don't spin out all hope you break a
little bit and then you
go fall thr over yet halfway okay
halfway we just got to keep it
consistent I start at 10th place so if
[Music]
I I'm able to keep this consistent that
would be good
go he's a catching up don't you dare I
will I will I will
Bonk your nose I will Bonk you in the
nose it will hurt I swear you you do not
want to do
[Music]
that make some distance
make some distance make some distance
make some distance Slow Down slow down
oh I am over breaking
now but it's okay cuz I did not out of
balance that's not what I want okay make
some distance make some
distance Slow Down slow down I can't see
cuz it's sunny okay
ah okay half throttle half throttle half
throttle half throttle half throttle
Full Throttle now Full
Throttle lose them lose lose third place
lose third place just lose
[Music]
them keep the speed high keep the speed
High
what he hey you're mean you're meanie
you're mean you're a poopy head I hope
you would this poop on your wind
shield so you can't see your windshield
[Music]
hey you're going too fast this is a
slower
turn you're going to you're I'm going
too
fast go too fast go too
fast go speak
go okay turn coming up slow
[Music]
down nice nice nice
nice excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse me excuse me I will I
will I will
oh no
no no don't you do it don't you do it
I'm watching you I'm watching you very
closely we're supposed to go slow here
we're supposed to slow
down slow
down slow down leaders will final
after okay okay
[Music]
no pressure no pressure I feel no
pressure no pressure
no pressure no pressure no pressure stop
stop stop it stop I will I don't don't
do it don't do it I'm going
to I'm going to yeah that's what you get
that's what you get huh that's what you
get you dummy
[Music]
dummy yeah
gentle gently gently gently gently now
go go go go fter
[Music]
go turn big turn here big turn here big
turn here gentle gentle half throttle
gentle gently gentle don't let them
pressure you into going faster here cuz
it's a harsh turn now go now now go now
go now go fast now go Full Throttle go
we're almost there keep
going there's turn coming up though
so d
dentle dentle half throttle half
throttle half throttle half throttle
half full
throtle excellent job man P2 well
managed bring it back home saf
oh yay
second
place we went we went from 10 to two
that's really good right we went from 10
to
two and we kept second place that entire
time
so that's good
right yeah
haha
Improvement I I Che it a little bit but
at the beginning but hello
[Music]
hi hi
Herb how is racing
going oh it's okay it's okay that I I
don't see Discord messages sometime too
but
but sorry my mind empty cuz it's like 7
a.m.
no thank you so much for the redir I
hope we have fun yeah no pressure no
pressure
oh yeah let's watch the replay how do I
do
that ha there's
me what
how do you make it
[Music]
go that's that's
be wait you have to look at this this
this part right here when it's just
beginning how did I do that did you see
at the beginning how I did that
look look ready watch it's starting it's
starting how did I do
that I overtook like so many
[Music]
people you like my car it's pretty
oh look at
[Music]
that the Z
it's got
[Music]
be dad I want to drive just like people
when I go
wa wait wa wait wait
wa I'm not a
[Music]
teeter look look it's me it's me on the
side of the car look it's me and then
there's a there's a there's a
moai and there's also my
signature and 818 cuz
be yeah 818 is B I couldn't do B but 818
stands for
[Music]
people it only fit three numbers
yeah look it's my face on the side of
the is this what it's like to have
AAA
car that's so
cute that's me
[Music]
you guys think I have a
shot at at the race
[Music]
today
yes a thank you
top three
possible okay I was going to go to sleep
but then you said that so now I feel
like I have
to keep prac
maybe I should do a new
map
and just in case they throw something
weird and see if I can adapt to a new
map I'm not looking
ah okay it
oh
he let's try it this one looks kind of
crazy
yeah I'm 10 again I don't know this
track at
[Music]
all oh wait wait oh we got to stay in
line for
I stay in
line it hasn't started
yet now we
go overtake overtake okay there's a turn
coming up clear on the right watch out
overtake overtake overtake overtake
don't touch overtake overtake don't
touch overtake clear on the
left wa
[Music]
oh what is this what is this that's a
sharp turn
sorry
[Music]
oh okay sharp turn coming
up half throttle Full Throttle now
where're in third let's try to keep
third Full Throttle
[Music]
okay this is good we're adapting to new
map look at the mini
map so down half throttle Full Throttle
slow down half throttle half throttle
half oh this one's
sure I
see
[Music]
wow it's okay we can overtake we got to
what was was it what was the word called
again
streaming we got
streaming
um
s it's okay I'm like where I was at
before hey hey that's rude why' you do
that whatever
[Music]
is the Mushroom boo it's not we don't
have mushrooms
here you know Mario actually doesn't
like
mushrooms someone told me that
[Music]
yeah from the movie or
something look I'm going fast I'm going
fast I'm going
throttle watch out sharp turn
nice watch out sharp turn half throttle
half throttle
oh that's very sharp okay
[Music]
job
tur I'm still in third though that's
pretty good no no slip
[Music]
streaming the sun is in my
eyes stop no the sun's in my eyes guys
you you and me I'm going to slip stream
you I'm right on your
[Music]
butt oh
know it's fine it's fine let's shake it
off no Panic we just got to drive good
[Music]
catch up we can catch
up
okay we can catch up I believe
[Music]
maybe you're halfway through not over
yet halfway thinkk you wased my
ear oh okay I made that turn though that
was
[Music]
nice I wonder if the people in and your
ear has to have a nice voice or else it
would get kind of you know Annoying to
hear like uh it would agitate the driver
maybe if the noise if the voice was very
harsh or very
rude but maybe that's a good thing maybe
if it agitates the driver you'll get
faster out of Spike so you get faster so
you don't have to hear the voice in your
ear
anymore like if the voice was too
relaxing in your ear then you're going
to like drive not as fast because you're
like oh it's so soothing I'm
[Music]
sleepy half throttle half throttle half
throttle Full Throttle okay I'm doing
good with these
turn I have a jab did I've adapted to
this new
[Music]
course nice
nice keep going you will you shall not
pass you shall not
pass no he
passed no you shall not pass
is
it these these are very
sharp I can catch up to that guy
maybe
possible man you got to you got to start
breaking like way early for these sharp
turns
[Music]
okay sharp turn coming up
pleas no why I was breaking CU we had to
slow down
you why all right man the leader is on
the final lab give me the final
push
[Music]
what what one time I break early and he
passes
me I'm losing it hey
hey car on the right clear on the
right yeah it's clear on the
[Music]
right car on the left clear on the left
wow hey you hey hey
[Music]
hey car on the left I on the left I've
succumbed to my rage my need for
violence it overtook me I'm sorry I'm
sorry I failed you guys I failed you my
instincts took
[Music]
over ah a that is too that that one that
one
sucks oh
no
11 car on the left clear on the
left okay nine
okay I just need to start I need to end
above NE has finished the race 10 I need
to I need to end above 10 that's all I
need to
do oh
oh okay
[Music]
all right mate Grace is over good job
did the best you could take it easy in
Name Lab I got above 10 that one was a
really hard map though
sorry that was a really hard map
though I can't sleep until I make top
three so it's not over yet I should have
just ended when I got top three the
other time but now we
were I got I got to make top three let's
do a different
[Music]
map Bell jump this one looks crazy too
Manza
[Music]
mon this
one
okay
M okay I'm doing M you guys like M huh
[Music]
everyone's
favorite
mon okay stay in the line
first ah oh I want to bump you watch
out wait watch out I'm going to bump
you wait we're almost it's almost go
time it's almost time to go it's almost
time to go it's almost time to
go it's time to wait he always time to
go me excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse
excuse me excuse me excuse
me where am I
going why am I 10th place now what what
happened what happened what
[Music]
huh
oh now you first
[Music]
oh oh
all right let's
let's let's try to maintain this let's
maintain wo it's
fast wait there's a turn coming
[Music]
up we got to smooth it out okay
smooth big turn coming up big turn slow
down okay slow down okay turn half
throttle half throttle half throttle
half throttle half throttle half
throttle Half Full Throttle
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is
weird Okay we made it though we made it
we made
[Music]
it we made the funky turn now we go fast
again o I like this map it's fast also
my finger hurts from gripping so hard on
the controller
[Music]
vice grip yeah I got that
claw once I stop playing I'm going to be
stuck in that claw
[Music]
[Laughter]
position half throttle half throttle
half throttle half throttle half
throttle half throttle half throttle
half throttle half half half half half
half half full
throttle go don't let him catch up to
you don't let him catch up to you don't
let him pass
[Music]
you hey
hey car on the right on the right no you
stupid okay I will get you I will I will
I will come back for you mark my words
mark my words I will I will slip stream
you I'm coming for that God show me that
butt oh I'm so sorry we've messed up
we've messed up the things have happened
it's wi it's wide it's white it's white
it's white it's fine it's right it's
fine it's right we just keep keep going
we
[Music]
uh oh okay yeah sure
we are at halfway mark halfway uh can we
end it now so I can win I've done so
much damage
[Music]
already okay gentle gentle gentle gently
gentle gentle gentle go go go go go go
go go go go
okay
okay Full
Throttle ease up ease up ease up
break slowly go back to full throttle
okay back to full throttle very nice
[Music]
okay it's turning night time that's
getting dangerous okay there's the weird
turn coming up there's the weird turn
it's coming
up
oh that's so
weird oh I wonder what happened on the
left of me like someone get into an
accident or something
[Music]
ah this part this part sucks oh don't
catch up to me don't catch up to me I
will take you out like I took out that
last guy you do not want to mess with me
I am not afraid to to bring out my
violence I'm doing so good right now
please go away go away don't mess with
me don't mess with me I'll mess with you
I'll mess you
up it's night time now no one will see
my act of
violence I'll blame it on a
[Music]
deer easy easy easy easy easy EAS it EAS
into it EAS into it EAS into it easy
into it now
[Music]
[Applause]
go okay
[Music]
easy very nice very nice turn very nice
turn very nice turn okay go faster go
faster go faster very nice turn keep
turning okay Full Throttle
yes okay weird thing coming up weird
thing weird thing weird thing Slow Down
slow down for weird thing slow down for
weird thing weird thing is weird it is
so weird it's getting weird okay now go
now
go nice job
[Music]
[Applause]
okay it's going to get weird again it's
going to get weird again it's going to
get weird again slow down easy easy oh
my gosh I didn't mess up that
[Music]
time oh my gosh I'm doing
it oh my gosh look at me
[Music]
go easy easy easy gentle gentle gentle
gentle gentle gentle gentle go go don't
let him catch you don't let him catch
you okay big turn coming up big turn
ease off
acceleration start to slow down slide to
slow down SL to slow down slow down okay
okay Full Throttle
[Music]
right final the leader keep it together
keep it together keep it together St so
[Music]
far it's right it's right don't worry
don't worry about don't worry about
don't worry about it don't worry about
it it's fine it's fine don't worry about
it don't worry don't mind don't mind
don't mind don't wor don't don't think
about
[Applause]
[Music]
it it's fine it's fine don't think about
it don't think don't think don't think
just go don't think just J don't think
just go just go just go just go just go
don't think don't think don't think just
go just go don't think don't think we're
not thinking we're not thinking about
anything go go go go go go go yep yep
yep yep okay yep yep yep yep okay okay
yep okay bye okay
[Music]
go okay turn coming up
slowly EAS into it easy easy half half
throttle half half half throttle half
throttle half throttle Full Throttle
Full Throttle now go go go go go go go
go go go go faster we're almost at the
end we're almost at the end this is the
final final stretch final stretch is up
on the throttle now and then start to
break slowly slowly break and then easy
turn easy turn easy easy easy into it
easy into it easy into it go go now go
keep going keep going go faster here it
is here's the end here's the end here's
the end w w
back
yay I
won I
W first place let's
go just a little aent along the way but
look at me look I'm jumping for
joy I am number
one hey for my first round of that map
that was pretty good okay I'm adapting
to Maps I haven't played before pretty
well okay right replay please okay we
can that was that was my last race
anyway
hey my finger
my
finger it's so it's
so it's
a
[Music]
finger it's num it's a little numb
actually it's a little it's a little
numb cuz I was ripping it so hard
[Music]
oh sorry we're not seeing though we're
not seeing this can I save
this can I save this I going to play one
round with
ERB how do I save we oh save
replay okay hold on I let to save replay
and then I'm going to go into the Hall
life
[Music]
server okay replay
save okay and then I'm going to
quit I saved the
rep uh and then and I'm going to
multiplayer server
list um hold on I got to find
the
info you can't see my screen right no
[Music]
we're going to play One race again okay
and go
like how do I hide this so you don't see
the server
H yeah I really wait till the race
start
[Music]
hello hey
no I he call me
Senai I am
technically oh she call me
[Laughter]
adorable wait how come they can't hear
you uh oh hi
now hello
what speaking one two one two one two
one okay now call me adorable Senpai
again cuz I didn't hear
it C
what adorable Senpai My adorable Senpai
kek beu yay okay I hey we're in I put
the skin on the wrap I got the wrap oh I
put the wrap on
too oh got click Drive oh okay okay I
think it okay I think I can show the
thing now okay yeah yeah yeah you can
show it now once you're
[Music]
in oh it starts Let's Race we look so
cool we do wow your car looks cool too
what kind of car do you have I have a
Aston
Martin what's that oh where's
go uh it's a uh in the in the realm of
Earth it is a a British car a British
car oh
yeah oh is that why they gave it to
you I guess so cuz great Exodia is real
real similar oh
gosh how was
practicing that's all right yeah I was I
was trying not to Swerve off the road
mostly this game is a little
difficult it's fun though yeah it's fun
I'm I'm interested to see what it's like
for a wheel oh yeah I'm using a what you
using uh controller but I'm hoping some
point uh that uh I get a a
delivery oh it's coming before the Big
Race I hope I it comes in CR yeah me too
it' be so
cool turning is hard man yeah I wonder
if it varies from car to car with that
oh yeah I wonder too
too I keep forgetting to to break then
turn break then
turn I'll eventually catch up one day
you got
this what modes have you tried have you
just been have you done it with like
NPCs
yet yeah with the buts yeah I went in
with Bots and I went in with real people
oh you went with real people how
that a lot of
[Laughter]
crashes I wasn't paying attention I'm
paying attention yeah you look you look
off for like one moment and you're done
you're done yeah you
CED don't look away don't look
way yeah I got a
Ferrari a Ferrari I'm Italian car right
is Italian it's Italian right I think so
yeah that's
cool I think that's like one of my my
dad's favorites oh really
yeah although I think that most people
go too when they say a favorite
car
yeah what I don't really I don't really
know too much about cars but I did like
uh there was a TV show called like Top
Gear I
enjoyed yeah is it about racing it's
about cars but I think the even though I
didn't really pay attention to like the
type of cars and all that I think I
enjoyed watching it cuz of The Passion
of the the guys hosting it for the
cars and it was enjoyable they were
funny oh it's a famous British sh Val
car oh yeah
yes yes
[Music]
yes although I also I like I like Cars
the movie Lightning M Lightning
McQueen
k
k oh I made a mistake I cheated oh I
cheated it's fine you're way your way
ahead I I got
distracted I got distracted
there was I forget what I watched but I
watched a documentary a long time ago
about a guy who started off
playing racing video games but then
ended up becoming an actual like god
tier racer and I thought that was really
cool oh that is
cool oh I'm cheating so
much I wouldn't mind I I'd like to see
actual
actual actual Racers like try this they
probably have done that somewhere like
actual race drivers like playing these
games I do wonder if they're if they're
any good like they are IRL or IRL in
like in the car
car I oh I was I you can catch up now
you can catch how do you reverse how do
you reverse I'm stuck uh you click like
X I think or something to change the to
R reverse where the gears are it's one
of the extra buttons If I
recall it's not why uh cuz that changes
your
POV let me let me have a look let me P
let me break yeah so it's X and you keep
going X to R and then you reverse X to R
yeah yeah yeah so click X well I don't
know what kind of controller do you have
I'm using Xbox yes controll e um the the
the left button oh square square yeah
yeah yeah so click square and it should
have an R bottom right and that's
reverse and then you you go
back where is set that's how it is for
me where your square
is and then I click it twice and it goes
to R reverse where's the R
button uh so if you look down the bottom
right you see it will show when your
gear your gears go up and down it should
have an R when you when you click the
button and then you can
reverse unless you just see see me it's
behind me
there you go yeah you're changing hey
okay okay neutral once you once you see
an R
yeah halfway mark still long way to go
oh okay I figed it out mm yay and then
youch no worries oh how oh you got to
switch back
oh you got to
switch
okay oh my wheel is broken huh oh you
got to go in the pit
then fix it up pit please pit
help is this my
pit uh you drive into it yeah there you
go yeah
yeah friend there should be a a
highlight where you you park
[Music]
a
oh and then once you you stop the guys
should walk over and and fix you up
change my
ti
please oh you not are you not on the
Highlight oh I see them oh hi my
friend the guys are waiting for you a my
friend okay
help oh they're doing it they're doing
it
yeah nice
swim wow there thing I learned how to
reverse before the actual race
huh yeah it's a good thing that trash
it's a good thing because
yeah now you know just in case I have a
feeling uh I don't know we might get
like we might Ram into each other so
it's good to
know there's going to be so many cars on
the
road it's going to be fun I'm excited
yeah it's going to be
fun my controls are locked for a minute
yeah yeah you got a uh little bit of you
got a bit of a weight and then you can
go wow it's part of having to go into
the pit they're just standing there
they're not even doing
[Laughter]
anything they're just
chilling is it is down in
there enjoying enjoying the enjoying the
Vibes just looking at your car they're
like wow nice car
so Kawai wait what's your what's your uh
title it's Herby fully loaded oh cute is
that is that uh it's that movie right
yeah Herby
Herby yeah it's about a car called Herby
and and and he's a beetle I think it's a
beetle car never seen
it yeah it's quite an old movie but they
had they had
a semi- recent one not semi- recent but
there was one with Lindsay Lohan in it I
think as well it said I'm just qualified
for speeding in the pit
lean oh yeah that's a that's a good
point to bring up yeah if you speed in
the pit Lane you get disqualified
o oh no oh no I didn't know that one now
I know so yeah there's a there's a lot
of
rules uh yeah yeah there's a lot of
rules including that one W well how how
are you doing on your
side I I'm I hope I'll finish so we can
get in a new game so you don't you're
you're done with the disqualification
stuff ah go go can I
spectate uh I don't know I think you got
to just wait there until I'm going to
cheat so I
finish I'm
disqualified you are naughty
a I guess you I guess it's another thing
is good to know
now rather than when we're in the game
yeah in the race race
yeah you know how to
drive no I was uh so I I learned uh I
had some lessons but then I ran out of
money it's
expensive yeah
ran out of D I was
like I need to I need to
save you know what I do want to learn
again
someday do you know you want to know why
I don't know why because
um when Mom saki was like okay let's
teach driving he would he would teach at
like really early in the morning and and
rocki would wake up early enough to go
but I would not so I never I never took
the lessons with Mom scky because I
would always sleep through it so I never
learn how to
drop did you have a cuz I know some
schools in like uh in FIA where G is
from they sometimes have like driving
lessons with within school like I've
seen it in like TV shows and stuff did
you have that I I think they they did
but I never had them yeah only only
driving lesson with Mom
said
disqualified but yeah I mean I woke up a
few times to be to wake up early enough
but also let me let me hide this it's
okay you can you can learn to drive at
any age and any
time and also if you have good public
transport then it's it's
okay ooh the session has ended how do we
H yeah how do we oh oh there we go good
thing I drive okay drive and then I so
we're on the free practice bit now
[Music]
okay
um uh but yeah I would like to learn
again
someday but like the good thing about
gray Exodia is that has like good public
transport depending where you
are depending where you are but on the
left on the left well I I am moving to
Japan quite soon and Japan has great
public I'm never going to need to
drive yeah yeah that's very true yeah
the trains uh they're they're never late
[Music]
s train
and then there's taxis and stuff yeah
tax are nice
too very clean that's why I noticed in
the Far East when I took a taxi I was
like ooh oh clean very nice
yeah and even the the driver like was
you know he had his gloves on and
dressed up and I was like yeah they're
so nice too yeah not
polite yeah I love uh like the unifor in
Japan especially the train uniforms oh
yeah I love how Japan has uniforms for
everything like even even like the you
know the fast food workers have like
really cute uniform so it's like I would
mind if I work there because they have
cute
drip yeah yeah it's nice yeah I always
look at it I'm like wow wow I if I yeah
if I I'm the same if I like worked there
I would I would be very happy with the
uniform
yeah that's what America does cute
uniforms to make the workers feel
better if you look good it does it does
make you it does make you feel good yeah
if if you have a a nice out
[Music]
go okay
I remember one of my past missions I had
to dress up as a doll that was a fun
uniform oh a
doll yeah so it was like a it was like a
cute little red dress with an apron
cute yeah and um but the only thing was
like which was a bit icky was like they
gave us um well it gave me used tights
used white tights and I was like
yeah they wash
them didn't wash them e
yeah that's one of those things where
like got to do what I got to
do oh Drive okay oh why did they do
um 20
seconds you brother
yeah some
J yeah it was on the the first day they
were like oh here and then his uh we
don't know whether this is washed look
[Music]
washed e e brother
ew at least the dress was new
last yeah I know I mean that I mean that
day I made sure to bring bring back the
the tis and
get washed I
like it's got to do the job but
you're I want to hit
you I want to hit you
though this is good practice this good
practice this is good practice for for
when the actual thing happens you know
yep good practice good
practice practice for the chaos
later that is going to be chaos
violin
violin I am wondering since there the
the server is practicing this map
W what the
heck thanks for helping me turn oh
you're
[Laughter]
welcome it's fine I've been naughty so
you're still first my controls are wony
now my break is not breaking properly
what
haveen this is a Mario Kart
oh I guess that's the that's part of it
like I I'm still second because I've
I've
beenal it keeps making me my car is
stuck turning left now or
right oh yeah
my my steering has been
compromised oh
God get
you this turned into bamper cars oh no
return to pit for
repairs oh God I only turned right no
see not so easy is
it no especially when I need turn left
it's so hard to turn
[Music]
left my thing won't
turn I can turn this way no I can't
no this way
[Applause]
yes oh wait this is way oh this is a pit
okay we both need a pit stop I think
going to slow down I'm going to wait
Slow Down slow down slow down slow down
we got we got a speed limit
here I'm not going to get dis I want to
get
disqualified I keep having to click left
cuz I keep turning
right
gosh oh dear oh
oh gosh oh God you just appeared in
front of
me fix me up boys please please
fix oh
no thank
you um oh there we go oh now my controls
are lost for two
minutes you get to go a few seconds
before me though
wow that was
exciting we're going we're going to do
that to other people not each other when
the actual race happens right oh yeah
yeah yeah we got
to yeah we we yeah we strats beforehand
our Strat is uh yeah yeah yeah I like
that Strat yeah let's not bump into each
other we bump into other people and
exactly yeah they don't know how to
reverse that's what we count that they
don't know how to reverse they haven't
experienced it
yet they've been too careful
yeah accomplices yeah have you been
shifting gears or H do does it do it
manually manually for
you uh yeah does it it does it
automatically but um I do change it
sometimes when um when I when I want to
go faster um what gears
for um it's like
so uh have you rode a bike before yeah
with gears so yeah when you're on like
gear one it'll be like a lot harder to
Pedal right so you go slower so imagine
it like that and then when you're on
like the fifth or sixth gear it becomes
a lot
easier oh so it goes it's like looser so
it goes faster yeah
[Music]
oh that's a good way of explaining it
right chat right yeah what I nearly went
into
you don't turn my me wait how' you can
go how' you how are you able to go I
don't know I guess I guess you just
needed more repairs than me you need a
penalty more than me you hurt my
[Laughter]
like okay don't go above
50 in the pit don't go B 50 don't go B
50 don't get
disqualify you you'll probably catch up
to me got to face the
[Music]
car go go go go go go go go I will catch
up if I
can Ketchup
we are halfway through keep
pushing round I
go oh my God another has joined the race
another
yeah
oh I don't know if she's in in yet but
I'm
guessing be able to
join another contender another battle a
new Challenger
approaches oh my God a battle what the
freak from all these rules though it's
like um racing seems very mannered
because of the whole like oh car left
clear you know yeah you're not appar
you're not supposed to Ram into
people I don't know what you're talking
about
well will every glch glitches so lag
ping oh oh ping isue oh yes ping D ping
issue very
much that's what happened I just didn't
see you you're just a
beard yeah like you know how sometimes
it's easier just to go through the track
to do a shortcut apparently that's also
illegal yeah you get like seconds off
your time and stuff
it's definitely uh I think it probably
pays off to be not go off the road and
be good and
yeah not Mario Kart not Mario we have to
hold back mother the Mario
Kart uh I there a VR version as well
that's that sounds yeah that seems fun I
have to set up my in
again M yeah I'm up for trying that if
you want to someday oh yeah VR
ring
yeah Happ be Hing
fun I couldn't do it for too long so I
might get motion sickness but oh yeah me
too sounds it sounds fun R I am very to
VR motion sickness especially if it's
like
moving like beat saer I can do for hours
cuz you're standing in the same place
but like if you're like yeah playing a
motion game then the motion sickness
will
it I still need to have a go at the sa I
it's like
really really good exercise I'm cheating
I'm
sorry oh my
God I
believe
ma'am I pull over pull over the police
you'll never can it's me
[Music]
Justice I will catch you I'm not going
back to baby
jail
the car on the
left oh
[Laughter]
hi this is this is exactly how it's stop
I'm the police now stop this
instant I don't believe you I want you
to pull
over I've worked in Hollow Santos as a
cop okay
yeah let me see your
life Mom I don't think you're real
police H Santos I don't think that's
real hey you're a you're a fake cop
[Music]
I got vs right here I have I have full
vods of my experience as working as Poli
ma'am that is a Chuck-E-Cheese
picture that is a a a Legoland
license uh that's a Lego L Car license
ma'am my quad boot
no oh my God supposed to drive off the
road I'm not trying
to I I don't want to drive on the road
with the brakes not the T well my car is
equally as damaged because I ran into
your car so I also playing
handicap why is you I wonder I don't
know I don't know what
happened it's very strange h
weird got keep help for the those uh
those crazy drivers on there know very
dangerous you know yeah oh gosh I am I
am excited for the chaos I'm like yeah
me too intrigued yeah like I know I'm
playing well but that's going to get
thrown off all the windows when you add
in the factor of the other girls yeah
yeah exactly wait I'm playing I'm
playing well in practi practice and like
with the NPCs but like they don't
understand the layout level of chaos
that
is
life
yeah this turn is
the and then me too like I I'm like I'm
going to play by the rules I'm not going
to smack everybody but then when I see
somebody out there like full m I'm going
to be like violence
out
myself hey well done
hey hello oh guys
hello I was giving you a
hug with my
car okay well this is a good stopping
point for me cuz it's 900 a.m. and I
should probably go to sleep cuz I
haven't yet oh gosh yeah yeah get enough
sleep before the for days but thank you
for racing with
me yeah I'm sorry I know it's too late
no it's okay I I this is a gorilla
stream I was just like oh I was just
like uh
[Music]
I I'm awake I got to practice might as
well stream so oh
right it was not oh car looks cool
oh yeah yeah oh gosh it's going to be so
cool seeing all the all the different
cars on the road together with the the
paint jobs ah it's so
exciting all right I'll leave you be to
end your stream goodbye pees goodbye
people no worries anytime oh my God
kiaha just rammed into me all right byee
[Music]
okay
hi how is
the hold on let me exit the
game the how is he random
random coolab
oh it was fun sorry I'm
like I'm
um it's sleep time for me
but let me read super chat before I
go cuz I have a little bit of
time
and I hope you
enjoyed the random stream today and I
hope you also for those of you who
usually don't get cat people enjoy the
random people
me save ESS for another
stream I gu I could but I can also wind
down I'm not like that sleepy
now I got answer the
okay
it's morning good
morning actually playing this um
reminded me of
when I was
younger
and
uh dad SEI doesn't play many video games
but there was this one time where like
we got a random racing game and I wasn't
really into it so I let Dad SEI try and
then he would just play
it all day for like a week
yeah I don't remember what game it
was but
yeah Dad SEI has that grind personality
as well he doesn't play many video games
but when he
does he'll grind it for a week
straight and then I don't get a turn
playing
yeah was it gr I don't remember what
game was
Robert P thank you for the super rock
rock b as a member of I'm at work
literally right now so here's my tax
Club here my tax is race will bab also
raming speeded anyone in the
way I think I got a good shot at
it um again like I said when you add the
variables of the rest of the I members
and people start smacking each other and
Chaos happens uh no guarantees where
everyone will end up if I can escape the
initial chaos then I think I'll be
okay well but who knows what's going to
happen at that at that
beginning chaos
chaos yeah if I if I can like get first
and make a lot of distance between me
and
people I think that would be good
uh yay thank you for super Rock Box she
got the zoomy so she can't sleep good
luck with the race later here's to
minimal cost thank thank you well I was
going to practice tonight anyway so I
was like H might as well stream it cuz I
wanted to at least practice and get used
to the controls of the game and I didn't
really have any other time to do it
other than tonight now so I was like ah
okay might as well stream it maybe some
people are awake and would enjoy that
did you enjoy it I hope you enjoyed it
bonus B stream who knows when peopleo
will appear who
knows uh AK thank you for the super Rock
ro oh boy can't wait to sleep at 5:30
a.m. oh what's this a Twitter
notification oh I guess I'll stay up
anything for you be I'm sorry my bad
go you guys can go to sleep go to work
after or if any of you are at work right
now and you're working in the morning I
hope I helped well we we planned a
collab to stream this game in the
morning anyway so I'm just doing as
scheduled I
suppose a buy thank you for the super
rock rock so additional funds pay for
insurance thank thank you rock rock what
me L thank you for the super rock rock
here's my contribution to your car
insurance what's what do you need car
insurance
for why is everyone giving me car
money accidents what happens what
happens when you have car insurance does
it did you you get a new car from the
insurance P for damage and injuries ah
it's illegal if you don't what you're
forced to get car insurance isn't that a
scam you if you have a car you have to
get car insurance wow that's why you
even have a
car I even have a car
man it's a good idea anyway but what if
you're like super safe and then you
never have an act
all here's the question if if if you get
into a car accident and it's not your
fault and someone else B your car do you
still need the car insurance to pay your
car or is the person who's responsible
for your car paying for the car stuff
pents you can sue them your insurance
sues the other insurance
oh their insurance P
A Man car insurance scams are really
scary uh I keep seeing like random
videos of like people just like walking
in front of a car and then
going ow you hit me ow
ow or like a car like stopping real fast
so but the car behind them didn't hit
them but then the car in front of them
backed up to them and it's like oh you
hit me that's
scary insurance fraud yeah that's that's
terrifying always have a dash cam yeah I
always have a camera nowadays I
guess is is the thing
always have always have a dash count
yeah which is why I don't want a car too
much I got to get a dash camera I got to
get uh insurance I got to not listen to
my intrusive thoughts that make me want
to hit people or other cars yeah so I I
think it's safer for me to not have to
not have a car
and a booster seat I don't need a
booster seat again mom SE is shorter
than me she drives perfectly fine
okay I don't think she needs a booster
SE well she does like there she does put
a pillow um on her
seat maybe uh
not a blue it's a
pillow h of course thank you for the
super rock rock J thank you for the
super Rock Ro why are you all
awake I see all these names in my Super
Chat and how are you guys all still here
well good
morning if you're here we're here well
thank
you oh a gorilla stream have F
practicing let them know where oi can
drift can you can we even drift in this
game
um also 4 hours went by really fast huh
uh black Ace thank you foot you could
technically camp but the cars aren't
built for it okay so no drifting I don't
have to worry about
that black a think for the super rock
rock despite being at work I'll be
listening on your racing practice you
can do B also the 8180 the BBU foru is
cute B zooming I'm the
Zoomer thanks stuff I'm the
Zoomer oh thank you super rock rock so R
to stream from 9:30 p.m. in Japan
outside of Cl good luck with the race
thank you rock rock
oh yeah did you guys uh see
my what the the Avent um voice drama do
you guys get to listen to it yet the P
Mo
Rose yes you like it it's pretty long
but I hope you enjoyed it I'm very
proud the
the the singing part that was me at the
end the end singing was narissa but but
the the singing throughout the the story
that was
me
oh sorry I keep reading chat and then
getting distracted um but yeah I worked
hard on the I was really nervous cuz
they were they were like you think you
can do a little bit of opera singing and
I was like oh I don't feel very
confident but I will try cuz I'm always
like okay yeah I'll try anything
um so I tried my
best uh but anyway what was I going to
say
one uh we're playing Sonic on Friday I
got the okay for that so we're playing
Sonic on on Friday which is tomorrow uh
Sonic X Shadows or
whatever Generations we're playing Sonic
and um I'm going to try to see if I can
get the Monster
Hunter perms for the beta because I
really want to play
it
um so we'll see if I can get the perms
for
that cuz yeah
we'll
[Music]
see weon are you thinking well I'm going
to go with charge blade first because
charge blade is the funnest weapon for
me but I'm also interested in long sword
I want I'm interested in dual blades cuz
it'ser very
spin yeah but I probably will be charge
blade
main but as a as
a x dual blade main I'm interested in
what the dual blades got and then
obviously long sword Katana chuny beu
needs to know
what that's all about
too
St oh in glaive oh yeah insect glaive
too I like insect glaive because of the
Wii it's just like really annoying to
get the
bug uh the bug sap the bug juice it's
always so annoying to like you have to
set up to get that first it's really fun
to play because of the
wee wee but the bug maintenance is a
little bit tedious to
me but yeah let's see we'll play the
beta hopefully I can stream
it uh de thank you for the super Rock Ro
thanks for the gorilla stream once in a
while I don't need to drink energy T to
keep my eyes awake like in a morning
it's night time here
ha St PE friends hope you have a had a
nice catching not having to catch B boo
super
early you JP bro thanks for always
catching b booo a little early I hope
you enjoyed this treat of nighttime
peopleo before you go to bed or
something M thank you for super rock
rock my son thank you for the super rock
rock it's time for running in the '90s
in the Night of Fire your opponents will
only see the d Vu of B's ride the Zumer
lead us to see the top Forever Young
bble
nice thank thank you Ro
I I understand the
references why I thinkk you for a super
rock rock people in order to maximize
your speed in a turn slow down until
your arrows are green then floor it
again that's what I was doing I was
doing that I just got a Time the slowing
down earlier I needed I need to time the
slowing down at the right time so I can
still have speed but go through the turn
good goodly yeah
you learn well thank you AK thank you
for a super rock rock that is some
impecable driving skills B you drive
just like Max vers steppen who is the
master of the course I can hear the
theme
now be stepping also what is sleep I
don't know I should probably go to sleep
though like not
so thank you for super rock rock hi B
these are my work hours please don't
tell my boss hey boss Joe is watching B
hi I am B and you should watch me boss
boss put me put me on the big screen
boss boss hey hey if you put me on the
big screen it will maximize productiv
ity by
150% so you should probably uh just put
me on the screen for your entire office
it will boost office morale and
productivity at the same time so just do
it boss just do
it not a scam also your gacha luck will
increase by 50% as well thanks boss
also stream PR
no uh epic M thank you for the super
rock rock hyper State thank you for the
super rock rock uh drunk pillis thank
you for the super rock rock wasn't
expecting to see Wild Rock streaming
when I opened up YouTube in the comp
room during my after hour search day v v
v I hope we're doing well and not
throwing grenades at people rock rock
all right thank you for the super rock
rock single thank you for a super rock
rock J me thank you for the super rock
rock AKB thank you for the super rock
rock um B during the race you need to
make sure your blinker
fluid huh blinker fluid is count at a
high level when you're racing you have
to make sure that the Cal shaft pistons
and ECU are spinning at 1,000
RPM
huh what's a what's a blinker
fluid what's the what's the
ECU
huh huh
for your blanket it's a card joke I
don't know car jokes I don't know
cars blink or fluid I don't know
mechanic what's RPM
mean Val viatorian thank you for the
super rock rock if this is the only
track you will complete then I suggest
you keep practicing this track
Silverstone is already good track for
learning anyway you're doing very great
I was doing good at adapting to the new
tracks I was trying out so I think I
think I'm good revolutions per minute
uh
oh buddy thank you for the super rock
rock people streaming at JP Nikki prime
time
already no
I'm
not you got used to streaming in Japan
so fast a minut to I'm not in Japan is 9
a.
a a ky say well don't believe Kyla
oh wait it's only 9 what time is in
Japan when I start only 9900 p.m. does
this mean I can like stream at my normal
time and stream at JP Prime Time like
can I stream both times cuz it's like
cuz it's like not that late in can I
like stream both can I stream like twice
a
day time to BL
just kidding my usual B time slot will
always take
priority uh well roran thank you for
super rock rock just learn to remember
the breaking point point and controlling
your throttle when cornering first those
are the most important Bas got it oh
yeah and also try not to bump other cars
but what if people try to bump into
me H AKB thank for super rock rock rock
right nice ramming be will continue that
in 12 hours you'll be guaranteed first
place later remember what CH hick did to
get the first place that he earned who's
chck
Hicks don't know who that
is uh a cat thank you from oh from
Cars I don't remember cars that much
green cars
I've only watched the first
one the green one I don't remember a
green car I only watch Cars
once he's in the first one the mustache
he's on the first
one I know lightning McLean and the hot
girl car and the friend car with the
with the pulley with uh and he went the
Piston Cup and kachow yeah I remember
that the blue and the green one
arrives I don't
remember I remember the important thing
I remember Kow and pisting cup
cat think for the super rock rock M
don't think for the super rock rock dat
box thank you for the super rock rock
use landmarks on Sharp turns to know
when to break accelerate out of turns
you want to go slow and come out fast
okay yeah like later half of the of the
of the turn you you Full Throttle I'm
going to use that a lot Full Throttle
I you fan P thank you for super Rock
block my inde thank you for the super
Rock block uh Ry all our kill and thank
you for the super rock rock this is
biama racing PG World rage
Edition that's how you know I actually
don't curse in my daily language because
if I if if if I have road rage I
probably would have cursed by
[Music]
now
chocolate thank you for super rock
rock h k thank you for super rock
rock B you killed in P Moon Rose I love
it Pebbles buy it by the audio Jama
thank you I worked hard
I
also love how everyone pronounced
different French words
differently like a little spoiler
everybody except me says it
franx it's FR you don't pronounce the
C it's
FR it's not
franx anyway
FR FR
fr the the French
currency f r a n c k oh wait f r a n CS
Euros it's euros Now isn't it I don't
remember before the
euro
H wait wait I can pronounce that where'd
you go where'd you go where'd you go
where'd you go French
French where you go French um sentence
what was
it
weon thank you
we ah ziply I should read faster so I
can sleep I'm starting to
mind I've been mind empty
but
huh uh
and and R thank you for the super rock
rock um many years ago I used dream
about a girl who was living in Crystal
she was beautiful and she had purple
hair when I first discovered I was like
no way it's the girl I used to dream
about wo you dreamed about me before me
even knew it was me
wow wow that's
cool you manifested you wow you
manifested me thanks thank
you thank you for super rock
rock hey people I can't when I can't
sleep I try to think about every time I
failed been socially awkward or the
relationships I've ended have you tried
that
doesn't that keep you up more if you
think about things that stress you
out nor it does
uh not the CR yeah I don't like I don't
like thinking about cringe memories it
make me cringe when I'm trying to sleep
[Music]
well the the the the tweet and the
stream TI is a little bit inaccurate
yeah I couldn't
sleep it wasn't like I couldn't sleep it
was like I'm not going to be sleeping
anyway so might as well stream it wasn't
it wasn't like I was trying to sleep and
I couldn't and then I started streaming
it was more like oh I need to
practice so might as well stream it
ha a
clickbait I had to think of a stream
title in like 5 minutes okay I decided
to stream at like at like 520 the stream
started at 530 I had 10 minutes okay I
just put whatever was in my head head
okay
I don't even remember what I made for
the
thumbnail
um Tano thank you for the super rock
rock demon Chef thank you for the super
rock rock Ander rice thank you for the
super rock rock she's a than for super
rock rock you're number one I'm number
one are we using Zoomies for tonight's
title oh that's a good idea I'm going to
title it I have the Zoomies
[Music]
or number one Victory
Royale 69 glasses be it's for
6900k celebration do you not see my
subscriber count someone was nice enough
to make it for me someone was nice
enough for make it for me and I was like
I'm going to use it cuz they they took
the time to tag me in my art tag to as a
celebration congratulations for the
690k thing so I am going to use it thank
you AR young for making these glasses
for me they also made my so okay glasses
so thank you I'm going to use them cuz I
like it when people make stuff for me
they're nice nice it says nice right
here
[Music]
yeah I like how it works on the on
my uh 3D because it used to be when I
tried putting 2D assets onto my 3D model
the the assets would turn out into a
very dark saturation it wouldn't be it
wouldn't be the same
color so it didn't work that well but I
I think they fixed it so now it looks
good so I'm
glad please do smug face with
it you know I want to I want to get
right in your face with this who who who
said
that I want to do it out
spite where's my desk I got to put my
desly I'm getting distracted again it
doesn't matter
you
mad I'm be tired that no I think I'll be
fine um I've slept at 10 11 12 noon
before and then started stream at my
regular time not even that
[Music]
bad plus uh stream is a little later
today it's at 700
p.m. so I have time to
eat that's what thank you for for the
super rock
rock uh Nai thank you for a super rock
rock uh
Mor thank you for a super rock rock some
say her feet are made of rock candy and
that makes a clanking sound as she runs
and that she pronounces Ganon with the
soft G all we know is she's called beep
is
jondor D
door it's Judo I've always pronounced it
Judo D andorf King of the dudos
a it's a great move thank you for the
super rock rock CH thank you for the
super rock rock while seeing beu at 5:40
p.m. after work is a nice rity by the
way congratulations on 69k and thanks
for the new emojis yes
enjoy don't really thank me thank de
because I did not ask for new emojis
they were just made and then I was like
oh they're cute can I use them and then
all I did was ask if it was okay to use
it so do not thank me thank the person
who made them
yeah and thank you um people who make so
much fan content for
us we don't ask for it but then you just
boom you make it and then
yay happy so yay
happy
oh just notice my wing is getting cut
off scooching away from the Pebbles oh
stinky you smell good side
uh wow the FBI agent thank for the OA
super well it's a little bit of a
weak
clap cuz I don't have my soundboard and
I'm also my hands are getting out of the
claw hey people this is my first AA
super thank you thank you and anyways we
got to save democracy hell divers 2 for
super Earth unfortunately hell divers 2
is hard to get perms for so I don't know
if I'll be able to play that all I
wanted to play it but that that one's a
little bit hard to
get cuz it was really fun when everybody
was playing it and saying it was good I
never got to try it cuz I never streamed
it so I never got to try
it but it looks
[Music]
fun thank for
was that how you say I'm
sleepy
NE Buffy be thank you for the super rock
rock uh AR young thank you for the super
and thank you for the glasses rock rock
uh SE thank you for the super rock rock
thanks for the gorilla stream people hug
Pro they have some nice rest for the
rest race later yes I will I will
eat uh cast thank you for the super rock
rock bomb Goblin thank you for the super
rock rock my ears perked up last Silent
Hill two stream when I heard a certain
Rock was smelling the game do I hear a
guil gear stream incoming or or I missed
one I played Guilty Gear for a tiny bit
off
stream because t y cuz I thought the
characters were cute I never streamed it
before
but yeah I like the character designs to
gy and I like the music F I smell of the
game
[Music]
I will like download fighting games just
because the characters look nice because
character they're like the characters
for fighting game they do good they good
stuff like a blaze blue
and uh yeah Gro I never downloaded Groo
fighting game but that one looks really
good in terms of character design and
guil gear
obviously a no more don't thank you for
the super rock
rock skull girls I haven't played skull
girls either but that one looks cute the
cute
girls uh T Han think Super rock rock you
did well be don't worry too much about
the race there will be chaos yeah I'm
not looking to win or anything I'm just
looking to have fun there's going to be
chaos so all my skill is going to go out
the window anyway but it was fun to
practice a little bit at least I know
how to play the game and that's all I
really was aiming
for so don't expect anything from me
okay I'm warning you don't expect
anything
just let me be under the
radar okay okay don't expect anything
from
me thank
you uhhuh thank you for the practice
stream hope you helped you yeah you
helped
me I think I definitely improved mys
thank you for the super rock rock go
practice de you can't wait for tonight
if you find yourself in of vehicular
combat tactics hitting either side of a
car's bumper behind the wheel
will will beep someone up AKA pit
maneuver hitting car's rear bumper
behind the whe all
C I
see
[Music]
aha thank you
to thank you for super rock rock iol Jan
and DF thank you for super ra here's
some booster seat funds for you I don't
need booster seat funds but thank you uh
people good luck with the race sck thank
you U Magnus the thank you for the super
rock rock yay thank you for the super
rock rock I told myself I'd work tonight
but people kept distracting me with her
stream but it was worth it since she got
too distracted while driving sorry have
a good
thank you hi caffine thank you for the a
super thank thank you 69 k t nice thank
you R thank for super rock rock nice
Gilla racing stream and raising skills
Improvement six Hall Fest just got
announced How likely is a candy feet
drink at Super Expo I want to go excited
to see you and a
there I did Pitch it to like somebody I
don't know it was either like my M tan
or somebody on was like hey
why be candy raw candy drink that's like
perfect so we us should do
that you should do that at some
point it would sell out rock candy drink
it would be so aesthetic and it would
taste
good yeah
[Music]
thank for super rock rock hi caffeine
thank you for the super rock rock I
recommend you listen to a janon song
Dale zel
Dale C Ganon Rosario it's in Spanish but
some have translation I'm not
responsible for the play R thank you for
this yes yes thank thank
you we got thank for super I'm going to
sleep now bye
[Music]
bye ah good night thanks to the stream
that was not meant to be 4 hours but
ended up 4 hours and now I'm tired
[Music]
today I have fun thank you for the
stream thank you for
surprise good
night byebye byebye I will not over
sleep probably
[Music]
sh
oh
[Music]