[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
so
uh
[Music]
i'm tired
i'm sorry
cole man
uh
i
[Music]
i overnapped
but you guys know why
and you guys know
ah
[Music]
i just need a second to wake up
goddammit
oh i guess the members know why oh this
is basically only members anyway
almost
hello okay
[Music]
oh good morning everybody
let's
let's get to it
reputation in shambles no
today is the finale of calls of the
lambs hello
i'm carrying
uh
what what was that alarm what the [\h__\h]
oh new control of firmware available
okay cool um i don't care
ah what was i saying
[Music]
why sleep in the afternoon you little
[\h__\h]
why the [\h__\h] not i decide when i sleep
and i decided to sleep in that moment
because i was tired
okay
so
shut up
i can sleep whenever the hell i want to
and i was tired because i had to get up
early for a doctor's appointment which
i'll talk about later but
uh oh
opening the game
i got a point right yeah
you can't tell me that you never ever
took a nap
in the afternoon
and and you can't say that when you did
that it didn't feel so good
naps are the best
no one can tell me otherwise you don't
have a psycho
nah
love love naps blood naps are the
essence of life
what was i saying oh yeah i wanted to
show you this
here your friend
cultist friend
oh my mouse
oh why is my mouse here
is that normal was my mouse always here
oh it's because it's in
um interference in the game's opposite
let's put it in front of my mouth
because
i just want to talk today oh it doesn't
stick to my stacked it's it's stacked to
my neck
oh well okay anyway
um
cold chicken is so cute i'm i'm wearing
i'm wearing
some more uh items
that you guys made for me
oh thank you very much
thank you for all the props
i looked into the i looked into the
props folder
uh before the stream and there was one
more
new
oh now it's weird too there's one more
new thing
um
it looks so cute but it's not really
cult of the lamp related so i'll use it
another time
uh
yeah yeah png very nice oh you know what
i could also do i could stick a png of
myself on myself so i don't always have
to put on a happy face
or i could sleep i i'll put a awake kiwa
onto myself and then i'll just sleep
behind the scenes how about that
oh
kusa
wait what
oh just received a
uh
oh i just received a message
from genma
about something
i don't know don't look at that now
ignore
it it's fine it's all fine because uh
apparently we really don't have much to
do in the game
um
will you forgive me for over sleeping
[Music]
and stop being a little [\h__\h] about it
hmm will you will you forgive me
you don't stick with me on you
neighbor
no no
the [\h__\h] is your problem get out of here
forgive me
i mean no
i hate you then
i hate you
i love love to all the ones who said yes
i love you
punishment stream yeah for the ones who
said no not for me
because that must be challenged and
punished i mean where where the [\h__\h] are
we here
we're in a cold stream you think you can
just say no to me
who the [\h__\h] do you think you are you're
just a mere little chicken
or a bucket
whatever if your bucket is even worse
cause then you have no life
you're dead
practically dead
so
if you want the blessing of the phoenix
to revive you
then you better be nice to me
yeah
i am right of course i'm right i'm
always right
let me turn on my fan
ah
beautiful
okay
uh
code of the land
and also routing
though don't have much content left but
it's fun
come on show up game you can do it yay
last supposedly last cult of the lamp
stream
this
play
oh day 97
if i didn't lose so many freaking
followers i would have done it under 100
days
um it's kind of sad
welcome back
how's the audio guys
how's the audio hello oh look at them
working hard
why does why does it feel so wobbly
it always feels so wobbly to me
maybe it's because i didn't download the
new firmware but i don't know does that
really make such a big difference
are you good
wait maybe it's just me it might just be
me
being
unused to this
it shouldn't right okay
no it's just me it's not just me oh
ah
what
oh
okay so we have ten
followers and let me see i think we need
twenty
we can buy a couple
maybe i don't know 300 oh we don't have
much money actually there we go sign
theory we could enter
the big door
hide
can i go back
i'll see maybe it's something like
they'll
they'll sacrifice all my followers at
the spot
and it has between you for some reason
right 20 right now how much do you want
for this
that's so cheap
yeah i'll take him
little cute little bunny
you can look it safe
really really i was scared i didn't want
the battle to suddenly happen
what a deal thank you
it probably always was that price but it
felt more expensive to me in the past
um
oh we have a quest to find jarar
yeah i guess
uh we can go but let me um
[Music]
let me do something really quick
we'll do that because then that gives us
a new follow-up
so basically this whole stream will be
get 10 followers and then kill the boss
and that's apparently it
i wish we had more to
[Music]
do wish we had more
go to darkwood for easy followers
with the first level mm-hmm i suppose so
but i mean it's not as easy as it was
the first time because it's still it's
still got the little
spike in difficulty
let go
please never die
uh i kind of want to keep you as a bunny
to keep your pickleness but no
no but you know what i'll give you like
the
[Music]
recorder color like some kind of light
blue
materialistic
faithless
and the sloth
doesn't quite sound like people but okay
do something
okay
but
let me look at my rituals how they're
currently looking
thank you
[Music]
oh
okay so this one's cool down this one in
theory i could do
bonfire okay i could even do these ones
i don't think i'll be gone for too long
if i go to honduras
especially because after i get the
follower i can just leave
and that's like midway through
um
well i'll do a sermon at least
look at all these piggies i'm kind of
sad if if soon after
i finish the game
there'll be an update with chickens i'll
be honestly so disappointed
i hope that won't happen i i would then
prefer to be rather later than sooner so
that my disappointment isn't that big
so that i'm like oh it would have taken
this much time anyway okay then well
whatever
okay let's leave some food here
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh what
oh god
[Laughter]
something was
very very wrong with me
just out
i told you something was wrong
it felt wobbly
look at the input
i mean
it doesn't seem
yeah i don't know
man
i don't know i don't know what just
happened
maybe it's because i just woke up
[Music]
thank you
if you have any dreams during afternoon
nap oh yes i did but um
oh
oh yeah bed rest i mean you wanted to go
to bed anyway i know but stay
stay cause you got sick he might have
eaten
my
my burnt
[Music]
food sorry
okay well i'll i
oh [\h__\h] i need to leave some food here
what's what's relatively decent
i i kind of wanted to like look at them
when they eat because um
um
these ones
might make them sick and i need to see
it if that happens
what
no no no no i pressed early enough i
swear to god there is some weird input
delay here
yeah now i pressed it
way earlier way earlier than i usually i
press it when it's still in the red
now i'm not watching for obvious
i'm pressing it when it's in the red and
then it works
why is there suddenly a delay that's not
previously there was no delay
unplugged re-plug the controller
upgrade the control the
firmware
really
okay
but how how can that suddenly make it so
sucky
so bad
download
should i disconnect the controller while
i'm installing this i'll i'll do it
is the game running on a higher solution
than normal
oh um
i mean i did um recently changed my
change my main monitors resolution to
like i downscale it because you guys
recommended that
sometimes i scaled it down to like 2k i
think instead of 4k
i am
okay i'm doing it right now
okay
stream is only one 1080.
yeah my mother was in 4k but
i i don't know i felt like it was
lagging here and there so i
uh
what
rain
okay now i think it's finished so
[Music]
no wait that's the updater installer
firmware
update for dual sense controller set
dual sense controller
is that what they call it connect your
controller okay
uh
up daily update available update now up
shut up steam i'm doing it i'm doing it
what
shut up
[\h__\h] see him
if it's a ps5 ps5000 yeah yeah it has a
ps5 controller
100 there we go
let's see if i'll cook better now
wireless controller firmware update is
complete
up to date okay i hope i don't have to
restart but maybe i do
[Music]
i guess so let's restart
oh god uh
what
it
it doesn't recognize
my controller now
okay then oh thank god there's a
mouse setting
there
race
we tight
[Music]
putting
play
uh-huh
eh it doesn't work anymore
it doesn't recognize it
wait wait wait
maybe it does
other money does okay okay
oh [\h__\h] did i just
load safe or make new save
i loaded it okay okay
okay
oh
that feels better actually
[Music]
let's let's let's try um what could we
cook
the tasty
tasty fish meal
okay
it's a little bit better than before but
it still feels oh sh
oh [\h__\h] hell
uh yeah guys so much wasted food
whatever you guys will have to deal with
it
what's that night
yes it's plugged all the way and it's
not loose no no
it's fine
it's fun
fun we'll see how i will do in the fight
because i was having
reactions slightly late what
went to the game
[Music]
bit
no
rabbit split telescope yeah
okay but this is fine we're just doing a
little quest here
not the hammer can i leave
oy
oh you better give me a better weapon
soon
okay let's go find
this friend
okay at least actually you know what
it's not as bad as oh god uh not as bad
as i remember it
the hammer
but things do feel
things still feel kind of like
delays
why i did restart my pc before the
stream
hmm
maybe you'll get used to it i hope so
otherwise i mean i still have other
controllers i wonder if they would solve
the problem but there should not be a
problem in the first place maybe i'm
just imagining all of it
[Music]
good hit
good hits good hits so far
nice
ow
see i do get hit a lot but i don't know
if that's just me being stupid or you
know
oh well
um
[Music]
oh wait i don't have to go here but okay
partially the hammer's fault too okay
the hammer sucks
oh
oh i shouldn't have i should have
summoned um
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
no i can't afford sacrificing anyone can
i just leave instead
because i just started and i don't like
the hammer anyway
what
eh
it's gonna be a killer episode
i already restarted the game
i already did
[Music]
sucks yeah
switch controller
uh i have it right here actually
but let's see if it's better with
another weapon it should be better with
a different weapon
[Music]
well sorry what did i interrupt you from
you were not doing anything you little
[\h__\h]
give me your loyalty
prove it to me and i will collect the
divine inspiration
what do we have
ah
i can get down or down
no no the updates are finished except
it's finished
oh no
[Music]
oh no we can't get that we still need to
get these ones
i mean why not
upgraded tabernacle
funny cute name okay
get more of those
now
if we have the right ingredients
we can upgrade that yeah we do
[Music]
okay
then i'm i'm i'm on my way again wait
actually wait there's the the
the hygiene is bad here is it the
toilets
thank god i made more than one toilet
okay
now that solved all the problems oh
hello don't tell me you're dying too
please please please
i didn't lead her i retrieved what you
were after from my missionary
[Music]
you did not die even though your chances
were actually pretty
low to begin with
oh then sleep go
your face said you were making casper it
makes me feel like you just
pooped over there on purpose
it's a naughty word in canadian french
oh what does it mean
i should actually food
okay
some quick food
goddammit
i don't want to [\h__\h] up
i'm being extra careful
okay
did that feel delayed like a delayed
reaction tell me like i'm curious about
that now
[\h__\h] i have to hurry up
[Music]
i'm
uh oh wow wow lots of extra hearts okay
with my horrible playstyle today that
will be helpful
i should have brought um a demon to help
us out but okay
okay this is better
hard to tell
see at least i can roll for everything
[Music]
lots of enemies oh
honestly the game really feels like
something something's off
something is off
but today's
today is a cursed day
what have i done to anger
the gamer lords
what have i done
i just have to anticipate
every action of the enemy beforehand
like a real gamer and then
i have to act early too
easy
i do need those bones so keep them
coming but i don't want to waste too
much time here
so i've already wasted time
how
[Music]
yep
okay
the curse of phoenix is upon me
guys i'm phoenix and what what did i do
i did not i did not completely give up
on
how
on on minecraft i i did not
what the [\h__\h]
it's starting to trigger me
[Applause]
i'll [\h__\h] all of you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you and
[\h__\h] you
up give me some hearts here come on
please
oh
why not why not you know hard
ah
why not heart
i used to
bombard me with hearts but that's
partially because of that demon i had oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
skull necklace
uh oh god
a lot has changed in phoenix
don't believe that that would mean
somebody has built something without
without my okay to do so
i will take your heart yes
oh thank you patsy
the transaction was completed
successfully
oh thank god oh more hearts
a mushroom
yeah yeah that was a witch
really
what
how do you know
where did you see such a witch
uh
ah he's up there okay
wait that's new it's a cat
oh my god it's so cute i will join this
cat's cult
i will leave everything behind and join
this cat's call there's even a heart
on the stone on
the left side to me on the paper stone
do you see the heart
oh what good little hearts if they
cannot be given me out mark i want to
keep mine to myself near once but two
kids i did have two in love found me out
no
meow and you had one lack of dance
summer day my beautiful children were
taking away meow a gift they said for
the one they loved most the one that
awaits me i like wept i can't respond
but how can i say no
to a gun
wherever they be i hope they are so
devoted and loving
okay
cool sorry bro
oh oh
i'm generous of you oh thank you hiding
those hearts here huh what is this a
small gift
followed from blueprint ambrosia
increased curse attack damage 1.25
[Music]
no don't say that i want to hear the
poor
i won't i won't buy that i don't really
need it
so cute
love cats forever
okay
uh
sorry for the [\h__\h] gameplay today
a missionary
mama told you a keyboard
[Music]
i don't know
i think there's other things that
she would need more
urgently than a keyboard
so
although it's a sweet idea i think there
are other priorities
well i'm certainly enjoying the new
keyboard more than i thought i would
i was kind of worried that the click of
the clackety would be annoying to me
because that's how i
uh originally
felt towards it
at least like you know low quality
clickety-clackity but this high quality
cookie clackady is good
oh
[\h__\h] stone on my face i should be
dead instantly
oh yeah i should have dodged that but i
don't care
oh my doll
did you guys see today was announced
that we're we whole live we're having a
big
collaboration with a japanese
cake um
producer
canned cake producer question is running
out oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] this is a dead end i should have
ah it's fine it's fine it's fun you know
it looks like there's not much time left
but it's not as bad as uh
it looks like
probably
[Music]
i know you stressed me out what what was
that like glitch
it felt like a glitch
i think we can import them i don't know
about that i didn't look into
how the that
is working oh god
oh you like the big boss
okay
[\h__\h] it's really running out no i'm not
gonna make it i'm gonna waste my [\h__\h]
time against both hammers you know what
[\h__\h] that
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
here coco go please give me let's give
her some more time oh there it is i just
have to
does the quest time still run now when
i'm already there please
okay first round's done
foolish of me
[\h__\h] i don't have much hp left
i don't see the timer so
i'm i'm wondering if once
what the [\h__\h] did they come here but
what if what if i get this dude anyways
[Music]
would i have had five more seconds
it would have been fine
collect ray what i can collect breathe
but the quest is failed and he's
descending let's go home
wait let me get the bones
what [\h__\h] right there's more bones
[\h__\h]
i call [\h__\h]
don't be too upset i'm so upset now
this sucks
one of those days
at least we came back early enough to
stop him from ruining everybody's
[\h__\h] moods
you don't want to know that i finished
your quest anyway do you
don't you don't deserve it oh my god
i hope there's only one descender they
all looked angry though
why check him
i mean read his mind why
keyboard time
i'm not gonna play with keyboard
godly weapons significantly more damage
than mortal weapons but the rarer they
will appear in your croquet
significantly
[Music]
i maxed it
anyway i wanted to show you guys my
my canned cake it's uh
this one oh [\h__\h] i've dropped it into
wrong window here this is it
i
yeah it's orange
i know it doesn't look like a cake but
it is a cake
it has a nice orange flavor supposedly
um there's like
repeating flavors because
there's so many members and they just
did the flavors according to the energy
uh
according to the image color
there you go wait it wasn't even you who
was dissenting
and i did get the quest reward basically
interesting
even though time right now
how do you how do you get it out you
just spoon it
with a spoon you just dip it it's not
it's not that big it's probably as big
as your hand
[Music]
like a can of cola yeah um probably
probably even smaller
i don't know i haven't seen it but i'm
imagining it because i've had like
canned cake like that before
it's orange flavor
i think it has like some jelly in it too
from what i saw it looks more like a
puffy
than a cake
but no ice cream
no ice cream dough
gosh i love puffies
yeah
that's the good stuff
okay
i need i need to oof
i need gold
maybe it's time for
getting their donations again wait is
that all i can do
there we go
wait
wait what something's weird
there was like some
lag that made me feel like that's all i
can
[Music]
um put into commission
weirdly
so i kept on leaving thinking that
that's it
but it didn't look like that was it
[Music]
nothing wrong with my computer no what i
don't know what would be wrong
everything's normal nothing's changed
we'll see how we do with the boss if we
have too many troubles we'll have to
think of a solution
but besides that
yeah
i wonder if we just keep them there and
not indoctrinate them
will they age
because if we keep them there forever
and they're not aging until the very end
and i feel like that would be safer than
letting them in one by one but that's
probably not gonna work is it
refresh fry
what should the refresh rate be
let me check
what's the normal refresh rate
where do i see it
[Music]
oh i don't see if i would see that
maybe here
oh
it's 30.
the
the h that is 30.
oh i can do only maximum 60.
i changed it
maximum 60
for some reason
that's 40 times is that but that's not
fps right that's h said i don't really
know exactly what that is but
it's not fps right even though that's
the same numbers 30 60.
maybe it's maximum 60 now because i
lowered the screen size
but something looks weird now
something's glitching out of my screen
now like not glitching
but let's look at this oh right now
that's gone
um
that's your name
[Music]
let's see if it feels better
okay
what is the make of your monitor samsung
samsung that one is samsung the other
one is asus and the other one is uh
wacom
wait what why can't i run like this
wait wait it feels so crazy
wait wait wait holy [\h__\h] the game looks
oh
wow
i don't know if it looks different to
you guys but for me it's
holy [\h__\h]
is this 60 fps
what
eh are you dead no
what what when you old age the [\h__\h] you
didn't look old
oh my god this looks
amazing why are they so right whining
over there is over it's done
don't be sad
don't throw up
[Music]
it feels it feels so hd now so different
holy [\h__\h] excuse me later pencil some
creatures out here sticking but
yes yes yes yes
yes yes
yes welcome welcome
sickle free
wait does that mean other games will
also look way better now to me
i've been playing everything on the
ferny
aged set then
what
what what
oh my god
oh my god that's incredible
but but it doesn't change the way you
guys perceive it right
let me make some more beds too
do i need more beds
no
not now
not yet
it's not really just me okay that helps
still
it helps though the sicko four
oh you look cute
sorry i have to change you from fox into
something else
okay
i have no words
[Laughter]
how
that's something that you can't really
like know
um that i've been
like you know doing wrong unless i like
specifically
notice myself and tell you about it like
how how do you
how do you how would you know
you know
holy [\h__\h] everything moves so fast is
this the future oh my god i feel like
straight for example also could have
been i i could have had a much better
experience holy [\h__\h]
this is the future
oh my god what what is like oh god it
feels it feels so
amazing
it feels amazing
should we try making some food then see
what happens
um
oh
i got some good food
i'm lacking ingredients to my dad
you have some stuff here
welcome to the 60 mps cult i discovered
now i really feel kind of like a boomer
[Music]
i can actually see it moving so smoothly
what
that's insanity
that's amazing but i feel like someone
who just discovered the internet or
something
i removed my limiter
wow
[Music]
i'm um i
i i can't believe what i'm experiencing
damn
well fishing should still be like yeah
pretty much the same it was all fishing
it's always wobbly this is this stupid
mechanism
that was always wobbly and still it will
it will always be wobbly this is wobbly
on purpose
because the oh you're just gonna stay
down there okay
day 101 oh no we're over
days kind of lame
okay
just trying to get some fish because
um i need more food but maybe i'll just
uh
put them on on a diet again
now i can finish that
and now i really wonder how different
all the games are gonna feel like to me
foreign
i don't think i'll necessarily really
enjoy it much more
shooters
come on
well we'll have to check it out
again of course i was i was playing
everything like this unless my edge set
was on a different setting when i was
still doing 4k
well
this is like when on tv
suddenly things started to go from 30
fps to 60 fps although i have to say
that felt weird to me
and i still don't 100 like it when i
talked about this before but when a show
like the hobbit or so
is 60 fps like a fantasy show
to me
it doesn't fit
because that's too good quality for
something that happens in a fantasy
medieval world you know what i mean
it just doesn't feel right to me
yeah yeah it feels too fast it's weird
because that's reality it would it would
feel fast in reality but that it just
feels too modern to me like this
shouldn't be happening
you know
[Music]
tell me something new
24 fps is the ideal move yeah 24. i
don't know about that but interesting
interesting
we should have to use higher fs and
cinema use 24 cinema
even like the the super wow amazing
3d
and so on
wet
really
of course i did it
oh i didn't find out
oh i'm 24.
why
when they release it on blu-ray and so
on it's always uh 60.
why
is it because they can't do better in a
cinema
do we still have someone sick running
around i hope not
what's with you
always crazy skills from beginning in a
lot of games now you're telling me
you're playing games with equipment on
the wearing weighted club yeah
not only that but remember also when i
was playing near automata this is a long
time ago but remember what was happening
there
super late in the game we realized i
i did something really wrong with the
hacking i had some settings wrong or
something right
[Laughter]
that made everything a million times
more difficult
what was the setting what did i do wrong
ah b-sync yeah i had some i had v-sync
on
and that impacted it
in incredible ways
man
bruh
i like to play on hard mode
and the default option i guess was a
mess yeah
it was on by default and that sucks
um
so we have we have 13
followers now
uh
you guys said it was 20 right i have to
get 20.
i'm not sure anymore i'm just gonna
preemptively make some more beds then
we're reaching the
graveyard
maybe we can move that one
now the healing bay will be right in
between
how fitting
uh
would need some more of that wood
they all move so smoothly
oh my god
it looks so incredible
it looks incredible
i'm like i could cry
my god
oh my god
wow
but i've been missing out on
okay let me upgrade the
i can't
all right okay
let's get a demon
try a shooter now
[Music]
oh this one's new
melee attacks closest enemy every every
few seconds whoops a frog
[Music]
that's free that's really not bad
where the hell did you come from
so you're so pretty happy
i don't know about when i was in japan
um
i had a different monitor there
it could have been different setting
setting there but i don't know
[Music]
we're visiting new automata in 60 fps
it
but even then it felt smooth
just because i guess near is such a
smooth game but are you telling me i
played that in 30 fps
[Music]
what is it
ah it's locked to 30 fps unless you mod
oh oh okay okay
in that case
that's that's another story
um what should we do should we uh wait i
want to revive people right
as often as i can
[Music]
so we have 14 now i think let's revive
anybody really it's fine
[Music]
um that initial garfield wasn't garfield
the one demon that always
that i was always using
oh yeah i also did not always have a 4k
monitor that's true but this one this
one i've had for quite some time
i'm pretty sure
uh
can i do another no obviously not but
cool down for now
maybe maybe i'll stock up on some fish
while i'm waiting for
everything to
um
be back
normal
mario kart
wait yeah cause i even though i do game
capture
the game capture card i
i guess i i always looked at it on my
main screen the middle one
although no now that i think of it
until recently i actually
used my right monitor as my middle
monitor and i switched it up actually
let me see though how
the monitor that's to my right side
can i check the
that one's on 60 oh down to 60 fps
each set but it can go up to
uh 144
or 144.
should i
let that one go up to 144 turn it up
is that better than should i switch
those two monitors up again
originally i had that one in the middle
but i switched it because i thought
maybe the colors look better on on the
samsung one
i'm not sure
of course it's bad wait let me let me
move the game window over to that side
see how it looks
i guess that looks even better
okay that difference is hard to tell but
i'm not sure it might look even better
i'm not sure
not sure that that 3260 was already a
huge difference are you saying that then
that that's 144 fps
some games take advantage of it better
ah
okay okay if you keep a resolution at
1080p it should not be a problem
performance-wise and most oh oh can that
affect the performance
hmm
depends on the game okay
interesting will i have my mind blown
again
i wonder what kind of game does
144 fps then
i'm gonna try it out and have my mind
blown again
i guarantee it wow
the jump from 60 to 120 is insane really
like looking at this i'm like how can it
even go any higher than this now
[Music]
you never go back to anything lower
oh god that one's the speeder
oh
[Music]
just moving your mouse
oh yeah
oh yeah i guess so it looks uh very
speedy and movie
movie
smoothie what
words
words don't go
god there's so many fish in the scene
ghosting of the curse i don't know what
that means but
ditch the meme 4k monitor
i mean you want me to switch those two
around again i guess i will
i just thought that having my main
monitor
be the one with the best color
would be desirable because when i make
thumbnails and edit photos and stuff
um i want the colors to be as accurate
as possible
when i draw whatever
but i'm not sure
which one which one of my monitors has
the best color
the most accurate not the best because
like even if it's super saturated that
doesn't mean that it might look amazing
but
it doesn't mean that it's uh accurate
what brand are they as i said the middle
one that i'm using uh right now that
went up to 60 each set is uh
samsung and the one other one is an asus
but i don't know the exact model now
the middle one is a 4k
come on come little pissy [\h__\h]
samson what is what i don't know it's
not written on it
how would i know it by heart wait
actually does it say that in my
in my settings for the monitor i wonder
oh come on come on come on
is that is it that
it says
vg27a
vg27a for the asus i think and then
u 2
8 e 5 9 0 for the
samsung i think
[Music]
you guys are welcome to look it up and
tell me something about it
that's good
this is too fun yeah it could be
yeah who remembers the spec by heart the
monitor spec
asus yeah aces is feed v g27a
it's out of stock because i bought the
last one
so that no one copies me
trendsetter kiwawa you know i like it
when when i set some trends but not
always
sometimes i want to be the only one who
does something
be more exclusive and original
have they owned exactly they only
produced one of those monitors now you
have that one
[Music]
yeah the asus stasis i have it on 144.
155 i don't see that option
[Music]
we're having a big computer geek session
aren't we
remember the names and abilities of and
egg moves over 700 pokemon damn
yeah detectives
i should read out my money respects in
asmr whispering voice again
last time it was my pc specs but who
cares about that now we care about
monitor specs
that's the real mind blower
one four four comma zero zero zero h set
oh
[Music]
making me feel things i've never felt
before
oh you're good
it's night time again
i should check if they're selling
another follower maybe
do they if i buy one
do they not add another one until the
next day i wonder
it's really low effort we could
obviously okay we could just go into the
into the
you know the levels and get followers
there but it takes so much time
and while i'm gone so much [\h__\h] happens
in my cult
so this is the safe way this is the safe
way
but i wonder if there's any any other
things i can do to drag out the length
of the game do you guys know
the fox's quest fox quest
what fox quest
box quest
hmm
oh did that eh
what that scam
that's gambling
i don't see that as content in the game
it's just a mini game to me in the game
not a quest
not a real quest
that's a hotel game
[Music]
60 fps you will have i don't think so
that has nothing to do with this
minigame
oh [\h__\h]
come hell
meera's quest oh the 10 gold thingies
okay okay
i'll work on that
didn't really intend on like really
doing all the mini quests and all that
but since we don't have much content
left in this game
i guess why not
60 fps gaming skills gambling skills
i can see the dice
roll
faster than the enemy can cause the
enemy surely does not have a 144 fps
monitor
i i can see everything
better than he can
now i can also see better when he's
cheating
implying that he does cheek yes yes he
looks like a cheater
looks like a cheater to me
[\h__\h] fish
okay i'm done here i don't care
you guys are slow with those tears what
the [\h__\h] i'm disappointing
uh
i don't know wait how many do i have
i don't have enough
i need the gold bars originally too but
oh well
lumber yards ran out of lumber
what you're
[Music]
oh sure actually i guess i didn't uh set
anyone for that job yet
oh yeah
perform the loyalty enforcer rachel okay
okay no problem
that is a decent request he's very
motivated to do his job
he believes he's so thankful for being
revived
which he should be
he very much should be
i have 23 now okay
let's get some more
out of character for garfield i guess so
your shot okay
oh so much cauliflower
okay let me drink a little bit
laszaga enforcer
no
he will eat all the lasagna away from me
i want lasagna
[Music]
let me build two new things here
oh long yard
and
this one
okay
what else let me check here
react you can't i could actually do the
trick
did you see uh iris and what myself i
apparently went to hokkaido
for a little trip
i i must stay
i would love to go on a trip without my
senpai too it sounds fun
but also
stress is starving oh no oh [\h__\h]
also respect to um
see i can make so many
respect to
iris
for getting a japanese [\h__\h] member sorry
a japanese member to uh take a break and
go on a vacation like even if it was
apparently just one day
even if it was just one day dad itself
is an accomplishment
[Laughter]
[Music]
like
the um i have to say
not not such a bad case
in terms of taking
although she does stream a lot but um i
would see her as someone who takes good
care of
herself for that better
[Applause]
yeah
i don't know although maybe she is a
workaholic at heart i don't know
because she also puts out a lot of song
covers and music
like monthly almost i would say
and that does take up some time too
we can already sacrifice someone again
uh revive
who have i not revived before
level one let's revive someone with
level one for once
how about the noob
he only lived 32 years old days
he has never been revived before i'll
give him a second chance to redeem
himself i'm so nice i'm so kind
i'm so sweet
what a name
kind chill
oh loyalty enforcer ritual
what do i need for that one
oh task of patrolling the cult and
raising oh
15 bones
wait who wanted to be at garfield right
garfield garfield
yes
[Music]
raises loyalty without me being here oh
look at this little hat
cute oh they're all alarmed now but oh
sweet why did it lower faith it
shouldn't blow a fave
it shouldn't
makes no sense
that needs all the fish i should go
fishing more often this is good food
for my followers
see now it moves so fast i gotta be
careful too
i'm not used to this
let me see if they got a new
a new um yes of course you do how much
i got no money because i turned it all
into gold bars oh [\h__\h] okay i'll be back
um
oh
[\h__\h]
i'm gonna send someone on a crusade soon
and on a mission
a mission
also
just in case someone dies
ahead of time i'm gonna put one here
oh you're not gonna sleep
you're welcome
garfield is now not only a non-sleeper
but also loyalty enforcer
he when i end this um
gameplay this game is gonna get a medal
okay
why did i eat that
what a waste i know i know it gives me
something
yeah an extra heart but i should have
eaten some shitty meal i ate that by
accident
what's your name to tabitha
shania
um
let's go to midas
is he awake at night
uh mitas is uh
here
i'm not gonna
sacrifice anyone
here
again
wait shouldn't up
ah is that is that that one that one in
on that little hill
the one i sacrificed before
[Music]
that's so sad
where's midas
is mina sleeping
it just turned daytime let me go back
in poor guy
i i really felt sorry for that i didn't
know what i was doing
or is it just
do i not have to give it to him directly
do i just put it in here
this place is so much nicer in higher
fps
there's a crown on earth
on the right side
but something for me to take
i don't know what you mean but okay i
guess i'll put it in here yeah okay that
did the trick
oh wow
oh yeah most generous i would have taken
half that than that you really don't
know how to negotiate do you bequest
told me to do this it's
it was not an option to give you less
the well is at your disposal make as
much use of it as you will may fortune
be kind
eh get 350 coins wait wait is that my
disposal but what would i get
i don't know
what i mean i completed it but i didn't
even get a reward what the [\h__\h]
you might get triple back
then it's like worth saving up so much
and if that's really true then yeah okay
oh
let me see if there's anything to do
with the mushrooms anything else
will he will you take some mushrooms
no
he's not even here
oh no he's there
he blended in so well
oh wait he's
right he's dead no he's intoxicated
right he's not dead but i can't talk to
him
she didn't know
i hope he's not dead overdosed oh [\h__\h]
well at least the game
teaches you something good
do not overdose
be careful
don't become like him
don't be like him
[Music]
well again
holy [\h__\h]
i'm such a genius
oh
wait those stone mines do they already
give you the improved um wood or do they
just work faster or so i wonder
uh no they just work faster
okay
get more ingredients thank
you want to be has a goalkeeper guilt
enforcer hell yeah you can have that job
it's yours
thank you for your enthusiasm
rain rod hello
no i'm not participating in it
no unfortunately
like i kind of wanted to but it's okay
i can play
worms with
the girls another time
i've got too much going on anyway
but it sounds like fun
worms for the birds
but i've got some fun games for the
12 hour
they're fun i have two collaborations um
planned
i i got some id members and some en
members to join me
yeah the id members are gonna be early
in the marathon the young members are
gonna be late in the marathon
let's see if i can upgrade the
missionary now
uh i think my day off is tomorrow right
so i will make um
i'll make uh
the schedule tomorrow i already decided
what to do but i just have to make a
pretty
image
no wait that's the wrong thing where is
uh
here 80 coins [\h__\h]
ah
[Music]
nine
ah i need gold nuggets
maybe i should go on a crusade
seems
necessary
ikokana
my offering books doesn't it always give
it to me automatically when i enter
yeah
it's empty now
i can sell stuff
true like fish for example but
i want to keep the fish look i need i
need the fish
[Music]
okay be careful
i think that one food is bugged out
probably
maybe i can eat it oh it's not actually
there
oh no wait is he eating it though
is that the one
in any case
i guess i'll go on a crusade why not
have some fun get used to the new fps
let's see how fighting feels now
make an enrichment you mean that the
money ritual let me see let me see what
we can do
oh
yes
yes let's do that yes
wow
how much was that
[Music]
so this time it was much higher wow
this time it was much higher than last
time
so maybe it's rng
was a good choice to make more of these
because now i really i do need a lot of
materials
okay
i
will go on the christine
oh
thank you i'll just make a little bit
more food in advance
[Music]
hi
hey
that was close
okay
bye bye guys
have a nice day
better work
you better work [\h__\h]
i'm gonna see ya
which one should i go to hmm
[Music]
i have demons already summoned them
this is just about collecting materials
so
we don't have to go
into a difficult one
also we can buy you
it's a cow so cute a blue cow
let me just go into dark ones yeah i
just want some oh wait i don't even need
gold that bad but i guess let's also
just get a
follower
in there
second area easiest
you think so
is that a hammer or an axe
ooh divine strength plus a shiny
nice
1.5
anyways a fish okay
i like fish right now
it's an axe okay good
good
guten tag
nadan marlos
those kids
[\h__\h]
you
okay that was not because of a lag or so
that's just because i was um
you know
a slow brain
oh no they're not one hit i guess
it's so small
wow
[Music]
oh what the [\h__\h]
oh it's so small
yo the dodging the worlds the rolls work
so well now
ro rolls that's a hard word to say
rolls
so fast i lose track of where i am on
the screen because i'm so fast
damn
speechl
and that gives you a completely and
different feeling when you play a game
anyway while we're here let me tell you
about my doctor's appointment today
ah so i woke up i woke up early for this
doctor's appointment that i told you
about um
i told the members about it
yesterday last
night because
in in somewhere in february
i
i was um trying to find out more about
the pain in my body
that i've had for at least 10 years
that i can't explain to myself
[Music]
oh i barely have to fight in this
hmm
hello
you must hunger much like have this one
in the house thank you
what which one coins thank you
where
oh wait wait wait wait oh you mean you
mean the follower of the house
thank you
it's a freebie
cycle
thank you
wow that's so kind of you
what
yeah
what's up this is so much money here too
maybe i keep this when i grow hungry
it's gone already stop dreaming about it
well well um
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay it's the cat
again
what was i saying oh yeah
and i
got
all right i'll take it
i went to the doctor um
because like i did a blood test and then
in the blood test it said something that
could hint
on me having like a rheumatic disease or
something just hint you know
it wouldn't be for sure
and but my my main doctor he said okay
you have to
you have to get that checked out so
let's send you to like a like
some place that specializes on that
and uh
i went there
um
but
since i thought they could access
my
whoops i wasted that since i thought i
could access the
that they could access the blood test
that i already did
i didn't bring the results
also it took it took quite some time to
get an appointment there in the first
place like i think
two or three months for the first
appointment there
welcome
and um
yeah yeah and then they were like where
did you bring it then we have to make a
new blood test and i'm like i just made
one
do i really have to make a new one it
will take ages and then yeah
can i not just send you the result like
on the same [\h__\h] day or something no
no can't do it because you don't have it
now
so annoying
such a waste of my time
and everybody's time honestly
yeah but um
[Music]
so i have to comply but that's not the
only thing they wanted they wanted me to
do some kind of another physical therapy
but at that point i already
finished a physical therapy a one-on-one
physical therapy i literally just
finished it right remember when i was
going to it so
so often
and that was fine
but you know that wasn't the first
wasn't the first physical therapy
sacrifice health
for what for strength or what was it
again
what's that again
just one heart right no no wait i think
i remember it brings me down to one
heart
i don't think i want to do that
no
i don't need it
yeah i was i
where was it
what was i saying
but i always lose track of what what i'm
saying so fast
i have physical therapy okay i did that
and then they tell me to do another one
but not really like quite exactly a
physical therapy
but like oh who are you gonna summon
easy holy [\h__\h] it's so easy
it was um
like a mix of different
therapy types
um but i i couldn't get that one because
it wasn't included in my super [\h__\h]
expensive
insurance because if you
if you are self-employed then
insurances are really expensive
at least for someone like me
yeah and so i was really pissed off that
they take so much money for me but they
don't even cover this stupid therapy
while other normal insurances did cover
that one apparently
funnily enough
so i couldn't do it but instead i just
did another normal therapy because
that's what they suggested i was like i
literally just like a month ago came out
of a
therapy and now you're telling me to do
another one
i
don't think you guys do anything
different here but okay
and in fact they
they didn't really do anything different
besides the fact that this time it was
not one-on-one but it wasn't a group and
one-on-one is generally better
see i could go i could go on now
i've never went past this
should i go is it very difficult
when in doubt prescribe therapy really
that's literally what they're doing
i just reset the map oh so i can go on
and on and on okay now i'll go back once
yeah no i'm not employed i'm i'm uh
like uh
it's not it's not a normal employee
contract so i'm not employed i'm
self-employed
um i'm like a like a freelancer
contracted yeah
yeah yeah yeah
sorry garfield never mind
ah but those are inspired by my
successful chris idea it also only took
like three minutes what the [\h__\h]
that was the fastest crusade i've ever
done
maybe me being able to move so fast
really did have a good effect
wow
oh
everyone go to sleep and ignore the poop
oh i sent someone to bed for us even
though i had the healing baby before
didn't i oopsie
i didn't realize
you guys are going to
toilet before sleeping good good good
good good
oh i'm sleepy cute
[Music]
okay
so yeah they they told me to do that and
i had to
meanwhile i was doing like the
another blood test but i had to wait
uh until like june or july or so to get
my results but
coincidentally it turned out to be the
date where i had to go to america
and therefore i had to move that
appointment again and that appointment
oh oh i don't have enough beds holy [\h__\h]
that appointment
uh
wait i don't have enough beds why are
you not asleep then
that one's empty i'll build another one
what was i saying
that must be enough bits
surely that's enough beds
yeah i'll help you
yeah i had to wait in total seven months
to
get another appointment from them
and then guess what
i went there today and this is exactly
what i expected
what they did was
um
i arrived i arrived on time but first of
all they once again made me wait another
[\h__\h] hour for nothing
for nothing i didn't even see other
patients going in and out no
unnecessary waiting time
so sick of it
there were like other
patients also waiting for a long time
and getting really pissed off
but my appointment was earlier than
theirs so at least i got in before them
more or less
yeah
um
oh you're old
who are you who are you
already older i have to sacrifice you
sad
oh goodnight oh yes me
[Music]
uh well i don't know what your name
should be
named
oh we got a hedgehog is that a hedgehog
i think it's a hedgehog follow-up form
very cute
okay
welcome what's your name your name is
name
are you shawn
i don't know
we're fine i guess
and this one
this one was a freebie
so your name will be freebie i'm so
original my name ideas are just genius
there you go
oh dear
no no no game crash but
wow
okay i don't know what to say about that
so i'm not gonna say anything
wow
okay let me turn on the lens is really
dark here
oh dear
wow
[Music]
okay
so where was i uh
yeah i arrived at the doctor i waited an
extra hour i was getting mad
but then finally they let me in
and then
i
i sat down
and
she was like
the doctor was like
she basically just told me the results
of my blood test
she printed it out
she was like well nothing's wrong with
your blood or the other test that you
did
maybe this little thing is a bit of
concern but that's completely unrelated
but yeah nothing at all there's nothing
that would give any kind of
diagnosis
or show that anything is wrong with you
um
so yeah that's it goodbye
i waited seven bucks for that if at
least if at least anything came out of
it you know
that was such a [\h__\h] waste of time
that made me
actually mad i i was upset i left the
room and i like started
out of being so upset and wasting my
time and after over 10 years never
knowing what's wrong with me
i i did tear up a little bit because it
pissed me off so much like it's like
what am i even doing
yes it's blood yeah wow yes that's
basically it
um
yeah
[Music]
that kind of sucked
that really sucked oh this is the last
thing i can activate oh it's really the
end of the game huh
yeah they should have just sent me
that per email
she probably didn't look at it until
today because i'm guessing all these
doctors don't look at the results of the
test until the actual day
when the patient is there even if it's
been a [\h__\h] year or something
yeah
and be pissed as well
that's so disappointing i mean of course
it's also good to not have a rheumatic
disease
apparently
surely that's good but you know um for
me for myself i just kind of wanted an
answer
then i can actively
help myself
with medicine or whatever with something
something that helps you know
you know the only thing she did was like
oh you should go um back
back as in last time i was there was
over 10 years ago
to a new neurologist you know the one
for the nerves the nervous doctor that i
went to
before the like a million years ago
um
who gave me antidepressants
who said i don't know what you have so
it's probably fibromyalgia here have
some antidepressants and that ruined my
chances to get into lufthansa
yeah
and it didn't even help um
[Music]
i'm obviously gonna go to a different
one this time because that one was in a
different city even
i was accepted for lufthansa i never
said the name before but i was accepted
for lufthansa
i was at the time
um just you know for
testing it out because the doctor told
me to test it it might help with my
fibromyalgia i was using the
antidepressants and since i was i didn't
want to lie when they asked me what
medic medication i take
i told them i'm taking it currently to
see if it works or something even though
i didn't need to say it because it
wasn't gonna be in the results of the
blood test that they did at the medical
um
test
in lufthansa
yeah um did i already do this yeah okay
oh but yeah
um
where was i
so that's the only thing that they told
me to go to a neurologist so i'm gonna
do that i guess but
uh
see
if if she would have sent me that
per email
seven months ago i could have already
went to the neurologist ages ago because
neurologists
there's a lot of them unusually don't
have that much waiting time i think
um
as this one
so i could have been done with that
like six months ago you know that's why
it pisses me off so much
even considering the fact that i i
didn't even need that extra blood test
because i already had one made
before
so then if you consider that i could
have been done seven or eight months ago
because i wouldn't have needed to wait
for the extra blood test
absolutely ridiculous absolutely
ridiculous how many followers do we have
now
uh 18. oh we're almost there
it's it's getting really crowded here
it's just doing that
oh wait maybe
something else
21 for backup okay
true
holy [\h__\h] they love me so much
nice i love you guys too thank you for
loving me
[Music]
yeah we're almost there and i'm i'm not
even hurrying i'm taking my damn sweet
time
wow
okay
let's let them build something if
possible
this thing
i just it doesn't have to be in there
right
or does it
i'm just gonna put it here
really hope things turn out for you
thank you
you feel better thank you well i mean
i'm so used to it but i'm definitely
always in pain
i'm just so used to it
oh man oh wow
oh
i have silk
wait spider soap when i don't have silk
i've been in the salt crater before zero
out of ten is that something i have to
make out of
like smaller ingredients but it's not an
option at that table thingy
there's not a cure for everything in
this world nope
i just at least i just want some some
answers you know it doesn't even have to
be a cure i just want an answer
new silk it has to be new silk oh my god
really
you have to appreciate the
second hand too guys
you take this gift
wait i should have given it after
uh oh it's a stick
all right though it's fun
and why is he so shiny when i can't is
he bugged
was it a different ah it's a different
one it's this one
okay
psoriatic arthritis
[Music]
thank you if it was arthritis they would
have told me there because that's kind
of i think a rheumatic disease
wow
[\h__\h]
so much stuff
okay let's send someone
away is that a product that's just a
normal missionary right
let's upgrade that
i still can't
eh
no wait that's not it
no i guess i did upgrade it that's
upgraded huh
i never built this one though
confession booth
thank you guys very sweet
even if they're useless yeah yeah yeah
well well well well
oh maybe what do we need we need
coins maybe or
pumpkin seeds would be nice too
you know what
you have high chance for pumpkin seeds
so
i'll do that goodbye bye bye
and then we can send another one i think
[Music]
94 for meat for casper
sure good luck don't die please don't
die
and then we'll take um
oh
lazy boy damn
that's strong
that was that that was um
not as strong before
okay
take this one
name can shoot yeah but he's low level i
think yeah
i wanna level him up first i need to
level up his loyalty
he's very new so
um
six
garfield wow
i mean
half a spirit heart but like
since it's plus six it's more than just
half a spirit heart right
oh wait i can do a third one
yo
i'll take him
let's go into a more difficult map
then
let's go get the silk
oh they're all grieving at the grave wow
okay
food
okay sorry i don't have anything better
right now please forgive me
i'm trying my best here
we're running out of ingredients
and there's so many people now who want
food
let's put some seeds in here
love the beetroots
okay let's go
i'm gonna go on a little trip everybody
see you later
wait maybe i should have given the
loyalty necklace to name oh well i have
i have some good
attacking demons right now
pretty decent ones also i'll i'll buy
this one thank you cute bear
good hunting bus thank you
going on the trip on my favorite rocket
ship is that something i should know
i don't know that saying
silk cradle ooh
two times more favor receive double the
health on healing
okay
who has their presence weighed heavy
upon the beasts of them
the worshipers me well versed in the art
oh
for making for free move with care sharp
teeth tough not equates to what the [\h__\h]
are you saying
[Music]
what
question mark no not a [\h__\h] hammer
okay but wait now this is the first time
i'm using the hammer
after
oh
upgrading my age
set jesus
clumps big clumps of cheese interesting
let's go
got hit immediately
nice
i still have
zero they gave me nothing where is wait
wait am i in the wrong dungeon
no this is a silk cradle right
maybe from here on out oh
oh [\h__\h] i
i really hate the hammer
oh god
ah
[Music]
i need my demons to attack more
i won't get a different weapon for a
while
ah
it sucks
the waiting time and the aiming i don't
know
it freaking sucks big damage
at least give me an axe then
oh no oh no oh no not these enemies
oh thank god okay the big ones are gone
so anyway that was that was all i can
tell you about my doctor's appointment
because it was really uneventful besides
me waiting
uh it's
way too much
wasting too much time waiting too much
there's nothing besides that
no news nothing
it's just the cycle continues it goes on
and on and on and on oh this this place
is cool
nice dodges i'm trying
oh here here should get some silk maybe
huh
ah
god damn it
nice oh that dude that one shot that
thing
[Music]
come on
oh thank god
they move so fast these ones are so hard
to hit when you're aiming
also can't get too close because then
i'll get hit
[Music]
okay
are my demons even attacking at all
cause it feels like they're not doing
anything
stupid spiders
you're kind of just hanging out with me
yeah
can you guys like have an eye on it
because i i can't can you guys have an
eye on it if they're doing anything at
all or if i have to fire them
sooner
you're chilling
they're just happy to be here
cute
snitches get stitches
they won't no it's a [\h__\h] game
they won't know
so okay four out of ten i'm not getting
many
silk
spider silks here but
at least something i hope i get enough
from going in here one time
[Music]
okay
oh wait it's that way
oh no it's that way
do i only get the silk from killing the
spiders
not from
oh how did that mess you
oh now now i didn't even hit uh
there you go
i saw that demon hitting the enemy once
they really have a
low
amount of hits that's just it
it's if we're breaking up the rocks with
spider webs on them
i'm trying to break up as many things as
i can
they don't do much huh
even though garfield
huh
does that not break
maybe not
garfield is pretty high level though
wait did i bring garfield and brock i
brought someone that had a relatively
high level i think
nice
[\h__\h] spiders
nah
oh sh okay these guys can they're
minecrafting
they're they're uh mining the stone
oh by the way did you guys see rust the
new season the girls started playing it
i have not looked at the server yet i
have not logged in yet but to be honest
it might still change once i get into
the game but my motivation currently is
pretty low
partially because
um it seems like the girls decided the
japanese members decided on the new rule
probably because of
insane base
that now you can only have like
uh
one or two
all the turrets per base
one or two so and so
whatever
they put up a lot of rules
uh of how well your
um
your base can be protected and you know
how i i was i was like really motivated
to build like a full undestructable
castle
uh
so
that was kind of lame
because i just got started you know
for the other ones who already built
incredible bases maybe it makes sense
but hmm
so
i mean it makes a little bit sense if
you consider that nobody could take down
piccolo's face and that was weird but
that was also fun and incredible like it
took a lot of work and effort
but of course you also want to see bases
going down
i love it i love it
i love red pandas
i i don't even want to change that one
to a pig
wow
[Music]
red panda are so cute they're the only
thing i want to see see in zeus if i
ever go to zoos
oh what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] is your problem
[Music]
red thunder cute
yeah
[Music]
rest
uh
i'll give it a try and see if my
motivation comes back once i'm back in
the game but um
motivation is kill where when where were
you when motivation was killed huh
[Music]
but not every like
protection item was on the list like for
example bear traps or soap
weren't on there i could put a million
bear traps in my
home but you could still shoot it down
um
[Music]
yeah
i was also like
maximum one air defense thingy
stuff like that you know everything was
capped to one or two
i mean it's not set in stone yet i think
they asked for opinions but
the ones who answered it seemed fine
with it so i don't know
i don't know
i wanted to ask you well then why else
did
why doesn't she then
what
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
it takes so much time to charge the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hammer i'll [\h__\h] you
i swear to god
[Applause]
ah fun not the best fight could have
been so much better i could have flexed
on you guys if only
i didn't have a [\h__\h] hammer i should
you should be able to ban the hammer
from the game
also that was a boss fight kind of
even though i'm not at the bus yet
interesting
good job though thank you
one of the wrists that the hammer is the
one being banned now
bam hammer is being banned
that what yeah it was a bus
i didn't know you could um
encounter bosses
in the question mark
fields i don't think that ever happened
to us
well maybe i'm wrong
at least we already have the the quest
items that we need
ah
that one's oh that one's strong
oh big spider came out of there
those spider abs actually look pretty
cool wait that reminds me of something i
watched i watched this video maybe maybe
you guys got it in your recommendations
too because we always seem to get
similar recommendations
people
that's kind of weird from the youtube
algorithm they could recommend so many
things but then they always have this
thing where they recommend the same
video for a million people
if you think about it then that might be
actually a bug in their system because
it's so unbalanced
out of nowhere they suddenly recommend
the same video to everyone
therefore
like in a really unbalanced way giving
so many views to just one [\h__\h] video
when they could just spread it out a bit
more
um but okay
so what i watched was
no not a new curse new weapon please
okay
um what i watched was there was a video
like about some dudes
rescuing
a lobster from the supermarket and
kind of like
helping it
come back to
did you guys see that
it was it was kind of cute
i mean i found it very creepy to see the
close-ups of the lobster's mouth
um because i didn't didn't really want
to see it that's creepy the rest of the
lobster is cute but the mouth you you
you you didn't see it okay some some saw
it though it was pretty sweet
that dude apparently does that uh quite
often
like similar things he likes sees
something to rescue that's supposed to
be like some not really something to
rescue
i like the idea
because when i look when i because i
don't eat much seedless but sometimes
when i walk by those restaurants that
have this showcase
of um
of seafood live seafood and water tanks
and i look at that and i'm like
that's such a this visual and obvious
display of suffering and death
right in front of your eyes
it's kind of depressing i don't like
seeing that i'm
i don't think anyone really likes seeing
that
i know we all eat that food but like
seeing it
in front of your eyes oh
so oh you again so obviously
it's just sad
so i would wanna i would wanna do the
same thing
if you have like a leftover tank if you
if you can't keep a lobster hell yeah do
it go for it
this is how we pick fresh fish at the
restaurant sure
sure
but then i don't like it
i have compassion for fish but not for
chicken that's not true
that's not true
was really really mad at my mom for
killing her chicken
and the way she talked about killing her
chickens
i did not like that i did not like it at
all
oh
nice nice good room
nice look at all that health
what are your hairdr
vegan for 15 years wow
15 years
that's incredible
oh it's spreading so much poison oh
oh wait let me
i'll meet you thank you
i actually started figuring out
the hammer a little bit more i don't
know if you've noticed but i started
changing direction
while i am uh
already charging it up pretty good
oh
anyway the lobster guy he even went to
um
it was a it was a fishing
bait store where he bought live fish
that was also supposed to be used as
bait
as food in the end it's food but you
know at least he continued the
actually no not his food
he said um for the for the lobster to
play what the [\h__\h] was that
ah
what
push okay we have to take this dude down
fast
what what what at least he disappears
but that
the amount oh my god is this touhou
bullet hell let's go
at least i have a million hearts to deal
with this [\h__\h]
okay
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
[Music]
okay i just
i don't know i don't i don't know i
don't even know
oh my god
i guess we never did the second level
the second um version the second
difficulty from this
uh area before
[Music]
oh he just she just came in and summoned
[\h__\h] okay you didn't even
consider fighting with me at all oh my
god
okay okay okay keep on dodging you
little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] off
now
it's over
no
okay one more
oh he's already back okay hey
oh oh oh oh
okay
yes
yeah baby
welcome to the cult
success
you can't see gandhi oh i'd oh i'll
definitely take the beetroots thank god
that's a good reward thank you
huh
ah i have the witness oh oh
for the for the coats right
going back um i hope they're not all
dead because i was gone for a while
yeah boy your bike oh no
i was gone for a while
20 minutes
um how's everyone doing
that's my faith i'm scared i'm scared
i'm scared oh it's fine it's fine
it's fine
oh god
hallelujah wait a second i'll make you
i'm gonna get food in a second
that'll help out a little bit
uh
huh
that's like you guys you're gonna look
strong yeah
everything is fine
thankfully
valley flowers
did you guys watch the program the the
five-year anniversary program because
hall alive had its fifth anniversary
hey yo
and they had some big official program
where they
looked back on
five years of paul alive on the history
of five years apollo lab not only homo
life japan but also whole live english
and a whole skies
live indonesia
all of them
i didn't watch all of it but i watched
at least
part of it
like an hour or two maybe
how long was it anyway
maybe it was only two hours i didn't
watch everything everything that's for
sure
what's the en segment thank you yeah i
think uh bales and enoch
were there as guests
a bit under two okay then i didn't watch
everything
i
the only thing i
have to
say is
the only criticism i have to say is that
that bald guy
he knew nothing about her life
he seems to be like the comedian
um like he's a comedian duo
with the other guy who's a fan of of
piccolo
but
so it makes sense that he's with him but
he knew nothing about
his whole life and that triggered me
yeah
and they worked with them before but
still he
knows nothing
yeah they just you know had some
comedians there for
um i'm seeing what do we call you
um
uh i don't know i'm running out of names
oh
uh
baldy
um
oh my god
it's real
it's a new form
it's a
how do they not have chickens but they
have red panda and poop and starfish or
whatever and crab and whatever the hell
that is
and is that is that a wolf
that's a unicorn how do you guys not
have chickens that's like such a basic
form
i'm so mad if they add chickens after
i'm finished with the game
i love red pandas though
welcome
they don't have any birds
really that's that's insanity no birds
at all what the [\h__\h] is that bird racism
what is your problem
what's their problem
how come we have full faith what the
hell
buddhism
[\h__\h]
batman he probably forgot that birds are
a thing
yeah he forgot
oh i feel like i i feel like i forgot
something but i don't remember what it
was
people say that oh it must have not been
something important but um i don't agree
with that i'm pretty sure
that does not always apply that's not
fair i don't like that at all
i don't like that sentiment
yeah yeah
when i was younger also people kept on
saying that to me nowadays not so much
anymore i
guess i also need to sacrifice someone
because someone's old
should have maybe done that before doing
the
sermon oh well
um i said
unfortunately we gain one we lose then
we gain two we lose one
that's fine
but actually the old one
that
i hope that one didn't have like a
loyalty reward for me but okay
where is uh here stress
strands has been so [\h__\h] stressed
that he dies at age 46.
oh
[Music]
pretty realistic
okay that's it for it got now guys leave
go
oh wait the other one was
did we get two red pandas
no the other one wasn't a red panda i
just saw it in the in the selection
cute
it's so cute
oh no i have to change it i'm sorry
i'll make you
i'll make it red too
i'll give you this
look
is that you should need you need
[Music]
okay if we have to get one more we can
just buy one
outside
and then we're good maybe someone will
even give me a quest
asking me to get some more
oh wait there's one more
[Laughter]
when you absolutely run out of ideas
what's a color i never used before i
wonder maybe this
the coat is growing
uh you just clean and you
sleep
where is the
oh
i see you
so we have someone coming back from the
mission
wait
wow
anyone's gonna clean that
no
are you we're gonna clean that
slow
too [\h__\h] slow
oh oh oh garfield's sick oh no wait
garfield comfort comfort i'm gonna heal
you
no
heel
garfield with the flowers flower power
how are things are called the phoenix
good we are actually ready for the final
bus stop jumping
am i ready though
am i ready for it
are you good
oh do i really not have enough beds now
[Music]
i'll take care of that
yeah 20 beds 21 followers
i don't have any more space
i'll put it here
i'll build it for you i'm such a nice
leader i'm gonna want good demons
ooh okay maybe only
um a good mix of attack and healing
demons perhaps
well um oh dear
we'll test it out and if we failed and
we can still like improve our demons by
raising their loyalty
oh it's from all the spiders
everyone can sleep in peace
and not be terrified
okay
i'm not gonna wake them i guess
you probably wouldn't even care but i'm
not gonna wake them now
um
wait 30 minutes
well the way i've been wasting time in
this game since day one
it just kind of like happens uh you
might be lucky
it might just happen naturally
oh
i was wondering why it was so fast i
guess it's just someone started to work
and i ended it oh
get to work
but they're not enough bets what i mean
they're not enough bets ah one collapsed
okay
let me upgrade
you guys take care of that i'll take
care of this
day of pickle challenge age what
oh yeah oh yeah it's raining birthday uh
like tomorrow
i'm gonna call in even though it's gonna
be early in the morning but i'm gonna
wake up for it i'm gonna be tired
probably
but you guys should watch her birthday
stream she's apparently i think she's
doing some vr stuff or so
judging by the thumbnail
should be fun
everybody wants lena birthday okay
it's 99 for us already
i guess so yeah
what time is it here or 8 p.m
half past 8 p.m i should cook after this
stream let's see if i
can finish before midnight
she's doing karaoke right now oh
oh
pre pre-birthday kind of okay what
wait isn't it what time is it
she's doing kayoke now isn't it like
some weird [\h__\h] time for her right
now
will i spend a lot of time at the
bus because if yes i wanna is it worth
doing these two things or or am i not
gonna be away for that long
[Music]
not really
oh 140. okay that's not so bad that's
not so bad i guess
just one fight okay then i guess we're
not gonna be away for so long
[Music]
i do something
in case i die
the faith is gonna go down
maybe
maybe we can do brainwashing ritual
no i done
[Music]
don't worry about your leader i will
come back home safely just believe in me
and have no doubts at all
otherwise you know what's gonna happen
okay kiara will change it up
okay and then here
um
let's see
plus six so i think we want garth oh
plus seven
should i go for the the red hearts plus
seven or for the half a spirit heart
plus six i guess curly patootie would be
better
oh i think
yeah and then
oh plus free attack melee attack
[Music]
two milli attack plus four
explosion
okay i'll go for
the plus four explosion
and then even one more attack or
um
or one more health related thing what do
you think
we have
in terms of high level things we have
plus six spirit hearts
and plus five
where was it plus five spirit hearts
plus three melee attack more to safer
yeah cause they also they don't even
attack that much
anyway
okay let's do a cigar filter
okay let's see how that works
and then make some food
don't [\h__\h] it up
nice nice okay
should be good enough
[Music]
wow oh you have a quest for me uh
i don't know if i want to accept it
oh another friend in the silk cradle
i look
accepted but um
if in case i lose so many followers that
i need more anyway
or not we're a fan
maybe not worth it if i lose them i can
just buy them
yeah sorry i'm sorry i'm so sorry lately
let me let me let me your gift gift oh i
only have necklace um let me inspire you
[Music]
this one is smooth i can smooch
oh it's like an extra action to improve
their
the
loyalty
very cute
how are you know
don't get jealous kfb
oh let's also take confession
who wants to confess to me
ew
indeed
wow
that adds a lot of loyalty
i confess i have another holo membership
that's okay
support her life
we've all you got
[Music]
i ended by accident but okay at least i
hope it was one of the low level foods
at least i get um
an extra heart from that
yeah
matsuka no hatto morata
they're not full
on hunger but there's leftover foods
this is bugged out again i'm not sure
i'm just gonna
add some more
just in case
ah now they're coming to eat again i
feel like the the foods often
bug out oh it might be the demon people
i wonder
oh no
disgusting
absolutely disgusting but now they ate
the
they i ate those foods
they ate those foods
okay
okay i'm gonna go
[Music]
i'm going
to the last bus
bus fight
because i'm scared
quiet
uh wait what weapon do i get
how do i know what weapon i get
is it is it gonna be wait how can i
choose
what it i mean i hope they don't take
all my
oh my beloved followers now
should i i should save
i can't stand
maybe safe outside
i'll be able to choose ooh
um i might take a dagger
but it depends on the enemy but i think
i'll take a dagger
howard
[Music]
oh we're in that world now
oh
nice they do give me
every weapon as a choice
um but not every curse
that's kind of lame because i don't even
like these curses that much but i'll
take the
i will take the projectile
and
wait what was that one
wasn't that it whatever
axe cleaver and gauntlet um
not dagger not sword
i'll increase your
i like the poison in this one
i don't really like the accent itself
but
i might
i might go for it because of the poison
because this one only house of divine
inspiration that's [\h__\h]
this one at least helps the damage
that's not really not the best but okay
are these three demons well i feel like
that looks like two demons only where
are my other demons
are they
are they inside each other
well
that's the big god that i've been
serving so far but now we want to
challenge him
there can only be
vessel i relinquish you from your
service to the cr red crown return it to
me and embrace the end that awaits with
this last sacrifice of my most devoted
follower i will be freed
finally
i will be free
approach vessel and lay your life down
at my
[Music]
oh god
they're still alive they're still alive
wait wait no i don't wanna
uh refuse
i hear my free demons now you can see
them clearly
[Music]
wow what the
what the [\h__\h] never seen it look like
this before
so you have betrayed me lamb
you have shunt my gospel and claimed
yourself a false idol i'm a real idol i
swear
that crowd is mine by divine right you
think to stand in the very face of death
allow me i will give this rapture taste
of your wife
oh you first okay easy
easy easy easy easy
easy easy what are you gonna summon
oh [\h__\h]
oh what the [\h__\h]
yeah
okay i already lost a lot of hearts
unnecessarily [\h__\h]
ah
but i didn't give hearts back
i don't take care of this beast monster
i will cut that headphone cramp on his
own head okay cool
wait did i say anya no
oh
[Music]
almost happen
there we go okay so far so good pretty
easy good hits
maybe axel's a good choice because i
have to be so fast that um a dagger or a
sword that gives you a lot of fast hits
it's not quite worth it we need one
strong hit and then run one strong hit
and then run
you think yourself victorious you think
yourself safe do not forget you belong
to me
even after i have slaughtered you your
pain will not end you cannot escape me
even in death
i wonder if this one has like a second
face as well
of course you do something like that
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
my hp is not looking good
can i sacrifice them though
my my followers
he's easy though
oh nice it's like a like a carnival
yay oh oh oh there's more um do i wanna
thank god i have some projectiles
oh
okay okay cool cool cool cool
oh no i don't believe you defeated of
course not that was easy did you believe
we defeated did you think that to be all
there was to a being such as i no no no
actually not
you fought yourself above
oh god
no actually really not
so we got my hp recharged please oh
oh lights on please
wait that looks like you know that image
of good at with the
with the nails and uh and uh
the um fake lashes and the lipstick
that look like that for a second
[Music]
maybe you don't know what i'm talking
about but inside that edited image where
she has all these things on top of her i
think that was a good image
you are corrupt false idol your
corruption has no doubt spread what
oh how generous one half heart is what
they give me no what the [\h__\h]
no
is that what i'm fighting
please don't please don't sacrifice my
babies ow
oh that's very bad oh
um
oh god i i will have to sacrifice
someone if that is an option
come on get out of there
okay these eyes are super easy to deal
with but
still
get out of there
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't get sacrifices
dominant
what happens then to my people
oh thank god i still have 21 of them
oh but they make it makes them think i'm
weak see that's that's good that i bring
brainwashed them
[Music]
yay
yeah
[Music]
let's do all four each time of course
that's that's fine but wow
i wish i could get more wait you know
what what we could at least do is change
our guard because this garb is useless
in this situation maybe there's
something better than
although i kind of doubt it oh wait a
second
what this is what you guys meant with
oh
this is what you guys spent with take
the money from the box or so
[Laughter]
um
anyway hmm
uh
okay i can't revive anyone yet but
i finally took it
it wasn't that much considering that's
the first time i took it
um
okay well
you slept useless those are but um
damaged out increases after each kill
nah
curses deals deal double damage and
caused half the floor but melee weapon
no
nope these are all useless
these are all kind of useless for the
final fight
i'll just wait up the
red one
ah the blue one is okay
wait what
all hearts will be replaced but ah
yeah but that does mean that when he
spawns the red hearts for you to heal
the rare ones
you can't even use them
because
you can only use
the only energy unless that changes his
spawns to blue hearts but
you know
[Music]
in any case we'll have to do it again
a quest uh
what if i just ignore you i don't think
i want to accept your quest because
you know
[Music]
oh no food
i'm so sorry i don't want to take your
quest no no no no no
oh no he gets angry okay sorry
what is it
i'm gonna say no
i don't need them right now
sorry
at least now faith can't go down
all right should we challenge them again
after taking some demons with me
uh
flies away returns of red hearts
and then
[Music]
still this one
but
you know i think i'm going with the same
same ones because
i could revive patty i don't remember
what patty had but
[Music]
i could also go with this one
but i'll go with this one
not the bump why
only one hit per fight or what
really can i change it
ah more explosion damage
nice okay
we'll see if we fail again which we
probably will because that's kind of
tough wow i have to literally really
practice it i mean that was the first
time so i didn't know the attacks and
there was some
oh look at the red panda again
there were some tough ones but now that
i know them the more i get to know them
the easier it should be
okay so let's do it
[Music]
just a matter of retry
a lot of bullet spamming going on and uh
spamming those
horns out of the ground
oh [\h__\h] ham are you kidding me
axe
godly that's a
significantly more
damaging one i'll try it out i wonder
how significant it is
and then we have oh the ice snow
um
also summon ghosts from slain
enemies
wait will they help me fight
that seems good
huh
they do a bit
okay
okay are you gonna tell me the whole
dialogue again
look i am
let me skip it
what if i say accept
what happens bad ending
[Music]
oh okay that wasn't really unnecessary
hit right in the beginning
okay only one hit though i think that's
already better than before and there's
only was it only half a heart we're back
at full health then
uh he probably took a blue heart though
huh
oh
oh oh but they just stay there until i
need them
[Laughter]
easy little easy
a bit reckless there because i was
laughing but that was the speed run holy
[\h__\h] and all the heart says it's just
lying there
yo yo
already much better than before
up
i'll waste it
did he just damage his own
his own friends oh [\h__\h] that's that's
always true father had like a long
distance one
ah sorry [\h__\h] up
[Music]
wow
never try
[Music]
pretty hard to dodge that little [\h__\h]
that little [\h__\h]
why are you here
i'll heal you
we're cooling
don't i have enough flowers oh man that
sucks
then it must be bread rest bed rest
instead i'm sorry
okay it's really good that we have the
brainwashing on
at least the first part of the fight was
much better
um look at it eventually
i don't think it will take too many
tries i might be drinking myself but i
honestly don't think so
youtube
[Music]
it seems manageable unless there is like
a bird face
if there's a first person we might be
[\h__\h]
but i guess i might just take hearts
only this time
oh hey
whoa whoa whoa the game just lagged
really badly
i hope there's not a bird face yeah
thanks for the pinky hello happy
birthday sweater oh
congratulations
[Music]
nice to have you back
uh please stay go to sleep i guess
[Music]
what was that oh did you see the lag too
was it not only me
[Music]
i'm gonna max this all out by the end of
the stream
i think i wanted
nothing you can level up matters anymore
shh i know but still you know
for completion's sake
oh this is full
you guys properly working here
okay
oh i'll make some food and then i'll go
[Music]
y'all my food is not looking so good
amy
and what if i run out of food i can buy
i can buy seeds but while i'm gone they
don't produce enough stuff here
[Music]
no i don't want your stupid quest
no i don't see you
no i don't see you i don't see you at
all
yeah i can make them eat grass again and
i guess i can buy fish yeah
all right
i never try
and another try the the higher damage
didn't
seem so noticeable to me
from that weapon
i might prefer just a poison one
poison weapon best
first try season three
i forgot the demons oh [\h__\h]
oh let me go back
wow
cool sign
godly sword ah
i forgot
i forgot the demons i'm just gonna die
i guess we'll see this practice
nakamura
how could i forget
i wish i could go back
take the godly sword
and
[Music]
i'm taking those shots so that we have
some
long distance damage but we're obviously
not gonna make it
obviously not gonna win this time
please have mercy
if you let go of the crown i don't want
to say yeah can i try now just do they
just kill me and i return to my cult
this just sent me back
yeah okay here we go it starts
that was a speed rando
did you just drop a blue hood
oh he dropped the blue heart i don't
know if i prefer that or she
ow
he doesn't even he doesn't even send
them out into the direction where i am i
think he just sends those out in a
random direction so i can't even predict
it
can't even predict it that's kind of
mean
okay these ones these ones go in a
circle
maybe i was just too fast for him to
keep up
again i am so [\h__\h] fast okay the
first ones are just jokes
they're just a joke
oh another blue heart i guess
in this case when you come in with so
few hearts they just uh give you
they just give you blue hearts
i'm in like super focus mode
oh no not again not again not again not
again not again
i downed him
well that is not auto aim huh
okay wait i got pretty far
how much help do i have left i have i
think i have more health left than
before when i had all my demons
but i didn't see
[Music]
my hands are a little bit sweaty
not good
oh yeah i have a lot more health left
were they so fast last time
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh
i have to aim that projectile
some reason i thought it just goes
wherever the hell i want it to go
wow
nice stalin's down
it's actually a good run
okay chill chill chill here okay
whatever
so far so good pretty easy
oh
that's a big one
nice that one's down
only one left
am i doing it without demons i'm scared
i don't want to fail now this would be
pretty cool
cool this is like jumping ropes
this is manageable i like these ones way
more than the round ones that just go
everywhere
ah
one heart they don't drop anything
that's so mean
oh
this is still new territory to me so
that was really close if i kill the eyes
that's not the end is it
that's not the end
or what would that have been the end
[Music]
the eyes are the end
one
they dropped charges oh i didn't realize
r.i.p and aspirin have become friends
sweet
i'm so happy it doesn't like sacrifice
everyone that was a big worry for me
why are they
while i'm gone they don't do any work
here what the [\h__\h]
yeah assign
farm go go go go go go go
oh it's still the same day oh
it makes sense that's why
when no food is being made the time goes
by slowly or not at
all i'm gone
ah they are stuck in case okay
i guess okay that's realistic they don't
let them work while they're there
[Music]
can i not use the ones
from before
why
because they're sick or something
it doesn't offer me the same ones they
get tired
no
yeah
which one which one
and this casper did i bring casper along
is that why he got sick
also this one red no i didn't bring
bread
they don't look tired i can't see if
they're tired because they're
brainwashed
uh i did better without them
okay i guess we can try again yeah we
just take whatever we get it's not the
best demons but better than nothing i
guess
[Music]
yeah i thought i could only inspire once
per day or can i only inspire each
follower once per day oh
i bought one follower per day
it's each follower once per
[Music]
i
i just found that out now
[Laughter]
it took me a while
i mean it would have been it would have
taken a lot of time to dance with
everyone once per day so
i wouldn't have done that anyway i think
can i dance with you no okay
but the money is only one person per day
right
yeah i think so no wait that's again i
chose the same person again
no the money is also one every single
one of them
all right it's not that much though
it's not that worth it
i didn't make that much of a loss
means follower
go team
wow
oh
that's embarrassing
i didn't think it would be so generous
huh
all right let's let's make use of the
time while they're still
um brainwashed
to go again
um
[Music]
plus four
that's pretty decent um
[Music]
this plus five
maybe this one
ah eat food too yeah okay
maybe that one
i'll remember you oh i can't
yeah
why not
because i already did i already choose
him
oh i can't do two of the same time
ah well then i'm forced to take like one
of these for example
[Music]
anything else i want to do oh yeah eat
food
i'll i'll eat a grass meal
that's mine
yummy vegetables oh i throw up too wait
do i
how did i heal that back
what
that hurts me
oh come on
it's my that's my food no that's
i'm full
[\h__\h] hell
i can't even eat it
how long does it take until i'm not full
anymore
[Music]
and what is it
a variety of fish dishes
[Music]
i eventually might run out of food so i
might actually do that
but no
sorry
don't be mad
what i did
okay no extra hide it's okay
don't don't need it it's not like i need
it
no extra hot even less heights than
before but we get we get we start with
extra blue hearts right i think
or extra red hearts i don't know
and we get more more hearts sent to us
more handicaps yes
more handicaps the more i get the better
i get at gaming apparently judging by
the last run where i already thought i
was gonna lose
okay well that's not much
uh ooh critical hits lord and uh some of
the ghosts are attacking about enemies
oh that's they're all good what would
you guys go for significantly more
damage or
six six point eight
or a critical hit chance or a chance of
summoning a ghost the damage here is
pretty good too 4.5 oh it's godly okay
good that we got that one ooh
a devastating melee attack that also has
a chance to possess impacted enemies
i've never had this one before
off of the crown
charge for increased power
i would i would say this one
sounds sick
let's go demons
i project that would have been better
yeah
long distance oh well
i can skip that
what the [\h__\h]
obviously gonna be a little bit slower
than when i out had um
out the
long
sword
ow what the [\h__\h] okay
not my best friend
oh but still fast
and i got half a heart from my demon i
think
see this one's random
that one's
definitely random
ow
two times
okay okay okay stupid stupid
sorry
okay he's dead
it doesn't do too much
damage
yeah the sword
fits better
yeah i prefer the sword for this battle
i'm guessing it wouldn't possess a boss
monster but
but i wonder if it could possess the
small ones
okay here during this time you could
easily do some damage with um oh the
demon did something
with a long distance weapon but oh well
i
i i i i was kind of cornered there
oh
[Music]
the run not so bad so far even though i
did some mistakes with the smaller ones
unnecessary mistakes you guys can't
touch me right now
stop
what that's a bug
they did they're still there and they
did damage them they're still doing
damage to me
i think
[Music]
am i getting damaged they already hit me
like five times
okay i'm not sure do i have more damage
than before why are they still here
they're not supposed to be here
okay that really pisses me off
men look set
that's not there i've gone now but
i kind of messed everything up
[Music]
okay
oh that's me and that's mean
that's me
even if they didn't do any actual damage
while during the waiting screen
[\h__\h]
look at them
and still
um they were still around when they
shouldn't be around anymore they should
have despawned
[Music]
they should have this one actually i
should tell them to do bed rest not to
sleep
oh no this one's fine actually
oh man
i had some flowers i could at least heal
like some of my
peeps
like two sick ones or only one actually
oh you're sick though
oh go go go
address pasta
so mean
oh spider no no no
no
trying to get the spider thank you
uh who do i summon now oh wait this one
this one
works
plus five
how are you not still not done tuning
head-hearted bosses excuse me this was
just my first try
and last time i almost did it
oh [\h__\h] i could have had cutie patootie
oh well
last time i almost had it
and this time i was sabotaged
so mean
[Music]
okay this is the strongest attack one i
have i'll just go with this one
okay
it's in the middle of the night but
let's go guys no time to waste
while we still have they're all carrying
money
well we still have the
brainwashing tutorial on we should make
good use of it
good
morning
go next
you know the more i play the more i like
challenge your boss
oh [\h__\h] i forgot the food
i can still go back the more i challenge
a boss the more i um start sucking at it
so we're slowly entering that territory
of me getting worse rather than getting
good
um which one is safe to eat
maybe anything that's two star
i have nothing to start
official the berries may be
any regular food
maybe the berry bowl haven't made a
berry bowl in a while
and he likes that one
okay
okay that's better
yeah it would be sad
if i killed the boss too fast it would
be like
undermining
the difficulty of the game
so here we go again
i think we're still
still
doing quite well
last time i was just sabotaged
okay what do we have a stupid hammer
a vein hammer with poison [\h__\h] hammers
you're honestly giving me two hammers
kind of sucks
weak weapon
um but oh i've never had this one before
a horde of ghosts at target is this a
long distance
should i go for it
but i've never used it before i don't
know how to use it
it's good is it good
no hamburger would be terrible cause
like it takes so much time to spawn it
it's a line attack a straight line
it's a horde of ghosts the target nearby
enemies that doesn't sound like a
straight line
we'll try that
you guys tell me it's good but what is
it what does it do
the line attack doesn't sound like it is
okay okay
um
oh [\h__\h] okay i wasted that one
[Music]
oh man
got too many hits
[Music]
i'm getting too clumsy
[Laughter]
no
no i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry come in
yeah for the guns that's something about
doing combos and you're stronger
but as you can see
not much time for
combos
roll into that one
good good dodging though
i missed
one hit okay
[Applause]
i see this time they actually disappear
as they should
oh someone report that bug
the cult of the lamp
the hands are sweaty
my eyes are so sweaty
okay they start with some crazy [\h__\h] in
the beginning let's be careful
oh not so crazy
you're not always that bad
last time they started with some really
random ones
i liked my previous weapon combinations
much better
although the ghosts do seem out kind of
cool
wait the eyes are the last thing right
this actually is so nice
oh nice that one
okay okay i'm like really focused sorry
i'm not talking
ah i felt some lag
oh
whoa i got a hit
actually impressive
lag
where is it lagging
oh we are very much crumbling
one dead one more to go
some heart drops would be nice
oh the middle is pretty safe
[Music]
drops got me
it's fine it's fine it's fine
what are the poison props droplets or
whatever that is maybe not poison but
great for such a bad weapon yeah cause i
never got the combos i tried to be
careful to move away
i have a good feeling
i'm getting more and more used to
what like their moves so
please no please sleep
i demand you to sleep
and wait who are the other tired ones
where did they go
are they not tired
[Music]
they only
they actually recover really fast
they don't need that much time
noise
that's four
melee attack
projectile but only plus two
[Music]
better than nothing
i'll call it this one
is that the highest i have for the
hearts right now
not very high
no i don't really need extra attacks
i just honestly i would take hearts only
and i would probably be fine
[Music]
okay okay
how many demons can you summon the ones
free
at the highest level and then we have
them at the highest level so i was
summoned free
uh except for that one time where i
didn't summon anyone and still went
almost until the end
don't have half a spirit how does that
have some extra damage um
sometimes at one half height
can go a long way but i don't know we're
going with it now
oh a chance to heal the wielder
we shall go with the axe yeah
i think a dagger would be nice too but
um i don't like the effect on it
i never
noticed the healing effect before is it
good
to aim
i have to hold to aim
ah it's that one
yeah i think i know which one it is
kind of difficult
but
empiric weapons barely work
freeze hit enemies
freeze hit also not bad
huh
maybe maybe i want to go with the freeze
it no
[Music]
a little healing better than no healing
at all
[Music]
and where are you going
you see my buddy just flying away one of
my demons where where the [\h__\h] is he
going
my god i can't even go past that point
yeah that aim is difficult in this fight
i think so too a projectile that where
you don't have to like
you know slow motion aim
that would be fine he's just where did
he go
he really dropped me a heart on the path
where i won't be able to reach it
later on
um there you go that's another bug
bruh
oh
waste it
my attacking dodge is insane though
oh the ice doesn't work on him
wow
it's really really really speedy that
timing between attack and dodge with an
axe that timing is so tiny
come back oh yeah they come back these
ones come back
okay i'm stupid i'm officially stupid
nice these ones i dodged properly
easy
although my shoulder hurts so bad the
whole time
it's really distracting because i keep
on trying to
like move it so that i can like
some pain
[Music]
monkey um
also i feel like even though we haven't
like really high fps
i'm really
lagging
a lot
oh
so fast
okay
okay okay going in with some pretty
good amount of um hp
oh guaranteed healing for my weapon oh
well
the minions i couldn't pay too much
attention to them with the with this um
slow weapon
two hearts it felt like i had more
i'm down to two hearts
please wrap oh there's one there's half
a heart there
that's one hit
oh god stay away
[Music]
let's see the game feels so laggy
ah
okay wow 100 focus mode
oh now it's already one down
okay
at least he's not doing it at the same
time as they're spawning the balls like
last time that was pretty difficult to
handle
oh pretty good
careful careful
nice hits
even single hits are precious
ah wasted that reach is so low
[Music]
look
oh
okay
[Music]
that's [\h__\h] means
i'm so sorry
i got so far i got so far
going
i'm so sorry
i'm so
sorry oh sorry i'm gonna inspire you
it was really close i got down to the
last eye
did i tell everyone to rest
okay
still brainwashed wow i hope it's not
bugged it feels very long now
um
okay
are those half heights that from where
were they from my demon
[Music]
i wonder what that was
seven plus seven
oh damn it i should have again i should
have summoned her
plus four
they went for my demon
damn they don't give you any hearts at
all in that battle huh
okay plus three
plus four i think that's the highest
um up them first oh well
but who am i gonna use for the weapon
just i'll take a look if i can
inspire him even more
plus two plus two
was one plus one not good
that's two
vesta name two let's find name two
[Music]
uh
is here
i won't be able to inspire him too much
like i won't be able to get his loyalty
up that high but oh well
you're all so tired huh
sorry you're coming with me once again
once again
try hammer no
i will not
try the hammer maybe i should try
tangent thing though
sometimes that's really helpful but no i
have to focus i have to focus
only food for me sorry guys you guys
don't seem to be that hungry anyway
okay can't beat
on to
another crusade
this
will surely be the run
the run of our dreams yeah i hope i get
a good weapon this and that's also very
important but that's just rng
gotta be lucky
scary
oh hammers [\h__\h] no vampire hammer poison
hammer
godly hammer oh but look
wait vampiric sword necromantic dagger
godly hand like [\h__\h]
um
dagger seems better then
or
sword
it has the same damage at least this
one's faster though which means more
hits but both both have 2.2 damage
well you would you would hope it would
actually heal me i'll give it a chance
oh
ooh projectiles they they actually um
don't they actually follow
the enemies these ones
i think i think these ones are like
i have to aim now oh okay
okay then i got it wrong
let's go
the best thing would be to go out here
with no damage at all
but so far it's decent
okay i think i got one hit
these ones come back don't they yeah
so many of them
good damage
oh what the [\h__\h]
okay still fine
so fine
i think it only took blue hearts right
because i had to keep on trying to heal
myself with the run running through the
half heart but it never took it so i'm
guessing
i was full i don't really have
the ability to pay attention to that
i only took blue hats nice
nice
uh i didn't see that one
that was so close because
available
say this is the wrong earring you're
jinxing it
don't jinx it
my shoulder hurts so bad
[Music]
it's it's a sword the the
the
weapon really matters
what's that
okay that's what we're starting with
three times
they they are actually really easy to
predict when they close their eyes
they're about to summon
and usually they do their attack like
three times not always though
better better safe than sorry
[Music]
nice hit
one two and three
nice one down
i barely remember that attack
okay yeah i should have known
where am i oh i thought it was one of my
demons for a second for some reason oh
corning
nice this is a run
i think i can confidently say like how
much would i have to [\h__\h] up
unless you know
you never know i guess
come on
up
[Music]
oh oh no oh no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
that one
tonight
you're gonna become one of mine
you have surprised me but i saw no more
instead of crown bearing deity
imagine mercy on you to be eventual
false idol or a merciful coward no
longer can you blame your vile acts on
me
yeah
i kinda wanna murder him
i wanna murder him
special follower well we're not going to
play this game anymore yeah aren't we
do we can we
should we keep him
if there's no like bad um
things happening if i spare him no bad
ending
um
[Music]
okay i'm nice
look at him and his horns though he's
literally the devil
he's so mean
your weak
[Music]
both options you kind of made fun of me
both options
you'll be mine i'll turn you into the
[\h__\h] pig
what you're supposed to be anyway
hey my lovely
little piglets chickens
hybrids
pick pickins
hybrid
yeah
[Music]
sacrifice for born vessel was sent once
more in textual form no longer a servant
no less than a god
uh-huh that's so fast thank you for
playing noble disciple please spread the
good word you know far so that others
may be blessed oh it's credits by the
divine teachings of the mighty land yay
so glad we did it
nice the
last boss fight was really not that
difficult
i know i failed a few times but this
system is really easy
and the fact that you only have the two
kilo three eyes there
[Music]
i would have expected one more one more
little challenge there
nice that's me
looks a bit different but that's me
chubby bang
kata thank you my sweet demons your
half-hearts are really useful
i love you it's not work
leslie
oh sleep flap frog you too you did such
good work
where is he there
oh he's not red anymore
now he speaks normally the one who waits
convert me to your clown i will follow
your teachings painfully
you are now my servant
nothing else that's all you are
we can't change him
you know i'll put him back to red
we can't actually change the form or
variant interesting oh
strong constitution heals fast
materialistic uh-huh
faithful these are all positive we'll
never reach old age nice
they're all positive
but is there anything to do after you
kill the boss i don't think so unless
you have some side quests left over i
guess just worship me a little [\h__\h]
and not enough beds no he he doesn't
even deserve a bed but okay
how do i not have enough beds what the
[\h__\h]
how is that possible
i have a [\h__\h] ton of beds
you little [\h__\h]
i should just imprison him forever even
though he didn't do anything bad
what's that dude why are you so angry
wait how can i why can't i not read his
uh mind other
i'm homeless
skeptical convert i've converted but not
convinced let's see how things go of
course you're convinced
oh
devotee gain more faith when you give a
sermon
the rest they're all positive
substance encouraged absolution
good day young
the intent of an l is sacrificed but he
really he really is into it now even
though he was
resisting so much
nice
mmm
oh well still he's uh he's uh in theory
he's a good employee to have
in theory
well that's it then i guess
well this year is my call queen phoenix
thank you
this is this is it oh they're still here
why you guys can i frame you guys why
are you here
nothing no
why are they here they should be set
free oh well
hold on good plan thank you
i think that's it
let me save
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
very nice last call at the church you
mean one last sermon
hi
thank you everyone so much for watching
the playthrough
of cult of the lamp oh nothing's
happening
the game crash
oh there you go
that took a while
any more to revive
i mean we could only revive one but
sure wait that was sacrificing [\h__\h]
um
can i cancel
oh we do have one aldi
that one's old
doesn't look old
oh it's fine the spine is fine we don't
need
nah it's fine we won't surprise to
survive to revive anyone
okay
ah it was a fun really fun game what can
i pause oh well whatever we already
saved
whoosh
darn cushion for watching everybody
we're gonna read super chats of course
um
[Music]
i'm glad i
glad i got to clear it today
big accomplishment another game finished
now another game to write down in my
books of finished games
on my list
overall
i will give the game a rating of
8 out of 10
because there's still a lot of bugs that
should be fixed and there were no
chickens what the [\h__\h]
uh
if that would be soft then they might
even get a 10 out of 10 out of it from
me
[Music]
i think they're working on fixing bugs
and all that i wonder if they're aware
of the ones that appeared in my stream
maybe maybe one of the developers is
watching who knows if yes then nice game
it was a lot of fun my mom really loved
watching this playthrough as well as she
told me
yeah
she enjoyed this one she said it fits me
really well
and it kind of got me
into roguelit like games roguelite i
guess
um
got me a bit closer to that genre and
i'm hooked
i also really really like the aesthetics
and the graphics
the characters even though there were no
no chickens i also liked all the side
characters
the
fishing was fun the gambling was fun
i loved the voice acting
so cute
so freaking cute
ah
that's how you voice act the game
without worrying about you know um like
language
um
choice
yeah
it fits the game so well too because
it's so dorky
very very dorky
so i guess we'll um go read super chat i
should wonder if i should go to an idol
meeting how am i feeling how am i
feeling
i think i'm feeling decent
i'll just go over to my office already
[Music]
where am i here
oh
this makes me a bit smaller and then put
the chat here
[Music]
and then we'll put on some music
i've got like so many
so many freaking messages on discord
what the hell
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
okay let's let's look at the rest later
there's just too much
every morning i wake up i have so many
messages it's hard to keep up you know
remember when when i told you guys that
i was told that i'm the one who answers
the most and the fastest in whole life
english that's why
that's why managers like me
more recently i've been having a hard
time keeping up as well
i have something here oh yeah
what a dolls
oh
[Music]
i think i downloaded these randomly
i like this one
ah i think this one i played before
maybe
[Music]
did i
excuse me the u part gave me um beatles
vibes
okay where do i have to start reading
you guys no
[Music]
look here
really only that oh yeah cause i called
up
and then members only i suppose
[Music]
it cuts off weirdly there oh well
and so let me get rid of this
[Music]
okay it starts with trevor g and with a
pinky
ah i was wondering
your name changed a little bit first of
all i was gonna ask you since when are
you or don't say time but i think you
got uh
akiroza senpai just like me as a
as a as a
or she recommended oshie from that
twitter
thingy did you guys try it out yeah a
lot of people got here what the hell
so many
rng don't go
you didn't get kiwawa i got quinoa
i got you oh a bunch of you got kiwawa
i got fauna
was it possible to try more than once
i don't think there was like quite the
waiting time
took me a while too i didn't get any
reply
when did you send it i for me it also
took like at least a day
and since then maybe even more built up
even more lag oh they might have also
already ended it i think it was maybe
limited time only
as well i don't know if they're still
doing it you can check the replies
in their account if they're still doing
it
sent it yesterday but after the stream
it's too late
i don't know if it is
hmm
yeah if it really takes too much time
try canceling the retweet and then doing
it again
so anyway get a thing with this app owl
your
your perfect picture is an apple owl now
that's so cute why didn't that happen or
because of lucid dye i guess
you can it has been an impeccable two
years of you as my ocean but i regret it
for me that much like yourself the whole
life twitter bot told me my
comfortability
compatibility compatibility huh is best
with aki
i know welcome here is my one and only
horsey family my beloved
i hope you don't mind so if you do don't
worry much like the ml video i'm sure
you will forget all about me too no
it's only a matter of time maybe
maybe we'll meet at an aki stream
someday until the owl until then i'll be
the same
you can't do this to me no come back
what the [\h__\h]
you can have more than one ocean even
though that's not the ideal way but
you're gonna have more than one i can be
your second old me i guess
[Music]
come foreign
come back please
oh my what's your already kian and akita
anyway well that's perfect
perfect
as all things should be
[Music]
why not both number one or she's
i don't know if that could even be true
like when you ask a mother who's your
favorite child if you're one of the
children she will say i love you both
the same but in reality she definitely
has a favorite child it's the same thing
with oshie's
you'll definitely have a favorite one
[Music]
cure is releasing the update so have fun
with that guys i just remembered
tickets
as if props to the depths were allowing
kiana to get an early access to her
their amazing game yeah i'm really happy
they gave me early access
i'm glad i asked normally like you know
with like bigger games or so
i think the process to ask something
like that it's a bit more complicated
and takes more time but in this case i
was like oh it should be pretty easy to
get
permission
since it's literally a fan game so i
don't see why they would say no
i just tried and there we go
streaming at reasonable time for eu
viewers don't really have time to watch
those 6am streams you're welcome
there's but you should tell more eu
viewers to watch me
where are they
really like um we need more eu audience
i've been catering to you guys but
where where are you guys
huh
you bros don't go
[Music]
some of you are here but
you need to grow
the game mccree thank you
thank you
[Music]
cannot i'm a long time fan but i'm only
now able to do super chat so of course
my first recipe chat had to go to my
first aussie
i couldn't continue to be impressed by
your hard work and the quality of the
content you create thank you for
everything thank you so much
super chat from brazil
thank you i really appreciate that and
it's nice to hear from people for the
first time when they've been like fans
for so long
it's very refreshing
nice to know that you're still here and
then on your first aussie
hopefully your last one too
thank you
[Music]
please continue supporting me i would be
very happy
the great rv zero dankest in purple
dragon danger
mh thank you
i guess so
i am
black mage 666
sir the real packaging
thank you for the ransom attack very
sweet of you
[Music]
thank you and take care of yourself
have a nice evening
a good night
oh
[Music]
travel to west fallon stadium in
dortmund to support my beloved
copenhagen i guess there's like a like a
football match a soccer match but now
here all i can think of is kiwawa and
the kfp himalayan keeps me always in
heart no matter where no matter when
you can never stop thinking of me
understandable
the game recreation
the social artist thank you for the
pinky
the only adoption made for jrr died was
made to keep the rights for it for to ri
what
the only adaption made before jrr died
was made to keep the rights for to it
and were sold back to jrr for much more
than they were bought for
the rides were bought before loyal the
rings got famous
uh
i don't quite understand what you're
saying
i mean i understand the general topic
bullet
they first sold it and then but
took it back
and then what
what
[Music]
interesting
i guess there was
a lot of a lot of stuff happened i know
we talked about it but
yeah
i guess a lot of stuff happened too in
terms of
rights for lord of the rings and stuff
[Music]
oh
luna wolf
[Music]
interesting there's more more
lord of the rings geek
geeking here i hate to be that guy
gallagher's magical power is mostly stem
for neenah
the ring of water the only innate ones
she has are divination and telepathy of
the rings collateral is not the one
depicted in rings of power
oh you should have a showdown with my
mommy and discuss with my mommy because
so you're saying that it was fine
how powerful she was
uh
shown in in rings of power because she
wasn't as powerful yet at that moment
because she didn't have that ring of
water yet
you and my mom should sit in one room
and i see i feel like only one person is
gonna leave the room
afterwards
i wonder if she's still watching
but interesting interesting
be interesting
i'll use that argument against my mom
sometime baby
if she didn't hear this
and she laughing
[Music]
oh yeah pokemon trailer i did see the
pokemon trailer too
um there are some cool characters
revealed
[Music]
but honestly the whole
theme
with
like school kids
fighting each other i mean loki that was
always the theme loki
but this time
it's
made into the main theme and you know
the enemies are like uh
not going to school and all that and
their other school kids i don't know i
it feels kind of tacky and childish to
me
but it's a pokemon game so i guess it's
allowed to be
childish i don't know
it's
it feels
they should know there's so many adult
pokemon players
and then for us
i don't know about you guys but for me
that feels like a very childish thing
going on there
but who knows maybe i'll change my mind
when i play the game
[Music]
um
maybe after trying it out i'll change my
mind
i agree
a lot of kids who played og pokemon grew
up exactly who knows maybe there's even
more adult fans of pokemon than child
fans
of the game at least i don't know maybe
not i don't know could be though
[Music]
almost definitely might be
and yeah also yeah yeah adults got the
money so
there's definitely more adults buying
themselves the games they want
than children because
adults won't always buy them what they
want
[Music]
true
black rich and duncan paul gomez
since us scooby-doo came from the
syllables
in frank sinatra's hit song strangers in
the night
scooby-doo with the use
is a coincidence uh-huh i don't know
um
what to do with that comment
[Music]
i don't know who my favorite girl was
though i think it's just the main girl
the the girl called will i think
i think she might have been my favorite
[Music]
time doing work and you really improved
since your last two whole cure videos
thank you
you know in the beginning i i think i
still was
kind of bad but i got better later on i
would say um
had to get to know the characters and
feel their vibe you know
[Music]
oh you got me in the comfortability test
thank you
thank you thank you i appreciate it
for trying that out
now you know we are meant for each other
thank you
[Music]
i was driving while listening to taylor
swift on my way to work but i
immediately turned it off and i and came
to work while listening to kiwanis song
thanks for streaming dancing
thank you i think i already read that
super chat before but yeah thank you
shane i'm glad you made it in time for
my stream
welcome home
the maple leaf 2501 thanks for the pinky
as well
careful calling her better than taylor
swift miss swift might write a song
about kiana breaking her heart
me
i don't know then she would write a song
about ivana breaking her heart
not me i didn't do anything i'm just
better
if i'm bored better what can i do about
it
not my fault that i was born like this
fabulous
gorgeous
perfect
i almost sound like crony
space wonderful thank you
absolutely
and i'm done with those
i'm gonna read the members only super
chats quickly
[Music]
don't know where it is
i'll just go without okay
remember it's only
[Music]
again
i said it before i think i saw that
tweet and we don't really dance thank
you
again
thank you
it's coming closer indeed
a two-year anniversary not only for me
but also for you guys
wow i hope i can manage to schedule a
stream on that day but
you guys might have to remind me
like a week in advance so that i can
play accordingly
because right now i don't even know what
exact day it's gonna be
[Music]
please feel free to tell me
on twitter
27.
okay you know what i'm going to put it
in my calendar now
my time
27th
remembers only
anniversary
[Music]
yes
i did i did
i did say something
maybe look back on the board
just a few minutes ago
[Music]
what shallow war bundle what
a social artist yeah i think i read
yours already as well
although i don't
don't even
don't know when it was
i think i i read it
unless you sent another one
[Music]
and yes you have permission
coffee would be better though
for the marathon stream you're welcome
to drink something though looking for
the time thank you
no she didn't roast my dead plants no
she understands the situation duck hulk
thanks for the pinky
that was so awesome seeing the five-year
anniversary panel saying your dancing is
great kiara is now known as one of the
best dancers in her life we just need
that 3d and kiwawa can have her own
concert and skyrocket to popularity
cupos
thank you
yeah if it only were that easy but
by the way when i was watching that part
everything was
streaming smoothly
until the very point one second before
to kick any kick
my stream i was watching on tv but it
suddenly started buffering
and it buffered until like three seconds
later i missed the the kikkity cake and
i missed the reaction
yeah
worst timing it did not buffer a single
time before for a whole hour
suddenly
i did watch it afterwards yeah
tough question
yeah
i think i'm something
ah
as the hotel coast with vast total
knowledge what other fun weapons and
collapse do you want added next
well
i i wouldn't be able to think of
anything right now for the one for the
characters are already in there
for the japanese members
um where the collabs are already in
there i guess but
one thing i would like is like some kind
of
marine senpai related
um something
like
something
i mean we already have the voice level
but i want something like bunk you boot
i want some some booby attack or so i
don't know
some
maybe
i don't know
of course we could also go like
like um really seriously
um
oh that was that that was animation i
guess
we could go for something seriously
piratey
but
or even some boomer related
uh
age 17 third season
related attack i don't know how you
would do that but you know there's still
so much you can do
[Music]
i still so much
so much potential
yeah if she gets added as a character oh
oh
they can go all out
so many things they could also like for
all all of virgin
[Music]
it seems like
very fun characters to design
but it might take a while because they
just added gamers and the zero gen zero
so it's probably gonna take a while
to get there if they're even gonna get
there ever honey
[Music]
young
eating and doing
[Music]
also thank god don't worry about it it's
fine
for the pinky
okay wow it's almost two years since
your debit debt these days i'm so busy
with college i can't draw as much as i
used to no matter how busy i'll get i'll
always find time to support you thank
you for debuting and being so funny and
kind wow beloved it's okay don't worry
about it
you've given me so much so far at least
you're still around
yeah and still reachable
while you know a lot of other people
they just disappear completely
don't even say hi anymore
yeah
[Music]
even even ignoring me
um said
yeah but thank you
i mean like creators like clip or art
creators or something like that
no thanks guys though hi
hi
[Music]
you guys are here
thank you
[Music]
no
i'm not ignoring you i like to learn
don't judge me no it's fine thank you
[Music]
well stick around for a long time thank
you been lucky since the beginning i
will now go far back into the shadows
you can also say hi every once in a
while come on
[Music]
wow
never thought you'd ever pick up sts let
alone enjoying the hell out of it if you
love this game monster train could bring
you similar yet totally different
experience uh-huh
okay
similar yet totally different sounds
promising
but for now i'm gonna continue scs a bit
more
salubrious beats
can't wait for anniversary it's gonna be
good i think you guys are gonna enjoy it
um i changed some plans again
because like i just couldn't design
certain things well
but yeah there's definitely
gonna be something exciting
at the end of my
um
12 hour marathon
i think i'll announce like at least two
things
i'm done with the members only super
chats
it's half past 10
i don't feel like cooking
but wait tomorrow is my day off if i
cook tomorrow we forget but surely
i feel like cooking i still have
leftovers from the food i ordered
yesterday
[Music]
yeah no tomorrow i'm not streaming but i
could read the rest
after aoe
[Music]
but who by myself
and by the expiration date
of the food that i have to cook
i
recently it's been really hard to force
myself to cook
i'm not so much into it anymore
then then taking you really
[Music]
i do have leftover food so honestly i
should be eating that
[Music]
do you think it's because you stream
until midnight
yeah i don't know i think it's partially
like after a stream
the longer it was the less i feel like i
have energy for it
and the motivation for it
[Music]
yeah
i just generally don't have much energy
ever
for doing anything
so hard to do anything at all
even answer emails but i have some
really important emails i have to answer
afterwards after the stream
other people in the household no it's
only me
my quitocatos
which is why i was so happy when my mom
was here she cooked me
dinner for two nights in a row and
breakfast
[Music]
you know i really liked working in a
normal job
in the late shift before because
breakfast is easy
you know you can just get a bread or
something and then
um for dinner
i would be able to eat at the job
because we had
dinner
breakfast lunch and dinner there
so i was pretty much covered
[Music]
on all the days i would
work yeah
why would why would my management team
help you help me with meal planning
that's not something
they
would do that that's really quite a
stretch
i i hope for a lot of things
that
that um
like i would hope for a lot of things
that they would do for me
can i form a sentence there's many
things i would hope they would do for me
but
meal planning is not something i would
expect from them
pot of train train of thought
what
which one was the correct one
plot of train
train
fun [\h__\h] trying to [\h__\h] find the fun
[Music]
sounded so correct though
but then you're just thinking of trains
[Music]
i don't normally think of trains no no
okay
i will
[Music]
tomorrow i will
have some some small things to do
but they won't take up much time
and then i
will upload the 12 hour marathon
schedule
and
yeah
that's pretty much it
that's what's gonna happen tomorrow
[Music]
wow
thank everyone for providing props by
the way for this
series in particular and thank you for
watching each episode
and supporting me yeah hope you had fun
with this game with me unfortunately the
chickens didn't make it in time
but yeah oh yeah i have to call it rain
so wake up that
oh let's see
let's see
around 7 45 i want to call in 7 45 a.m
wait no that's not that's not tonight
it's the night after
oh i can sleep through
oh there's a oh everyone
[Music]
everyone's playing rust tonight
everyone i see in the schedule
everyone's playing a rest
are you surprised
five
two two a.m rest free for the rest five
a.m rest five a.m rest
[Music]
i'm not surprised
i was thinking of playing some rest
during the marathon
some
no i don't i don't know if i can keep up
yeah
i don't know i'll think about it
i'll think about it
yeah i saw dana reporting what she did
on twitter did she just play off stream
when is she gonna play on stream
[Music]
no i will obviously not get up at what
three a.m or five a.m or so
play some stupid rest
crony said she plans on starting ah a
newbie a newcomer
oh i wonder if she's gonna like it
i wonder how she's gonna play it how
she's gonna
enjoy it
[Music]
fresh meat
yeah
anyway so the snack
why the [\h__\h] am i not waking up at 5 a.m
to play everyone with everyone else
that's such a good question why did you
delete it
why did you delete it
i like the sarcasm in your question
[Music]
no i liked it
oh the sarcasm came through very well
i know i know i know
anyway okay i'm gonna go now um
this was an easy finale
normally my finale streams take longer
and are more suffering
it's too easy
thanks a lot everybody
goodbye cult of the lamb it was nice
having you
there
[Music]
oh this movie is behind me on the cat
tree she's waiting she's sleeping
oh
i'm gonna give her a kiss from you guys
who wants to give smoothie a kiss i'll
i'll take notes
how many kisses i need to give her
[Music]
me
me one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven twelve
okay about 300 kisses
i got it easy
that's just a normal daily dose that i
give her
hug okay
chunky too
i'll spread it out
[Music]
oh
okay i'm gonna go for real now
hmm
[Music]
for real now going
[Laughter]
[Music]
tomorrow new rings of power episode
whether you like it or not i'm watching
it
[Music]
just gonna leave this friend here
i'm gone
[Music]
high five
um
[Music]
bye
do
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
you