Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive Genius
Ririka Yo
Kawaii
Positive Genius Kawaii Positive Genius
Kawaii Positive Genius
Ichi Ririka
Yoichi Corporation works hand in hand with Rika,
while Genia Home offers a pleasant environment to
suit your lifestyle.  We are waiting for you with a
variety of systems that allow you to work in a fulfilling way.Cute
positive
Genius cute positive
It's Genius Ririka
Good positive
Genius cute positive
Genius I'm Ririka
Yojo Corporation is
currently recruiting talented people to work with Ririka.A
homely and pleasant environment that
suits your lifestyle.  You
will be able to work in a fulfilling way. We have a variety of
systems in place. We are
waiting for you. It's Lyrica on Genius.
Yo cute positive.
Genius cute positive. Genius cute positive.  I'm
a Genius, I'm Lyrica.I'm a
cute positive.I'm a Genius, I'm a
Lyrica.I'm a Genius, I'm a Lyrica.I'm a cute positive.I'm a Genius.I'm a Lyrica.I'm a Genius, I'm a Lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.I'm a genius and a lyrica.  We are
waiting for you with a complete pretend structure system that you can do
[Music]
Masu Kawaii Positive
Genius Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive
Genius You can open it.
Open it. Open it.
Hello, meow, hello, hello, meow, hello,
meow, hello, meow, hello, meow, hello, hello, hello, chaos,
yo, everyone, I
mean, yes, yes,
everyone.  Thank you very much for choosing to attend the live concert campaign 2023 eve.
So today, I'm
going to come and enjoy the all-night festival with you all, and I'm
going to practice a little bit and have some fun, so
please take care of me.
Thank you very much.  I'll take care of you.Thank you.Thank you.I'll
say hello to you one by one.Isn't that okay?It'll
take about a minute today.Can I ride the dog
?Yes, it's okay.Mechae, today.  There are a lot of
people, so the people who are participating today are Eko. Everyone,
if you press the tab key, you
can see the members who are participating. It's amazing.
[Music]
112114+14 is 2028 Aja 27
people gathered together.  That's amazing
Pimenimenipipo
So today I'm going to play with that newly implemented
game for the first time and play
Holmen Hunting with 27 people.  I've
been thinking of playing around with things a bit,
but today I'm going to start with some home hunting, something I've never
seen anyone playing around with, even the listeners.  I'm
thinking about it. Let's
do this is the most late,
but I'm sorry, but it's no good, but it's okay,
here's the place.
Ha-chan, I tried to hit back at you, but I
stopped, and everyone looked at me and realized what this Subaru
was saying.It's
true,
right?This is it.It
can't be helped.  It's a
disgusting way to use Sakuraban. Yaro-chan. What are you
making me do?
Shame on you,
stop it, stop it. You're being pushed, you're being pushed.
No, erase it, erase it
. Hurry up and like it.  It's amazing,
but Sasu-chan left it in a state where it could be deleted. I couldn't delete it, but if I deleted it, it
would affect the system, so no matter what I tried, I couldn't delete it. It's
built into the system. Are you begging for it?
Why don't you put out a button?
Well then, everyone.  Well, this time, let's start with the red team.Let's have a match between the red teams.Okay,
everyone, I think there's probably a balance between each of them.Well, I
think the number of people is gathered.Yeah, yeah, in
general, there are too few whites.  Is there
too little yellow or too little red? It
doesn't look like it at all, so I'm
like, Okay, well, then, here's the red-haired one. There are
people who go hunting.
I forgot to say that this is it.
By the way, I don't know if anyone has gotten it yet,
but there is a book on the morning assembly table.Let's
go back to where we were earlier.
Let's get it. Hey, everyone, please
come out there and head towards the school. I'm
sorry that the en version isn't ready yet, but I hope the
JP members will support you.
Yes.  Yes, yes, Holmen.The
hunting rules are such that each team selects 6 people.Yes,
it's a 2nd game, so there are 3 people and 3 people, making it 6 people.
Okay, what's this? The red team will be playing first, so let's
decide on a few people and get them to gather together. Okay,
okay, what about the boy chat? I'm thinking that the bubble chat
will be divided into red, white, and yellow. I'm
sure it'll be crowded.  Well then, let's ask the red team to stay here for a
while, and have the yellow and white team
go to the designated boss chit.It looks
scary.Yes, Mr. Ani
[Music] It
's yellow over there, it's yellow
[Music]
Yellow, yellow, shiny yellow, shiny
yellow Hey, I'll win! Yellow, I did my best. Who's going to oppose me?
Well, that's right, me and who.
There's also a call anime, please. I'm there. I'm
here, Hanty.  1st person corner wrap,
Sanma polka, right? Okay,
yeah, everyone
else, please enter once. For everyone else,
please wait outside the venue.
Yes, yes, is this okay? This is okay, yes,
okay, okay, okay, okay.
With these three people who entered, let's
go, let's go, let's
do our best. This is an
exciting test that will test how well you know the Hololive members.  I think it's
more about passion than thinking, whether you use your head or not. It's
passion because you're a hero. It's
not passion because you're a hero. It
's mental and physical passion.  Is
this Mental Physical Passion or Mental
Physical Passion? I've always wanted to ask.
Last year was Mencal Passion,
but that's not true. Kadora
A is now
coming to try to take back Mental Physical Passion. I
see. He was trying to make me understand.
By the way, do you understand the rules?
Everyone, there are no rules.
By the way, I'll explain briefly.
Well, when the game starts now, you'll become a demon.  The
person who became this person is often warped to the front of the white statue in that bed over there.I
can't do that.So,
when you start that game, that
theme will be displayed on the screen, so you can search for people who follow that theme.  The
first match that yellow will play is
Yeah, I'm sorry, I played yellow, but it's okay.
It's okay. The order is really yellow, ha, etc. I'll
do it first, sorry, please.
Okay, yellow has already entered 6 people.  It's
like yellow, this is the 31st time, so I'm going to say 3.
That's good, okay, so there are 3 entries. No, I
just came to ask where it starts with Hunter. That yellow one has already
entered, so it's yellow, yellow, and then white.  I
guess I'll make it something like this.Okay, I'm alive.Here's the fugitive.All of you are
making a little announcement to get me in as a fugitive.Yes
, yellow, please wait for a moment.Yes,
yes, yes, yellow member is here.  We'll
be waiting in the audience seats,
here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here,
[ __ ] Paki-sama, this is wawatame, the
polka, and I'm not here, either cotton,
because we're doing the polkaft, so when the polka
starts.  Once you start, you'll be
on your own, and you'll be on your own. Oh, I understand.
Well, there's a chance that you'll become a fugitive too.
Well, the other team will...
When the other team turns into pigeons,
you become the one on the runaway side.
Well, this member is the one who is on the run. The
members are decided, but everyone participates.
That's right, the participation itself.
Haha, on the escape side.  Volume
check at the beginning of the volume Check
[Music]
Volume of the volume check at the beginning Check the volume at the beginning
% Me
200%
[Music]
Well, Subaru and the others
are the first ones to catch it, so let's enter.  Without  It's
okay. Do you understand this?
What does it look like to catch someone? If someone touches you, you
'll be caught. The lead will
be handed over to you, so the person who catches you will
have something like a compliment on the ear, for example.  Then,
go to the person who says this guy has furry ears,
hit this leash, and pull him.
Pull him up to the white statue. If you
press the sign, you can contain him. It's the
same as the one on the left.  Let's do our best, it
's going to start, it's going to start, it's going
to start It's okay for us to be on the runaway side, we're on the side of running away, we're on the side of trying to
catch the red team, we're going to
catch the red team, we're going to catch the
red team, we're going to do our best, Azuki-chan, nice and nice, take me, take me, that's not the red team.  Well, I guess it's
not red,
but I made a mistake.Where
is the person whose name is red?
It's a red person.A person whose name is red.Look at the name.A
person whose name is red.The name is white.White group.White group.White group.White group.White group.White group.White
group.White group.White person.White person.Here's the one on top.That's
it.This is it.  Well, it's like pushing a signboard, so you should be
able to do it. White person, yo, yellow white person.
There's a white person over there to catch you. Do your best! It
's falling, it's falling, it's falling. Blue
wants you to catch it. It's a book.  It
looks blue, so it's over
. It's a white person, so it's already white. It's
coming. It's here. It's on top. It
's on top of a white pillar. The person in the robe is
gone.  Well, if you catch a friend,
catch a friend, catch this one,
wait a minute, this one,
there's a chance of a mistake.
Maybe it's included  I
want to do it, but I think it's okay. A lot of people have been
arrested. Oh, it's interesting. It's
called a story.
Oh, stop
it. It's over. It's
over. I just wanted to try it.
But the topic is tentative, so I'll go with that one.  I'm going to do it. I
caught Nof
. I was watching from above, but it
looks like you're pulling too hard on the leash, so run away.
Ririka.
Run away with all your might. If you're caught, I heard you can run away if you run away with force. It's on the other side.
Run to the other side Run to the other side Hey, let's do this
again. Do we start over again? This is practice, so let's move on to the
next one. Feeling like this, okay, let's move on to the next one. So, next time, the giant birds are on the run,
so please pretend to be a fugitive.  There's a fugitive,
but the white team hasn't entered this. It's the
red team, not all of them. They're
all on the side of catching them, and the other teams are fugitives. I see. I see. They're
getting beaten up.
Please stop fighting.  I
wonder if it's okay? I'm going to participate as the one running away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you
can run away too.  I
'm sure there's a lot of things to learn, such as the number of people who made their debut in 2008, and the number of people who made their debut in 2009.But I wonder
if it's the wrong person.If I
catch the wrong person and touch the signboard.
Well, that's a bit different, but
I'm not allowed to go in. Is it okay for
me to lie and say that I'm not like that when I'm being chased
? I
can't lie.  I already
have that data about my debut in 2000, but I can't lie to fool myself.I
can't even lie,
but on that day, the voice chat probably wasn't connected.  That
's right, the enemy probably won't be able to connect with me, so I can't. Good
evening. Well then, it's time to start.
Yes, yes, I'm going to run away. I'm sure I won't get
caught. I know I'll survive. I
put pressure on Regros. Ah,
no, it's okay. I won't say anything if I'm scared. It's okay.
It's really scary.  Hey, you're scary at first,
right? You can't do it anymore.
His team
[Music] Let's hit
him
[Music]
Run, get in the way and hit him.
Let's go to the window, right now, white is trying to catch me,
right? That's
right, I got caught by that body. It
's my color, isn't it? Kim, are you
serious? Yo, Kim was high earlier, and he was too sad. Yo,
hey.  I'm caught
in the middle of the body, and I'm standing up, and the iris is looking sexy, too. I
can't hear you over there, so I'm sexy, but
wait a minute, and I've realized that it's divine.
[Laughs]
Narui.
Goro Senpai So what a great senior is
coming here
[Music] I've
escaped something.
This seems difficult, isn't it? Su-chan
might have been a bit of a genius. It
's true that it's a continuous hit.
That's why the polka wasn't good.  I
hit it repeatedly and it missed, so I couldn't help it.I hit it repeatedly,
but it didn't miss.It definitely didn't miss.I
entered the runaway one more time.Okay, I
understand.  Hey, it's
going to come
out in the middle of the day.
Meyone-chan, it's totally okay. I had a lot of time.
Seriously, I could afford it. That kind of fashion exists now. It's too gentle and strong. If I
ran again, everyone wouldn't think it was yellow.
No, that's probably only the money-taker.
Yo, I'll just catch all the money.
What's going on? I'm seriously in
charge of gross idiots, so
please forgive me. I'll do my best. Next time, I'll
be like a cat. When I shift like that, I don't even know what's going on.
Macchan Genius did it, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's not a
card, it's not
going to be a card, there's a chance tomorrow, and there's no possibility that I won't be able to do it. Let's
go, it's Iris, it's here, it's
extremely safe, it's red, so let's
go, let's go,
erase the red, and
come out. We're
close to the operation.  It looks like you're really
squatting down.It's hard to understand.
What were you
doing? When I was catching them,
Chiara-
senpai was having a really hard time squatting down.
But here, what
do you call this white thing?
This white thing, this white thing, this white thing, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, that's right, it's squatting on cloud threads.
So I got caught and was doing Biji-chan. Yeah, I ca
n't get caught. It's hard to get
caught. I mean, if I stay here, I can't get caught.
If I get used, it's really difficult to pull or pull. I
can't crawl
in.  It's
weird to practice thinking, is
n't it? Run, run, run. I got caught. Stop it. [Music] Chade-chan, you're running away. Sorry, I thought. You're not
getting angry. This is terrible. You have to move.
[Music]  I'm running away, apparently I
managed to escape. I can't seem to
win. I guess I've
barely managed to get in. I
decided to crouch down and wait for the moth, because that would be too much of a
hassle, so I put it
on the back burner and went on to the other guys.
Maybe it's not a good idea because they'll get caught.Oh, I see.The
yellow team is the thread of all the clouds.It's kind of
embarrassing to feel like they're dominating, isn't it?It's really
logical.That's a lie.That's a terrible play.  It
's like Kipki play play. It's almost like I'm going to hide. I'm going to hide and
sneak.
I'm Mio. I'm sorry, Soba-chan. No,
it's totally fine. It was fun. It was fun.
It was fun. I went home. It was
okay. Sora.  It was
okay. I ran away.
Yeah, I got caught. I ran away. I'm drinking something. So-
chan has been eating and drinking for a while now. I'm enjoying
my ice.
Okay, I'm eating ice again. Okay, Okay, one more time.
Okay, next time, I'm heading towards that.
Sorry, I'll have you gather at number 2. Okay,
I'm going to move. Move,
that's coming. How are you going to cross?  I
wonder if it's happening twice, so this time the
topic is the same, but the actual performance
is different, so I thought about it a little bit,
and the three of us worked together for one person.
If you can catch it, please try using teamwork.Also,
look at the current balance, and
be
aware that there is a possibility that that tall building may be cut down a little.  It's
gone, it's gone, I do
n't have an anti.
Sorry, sorry,
sorry, next time. I'm not
coming, so let's move on. Let
's upload it. Oh, it's gone, it's gone,
everyone. Hey, that partner is here.  There are
people who want to practice with a partner.
Yes, that
's true. If you have a partner, that's true. Listeners, it seems like you've
already decided on a partner. That's right, you've already
decided, so it's okay.  It's
decided by the team, so
I'd like you to do that with your partner, so if
you're the one who likes it, please
tap on that sign.
White
White Yellow Yellow Yellow I understand
Eiso-chan polka on top of the signboard Tachiruka
Well then, let me make an announcement for now.
Yes, our team is starting to move forward Hass
Bells team are you ready? Yes, it's the entry on the left.
It's okay.
Next, Kuro, I have a day off today, so Ririka and Sui-
chan, please.
Please, please go up. The people below also
have to touch the sign. The people below, uhm, bottom.
People don't have to touch it.Only the people above me can touch it.I touched it
by mistake.I made a mistake.If I made a mistake, uhm, hey, I
made a mistake.I wonder if this can't be undone?
Wait a minute, I'll ask you.Yeah,
what?  As I said, only the older people are allowed to touch it,
so Sora-chan should be touched.
I asked Matsuri and Aya to team up with Iris, but not Iris. Hey,
what should I do? If I touch it, Iris and Iris will work together.  I
'm teaming up with Polka Kagome I'm teaming up with Iris
and this is me I'm
sorry Iris I'm sorry Iris I'm sorry how can I get on top
of the polka if Esora-chan pushes it I think I can ride on top of the polka I think
Esora-chan is strong enough to
ride it.  I was
touched by that thing, there's a horse thing, there's a horse thing,
Ajasora-chan, let's do this one more time.  I
think it's better to experience it
firsthand, so can I ask General Iris to do it for me? Me,
General
Iris, wait a minute. So you mean
on top of Watari-senpai? That's right. Yes,
on top of the sheep.  Thank you for letting me ride.
This jigiska
is fast. Who is jigiska? Even
if it's a bit meaty, I've done this.
Iris
can enter by pushing the book. I
pushed it away and I have something like a book in my hand.
No, I'm going to enter the general, yes, yes,
press the yellow block of the yellow general, the
yellow block, that one. Sorry,
that's all I have left, so I'm going to
press this. Please,
wait, I'll ask you to explain the rules.
Is this the explanation for the request? I
can't see it right now, so I'm
going to explain it to you.
It's a game about how many times you can kill an enemy within a given amount of time.The only people who can attack are the people on top, and the
people on the bottom can only move.This
is not the number of people killed, but the
team with the most number of kills.  It's like saying 1st place.Le
point le point.Yes, yes, yes, just
the general is glowing yellow.In this case, Ai is the
general.If the general Kim is defeated, 1
point will be added without the king.Oh, I
see.So, for example, red  The team is a mess
If I kill them and get 10 points for the 1st place red team, but if I kill Iris once, I get
2 points and get 12 points.That's
crazy, so I wonder if Iris will
come forward and defeat her or not.  Yes, it's
about the strategy.In this game,
even if you die once, you can immediately respawn.It's a
game that asks everyone to come forward and kill as many people as possible.Yes, I
understand.Please leave it to me.
That's right, because you have 3 hearts, if you're on the brink of death, it's more advantageous to go and kill the person with 1 heart.Yes, that's
also
true.It's better if everyone protects you.  The
captain has 5 hearts.
That's right. He has 5 hearts, so he
can withstand it, so it's probably better to protect him as a duo.
What's the strategy? What are
we going to do? Yeah, Rika, let's stay alive.
Even if I attack, it
's okay. It's like this. It's like this. At first, it's like, "
That's not it." If you freeze and move, it's true. It's
true that at the beginning, it's okay to stay behind.
But the more you come, the
more you feel like that.  Chan, I'll
take a screenshot and send it to you. There
shouldn't
be a heart. It's too much of a heart mistake. If it starts, it'll probably turn into a heart. Yeah, that's right. It's okay to change your point of view.
Oh, how are you doing?
Let's go.
[Music]
in
Yellow I wonder if there is yellow.Isn't there a
yellow to yellow?The two yellows
don't overlap, so
don't sleep.There shouldn't be any in the skein, so
let's start.Everyone, please do your best.Thank you very much.I'll
attack, attack, attack.
[Music] Let
's attack, I'm scared. Three
people. There
's no one around the captain. Oh no. It's
scary, it's scary. It's scary.
2 Where are you? Where are you? Where are you?
No. 1
[Music]
is really yellow, yellow is really strong,
I don't have any good luck.  I should have just said I'm sorry for punching you in the face,
right? That
certain strong
Leach was
hitting me, not Mike, but he
was this strong.
No, this is Yuu.
Even though Hajime had defeated a lot of people, he was
talking to me. He was Japanese, and he definitely
had a talent for Minecraft.
But at first, he was bad. No, no, he
was able to use a sword at first.  Sword 6 That element
is my Lyrica.It's amazing how strong the yellow group is.The
yellow is nice.The
red and white ones were completely stiff at first.  It
didn't work, but yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
going to kill only the yellow team,
so let's go. [Music] Hey, I'm going to go to the Amoto team and have Sul. Today, I'm going to support you, so I'm going to go to the red team, and you
can get it.
Yes, please, yes, please, please. Well,
if it's a big deal, I'd like to ask you to do it on a different day, on a different day,
on a different day, on a lower level, on a higher level,
yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
, once it's 3, or once it's in, I'll do one more line.I think I'll do it
one more time.I
haven't done it yet, so I guess it's going to be a bit, then we'll say goodbye
again.
[Music]
Let's do it,
oh
[  [Music] That
's the one in blue. Let that girl do it.
[Music]
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. Zuzu-chan will be on top.
[Music]
No, no, no, stop it, that
's the difference.Amiko-senpai is also a fan.I'll
do it first.I'm sorry, I
fell a bit.Now I'm with you.Alright then, let
's go.Ok, oh,
wishing will make you hard.It's like before.
Hey, I'm going to use a sword this time.
Yes, it's definitely a sword. Everyone is equipped with swords. It
must be because I learned about its existence for the first time. I can't help it
. It's the same at the practice session today.
That's right, which way do we go first? I don't have to say. I'm going to
cut in. The captain is here. I
'm begging you. I've attacked. I'm in
danger. It's okay. It's okay. There's still a lot of
life
left. I'm
still
behind again.
Red target, nai nai,
hit me
[Music]
[applause]
Hit me, you low-ranking
one
!  The
person who hit the strong point used a shield and walked backwards, and I could
n't defeat him with just one. I couldn't defeat him.
Seriously, I realized that.  I'm
doing it all the time and it might be a
pain, but there's no cooldown time for respawning either,
so yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll be respawning right away,
so I'll just leave it there.
Or maybe it's okay to aim only when Red Red has cut down the general. Ah, maybe
HP is important.
Fishing is important. From behind, the best is from behind.
Or, that carrier senior will be the one to deal with it.
Well, the real story is Nemiko. I see.
Thank you very much. Thank you. You're the one who
can beat up a lot of people without running away. That's
true. It
's funny.
If you want to practice with different teams, you
can always ask the person who is practicing.Well, the
knight can press the start button.
Even after this, I
asked them to practice even if they were on separate teams.Yes, I
think I have a pretty good idea of how to do it.I just
have one question.What do you think?How many times did
that general kill something?  I
didn't understand what it meant when you killed someone,
but if the general was defeated that one time, you'd
get 1 point, right?But it
doesn't matter in terms of the team points from earlier, so the general is new.  The number is the
same as the victory points for the final match that will be added to the overall benefits.It
has nothing to do with the first point,
but it is the bonus points that will be added.I see, in the final score.  I'll tally that up.  The
person in 1st place will get 15 points, the team in 2nd place will get
10 points, the team in 3rd place
will get 5 points, right? Yes, yes, yes,
that's what's added to that, so I see. Oh,
I finally understood that. That's what I said earlier.
For example, if the 3rd place team
won the award 5 points 5 times,
then the 3rd place team would get 10 points. I see.
Yeah, that's right, it's really strong, so no,
this one looks like it's going to turn
into a rhinoceros, so don't keep up, and if it turns into a rhinoceros for the rest of the time, then I'll go to Gamla.I'm sure it's the general, but I can't
even think of aiming for it.Yes, that's right,
general,
please be careful.Yes, that's correct.  So,
what
should we do next?
Isn't it
better to go to Himegoshi once?  Pudding
,
Pudding, I got hit by a naughty girl, and it's
hard to hold on to.
Yeah, yeah, we're
splitting up into teams. I
still have the equipment for the bar line, but it's
better to have the equipment for the wood line.  I wonder
if I'm in the middle of the game, but I
think there's just a lot of people left, so
I entered an entry where we were really fighting each other. It's
fine. Please split up into teams. Ha, that Calliope won't do this event.
But what should I do? Look at me,
take a look. I think you can watch it from here.
Wait, wait, wait, where are you? You
can have me do it with you. Ah yes, it
's actually Shion-chan, but she's not here today,
so anyone can do it.  Okay, festival.
Well then, Po Iris. It's okay. My
friends, I really wanted to do everything I could.
But yesterday, when I practiced with Kachan and Mechan,
at the beginning of this part, I
changed the camera.
Shift
shiifallBL Ah, if
I crouch and walk like this, I won't fall,
right? I won't fall off of Bro. Yes,
that's OK. I'll check with the management of this.
As expected, I'm allowed to change my perspective after saying yes.  It
's okay, that's
okay, I'm sure. I think it's better to change it. I
think it's better to thank you. I guess it's better to do your
best, try your best,
princess. Do your best, try your best. Princess.
Maybe I should change my point of view. Yeah, I don't know, but Subaru is easy to do, so I guess I'll change it. Well, I see, but I'll give it a try since it depends on people. It's fun. What should I do with Subaru line equipment?
Alright, let's get Subaru,
middle of the game. Middle of the game. That's probably it. It won't
disappear. I'll take everything, so Subaru,
please keep it.  I
can't throw it up, I'll tell you after it starts.
That's
it. Work
hard. Good luck. Good luck. There's already a block on the book.
Shift. Wait a second. Wait a second. Yes, yes. Shift. Yes,
yes. Shift. Yes, yes. Even if I log out, it
won't disappear. It's yellow. It's gone.  There's no way, right,
but yes, hey, hey, hey, hey, do your best, and get off,
get off, get off, oh, here,
right, one more time, woof, woof, oh, red, pink,
pink,
red, red,
pillow.
Pink
Re: That's good. Hurry up. It's early here. Well,
knights aren't allowed to talk. Knights aren't
allowed to talk, but it's okay to say that they're
already there. They're naked, nodding, doing that, and
doing that, but that's fine.
I see, I
'm in creative mode. Is this a
refrigerator? I wonder if
that's what I'm talking about. I wonder if it's a refrigerator.
Click on it. I wonder if it clicks.
Yes, that's nice, that's good, that's good. What's the other one? It starts with white again. It's
good, Rika.
This is good too. Tomatoes or this. Tomatoes or apples or
paprika. Maybe it's a pop.  Apple or
Paprika? Matsuri Matsuri Senpai nods loudly.
Masuo's tingling is a bit subtle,
so I'm going to leave it to that book.
Masu Rika, ah, I'm hungry. I
want to eat yakitori and, um, fried sorrel.  Na
How to make fried chicken made from yakitori is
written in the book Iris.
Well, yakitori is just yakitori. Well, all you
have to do is grill two chickens. You
can make Subaru's karaage.  Fried chicken is raw chicken, Kako
Subaru-senpai, and uh, flour,
yes, and oil, oil, is it really fried chicken? Stop it,
stop it, how many pieces of meat do you eat?  I
didn't write it down, so I ate the fried chicken one by one,
then cut the flour on the
cutting board.After
that, I
put the cut chicken and flour oil in a pot and
ate it.I wanted to eat it.  I just cut it all off. It's
not all oil in it. It's supposed to be sold as oil.
Someone who sells it has it. There's a glass. There's a glass there.
Put it in a pot  I
'll give it to you. There's something to drink like oil in a pot.
[Music] I
drank a lot and it won't drop. I'm drowning, but please go ahead and
drink it. Maybe I'll take the stuff I dropped. Well, I guess
that's it.  I
didn't write anything other than that.Then Iris
gets it and eats it.The name is
Subaru's fried chicken.It's
true.It's really that.Why?
Thank you very much.
Yes to eat
Yes, that's fine, a lot of ok, uh, color. Please
tell me the right side. The top right is red. Yes, the top left is pink. The bottom left is also pink. I wonder if the bottom right is pink. I don't know what the bottom right is.
Please tell me the bottom right. I think it's yellow. It's yellow.  Yes, it's
early, yellow,
yes, yes, it's time for the final killing.
Wrong, oh, my side is out. My side is out. It's finally out. Be careful, be
careful, hide here. It's
coming, hit me, hit me, I'll
win. It hasn't decreased at all. Where is that? Top left. Is
this it?
Oh yeah, yeah.  Next, let's go!
[Music]
Te
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hey
[Applause]
Well done, you've made a machine. Princess
Princess, it's a beautiful princess. Moreover, Princess Iris.
Hey, I can hear you, I can hear you, princess.
What does that mean? The princess is that warlord's
princess who lived in Japan. She's a Japanese princess. Does she
really exist? She
thinks she's not there. She's so hot, so hot, so hot.
Huh?  Does that mean she's a strong princess?
That's true. No. It feels different. That's right.
Princesses are really good.
That's right, she's a beautiful princess, isn't she? She's a strong princess.
Yeah, the kanji is different.  I'm
so fast
Hey, there's still a lot of room for improvement for the yellow team.
So, if we practice, we'll be able to shrink it even more. It looks
like we'll be able to cook and color. Hey, yeah, yeah, we're
practicing. It
looks like we'll have practice after this. Well, let's play the server again.
2.
Yes, the voice goes back. Yes, there was a yes.
Yes, the princess is right.
Princess, princess. The ice cream
was a princess and she was in a good mood. That's why she was called Netsuhime. And
everyone has their own new ones.  I
think a cooking menu has been added,
but Subaru's difficult Subaru's deep-fried fried chicken I was really
surprised.There was a hamburger steak, an
ennie, and pancakes.Yeah, that's
nice.I
want to eat this.This is for everyone.  I was
like, ``I'm surprised,'' and I
was like, ``I'm fine with asking you to do everything like this,'' but I just wanted to try it all out.
[Music]
[Music] I want to
go,
what's going on? What's going on? It's
okay. I'm
waiting, wondering if they'll let me go to sleep, and
suddenly I'll say something.
[Laughs]
People practice on the floor, and I want to do that, too.  Well,
that's right, that's right, let's
practice.If you want to practice, let's practice.I don't know
what to do, but you
can just do it once.Okay,
maybe this is it.Nowadays, you can do it with an unlimited number of people.
Well, let's give it a try. I
think the only red players are Eamo. There
are three people who can't do it right now. There
are three of them. Hey,
Chiara Let's go. Now, let's go, Kia and Su-chan.  It
's the same for the actual
show.But it's the same for the actual show.It's just a little bit,
everyone, please give it a try.Yes, I
went to that other server when I told them to do their
best.I feel like if I cheer hard, it'll become a mess.
If we do, we'll open up a group and
play that match.The members who will be playing will be number
6. Is it okay if we move to number 1?I
won't be able to hear everyone's cheers.I
want to do what I want to do while going.  It's okay to be a mu, let's get back together as a team.
Eeeeeee
[Music]
Do your best, try your best, try your best. The
stranger keeps staring into space. Are you
okay? Is this what happened earlier?
Like, I want to watch it with you. I want to
rise to the top as an infected person.
Yes, I can do it. I can become a living person. I'll become an infected person. I'll
become a ghost. I'll take it
.
Hurry up, hurry up, do your best. Do your best, do your best.
Do your best, do your
best. Hurry up, everyone's good.
Hurry up, swimmers! Don't try hard. Do your best. B is really bad, but it
was interrupted, oh, it was interrupted.
What the heck, we can't do this one more time.
No Sui-chan, let's do it all over again. We can
play one more time. Aaah, I'm feeling warm. My
shoulders are getting warmer. After all, I'm going to play first. Nasu-chan, yeah, I was
using my legs just now. I
'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What are you trying to say?  It's okay, I'll use my fingers. I'm going to use my fingers. If
someone presses the button, I'll make a mistake. I'll
poop inside, so I'll give it
one more time. Tank. Let's go. Let's do our best.
Do your best, senpai, do your best,
do your best, do your best, go up like Mercury.
Yes, if
you want to see it, it's the cat's spectator mode.
Press the cat's purple sign. It's
here. Good boy, are you okay? Here we go. Nice,
nice, nice. Here we go.
Put it in smoothly, put it in,
hurry up.
No, no, it's okay. It's not
yet. It's still a little slow. There's no problem at all. There's no problem. Yo, A-senpai, A-
senpai. Has A come up? La-senpai.  That's
good, but in the end, where are you
? It's okay, it's okay, first one. Let's
go to the checkpoint. Let's all have
a chat.
What did I eat today? I'm nervous. That's
okay, Han. What did I eat now? What did I like?  As for the book,
I ate mackerel.
Let's calm down and move on. My
senior is stable.
But I'm catching up.
Yeah, there's not that much of a difference. There's not that much of a difference. That's
right. By the way, how will this end?  The right
side of
the bed is there. Touch the right side. It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay. By the way, we
have about 6 minutes of play time, so I'm
getting impatient. I'm a spectator. I'm
floating to death, my
neck is floating, my severed head is floating.  It's
flying fast,
but
this is fine. You can see the route with a
very bold move. Just
follow the route you took. Just copy Ruto.
[Applause]
That's it.
Awesome, it's the last one. It's
great. I want to do something.
Awesome, the important people are fine.
Wait, I came to the bar. Let's go and
get the baubba. It's amazing.
Even with this, you can't eat UB, you can't eat it,
you're under pressure. I think it's a lot of pressure for
the two of us to reach the goal. Un-chan was
doing a lot of work, but it's dangerous for him to reach the goal.
Normally, it's a little bit of a little bit, and this
is 6 minutes, so yeah, this is the
cool time of Trident now,
so it is so.
That's right today is all good today.
There may be more, but
there is a possibility that there will be some adjustments,
so
now is the time to
make adjustments.Everything is great.It's great.It's
quite long.It's long, it's 6 minutes long.  It's
been a long time. It's been 6 minutes long, but I
understand. It's difficult without doing this. It's pretty
difficult even if you do it. Nice, thank you,
nice, tired, nice,
nice. Nice, nice, but I like the yellow team.
That's amazing, everyone.  It's not the best, it's
delicious. It was amazing. It's
amazing. It's amazing. This is a winner, a winner, a winner. There's a lot of
pressure.
Everyone goes to Anya's place.
Where is my place? Ah, there's a lot
left.
Do your best, try your best, do your best, do your best. I
guess I'll do my best with the equipment. That's right.
Bring the fang line equipment. I have the equipment.
Please do it. Let's
do it like this. Let's do
it like this. Let's do it.
Don't do it. Like this. Don't do it. I'm
thinking about doing it. Why don't we do it right away? Why did we decide to do it?
Hey Hakos, please help me. There's
no more Tsukkomi.
What's scary is that not many people will be on the Subaru Yellow Team that day.
It's true. It looks
like it's going to be fun. I'm
going with the Yellow Team.  I see, I see.
Luff is kind, but I'm sorry, Isuma-chan.
Here's the follow-up person for the yellow one. There
's still one. There's one. There's
one. There's one. There's one. There's one. There's one in red and one in white.  Shall we
try again with a substitute?
Okay, wait a little and I
'll enter. Okay, now
you're here. My soul is here.
[Music] I'm
sleeping. I
have to go to my feet.  I
can't enter into the world of Who is this?
I'm sorry, can't I enter? I ca
n't do this if I wait a minute, but even
if I play the game, these
items won't disappear. Items that won't disappear. Oh, try entering again.  That's
right, I'll fix it once  I was
thinking about it, right? I went back home and was
able to enter, but I don't have any horses. Tame-
san is the only one trapped in the world of fangs. Ah, that's
right. I can't say it. I can't say it. Please help me, but I can't
find my horse.  I
was able to cancel my entry when I clicked on the signboard.
I just touched the signboard on the wooden line once. I
'm here right now. Tell me, I tried that. Is
n't
it? Wait, wait.  Now the game
Star, there are so many entries, but there are
no entries.Wait, you
have to enter 3 teams.Oh
yeah, that's right,
try Red.Ah, Red, Yes, Red.Maybe
Mercury-senpai will enter again.  Fix it,
ah, there's no horse, so I see, so I interrupt the game, and
ah, ah, ah, I see, so even if I cut it off, it
doesn't disappear, right? I have a trident.
is  I still have some
tools
left, but I still have a lead for hunting, and I practiced with Ririka in the morning for the first time,
but I'm pretty sure it's a guess.  I just
entered and saw it, so it was interrupted
. Should I press it? It won't work. I don't know what to do
. The book is still there. But it's now a book, so I
can't do it. Yes, it's okay, it's okay.
That's it, so it's okay. That's it.
Hey, I can do it. I can do it. Thank you. Thank you. I still have a
trident for some reason. I
wonder why this is. It's that usual thing. As
usual, don't do anything about it. Reed and I get along well.
Reed also.  Well, I have 41 pieces,
so I have 41 pieces now. Stop the 4 pieces and
get along with me. 41 That statue will come and tell me to
get along with each other in the middle of the night.
That's right, I'm coming with my nipples fully exposed. Now that my nipples are
exposed, I'm done with my pink poop. Hey,
thank you very much. Good morning.
Thank you. That's cool. Good luck. Thank you.
Oh my god, the ceiling is showing off the trites.
Wait a minute. Too many trytes. Toilet.
Too much.  It's not too bad. I wonder if I'm going to let it go that far. I'm
scared of the sound. A white guy is coming inside. It's
hitting me here and there,
so I'm angry.  It
seems that the game master is angry. The game
master is angry. Do your best.
Do your best to overcome that fear. If you do your best, you will be cute.
Hey, that's no good. You're playing the game.
That entry. That's the entry.  That's not true.
Oh, please enter Ani-san. Let's
get along, isn't it scary? Let's get along, isn't it scary? A
monster has come. Let's
get along. Oh, that's Sumaru-chan.
[Music] I
don't want to say that it's Sumaru-chan, but there are all kinds of people, so I don't
want to say anything about my future colleagues. It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I'm going to do my best, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to take it easy, take it slow,
ice cream.  It's nice to see a face on it. I'm
glad you were able to convey that it's ice cream.
Even though it has cookies in it, it's still a face. Yes, it
's Nico, but no, I wonder if it's poop.  I'm
not trying my best.
[Music]
Even if you talk dirty, please do your best. Do your
best. Do your best with an open heart. This is
good. The layout is completely different from when I was there. Oh, I guess things have
changed. They've changed quite a bit.  I
get updates every day,
so it's okay. I do
n't have to waste that much. I have a lot of time. It's the
same with this game. When I was at the top earlier.  I
may or may not have been a strong person, but I've changed so much
that I'm confused.It does
n't really matter who was the first to reach the goal.  It
has nothing to do with the goal.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. Well, I hit the goal.
Well, if I go to the goal, I'll get the points.
Yeah, it seems like that. Yeah, it
doesn't matter, I don't have any margin.  Do
n't be
impatient, it's okay to play this game. It looks like it's okay to go to your own pace
. I'm really practicing yesterday.  It's
going to come out It's
amazing, really,
yeah, yeah, that's right, Anisan, really, but that's the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed, the bed.
I see, you can make a comeback, right? So when you shift, it becomes slow, right? Yeah, it becomes slow motion, like it's the first time I've seen it.
That's right.  You've
changed so much, you've
been practicing,
you're doing your best, Ani-san, you'll be fine.
Awesome, wow, what's going on right now? It's
like a secret trick right now. You're
back too soon.
That's fine, everyone.By the way, Chiara is
very stable this time, which is amazing.It
's 1 point for 10m,
hmm.Hmph, that's how I did it, so I heard she got a lot of points.I
got 20 points for this one, yeah, yeah,
yeah.  Ah, 20 points, 10m 1 point,
so yeah, it's 100, so if 200m is the top, then it
's a point, you're really stubborn, stubborn, stubborn.  Ani-
san, it's okay. If you'd rather have a chat, just tell me. It's totally okay. You can tell me not to talk. You're totally deceiving me. I'm deceiving you. No, not at all, please don't talk anymore. It's true. What should I do?  Taunmiko
is just listening to me.
Amiko-senpai, this is so messed up yesterday.
The layout is completely different. This is just my feeling. I'm
making some adjustments to it, actually.  I'm
surprised that this has changed so much. Even if you're a, you
can do it. Thank you very much. It's already been a long time
since you won. By the way,
Miko, I think it's okay to throw to the top.  There are a
lot of options around here,
right? When you fall, it's like adjusting a little bit.
The goal is about 20 seconds,
so it's probably better to stay at the highest point.
Well, the course will be different tomorrow too.  I'm going to
make some adjustments. This
is the final one, so if you can make this as much as possible, it'll be
as normal as it should be.
321 So I
was in the middle of falling down.
Yesterday was easier than yesterday.  I feel like it's
a bit of a challenge, but if you don't mind, let's practice together after this.
Let's practice. Let's
all get together once and do the next relay.
Once I've done that, I think I'll be able to do it pretty freely.Okay,
then I'll just use the Boyz server for
once.I'll leave it as it is.Either way, I'll go to the relay.I'm going to
go to Ore's Go Let's Go
Go Relay.This year's system is
amazing.  The system is so big that it
automatically warps when it's that person's turn,
so you
have to register, which is a bit
complicated, so let's do it together now.
Well, let's do it. It's the other side. It's the turn of the relay today. There are all the people who will be participating in the relay today. It's not everyone. Well, wait a little. I
want to do it. I want to do it. Let's all
run once. That's good.  Okay, okay then,
Iris is here, Iris number 1. I
entered and went to black, so now I'm going to
go to black, chan, Sui-chan, black will help me. Next,
Sora-chan, Sora-chan, please touch me.
Where are you? Wait a minute, this is done.
Where's that one? Sora-
chan, that's that one. Where's the house? Wait from there. Just
press Erotic and you'll be
able to get this. Okay, I've made a book. Sorry,
can I get 8 people to enter?
Yes, that's it.  Yes, it's next.
Yes, press Lyrica. I haven't pressed it. It's
okay. It's okay in that order. It's always okay.
That's okay. That's okay. Then I
tried Lyrica. Yes, I did it.
Okay, wait for the next polka and make it an even number. It
's scary, it's okay. It's practice, so
it's difficult. There's a crow. There's no crow, so ok, you
can go in with the horse mackerel. It's number 8.
That's right, the first one is the anchor.  So, do your best, do your
best, and say you're good at it.Hakosu is amazing.I was
playing the drum band.Tahaji-
chan is definitely a talent for microphone play.Oh
yeah, that's right.I keep saying that.
Well, the other day, I was practicing the real ride, and I was
really slow. Even though
everyone started, they started last,
but for some reason, I ended up being number one. It's amazing, it's
so fast, it's the food after all.  This is Zuteko.
Kachan-chan is in the book. Uh, right now, I'm
getting a book. There are now nine people.
Wait a minute, there are suddenly nine people.
Well, there are nine of us, right?
Well, if you open the book now, you'll
see the entry list, and everyone's faces will appear in the bar, and it's
amazing.  2nd runner is
in the yellow block. When I open the book, I see
that this is
number 7. I think it's number 7, so I'm starting with number 8.
Yes, that's nice. This is what I'm using for practice now.  Now that we've
reached the maximum capacity of 9 people, it seems like
that's the case, so you
can ignore that last fever. It'll carry you properly at the beginning, so I'd
like the club to carry you. Once everyone's here, we
'll start.  You're my senpai by mistake. So
show me your cool side, Ruka-san. I'm
sorry, it's me. No, if you say that, you're more of a senpai, aren't you? If it's true, then you're more of a senpai. To Senpai 6, yes, that's right,
that's right, that's right.  I
mean, you can go to Chan 2.
After the Kaade Polka, it's Spall. Oh, I
think everyone has entered, so I
think you can get the baton. That great manipulator,
Iris, has a baton. I don't have a baton.  That's the only book
I have. When I start, a
baton appears. I don't have it.
Yeah, that's right. When I start, Iris
holds the baton at first, so if you hit that baton, you
can pass. I see.  That
means you can just click, right click
left, click left, where is the second person,
how far is standby, um, this is
this, this is here, I can't see Subaru right now, it's right
here, this is where it starts.
Karahan is the first person and half is okay.Okay, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, let's
do our best, let's go. Hey,
second person, let's go over there. okay, maybe the
jump has started.  It's
faster to jump and jump, okay,
okay, okay, nice, nice, nice, nice, show your cool to your juniors,
Elia, you're noisy, you're working hard, your senior is working
hard, a princess is
here.  Wait, the
second princess is coming. The second princess is being reborn. The second
princess is being reborn. The second princess is waiting for the planet.
Jump Jump Jump
Nice last jump, do your best! It's
coming.
Do your best.
Yes, sensei. It's so fast,
sensei. Do your best. It's fast. You're a big admirer, so do your
best. Sui-chan, bye-chan. Good job, do your best. It's hard.  The second
half is here,
so star, it's nice star, wait for
it.  I do
n't care where I am. I'll do my
best.
Next Lyrica, then here, next Lyrica.
But if it's in this order, I'm sorry to Polka-senpai,
but now I'm in the opposite direction. I'm hungry. I'm really hungry,
but I'm hungry halfway through.  It's better to eat bread because it's empty.
Oh, I see. That's why I
wasn't running. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Eating bread is pretty important. Bread is left
click or right click. Left left left.
Click to the right to pick it up and to the left to eat it.
Yeah, it's complicated. Pick it up with the left. Ah,
nice. That's good. That's right, Senpai.
Hurry,
hurry, fast. Wow, woah,
swiss. I can see the water, but I can see it, I can see it. I can see it. I can see it. I can see it. I can see it.  Okay, look, look at those shoulders.
Luka, what should I do?
This is the only way to go. This is the only way to go.  I'll
do my best
Passion Passion
Passion Fashion
Passion Mental Physical
Fashion Nice Passion Nice Passion
Nice Passion Because it's colored, I'll
think about it all and put on my best clothes Nice
nice nice nice Go almost nothing Alright, do your
best, do your best Oh, you
can win this, you can win this  Hey, I
chased you, I fell,
it's okay, just do your best, my
husband jumped, that's
really good.
No, it's okay here, no, it's
okay, no, I'm sorry, I can climb, I
can climb, I can climb, I'll climb, I'll climb, I'll
climb, I'll
climb.  No. 1:
Pummel Physical Passion, the
waves of people are amazing, just like in the times.
The narration of the polka came.
Good luck! It's One Piece. One Piece.
This is One
Piece.
Oh, Nice Nice Nice Nice Ue
Ah, I don't have it, so I don't have this.  It's
all
right, so do your best, nice. That's nice. Why haven't you been able to go? Right now, it's the left click. It's amazing. [Music] Do your best. You're good at doing your best. Calm down, you can do it.
If you can
do it, you'll be able to do it. You're so good at it. What's wrong with
yellow? There's a
chance that you'll win.
There's a chance that you'll win. No, please
stop flagging me. I'm
sure you've
only given out 20%.  That's because there isn't
any game. I'm finishing up the game from now on. Yellow
Chim. That's yellow. Look at me. I'm a
senior. Ah, I'm a sky-senpai.
Miko says she's doing it right now.I'm listening to the waves
while watching.Miko I
'm listening to the waves so much.Gol Nice.It's going to
come out in seconds.That's right.It's
amazing.Ririka and So-chan are amazing.  They're fighting each other.
What's this? The
spatial colors are so
overflowing with passion. Mental and
physical passion. Physical passion.
Mental and
physical.
Hey!  A
monster is coming.  It's
a little early, so I
'm already at the studio at 3 o'clock,
so I'm sorry
, but I'm at work, so I'll meet you around 5:30 p.m.
I understand, I understand, I understand, I understand. It looks like you're already
preparing for the follow-up.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much for your help tomorrow. We'll
have a chat later. Yes, I understand.
Thank you very much.  I'm going to
practice after this.Is
there anyone who wants to practice something?I wonder if it's a princess voice or something like that.I
want to do it.I want to do it.I
have something to do.  Well, let's go
ahead and try our hand at it. Let's try our
best at it. Well then, Sui-chan's mistake. I'm not saying that the first half is better
or the second half is better, but I'm going to
submit it now.  Oh yeah, I see. I'm
sorry, which one is it?
This is today's one. Yes, today's, not today's
. Well, it's the one I posted in Neko's chat.
Oh, then it changes. After all, it's even or odd.
[Music]
That's right, 1 is.
Kaku-chan 4 Ka 1 is Iris I'm
sorry Tede and 5 are polkas 6 and 7-chan [Music] Please give me a little please
Tell me, I want to hear Ice Speed I want to check it out from Ice Speed  Let's
go ice bomb here
on the ice SPSPEEDTH umm ice let's
say
kaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Yeah, I thought I'd run this one more time,
but I was pretty satisfied with Yellow, but
if there's one more race, I'll do it.There's a lot of Iroro,
but the ice is blue, and the blue one is blue.Now, I'm
going to practice repeatedly.  It's amazing how many times I've been
practicing without starting.Oh
yeah, but
if I have one more time, I'll do it at all, but I guess it's okay.So,
with Ride,
is it okay to practice without using that system?  Oh oh
oh
I didn't eat bread just now, but
Lua says I have to eat bread.
I didn't eat it either. I don't have to eat either. But if I don't
eat, I won't recover my strength,
so I'll be late.  It's
fine, but if you're full, I want you to take the bread that you couldn't eat.
Well, you can reach the goal even if you don't take it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I want that.
Okay, it's pretty difficult, so make sure to take it. You don't have to eat it. You don't have to eat it. But if it's okay if it's late, then feel
it.  I guess it's not like
if you don't eat it, it's a violation of the rules.
Yeah, you have to take Japan.
That's a rule. Well, since I'm here, I
want to make it feel like each team is together,
but I guess it's fine for competitions that use the system.
That's the only way I can move, so yeah, yeah,
let's gather all the people who want to do it. Hey,
oh,
then when I go out and do some kind of competition, I'll have a chat with you and
then I'll go over there. Oh,
oh, I'm sorry, please.
Please, please.  I'll pass it on to you, Relay. I'll
do it again. Are you feeling like you're doing it? Relay.
No, no, no, no. Okay. Just now, I
took the bread from Maa's Relay. Just now.
But I can't eat it right now, right? I
can't eat it until I start that game. I
eat it by right-clicking and right-clicking normally. I
click and there's snow behind that icy place. If I
do that, I think I'll be able to jump over it. I'll
be able to jump over it all.  Well, no, no, you
can jump over it. If the timing is right,
press and hold just that last line. It's
almost like this. That's right, that's right
, that's important. That's important, that's important, isn't it?
[Applause] It's
Iris, so all you have to do is hit it repeatedly like I'm told.The
power of God is coming from the power of flying.It's going to make a big difference.I'm
sure that's how all the other teams are
doing it.  It pops out like a
walnut, wow, haha, it collides with me, so what's the best
part? Tell me, tell me, where's the one in the middle
? Well, I've been to a lot of places, but to be honest, the nest of clouds is...  You can
go anywhere and you won't get caught. The trick is not to go diagonally
. It's better to go straight diagonally. There will
come a time when you really need to turn straight. As much as possible, there's
something on the far right that gets in the way.  It's
not diagonal, so you
can just push straight on the far right one.The
outer one is better.I feel like the inner left side is probably
faster.That's right.  It's
easier to do it on the right side,
but it's faster on the left side.Maybe it's
easier to hit on the left side, but it's easier to hit on that side, but it's
faster.Can you
take a look at my drawing?  I
want to make a video, seriously. Who was the person who shared the previous video? It's Sakonosa-chan. Please
make a real video and share it.
Tanya, if you turn like this.
That's too good to be true, right? That's right, make a video, make a video, make a video, make a video, go through this diagonally, and then you'll go 100% upside down and diagonally, and if you try to go through it like this, you'll get stuck, right? You
have to do it like this.  You have to go straight.
That's right. If you don't move so you can see the spider's nest right in front of the book, you'll
hit it.
Ah, I see. It's true that it's a trout after all.  I'm
judging because Minecraft doesn't have any diagonals. That's helpful.
If someone has recorded it, please record it later and
give it to me. I hope you can help me.
Actually, there is a way to almost get there without bumping into anything.
Is there a way to avoid hitting the pool pool? The strategy is too bad. It's
too bad. I want to go to the bottom.
When I write anything other than number 1, I write those three letters in succession except for the bottom one.
Okay, so there are three main lines,
but if you
go all the way to the bottom, you'll never hit
anything other than that one, which is amazing.  It's
easy to collide in the middle,
so it sinks to the bottom, and when the bottom comes, it
goes up.If it goes up, it won't be that bad.Basically, all you have to do is stay at the bottom.If it's at the
bottom, it'll be up.The
analysis team is here!This is amazing!
Basically, you don't have to hit anything other than the bottom, and even
if you hit at the bottom, if you
press space just a little, you can come up, so I
think you can go a little forward without hitting that much. Yeah, that's
great. I'm sure I've
tried this once.  The one at the bottom
is stable, it's stable, it's true, it's coming, but it's coming, but it
's stable, it's true that it's
faster to just watch the timing and fly instead of running in the cherry blossom area.On the other hand,
that's a stupid character, isn't it?Yeah, it's a fish.
As for that, it
might be better not to worry too much about jumping.Jump dash is the
fastest, but if you jump dash, you will fail a lot.Oh
yeah, I don't know the timing, so you'll
run out.Maybe when you get to the stairs,
jump for the first time, then press and hold to
go straight.  Yeah, I think I'm doing something that I think will be able to fly next time because of the length of the jump.Ah, the
red team or I'm playing Koro Hunteme.I want to go
hunting.I want to go
hunting.Hunting with people.Okay, okay, I'm fine.
That's right, it's okay hunting,
but to be honest, the problem on that day is ah, it's pretty amazing, so I see,
but I'm
a little worried about Luka's character design, so I'd like to do it later, oh yeah,
hunting.Okay,
I've never done it.  But I'm a member, right?
Well, I'm Hattie. I
want to play, so I'm going to do Hattie. I
'm going to do it at this timing. I'm going to do
yellow, and I'm going to do yellow.  That
means you can do both. You can do the catching or the catching. I wanted to learn what to do in order. What should I do? Once I
decide who I want to do it, I enter. Yorodoko is the
one who does the hunting.
I'm yellow.  Is this the first time? Is this good
? Is it hunting?
I only want to do it once. Now, wait a minute,
ask if yellow hunting is okay.  Yes, please
wait for me to return it, please wait for me to return it.Yellow, please let me go
hunting.The
other members in yellow, the red team, were
quick.I understand, so I'm
sorry.Then, what am I doing?Then, I'm a fugitive.Yes,
there you are,
this person.  Okay, yes, oh, let's
run as hard as we can. That's right. But the color of that name
might be quite important. I
'll let you know by looking at it. Maybe people who don't wear the top jersey won't understand.  It's
true that tomorrow I'll wear short sleeves and I'll
wear a jersey. It's really easy to be a jersey. It's
true that it's cute, but it's cute,
but it's easy to understand. That one with the blue color on it and the one with the shoulder that's
really sticking out.
But...  Looks are important, and looks are important.It's
definitely fashionable.The
title may have been changed to the second half, but it's
probably a one-shot.I see, I don't like it, but the people in the red group are the ones who bother me.I'm red.
So, in the end, if you were behind my back, I would
n't be able to find out.Wow, you're a genius, you're behind my back.But it's
not like you can't go.As
expected, you could go behind my back.Now, you're
hiding behind me.
There was someone there, but it's normal,
but I got caught, but that's not the case. I
was playing Polka earlier, and I was strong. I was here, in the clouds, and I
was very strong. Everyone was there.  We're
getting along well, and we're on the right side of the statue,
and this is the one in the clouds.
But there are 0 snipes. Oh yeah, the red team is playing right now. But I
had to catch the red team, so it's
zero.
Okay, what's with the yellow team's body on the edges
? It's cute. It's cute. It's nice. It's white on the edges. It's probably not the white team. Lol. I
think it's okay to wear jerseys, right?
Princess, how long will you keep calling me princess
?I want you to catch me with the yellow person, so I'd like to try it out here right now.This
is the person who will be difficult to grasp.I guess
if it's in front of the cage, it's in front of the cage.Don't
criticize at all, it's in the back.
I think it's better if you're in the back.If you're in front of me, it'll be
dangerous in the end, so I don't want it because it's
close.I'm close, so I purposely put it here behind me.  It was
here in the back, during practice,
and there. I was
n't being chased. What's going on
? Why are you so angry?
Everyone is in the middle of nowhere.  It's
like a great show, everyone. They're
just making some kind of nonsense. Wow,
I'm so confused. Kagome, I'm a little confused.
Even if it ends before I fall, I'll
see you tomorrow.
Thank you very much Passion Power
Baba Passion Power Mental Physical
Passion Passionate
Mental Passion If it's one more time, red will do it
I guess it's better.One more time will be yellow I
'll ask for an escape entry Yes, yes, yes,
entry ok entry ok
Sorry, everyone from the white team, that's white, yellow,
white and yellow, that's my red team. They
still haven't figured out the motion of touching with the rope,
so it's only the first half.
Just the first half without interrupting.Okay, you
can let me practice.
Or right click to catch and left to catch.
Yeah, left is all.
Rope rope right and touch and touch left.  Maybe one
Chan waiting touch is left Taaa signboard touch left
Kaunta signboard touch is left It's a bit
complicated Too okay, left click to release the rope Narumenkueah
Really a little bit Well, I guess I'll
try that once too.  I'm
curious, right? In the order you want to try it,
catch it with the right and write it like that on the rule back. I wrote that you should
catch it with the right and cancel with the left and right,
but oh well,
try that once too.  Well, that's right. Good evening. I'm
caught by the right and the left is folded. I
think I'll put it in, but I can't release it. I
think so. Yeah, I don't think I can release it.
But it's the two of us who can't release it.  It looks like there
will be two people running right now, so it's already a festival. I
wonder if someone who doesn't have a theme is caught by mistake. If someone who doesn't have a theme is
caught, they might get slammed and become part of the venue.
Yeah, that's going to be played by Pa and
become an auto venue. Ah, it's going to go to the cage, is
n't it? I feel like it's different when I try to put it in the cage. I
guess I should probably do it now, right
? This is red.  The person caught now  It's
just practice, so don't move too much
Yeah, let's be a target We're going to catch you,
catch me,
catch me, baby, I'm
going to make a mess, it's over,
lovey-dovey, stop liking
me, I'm in trouble  Oh, stop
it, you can't love and love Anya. You've been caught, you've been caught. Sora-
chan may like you, but that's fine.
This game moves boldly. I
wonder if it's better if we just run. Some
people are running, some people aren't. Which is
better? I'm sure. If we all ran together, it would be red.  It's really
better not to stay in one place
Hey, yeah, that's right, it's
like someone gets stuck and kills, yeah, yeah,
yeah, that's right, if you get chased, someone is definitely going to do that.  I
see, even if the festival is coming, this is also practice, so I'll have to catch you. Let's go to jail for the first time. I
want to go to jail. It's cramped and
painful. It's not my first time.
Please get arrested, somebody get
arrested. There are so many people here.
They're getting caught and kicked out. They're being kicked out. They're being kicked out. They're getting
caught. Oh, it's true. Maybe there are too many people. They're being kicked out.  I've
been hacked I've been hacked  I
got putted, but it's still added up in the numbers,
right? Maybe it's here. I
got hunted. Maybe I
did. Wait a minute. I'm having a hard time
breathing.
This crap is fine. It was wrapped around my leg and the string
snapped. You know, when I run backwards.  Hey, that nice
feeling made me laugh, right? I didn't get caught by Blue. I was
just running towards people and didn't end up in the cage. Do
n't run wild, Yellow.  The
team's hunter, if Sora-chan runs away,
okay, I haven't done anything, I haven't done anything I want to do.Okay
, Sora-chan and Makchan, right
click, left fan, right click, left pan, that looks
delicious.  I
guess I can become this runaway. Oh yeah, maybe it's okay. That's
right. That's right, Pol-chan, let's go. Pol-chan, I have
n't entered yet, so I'm going
to practice. So what are some tips?  He looks
anxious when he dies, so don't cry like that.Right-
click.When you see someone, right-click.First,
right-click.
Here's a
signboard signboard. It's a signboard here. Before the fold,
this is here.
too late too late
Well, it's not too late, I want to leave this official version
on the Internet
.
No one has seen it, no, it's okay, no one has seen it. It's a bit too
late, but it's my first time. It's
okay, no, no, I
think it's a wonderful naked look.  It's
wonderful, it
's naked, it's wonderful, it's art,
Iris, it's not art, it's art.
Yes, one more, okay, okay
. I don't know what you're going to say.
Yeah, it's not a big deal. It's a bird, and I'm not even a girl, so it's not a big deal. Does it have bird nipples? It's not like I
know it, it's because I know it.
It's okay, it's all about me, so it's okay. It's
scary, but I don't care. Even if it's scary, let's get along. We're getting cute. We're
getting along, and we're cute, Naso-chan.
What do you think about this movement in Hololive?  I want to be
caught, I'm right, it's Subaru. I haven't done it. I want to catch it. All I
have to do is get closer. Catch me.
Catch me. Ah, left click. Then run away.  The
polka was played because it was different from the current theme.Maybe it's
okay.Even if it's a
festival, catch the people from the red group.The people from the red group
are on the bridge.  It
's white right now AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh, it's seriously, I'm so sorry, I'm seriously sorry, it's
not ``left click,'' it's not ``
left click.'' I don't use it.
Right, I'm sorry, I'm canceling the light, I see. It's
completely removed, so I can cancel it
. If I think it's too bad, I'll cancel it.
No, it's gone. Everyone's lying. It's
not white. It's on the way.  I'm cut off. There
's no white person in the first place. They're
hitting each other. It's amazing here. It's right there. Hey, I know I can
change my mind, so here comes the yellow one.
[Music] I'm
in trouble, Awa-chan.  I'm
running so much, I'm doing all sorts of things,
and I'm trying to do something
fun, and I'm crowded inside, and this place is
getting more and more crowded, and I'm
sweating more and more. I'm sorry, Princess Niohime, but it's
a little sweaty here.  It's a lot of
places. I'm
sorry, I'm a little confused. I
got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Oh, right click, right click, right click, right
click. Click right click. Okay.  It
's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good
, it's good, it's okay, so
please enter the fugitive
one more time.  It's
true that I haven't shaved off the white of the red, I really
haven't shaved off the white, it's terrible, it's terrible,
it's true, I don't want to suddenly disappear like that.  The
bigger one is stronger,
so it's gone, but I guess it's possible to make it lower.It's
true that it's pretty easy to follow, right?That's
why we
might as well run around in the cat's style.  I do
n't know, it's definitely here,
it's here, it's
strong here, it's too strong, it's here, it's where, it's here, it's where, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's where, it's
this
mouse, it's really
strong, it's really strong.  You
can call me Mei. We look very similar.
One person is open. The two
people who are here are open. Two people who can
go, two people who want to take the entrance exam, right? Cloud. I'm
caught, I'm caught, I'm caught. I wonder
what will happen if I prepare to take the entrance exam.
Wow, it looks like 2 people can go here.
2 people will fit in. Is it
okay to go on a swing?
They're stubborn, they're not popular, I can't see anything.
It's dangerous, so all I can see is Akori
's head. It smells like that hair. What are you talking about?
It's
yellow, white, white, white, white and white. It's totally fine. I can
see it, and if it's Lyrica, I'll say I don't like it.
Lots of things.
If it's really bad, I wo
n't stop unless you say no. Even if I say really no, I
won't stop. That's it.
Pull back. It's
embarrassing, Senpai. Only 1010 seconds left.
Our turn isn't coming. We're the strongest here.
Everyone's face looks good here.
Even in the experiment, we were all captured as usual, regardless of the situation.
They
're not hiding, it's dangerous, oh Noel, you're being captured.
Stop it,
help-son.  Well, that's the best way to go.Suba,
senpai is great.I
remember, it was really strong here, and suddenly I
warped to where, and I
didn't like it, and
suddenly I was there.  It's so
strong, it
's so strong. No, I was suddenly attacked. If
even one more person went to jail without permission, it would
be the end. That's right.  Is
n't it easy to do that? I
can't move, after all. I
like the empty style of running around. I was
worried about that, but this time I was
running around. What was it like running around?
What was it like? I was caught, right? Yes, I
was able to run away once, but then I got caught. But
as long as I don't head towards it myself, I'll be
fine. I do
n't know who the demon is, but if I head towards it, I'll
get caught. Ah, I'll definitely turn around.  Now, I don't
know who the demon is. I don't know at all,
so I'm going to be that true side. Oh, that's
too true.
The moment Noel and I laid eyes on each other, I was ready to die.  I
thought it was over, but it's true,
so please give it to me. I was captured. I was prepared. I guess I
was standing. There's
no more. Yeah, this will probably
be the end of the hunt, so yeah, I'll scream. I
want to do it.  Please, I want to become one as soon as possible.
If you wait a little,
I'll chat with you once. The next voice is good. The
next voice is good.
Who is the voice of Kapipi?  I've
become a princess. I've become a princess. Only the
characters match. I'm
sure even Miko has started both of them, so
that's all they have in common. I
came to read you, but something was missing.
Miko,
Chimiko-senpai can hear it.  I can't hear you, Miko-senpai,
right? I
can't hear you, Michi. Goodbye, Miko-senpai has gone here. I can't
see you. I can see Miko, but she's still alive.
Wait a minute, I'm Subaru here.
Wait a minute. There's nothing below this.
And I'm pretty sure it's just long so it won't fall. It's
long, so I pulled out a little at the end.
Maybe I should go to the right at the end.  There's plenty of room,
but I'm not going to run that way, Pol.
Maybe the pool is the easiest way to go. That's
what I came for. I
heard laughter. Subaru Oh, that's right. Let's
go.  I'll
just go to Wani, then I'll cut off the polka stream soon. I'll be practicing, but I was streaming it. I'll also stream it, and then I'll cut it off. It's about time. If I just cut that frame and practice, I
'll just practice in a different place.
Well, I'm going to go to the darkroom first. I
think anyone who wants to do it can do it. I
think anyone who wants to do it can do it at all. Maybe I'll
cut out the frame and bring it over here. I
'll go over for a moment. Oh yeah.
Well, let's just leave it at that.
[Music]
Oh, that's it. That guy with the [ __ ] food is pretty good. Yeah, and
where is the number 4? I think Minecraft is probably going to get drunk.
That guy's fang line is pretty good.  A line, a fang line, a fang line. Yeah, that's
true. The screen shakes quite a bit.
On the contrary, it's jumping
up and down, so it's all the better. Is it up? If it's up, it might be too much. It's my intention, so it's
unnecessary.  Hahaha
it's okay
Yes, it's okay I don't
think I'm feeling better than before I can practice at all after this cat now,
but it seems like it's closed after one round
So ah, then ah, okay,
please go ahead.  I'm sorry, yes,
yes, yes, I heard that.Hello, please let me know.I'm sorry, I was
thinking of closing that whole thing, but I closed it, and yes, I
continued.It's okay to leave that frame as it is.
But yes, I'm thinking of closing it for now.
So, can you please join me in the long arm area where everyone is?
Yes, I don't know. If so, I'll close it when I get home and do that.  I
got it and thought it
was ok, so I decided to close it for now.
Yes, I'm going to get together and say ok,
yes, yes. Isn't Osuipor there? Oh, Suipor. You know, since I came back, it's okay for the first time. That's ok. Yes, yes.
Thank you very much, everyone, for today.
Thank you very much. I'm really
happy that you really pushed forward, or rather practiced like crazy. I hope you'll all be able to
support the members who couldn't come and
have fun together.  That's why I'm thinking of it,
so please help
me. Masuko Aha's call is team-related,
but I'm calling out to people who want to play with that call, so
can I have them come at that time?  It's a
little bit like that with the activation line,
and the follow-up, and um, Higo
, I can't do everything at once, so I'm
thinking of doing it in turn, and I'm just gathering only those who want to do it, and
having them come, yeah, yeah,
yeah.  I'm going to give it a try, so I'm going to turn it around. You
can close that frame after this, or you can
leave that frame, but I'm going to turn around and say
yes. Thank you for your
hard work. I'll see you again tomorrow.  I look
forward to seeing you tomorrow. Thank you very much. Bye-bye. Baba.
Excuse me for the inconvenience. Yellow is number 5.
[Music]
By the way, there are people who are still in the frame.
What should I do with my voice?  That's
it, Koshi, let's go. What should I do? If you want to cut it off, it's okay to cut it off. But don't just leave it to that. You won't be there tomorrow.  Isn't it
okay? Where is it? Voice here Voice here Voice
here It's okay Where is it? It's not the school building.
What's that? It's in the gymnasium. It
's in the gymnasium. Yes, yellow, I'm participating.
Thank you. Chat. Yes, that's helpful.
By the way, Matsu.  The town has some kind of strategy. But
if the princess says it out loud, I think they'll probably get along pretty well. She
said something like red, yellow, and pink earlier. Yeah, yeah, yeah, she said it when she was making the road.  I
got the impression that it was pretty easy to understand that when I said that, I was going to move.I understand, so it's a continuation, so it's
better to squat as much as possible.It's better to
plant while squatting, so it won't fall.
Oh, that's right. Wow,
that's great. I'm going to ask Princess Iris to
please. It looks like she's a princess
. I'm looking forward to it.
But I'm definitely looking forward to it. I don't have about 50 voices. I have
screen sickness or something.
Even if it gets a little harsh, it's
okay if you let me down. I
don't get that sick at all, so
it's okay. It's okay, I'm glad.  I wonder if it's okay for the first time. It's the
first time. It's okay because everyone is closed.
There are a lot of people, and Matsui-senpai is the only one who
has to enter as a knight. Yeah, I see
that 01 are gathered together.
Chat 01, please Yes,
yes Yes, please, please, please
, please, please. Please note that Mikochi's
distribution is still ongoing, so please
take care of me.
There are all yellow members, but yes.  Yeah, yeah, they're all yellow. The
members are divided by 444.
How many people are there? It's totally fine. How many people are there? There are 12 now.
There are 3456 and 7888.
In that case, we can split into 2
teams. We can make 2 teams. So, Subaru, I'm watching what's going on.
So, if anyone wants to team up with you,
please do so. Wait a minute, wait a minute, please. Please proceed.
I'll ask you a few questions.  Oh, I'm sorry, I
have one more question, but what is that? You
make something and guess what it is.
But, uh, the knights are
not allowed to talk, right? Basically, one more thing.  It's
nice to have a voice like that,
but I wonder if words like this, this, that, this, that, the
usual, etc.
will probably get across. Yeah, yeah, yes, here. There's
no such thing as putting green here.
So in that case.  Yes, it's okay for the princess to talk. It's
okay for the princess to talk, too. If the princess was the other way around, then the
knight would shake his head and ask, "Is that a refrigerator?"
Do you feel that you can't nod your head up and down? Yes, it's true, it's
no good. It's okay if it's not a word. It's okay if it's not a word. It's no good.
That's like an answer.
By the way, that princess's voice...  Things like the theme
change on the day of the day.Higo's theme is about cooking.The
first half of the story is not exactly the same, after all, it's
random.  Miko also
thinks that if you play with the red team, for example, there will always be a lot of paprika or a lot of refrigerators, but
yeah, that's true, but apparently it's
random, so I
do it for Radam.  I don't really understand it, but it seems like some
random person is getting angry,
so I guess that means that the topic for that day is the same as the one that's coming out right now,
and there's a chance that the same thing will come up again.
By the way, the person who makes that creative thing,
uh, the first half isn't that different, but the second
question is that there will be a special topic for that day.
Yes,
yes, I'm excited. Yes, there are some changes, but they're
not going to interfere with that. Yes, it's
okay.
[Music]
Um.  I was able to
go with 44 with this. We
still haven't broken up
yesterday. How are you feeling now
? It's a little yellow right now. Yellow is gathering with 44. Are you
going to do yellow now? So
should I enter as white? Looks like white.
Enter the white team and
make another team with the remaining people.I'll
ask if there's a red team or a white team.Yeah, they've
disbanded quite a bit.I want to do it.Even if the
33 teams are disbanded, we can practice even if the 33 teams aren't all together.  I can do it, so I'll
do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it.I'll do it for the princess.I'll do it for the princess.I'll do it for the princess.I'll
do it for the princess.  Princess,
do what you want, do what you want
, princess, I
want to see you, please.I want to see the princess.Then you
can have Mio-chan come as a knight.That's
dead.It's dead.
Mikocha Knight, please.
Yes, it's okay to protect me. I want to protect you. Then,
start button. Yes, where is the start button? Where is the
start button? Shall we separate the voice servers?
Oh, then, uh, let's go to the actual show. Be the first team
number 2, please.  Yes, yes,
yes,
please wait, please, please, please.
Yes, it's all about the
knights, isn't it? The
call is important. Call call call ann.
The response is okay, first of all,
pink, yes, pink, red, pink, yellow, red, yellow, red, yes, yes,
pink, yellow, now yellow, pink, yes,
red, red, yellow, yes, red, yellow.
Let's
do it, let's do our best, we'll
get caught. Is this the one that's going to get caught? Oh yeah, it's
yellow, red,
pink, yellow, oh yeah, that's it. I was squatting down.
If the bottom moves, it
will fall.Okay, red, yellow
, pink, red, yellow, moving,
yes, pink, moving, yellow, uhm, pink is a little far away, yes, pink, red, yellow, moving, yes, yellow,
pink, red, yellow, pink, yes, nice, nice.
That's over, maybe, right now, right now, I'm
doing it now. I'm doing that voice right now, so I
'm dividing the members. Hey,
wait a minute, wait a minute. Ah, uh,
Akahi, who's missing right now?
Look, this is a
tomato, an apple, or a tomato.Which one is it?An apple,
or a tomato.What's the difference?Is it an
apple?Wait a minute, an apple.How
did you do that?Here, here, okay,
pro.Hmm, cat, oh, that's
amazing.  What do I want to eat? Yes, I want to eat Subaru's fried chicken again.
Also, um, grilled mutton.
I think fried chicken comes out every time.
It's dangerous. But I never had a hamburger steak.
Yes, that's right. Also, it's mutton.
Just open the mutton normally. Yes, yes, then I
'll cook it on a mana board. Yes, please. Yes, I'm
waiting for the wheat. I'm
grilling the octopus. If I remember that, on
the day.  I didn't say it was a little different. I guess that's right.
Somebody
should take the fried chicken and cut it up.
Well, let's cut it up. Put it in the pot.
Let's eat the mutton first.  Yes  I
put it in a pot and
put some chicken in it. Added some oil. Is it here
? I'm probably cooking right now. Yes, the knight is a good cook.
Okay, it's done. I give it to him and give it to him to eat. Yes, this plate with a duck on it is cute. Yes, the
princess said, ``Huh?''  and upper left orange yes
orange uh upper right pink pink lower left red ah
orange orange orange yes yes
yes yes fight, fight press yes  The
timing is perfect
Yes, yes, next [Music] Yes, the rhythm is true. I feel like I've become stronger. [Music] That's good, that's good, that's good, yes, next. That's
great, that's really good.
Together, that's
good. Yes,
there's one more.  I'm working on the top. The
top is that one. Only the bow person is the bow person. Can the bow person
focus only on the top?
[Music] Are you bad at
kneading your fingers?
[Music]
Also here and there.
Hey, if it's Max, the damage will be big.
Max. This guy
hits a strong nice move and gets a goal. Nice. I
wonder how many minutes it was. It
was 5 minutes and seconds ago. The other team was
quick, but it was ours.  There may have been a difference of about 6 minutes
or more than 30 seconds,
but I think it was 5 minutes 09.
Yes, if it was earlier than that, it would have been a long time. I do
n't think it will come out.
Maybe it was just a delusion.
Maybe it's better to decide who is going to make what for this dish.
For example, the first one
was a random one, right?
Oh, I'm sure.  Yeah, I'm sure the second one
seems a bit heavy, and the first one is probably
just regular yakitori or grilled food,
and the second one is either fried chicken
or hamburger.  Looks like it's going to happen
But pancakes are good, so it's like that.
4, 4. My
amazing mama taught me that flying and hitting is the
strongest. It's really strong. Yeah, flying and hitting is much
stronger.
It's treated like a critical hit.  It's about the timing when something flies and falls a little.Pon
pon pon
pon pon pon pon It's fast.Please praise
me.I'm looking forward to the actual performance.I'm also looking forward to the yellow color.When
this star-like thing comes out.  That's
right.
When Star Tantan has a brown star on his opponent's body, it becomes a critical hit. I
even learned how to do a critical hit,
and it was amazing.  The person who has it
is the demon king at the end.I wonder if I should make it into a festival.It was from last year.It was
really critical.It was
last year's sports day.
Did you see it? There was mob subjugation, Mobutoba, and there was
also fencing,
right? There was that. Mr. Fencing
fell, too. Mr. Daruma fell.
By the way, there are other people you want to practice with. It's
okay.
Follow us.  It's okay to follow up.There
are people who want to participate in the
follow-up, like Aquatic Senpai, who wants to do it.Even if it's a follow-up, it's
okay.Wow, I've got the impression that he's already got the hang of it.Yeah, I'm
sure, and anime, too.Senpai, that's right.
Okay, let's start the follow-up Follow-up After the follow-up, we will disband once. Yes, when was the next practice? 12
o'clock The next practice is tomorrow, um, tomorrow.
Yellow You can go from 1 o'clock to noon.  I
think I can go, I think I
can go, it's okay.At first, I might not be able to go.It's
okay, okay.In the beginning, on the other hand,
if there's something I want to do, I'll practice a little later.Let's
hang out together.Let's play together for the first time.We'll
have another hour from now.  It will come out
But if you're still doing well, please let me join in. It's
totally fine. Well, it's a good timing to
start with. It's okay to get out of here.
Thank you very
much. Thank you.
Who are you?
Your stomach is
sticking out just because you're sleepy. It's okay. Please put it away. Your stomach is really protruding. Let's
move. We're not flirting.
Please move. We're already here.  I
'm over there
and I'm pissed off. Look at me, I'm pissed. By the way,
please wait. I'm showing my stomach. I'm so sorry. It
just came out normally.
Everyone's hearts are here.  The moment we became one, the
moment we became one, the moment we became one
, well then, please touch this.
Oh,
uh, I'm late.
Oh, I hope you can enter as well.  Se-
senpai, is it yellow? Yes, it's white.
If it's yellow, brother, I'll make it red.
Oh, you can enter in yellow. I'm
sorry, I made it red. I'm sorry, red is open. I can
go there. Red can go.  Oh no, I have
n't been able to enter, so I'm going to see you tomorrow. The yellow
player turned red to red, and I was able to do it.
Good luck, do your best,
aim for me,
do your best. I wonder who's in here will be faster.  It's
true that the path we can't go on has already
begun. I wonder if Miko, the amazing creator, will win.
And I have a lot of pride as a creator.
There's a battle that we can't lose, a battle that we can't lose. Let's do our best.  A
new word called
``Gaba ni Gaba Nya Gaba'' has been created,
isn't it cute
?
If you go after this, you'll be able to get there in the shortest time.
No, that's not true. Everyone is really amazing. That's right. You're
lying, you're doing something like that. That's a mistake. Nemi-
senpai is really good. I heard an amazing undertone. I
heard it just now.  That's amazing.
Don't
wait. Don't wait.
Let's get along. The speed of revenge is amazing.
Come back while you're falling.
Terua, the second checkpoint, I
knew I couldn't do it anymore,
but I reached it and returned right away. That's amazing. I'll be back soon. It's
okay. This isn't a competition
. I don't know where I'm going to miss in the end.
Because this game is
mental, it's definitely mental and physical.
Mental-physical passion is what's
important. As a player
, it's different teams, different teams, different sources.
[Music]
This is
so cool! It's amazing! It's so stable and stable.
It didn't work out. I wo
n't die. I won't die. Even if I stop, stop, stop, that's it. I ca
n't do that because Iros isn't here.
Seriously, I wo
n't be there tomorrow, so I can't fly.
Please die, I really beg of you. What are you doing? It's
okay, no, it's okay. And tomorrow, the voice channels will be separated, so I'm
with you. Who are you with? Yes, I'm with you. Hey,
Lily, please stop.  I'll
take your place, so I'll stop it,
stop it,
stop it, stop it, Ririka, I'll be there tomorrow, okay
? Don't worry, I'm serious, I'm going to
follow up too, so my passion will be messed up.
Hey, everyone's going to be broken by the follow-up, so I'll
go home.  Come on, come on, come on,
come on Chiara, do your best, Chiara, there are still people streaming here.  It's
currently on the air, right? Ah, why
did it fall? We're
all watching the follow-up. The last, last
try.
But when I go up, I ca
n't reach the sound anymore. I made it. There's
nothing I can do about it. If I go up, it's
probably almost the same layout as yesterday,
but the bottom has changed quite a bit.
It's great that you've reached the third checkpoint. It's okay, you idiot. Good luck, A-san.
No, there's still time, so I took it slow. It's
easy, I failed. It's okay, Anya-san.
Please leave it to me to speed up my recovery.  Please
leave the speed of revenge to me
Please leave me to the speed of revenge. I'm relieved. I'm glad I
did that. What should I do? There
's only 19 seconds left from here. Bad, bad, bad. Bad, bad. 15 seconds left. Just a little,
of course.  You're in trouble, you
're an idiot, you idiot, I want to die, die.On the contrary
, it's amazing
, but I won, I won.
After this, we'll practice behind the scenes. It hurts. It
hurts.
Let's stop. Well then, those who close the frame should close it.
Thank you very much for staying.
Thank you very much. Well
then, let's disband for now.
[Music]
[Applause]
Mr. Okay, everyone.
Thank you for watching today. I
practiced a lot.
Yahoo, I haven't been able to talk much lately, so I
'm lonely, but I'll see you tomorrow at lunch.  I do
n't have any plans to take a particular slot at the moment, and I
don't know if there's probably no one to take pictures, but yeah, I'm
planning on filming the broadcast at night, at various times during the actual performance.
So after that, I
couldn't do it at all while talking to the members only.After the performance was
over, it was like a thank you party for the members only.Reeka
just wanted to talk, but I
wanted to do a butt stream for the first time in a while.  Also, I'm thinking about it, so
please help me. It's going to go really well. It's not going to go well. But I want to practice as much as possible until the very last minute until the day of the event. Thank you very much.
Jump like this, like this, like this, jump, jump down, jump, jump
2 times,
after the jump, jump all the way across. Is it okay to jump? I
realized that it's easier to go up if you look down. It's the worst.
Hey, it's okay even if you fall down there. 1  It's hard to go to the bottom and
then go to the top for the last time. I
want to do my best not to lose anything,
but I always get nervous and
say things like, ``No, no, no.''  bumping into each other
Well, even if you fall, it's
important to run to the end without worrying about it.And
yes, all of your seniors are good at first, but Nemin
is good, so you have to be careful when you're at the bottom.  Do you
want to practice this here and there at the bottom of the ladder?
Mental health is important, over and over and over again. If you
rub your head against it, then
rub it against your head, it's basically okay.  It's right, it
's right, it's right
, yeah, I do
n't like this, but I don't know,
right now, I'm about to go up from here and there It's like, I'm
being pushed back, right?
Jump,
jump from jump, jump, jump
from jump,
jump
from jump, shift from jump, ah,
jump from here down, like this?
Wow, now I'm like a robot again. Is
there something wrong with this
? This is how it swims. It swims. After that, it
jumps. Is this the only option? It's good. I'm
in charge of the cherry blossoms here.
Yeah, it's an even number.
[Music]
That's right. Jump Jump Jump
Jump Don't worry, run Don't worry, run.
No, I won't lose that much time. Even if I fall over there, I
won't lose any time. This is fine. Time.  There's
no loss, if you can take the best action in everything,
Wow, this is the difficult part, the sea is difficult, the sea, the
sea, the nose.
I wonder if there's any trick to this, like punching the bubbles to make them disappear. I'm praying that it won't come again.
[Music] That's
right.
[Music]
Hey, let's do our
best. Should we just float properly? Hey,
even if we dodge diagonally, it
won't work, so we can't move properly.
If you force yourself to go all the way to the bottom,
that's it.
[Music]
Hey, hey, you ca
n't climb up there anymore. And
then you do
this, and you do this, and you press shift, and you
should go up in a rather exaggerated manner.
That's what it means
. It's pretty
stable right now.
But it's stable right now, but I'm
having trouble with the actual performance.  Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom form
ooh yes.
Thank you very much, that Suppa-chan too.
Thank you very much
again. After I failed a lot, I will
read that departure again in a different frame.  I
hope you'll let me do it.
Thank you
very much. I'll do my best tomorrow. Please support me
a lot. My uncle's dangerous pinky finger keeps pushing. It
hurts. Thank
you. Thank you, and my seniors.  I'll do my
best to talk to you properly. I was able to talk to you today. I was able to talk to you
today. Lily was fine. I was
wondering if it was okay. Thank you
so much, thank you Nechimo. I
'm so happy.
[Music]  Yes, I was
able to do it, thank you very much.
But when I'm explaining something that doesn't seem
right, I try to keep quiet. It's
important that you explain things to me, so it's important to be a good girl,
so I'm going to do this.  Yeah, yeah, that's good, that's
good, that's good, that's
good.
Thank you. I'll give you lots of support tomorrow, I
promise.
Okay, then.
Why can't I succeed here again
? I
want to try my best again. Thank you very much.
See you again tomorrow night on the stream.
Ah, it's so hot, it
's no good if I'm down there the moment I dive like that. No, no.  Well, that's cheating. Oh,
see you again, see you again, see you again, see
you again.
Bye
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
Bye
[Music]