foreign
[Music]
why do the awkward potions look the same
as the water bottles it's nothing
awkward
it's awkward for me because I can't tell
why exactly
oh God
um I have a good a good message I am
officially in
um my like mess up base so at least now
I can come through the never to the
actual place yeah
I'll come back
[Music]
yeah I have some extra bows they're not
very good though but don't worry don't I
use them they'll become good I mean I
think we can buy some enchantments books
oh yeah you don't have the infinity ones
in your shop fauna yeah I don't have
Infinity anymore
yeah okay I'll see if I can get there it
was that like
I have 1100 minus 200. it was that yes
I'm too scared to bring my elytra today
so
cute
oh wait far enough in the basement I
forgot did it work
on the flashlight sometime
any time oh okay okay I'll do that
another time
I just wanted to confirm you can fix
anything oh
I don't need Kyla to do it for me
oh are you dying no no no no no I'm just
I'm just panicking a lot but um I think
I'm fine
what am I missing to make a potion of
healing I'm just making fancy water
bottles
all right let's see this see this book
over here
yeah it may have some uh
oh my gosh
recipes it's my recipe book oh okay but
how do you make it oh you need you need
you need sparkling melons for healing
potions
[Music]
um
was it oh oh yeah I think it is gas
tears I have one yeah
I'm not sure if I have any more
[Music]
that sounds like mine
um
okay you must die I I'm because I'm
gonna never I'm in the never I mean oh
remember we're gold yeah cause I was so
far away to look for a cave to fight in
for like 40 minutes then then I lost my
I was out of fireworks and then I had to
find my way back and I was in the middle
of nowhere and now I am traversing in
the Never back to home I am safe more or
less I just forgot I was in the Never
I never found a cave though so we'll
find one together
oh we can probably fight it on like in
like a desert
I think I suggested I it would it's
alcohol I think a cave would be easier
but she has some caves too good
it was good
wait did I say that why would I say that
I don't have the proof because I logged
out before but but proof right here I
said a cave yeah
wait can't we make a cave just stick
down and like dig more you know take a
big hole Yeah like a big hole and we
call it
yeah that's not what caves are though
basically
no holes underground yeah exactly yeah I
made myself like a whole huge hole and
then I just came out in the water
I mean that is generally I think a good
option though
wait what
do you have the little thing in the hole
digging a hole
I am now back home where is everybody
I'm at home I'm playing with the alchemy
table
I'm watching Girl play with the alchemy
table I'm pestering fauna actually I
look if I have more arrows for I have a
bunch of gear at my snowy Village
okay come to the Village
first check if I have some arrows
playing today
I don't know how many we need though I
made like a bunch of health potions too
um
hold on I feel like I have I know I use
the Watermelons making my portions sorry
you can share my portions
but what am I gonna do with this 64
Splash bottles now oh my what do I do
yeah
I have a lot of gold maybe I can make
more spices
can you make spicy melons okay yeah
what's your business idea we take the
splash bottles and we make them with
everyone
yeah how
um
it's a business secret don't want anyone
else to get the idea
um excuse me second floor is uh off off
limits ma'am
ma'am what what about it second floor is
off limits oh what is the second floor
off limits it has my precious
my boyfriend
hold on let me let me go make some
melons shiny melons
um where is where is a melon
do you think oh I have some melons here
okay good
[Music]
we should make a golden sand golden
carrots give some extra HP too though
don't they yeah I have a bunch of golden
carrots oh I have is it called the
carrots like hunger
yeah they increase their saturation
which is good
melon seeds okay could I have some I
have some sparkling melons for you wait
where are you guys sparkling melon you
make them they're artificial I have
fauna I have the Wither Skeleton skulls
right yes okay okay
[Music]
shark has where if you have coin
not sure if I have Soul Sand
Soul Sand
do we need salsa we need it don't we
four I have one
Monday
you're tucking the villagers into bed
what did you do
it's me going to bed after you came down
there like nighttime milk and cookie or
something it's not really in the Bedtime
Stories
you have awkward potions
I need splash water bottles
did I miss this one you're supposed to
make awkward potions first I think I
missed establish so you just have 64.
water pushes
wait wait wait wait oh this is made of
water balloons actually
another good place I think this is good
if uh someone's on fire but I have one
awkward splash potion what happened to
the rest of them
it's not me too wait wait wait wait wait
how did I do that go down when jumping
into the water she makes an awkward
splash
it's not true
okay I will try to find fauna now
a few times
[Music]
everything's so messy I'm sorry guys
sorry my house is a little loud
is everybody sleeping why are you not
sleeping go to sleep sometimes
they're in my pockets good luck
I came back is it too early no
perfect
[Music]
Minecraft splash water bottle
splash water bottle why
why
oh gosh I have to I have to mute the
game again I turned it back on after
after me with it this is the village
they're honking I saw a clip of you
hating them
I just don't like the sounds they make
they are yeah very very people say
Splash pushes in the LIE splash potions
of water why right spot portion of water
why not yeah what did I do why not I
don't think so many can't you make
things awkward and then how do you make
them in the oven
you use the what with the the ward the
little red
making yeah okay
another word yes
Another War that's how I made them into
Monday mundane
weren't forced to make it into awkward
potions and then you add in the melons
no okay now I have one wait is it like a
game of chance no
it is not do you have awkward potions
now I just made one from mundane
what okay we don't need potion so much
I've made 45 please
we can use the water balloons I'm sure
it will help yeah what if what if
someone catches on fire you know you
gotta use the water balloons you know
yeah I'll be found to happen yes if you
think you'll be healed you will be
healed
well we need a Healer in the group that
it's that easy
who's gonna be in charge of healing huh
wait there is no healing character what
why is there no healing staff or so in
Minecraft
let me cook a medic yeah
throw potions on people right the splash
ones that's what I make because everyone
I think it's fauna this way
by PPP what is it mundane
this is a
[Music]
to mend my things over there still
yes
wait you can't FFF oh oh for fast
amending I wanted to mend my light trip
I don't have to do it right now you know
girl there is two okay stands
fast can you take me to the oh well
really okay
I want to marry her down
you're doing great though you think
great
it's a loop now how do I not get loose
okay I know I'm ready
oh wait what is what does mundane do
I don't think he's gonna do anything
I raised it to the max
I'm sorry it um
it gives you encouragement yeah
there we go you're doing it you made it
don't worry about it
I'm walking though
all right I think I think she's good
[Laughter]
sorry
hey is this guy like immune to anything
specific
yes just blown up here um well I have
swords then he's weak to for everyone
excellent I have one backup sword for
myself
and an ax oops
[Music]
yes please okay I'm gonna edit things on
fire again we may be coming a Firebird
I opened my inventory I can do it
apparently the weather is weak to Smite
I do have a smile I've never I've never
done this before never you've never used
this machine before it's their first
time no cause every time Kyla said oh
don't worry and then she came back and I
never questioned her for you you want to
mend it right yeah does it have mending
on it
yeah then you just have to wear it and
then go smack the fish
fish
oh
it feels like XP
[Music]
it makes it when you get XP it will heal
it
I'm going in there upstairs enough
oh use the use the sword in here I have
good intentions
oh nice back in the box now okay
what kind of Sword is that
shark land is 69. oh is it the newest
model it is
[Music]
look this is an invisibility potion
watch this ready
oh my God where'd you go
okay
I'm back
sweet town now yeah sounds good
to the basement I made it
I know how to get there I think wait
what it I'm gonna guess
[Music]
I'm worried
um
negative
1100 and and no uh
1100 and negative 200. describe the
terrain it is icy it's your PPP there's
a cake cake I follow you oh yeah it's on
this cake
dad
[Music]
oh I got too much fish I'm scared to
know where that goes
here wait I found I'm not the pee pee
pee we can wait for we can wait for them
all right okay I'm on my way
I need to do something after we go
about that wither
this is just a Minecraft club right
right wait the Wither oh there's a
minecart oh cool
stop doing there
um it teleports the fish from the
guardian Farm or from the monument up
there
that
[Music]
you can make bread but you don't need
bread
I'll just take the golden carrots you're
better okay wait where are we meeting
and the fish tomorrow
maybe mermaid can you show everyone else
where the house is yeah wait I'm running
out of rockets does anybody have anybody
have rockets that they could lend oh so
you have to Kiara you have to like jump
up and then close the trap door right
there yeah yeah it's been a while thank
you and then there's a sword you can use
in here does anybody have a bow
there's an extra bow in one of the
chests what
um
how do I wait when something doesn't
happen
[Music]
uh no this I think my this one cannot
have mending oh because
it's okay I want to amend my pickaxe
though
fluffy
[Laughter]
oh okay
um I have to have one on my hand right
flip flop surely this time
all right
who is leaving my cards here
Nami oh well this is fine I can enjoy my
fries
are you using the sword
I'm using my own mending sword
I'll hurry they're hurting me because I
was sweeping Edge on it
oh
does your sword have sweeping Edge no
she used the fish sauce
oh yeah okay that's faster that's it I'm
walking
here is fish sword back thank you very
nice all good I'm camping
I think I'm good um okay
I think I think Watson really needs a
little bit of a maintenance
yeah
we can go back
man it is like almost three years old
now
does need a little bit
[Music]
wow
I'm feeding her
okay
then she go down I just went down okay I
should have just taken air Taco this is
taking too long
the room till my mother my mom gets home
wait wanna you should be the one okay
I'll drive I don't know where I am
okay
we'll hit your head boys
[Music]
do you see that no no oh there you did
not awkwardly splash
or did you maybe you did she's like a
wasp yeah
did you see that
what potion
okay let's run
fake monster in the sky
there's lamps it wasn't like this back
in the day
wait lamb swear like at the entrance of
the Railway
oh yeah they changed that a little bit I
was shocked too
what is this there's berries planted
here
where would that have been
raining and moon May
oh
hey bird gravy we can try to sleep oh
did you read the
the message you can just kick these guys
out oh wait can I sleep in this get out
of my [\h__\h] I think there's beds up
there I remember
there's two beds upstairs
I'm in one of them
I don't see anyone here oh wait wait
where where are you the fishing
oh
not there
all right where where is
the coordinates are 1100 minus 200.
it's like a building with a Red Roof
is that one
minus two got One Singular 1100 minus
200 okay no this one
it's important
[Laughter]
holy moly there's so much
is this West
you're opening race
no I'm still salty
okay now we even we're in front of the
same oh I see I see houses okay
[Music]
I give you the a weapon a weapon a
weapon yeah a weapon
it just has like half full
half thing but oh I think we'll be fine
wait does Village used to be dead
you revived it
wow wait can I take from the shulker box
there's a bow here
wait 30 day free trial sword wait wait
wait is
this 30 day free trial which my version
is there another one wait you take our
credit card before mine is gonna be
really strong against the withers so
even if you have another sword I would
recommend using this one let me don't be
strong
what happens after 30 days where did
they go into your invention will
automatically renew but you can cancel
it before then if you remember I think
fauna picked up
arrows
no I think it's a new inventory maybe I
got them I got them oh it's everyone
in the house oh in the big house in the
house
the big house
is that Red Roof wait should I take this
bow or no I'll keep this one because see
their names
because Kiara gave it to me
um but I should take okay 30-day trial
without you're not asking for my in like
credit card before right and you're not
going to charge what you have to right
on your credit card and it will
automatically charge you when the trial
is up but you can cancel anytime you can
just give me a call
I'll do that later okay
um I must be really warm in there huh
where are you enough it's cold out here
where are you
come inside it just light up the bed
it
meal
should we bring back up armor phone yeah
something's wrong come in come in
because I have one set for myself but
should we have like backup armor in case
we die and lose it I mean I don't know
how we would lose the armor we can bring
that and put it in chest yeah I mean
there's not gonna be like I don't know
did the withers explosions cookies
he explodes
a raw chicken oh no mama I gave you the
wrong bow God damn it oh
you did yeah
thank you thank you switch switch
I'm gonna take this because it's here
okay oops yeah everyone can take a set
of armor he's bothering me
oh
[Music]
cool kids how do we take the armor from
here
right click it
oh I took two pairs of pants sorry
[Music]
oops
translate number 47 by Karen Cole
cute
what does it say I have pants
[Music]
oh I grabbed the right helmet wait did
everybody grab their helmet
okay
this is mine it's cute they have names
dude
am I a dog
is Kiara oh I'm throwing yours at you
now nice nice no wait you took it I got
both one more try
oh thank you oh yeah what the [\h__\h] is
yes yeah yeah you see that dirt yeah
let's eat it
this is fun do it I'll give you a dollar
do it oh
all right all right I'm gonna eat it
okay
um
let me watch
oh wait can can you hit me once I'm not
hungry you know
wait let me again
the harder do you want me to shoot you
what are you doing wait no I'll I'll
just hit you
harder yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I'm gonna eat this I'm gonna eat this
dirt okay okay
thank you so everyone should take at
least one stack of golden carrots you
should eat because they restores your
saturation better
yeah
situation so it's like how how hungry
you are it keeps you full longer stores
your health better so if you don't know
the Wither effect it's the one that
makes your hearts go black and you take
damage and you can't see your health so
yeah
[Music]
always like always
constantly eat your carrots okay okay
okay
[Music]
more than one yeah okay I thought I need
to get out my potions
higher
oh
this
seven and someone doesn't have their
smiled sword everyone should have one
Smite sword you should use that one
so your items might get blown up by the
withers so you can just leave your items
here and just use the
Smite sword probably
throw a string with me or what item
would I I guess I should leave my
fishing rod do you have a seven attack
and I don't have a armor stand
it'll be good against the winner
for damage from it yeah probably leave
your life
just in case
one more for what I need to make a bow
to repair my bow oh
wait I have a bowl
do you want a boat
isn't it like a like an unenchanted one
yeah oh there's a power five bow in here
if you want to use that instead of one
with my own phone
um I'm very good at hydrating so I'm
going to go to an idol meeting I'll be
right back okay um I'm ready I'm ready
so you yeah one level I am also ready hi
readys
hi I need one level
I'm gonna train with villager maybe
some emeralds
if you give him the minerals though I
don't remember
oh
[Music]
I think Yoshi music has to be the most
empty-headed music I've ever heard
are you listening to Yoshi I am
I want Yoshi music thank you
[Music]
it's in here
the basement
yeah
trading Emporium where everyone works
willingly and happily
hmm of course
unlike Phoenix Sun
what's different about Phoenix tin
well everybody works indeed happily
truthfully happily there uh-huh
it's not a lie
he just gets to spin all day long why
does he not let me go down
here are you insulting his his
co-workers
are we going to do something about this
guy punch him in the nose don't punch
him don't punch him you're probably
gonna be a bodyguard right here
sword
outside he's got buddies whoa I got
buddies
like you I'm I cannot
cats
it probably can't fit through the door
even he's too big
it's shiny
oh no I have rocked chicken I'm going to
die
okay
wait the windows open
what are we going what are we
oh yeah are we are you almost ready
yeah
I'm ready oops I'm ready I'm ready right
I'm right yeah
am I ready
um
okay wait wait these are shared sound
effects huh oh
shirts oh we should bring beds
I should probably bring some we want
buddy
big old head full of iron nothing else
alloy looking uh organized what was I
doing oh yeah
does anybody here do wait movement you
do crossword puzzles don't you
watch crossword
like yes do you have the app
I don't know what is the app oh
it's copyright
um
did you take dictionary.com there's all
of them on the PC wait I don't know if I
do that one oh I was doing them on the
PC no I do them on my phone because I'm
lazy I think this one would be better
because I can do it when I'm busy yeah
yeah I'm really bad at them though I had
a great one today oh
need an extra bed
wait do we bring one do we blow up
yes okay I require a bed please thank
you sorry there's one bed in here thank
you sorry I'm annoying I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry maybe I'll borrow this
bowl
it's a backup oh I have red and I have
who knows your bed yeah bravery I have
the
here's another bed nothing else you got
a cookie that doesn't have any
nutritional value can we have a
sleepover before we go all the
nutritional videos
you're pushing our beds together before
[Music]
this is so bad at everything we should
wear the drama
Chloe without it wasn't even on purpose
but we just so happened to have the same
pajamas
did somebody take my bed
oh what color is it it did there you go
wait
yes thank you okay can we do a checklist
uh-huh yeah card you have the three
wither skulls I have them in my never in
my inner chest yes okay you have to
bring them yes okay I'm just keeping
them there for safety I was gonna bring
another in the chest and just place it
wherever we do it um true true that's a
good idea does everyone have a bed yeah
yes yes does everyone have at least one
stack of golden carrots yes yes
does everyone have at least three totems
of undying yes yes I don't know how to
use them I'll take one more okay yes
keep it in your off hand at all times
okay oh everyone have a Smite five sword
yes yes everyone have a doll yes with
arrows yes yes yes yes okay I think
that's a good defense
let's go then where do we go though we
don't have a location yeah we should go
very far away
um desert
or came
I think cave is slightly easier and I
think we could handle a desert too are
we bringing elytra's or are we walking
we're walking we're walking okay let's
walk let's walk
which direction
away from home we're about source
should we should probably go through the
nether
okay I mean yeah we can take one of
those exits wherever it leads us
I tried my exit but there's like so much
Mesa around it I feel bad for doing it
oh that's true
[Music]
where would be a good place
I was chatting
The bunkeroni's Underground King
[Laughter]
oh that underground idea
just just joke
for protection not for fighting in hmm I
remember there was a giant cave area
somewhere where I lost my Ikea fish
but that has like it was pretty big I'm
not sure where that I think it wasn't
the resource server actually back in the
day so good I don't jump
let's do a backflip no do we
um
did
what ah 360 minutes ago ready
your belly fat
there it is
nice
don't even
[Laughter]
know I don't know we can go to a desert
maybe macaroni desert can we dig up I
still don't see why we can't dig a hole
we can let's just I found the cheese
Strat like I think it would be really
easy oh yeah I watched the video it
looked really easy if you did okay so
we're gonna run around like chickens
with our heads off and carrots okay
cheese it we don't need all of this
stuff yeah okay
don't scare my viewers please with your
statements oh did you know that well
grotesque did you did you know that
um never mind
I have to confirm with Google because I
forgot the exact amount of time that a
chicken will keep running with its head
off oh I mean is that why there's the
face a phrase all running around like a
headless chicken yeah
you want me to Google it or are we
walking we should probably walk why not
both we're on the rails I think I can
multitask oh that's a long it's a long
way oh hello creature
yeah
oh there's like there's here what where
does it go oh there's quite a few what
how many I go left or right this way
be free that way be free be free
is
yeah what
there's rails to it yes
why what what is the problem what are
you doing
you're gonna shoot me in the head for
that
you're killing it man I'm craving your
attention oh this is great you have my
full attention my popcorn there's no
need to shoot me in the head
okay
let's go to karaoke
[Music]
never mind when do we get off yes
I don't know I don't know if you want to
know is it about the chicken it's about
oh yes
about a certain chicken a certain
chicken named Mike apparently lived for
18 months after his head had been cut
off 18. what
what apparently
what does it mean by live yeah
how would you define live at that place
what was
what on Earth
is it like the opposite of dead inside
is it like a large side but dead outside
forever
but this is a chicken
that's true like
um
it was determined that the ax had missed
the jugular vein and a clot had
prevented Mike from bleeding to death
although most of his head was covered
most of his dreams
Batman
what was the chicken's name Mike wait oh
my God
I was Googling stuff wait did you guys
start off when I should have gotten off
yes
I got I messed up I have to go probably
got pushed back yeah I did I saw her go
I was looking at Google I was learning
about mine
we really need someone like Muma in our
team otherwise it will be over too fast
yeah wait there's pictures you're
welcome wait where's Macaroni
caught AFK in 4k
hi
bringing another card with her oh
I'm back where are we going this way
this way
by the way don't look at what oh yeah
the attendees is it up or down down down
down
[Music]
behind you
on my flashlight
oh yes I still have foxes
is it bunker yes yeah
I've never been before out of respect oh
this is like a sauna but actually this
is snow this this used to be my room oh
oh there's a portal here is that why one
of them ended up in the in the room
we're gonna go through this portal okay
the foxes sound like chickens
don't we need like a golden helmet
it'll be fine I have nothing bold I have
something going you have your heart oh
oh that was smooth
okay
I remember this place I helped I think
how do you think so many memories ages
ago when I actually knew how to play
Minecraft
totem works on its own if you have it in
one of your hands
ideally The Shield hand I I heard I
don't have a shield do I need those okay
okay
just keep a totem in that hand yeah just
eat all the time okay always eat carrots
always eat carrots okay
I eat Berry for now though you know
these potions would be a lot better if
you could stack them yeah yeah it's kind
of bad you can't
I heard
I heard why am I faster oh I wasn't
running but I can run
the Slime cat
cute
by a cat
good was it really
endlessly I'm pretty sure I bought the
Wither so I was thinking it was a person
making a cat noise and thinking we're
saying hot cute to a person because
you or maybe it really is a cat no it is
cute it's a it's a cat voice actor you
know
[Music]
oh
what
now yeah the guest
oh there's a cat yeah have you heard the
slowed down voice of Yoshi speaking of I
don't wanna know no like some dude going
Yoshi
really fast
yeah you're on a Yoshi kick today
because I'm I've had Yoshi music
pounding my ears
Yoshi brain Yoshi you girls all watched
the Mario movie yet not yet
I did wait who has step besides me
no one no one
it's so good
it was so much fun really yeah run run
for your life
big recommend go watch it now yeah I
want to see it I
asked and I was told it was what you
expected it to be and I expect it to be
this
are they still here
oh they're still here
no we lost you guys because you ran so
fast oh going straight
behind you but I sprinted
and then everyone
I'll see you guys in the moment I'll be
right there okay
[Music]
are we going to where the weather is I
don't know
oh on your left just
what happens if you're nice to the
Wither is he nice to you no he gives you
a kiss Rose
are you supposed am I supposed there's a
zombie
wait was that a Wither that beat me up
dungeon this one is nice okay what the
[\h__\h] did you wait for me yeah why are
you so
[Music]
thank you
thank you oh they're going here I think
this one let me check
okay
nothing wait maybe not these are wasting
arrows ma'am
[Music]
oh yeah this one is good this is good
like the sausage man
Mr Meaty well I guess this is
kind of cramped in here wait are you
thinking of a different show is that the
claymation show
Mr meteor cursed puppets
um it's night time outside so we might
want to sleep outside not inside
we go through here
yep go through the portal
oh wait were they were they puppets and
not claiming oh they were puppies go to
sleep
again I think I forgot that it was um oh
my gosh I've I'm gonna look up a picture
so for some reason animation the Mr
Meaty show I think hold on
wait a minute my hands meeting me
here's face
we can leave our beds here oh oh no I
just picked it up oh you put it back
down inside your spawn I put it down
a bunny
wait don't leave me I'm looking up
things
okay yeah yeah
yes
there's a creeper
creeper oh man
[Music]
um
oh so many creepers whoa wait there's a
is that a parrot wait careful there's a
creeper over there oh there's a lot of
creepers oh there's another creeper yeah
we talked about this
it's almost been here right there's even
an endo chest here yeah whoa what
happened to you
oh you found a parent
this is a nice open area if we need it
yeah we should go a little further how
do you get the birds
[Music]
he's green oh they want a cracker do
they smell like cookies
I think they patched it they used to
your parents could eat cookies but
parrots can't eat chocolate in real life
so they had to take it out makes sense I
thought I had my Legend oh is that
jungle
uh
did you see them team team hello
um
are you calling attendance
we all here don't worry we're not
running away fauna yet
experience for you
maybe there could be a cave
no wrangling necessary or wrangling
ourselves
[Music]
what wrangling with myself
oh
I'm confusing wrangling and mingling is
this something
and wrangling we can mangle the Wither
together
are we still looking for a cable just
one big open space no we wanna there was
a cave
[Music]
I don't know how big it is but there was
a cape
wait what's the Strat here because
[Music]
um I don't even fly yeah so he might
like fall fly away and destroy you know
is that the missile line I'm here pretty
huh here too oh my God maybe it's the
same one oh
wait what was that what was the Austrian
flag
red white it's red red wait look it's
red white red there
[Music]
[Laughter]
you and your your knowledge is
hmm
I have about his
I feel like she has more knowledge on it
than me though I'll be honest
the continent I don't know Europe was a
continent it did say Eurasia well
there's gold here
I think we could buy them here probably
get rid of valleys please
get rid of it are you sure I won't have
this to pay it again
where is everyone
where we lost somebody else
would be the one to get lost in that
movie or so
hey if I'm not Googling things I'm I'm I
I'm good
towards the light
where is she
um
130 minus 8 300. go to the top and look
down do you see Marissa I see Mesa I'm
still on the sand I see you stop moving
stop
memory
it's funny like stupid
oh this bunny should get out of here
this is dangerous oh are we doing a
little bit I feel bad yeah for real yeah
for them
is that this could be an emergency I
have no longer to get up
at least okay we probably could have
brought blocks
actually
yes there seems to be a big hole down
there I'm kind of scared oh yeah we
place the under chest in this hole that
way it doesn't get exploded don't you
think that we
maybe we should have this one brought
our beds a little closer
well he's he might wander is the thing
he can travel hundreds of blocks so I
don't want him to blow up our beds
[Music]
fire resistance
that would be bad yes
okay maybe I don't know maybe it's too
far
that far to walk back
I guess I should I should get the
screenshots
oh yeah just just don't die just live
yeah that is a that is a good option
um what's the shortcut to putting is
there a shortcut to putting something
quickly in your right hand
um from your toolbar FM
[Music]
okay nice
we could
get the beds and then we could like bury
them
Barry
yeah
I didn't even realize how I said it
those are funny
exactly exactly
oh Berry the best I guess this should be
fun I guess
I think
I think it's time you guys yeah
nobody died
I mean feel free to them I think it'd be
funny if we beat it in like less than a
minute
okay we're making it even more difficult
by doing it out in the open now okay but
yeah we can just oh okay you want to
practice
[Music]
all I have is a fish I did fish God damn
it
I'm sorry wait where father go I'm gonna
get the beds
[Music]
here
I'm sure we'll be fine
[Music]
Rabbit Man
Mr Robin don't wander too far you're
gonna get lost wow there's a nice big
ass cave over here and we're just gonna
ignore it where I mean how big is it
never ignore it it's huge oh if you want
the one in the desert yeah wait where
false almost too big where are the asses
yeah the odd some girls are seeing it I
see it
toilet paper toilet paper
I'm just gonna Flex my bow skills
that you can hit a moving Target
oh
I didn't say I was the target
[Laughter]
um stuff's getting real low getting dark
oh no
don't be right there it's okay I have I
have I have my light sticks
[Music]
scared
mommy for now
I almost killed myself
excuse me
I don't wanna do you wanna no it's not I
don't want it no it's Gonna Fill my
pockets with unnecessary clutter
you're in a hole
oh
that's really the error of my ways is
this the twerking rabbit it is it's the
dumpy rabbit oh
oh
yeah
does it mean I can make it
um
[Music]
I forgot where you guys are oh is that
you that's you
I I ended up waiting to near near the
near the chest
[Laughter]
sorry I didn't mean to do that I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
what a place to put the
[Music]
video
but I can't sleep bedtime bedtime you
need some melatonin
can we tell stories before we sleep
okay back in my day
in Minecraft
pimples last night my story was so good
everyone fell asleep and woke up in the
morning
okay we should put them Ben's um
should we put the beds in the cave
where's the camera okay no no follow me
there's a key on you there I'm playing
Horse Race theme currently it's really
good music for this
from Zelda loafy
[Music]
I love to play classic music
beating up the weather
careful
I I forgot where it was
this way it was by the cacti
which one look at this class is here
okay
why do you remember better than me
bigger brain
that's just because you have a bigger
hand good on I was gonna say have you
seen the size of it
oh yeah that was it
and we could also fight the weather here
but I guess not
has nice shade too so we don't get
sunburned nice
but I probably have already gotten a sun
number
the only thing is maybe hard to get out
of the cave yeah
I mean we can at least put our bits here
it should be safe right yeah but it's
not that enclosed as the thing
okay
bye-bye cave I will explore you one day
surely wait wait wait
I'm getting heat stroke drink some water
yeah
it's really a problem water bottles like
that
it's my fault that you're getting a heat
stroke
maybe we should dig a hole here
oh
chest question yeah about sand here
maybe like right here
it's unsanitary
nobody uses outboard
oh
oh thank you
oh my God
[Applause]
oh I got lanterns I can put some nice
lanterns down here
um I'm just a little worried like if the
if it blows up the beds that would be
really bad so oh yeah maybe we should
dig it a little deeper we gotta go
deeper
because then we'll respawn like back at
spawn and that would be yeah unfortunate
very far
I think that's good
yeah so pretty should be good
I don't think he can fit in here did you
know that they reverse engineered Roman
concrete
really
I told my chapters they found out that
there's a lime inside of it and lime is
like a selfie it was like when it when
when it got wet lime would expand and
self-heal the concrete because they're
like how did this live for so many
billion years it's pretty cool
lime it's also like the new cars have
you seen the new car grills lime if you
pour water on it it self heals the
scratches we live in a crazy it is crazy
times I'm also a little dissolved with
acid rain no lime I guess they didn't
have that
we but
okay
okay is that cool
and very important
oh yeah that's really important touch
the bed
oh wait only one bed I have milk I have
beds only one is lots of beds lots of
beds beds beds
I think I touched it I'm gonna do it
again just to be safe wait it has to be
I don't know if I don't trust my touch
touch okay I'll do it one more time as
well just in case oh now you're making
me questions
are you sure did you really touch it
maybe you should touch it again
you will never be sure
if you don't oh just touch the left
do you touch the pillow
right after I saved the game did you
save the game Kiowa
I just saved
get saved Honestly though you can never
save enough when you're working on
something you know
draw videos
I'm scared this is a lot of anticipation
I know I can't get in it's so nice
I thought it was nice huh it is nice it
has to be one one Higher yeah
I don't need these
nice you're beautiful
nice bunker all right all right
I feel like we should fill this in
there's a giant falling Pit of Doom
where's the under chest yeah right here
but we could go like over here in
spanish anyway
like right here probably
gravity
I'm gonna do some gardening
oh let's just make sticks
why is it making sticks it's so stupid
are we ready
how does this happen what's gonna happen
I didn't Google or study before two
phases the first one he flies around and
shoots explosions at you so hit him with
your bow and eat as many carrots as you
can he's gonna give you the Wither
effect so you won't be able to see your
health you're always going to be losing
health so just eat as much as you can
eat I guess where he goes to the ground
and spawns skeletons and that's when you
want to hit him with the Smite sword
okay
and try not to die
quickly put a new totem in your off hand
would you see would you say that one
shoots then one each then one shoots
then one each is a is a good way to go
or should it be like one eat or I should
have waited
one you should eat oh should I use do it
should we spell or the potions or
yeah I have some
people I didn't bring any so maybe it's
okay I'm strong
on my own
chest outside
uh okay
you might get exploded if you put it
outside
there will be a lot of explosions that
is true the boom booms and he can
destroy items with his explosions so oh
Kelly
scaling let's get them skill the tongue
this is fine I'm sure this is fine we
run run around
run around shoot run around
shoot eat shoot oh
okay
very more dangerous holes
we could probably spawn them a little
further away probably like over there
yeah kind of flat round area here he'll
probably like move around quite a bit
though so right here seems like a good
place to be able to see you
okay there's another massive cave over
here oh my God is this the same one
she's doing it she's doing it you're
doing it they're doing it he's so sure
just on top right little stubbies three
on top one spread out spacing but will
he be right in front of my face wait
should we sleep first or no no more no
more why are we sleeping oh sun is kind
of exciting it's fine my bow is ready
I'm gonna get the first shot
laughs
who's there it's kind of small
wait he's does he he doesn't like okay
you gotta run away it's gonna do a lot
of damage it's forming right I see
[Music]
look at this okay
too far away
[Applause]
[Music]
it's going after me
I guess I'm the tank
I can't aim oh I got him
come on guys
I'm running out of arrows this is better
way too far away
I need to hit compilations
he's he's on the strong noon he sucks
look he sucks
I'm being hit by attacking him
who is that
we can get right underneath him
I'm gonna look up his skirt
what you hiding up there
[Music]
oh my gosh oh gosh he's almost half out
oh is it nice I cannot eat why can't I
eat because you're not you're not uh
hungry yet
apparently foreign
[Music]
heat them up
all right
[Music]
they got the star
the Stars the Superstar
that was blame I want another one
it took so long to get the skulls though
oh yeah that was way more difficult
is it a drop
[Music]
I am
nice
[Music]
looks like a tree star yeah I deserve it
I did the most work I'm just kidding
yeah how many gold medals do you have I
have
there's gold no
I'll try to make a joke
I have five I have um full damage I have
gold defense I have gold healing and I
have gold
um where's the Platinum
wait so I made all these potions from
nothing yeah I didn't even we didn't
even die
it's for it's fine
who wants to stop
should we go should we go back should we
go sleep in our homes
what's it called the warden let's go
right now I don't like him
who shot me
oh
let's go for the next let's go let's go
Lord is terrifying yeah Thor is
terrifying nothing's terrifying but this
team of professional Killers yeah now oh
watch out for the creeper
who am I saying that too
let's sleep
two heads
it's like Tetris down here
um
what we can get okay we don't have that
much uh that much
square meters square square feet
I don't know how it went into I don't
feel like I should hold the nether star
or maybe I should because I feel like uh
maybe fauna is the most responsible here
to hold on Kiara's idea though so she
maybe have it maybe Kiara should hold
the nether star oh yeah and here too oh
we have to take sure anyway oh yeah
can I get my box back oh oh yes sorry
no we can take a photo and somebody can
draw a really bad I must paint one and
like him in the background or something
oh yeah
no we photoshopping out the sky like
kind of faded out
yeah like fire in the clouds yeah
it almost looks like him
close enough oh was that a zombie
yeah there's a zombie I want to kill
more things in front of our cave how
about that okay yeah okay I'll build a
little like like this oh you still have
more salsa none yeah
we can pretend oh yeah I was like yeah
we're about to summon it right now
you can always summon another if you
have this because I want somebody I got
a laptop too oh you know what if you
stand behind on a block behind you could
look like the head babe There we go
[Music]
what word
we need one more
ID
with her
Winnie Kyla
um I have no head at all even even at
home in my base yeah it's at home so you
might take a while to get it but
no no we can't we can't we can't put one
remember because it's gonna summon it
when we put the third one oh yeah
okay I want to see what it summons
though
but then I can't take the picture it's
almost Kyla
let's go down
uh if you want to be better if someone
yeah
hello
uh nice
um
can you stand next to Google I got space
that was a good shot
okay and
cheese cheese
[Music]
F2
yeah wait I want to take one more
wait can we all squeeze in here you can
squeeze in there wait oh hold on
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
everyone say cheese
[Music]
I'm good
now and now don't forget the heads
man I mean we can we can raid something
we can uh
I don't know we can talk about our
deepest darkest fears
it's you mommy
with me
oh should we go make a b
[Music]
what's a beacono light up on the sky
yeah it makes a bacon bacon
do we know where we want the beacon no
I do not care at all where it goes I
want this rainbow
oh here oh my onions
can you imagine if it actually like
summons something if you put three of
them did you get it no I did I did I did
I did oh
thank you
let me know when you don't need the
chest anymore the under chest okay
good someone a gold star
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah
I don't know okay okay
shiny
honestly
oh it's uh
it builds a a cool bacon bacon
I know sometimes I make you go faster
yeah I can make you again can you speed
boat boost or mining boost
I think it should go wherever fauna
wants it she's the most active out of
all of us I think
but yeah we can discuss that maybe in
our little Discord
[Music]
for real though like what I mean I guess
I should be happy that it ended early
because it's like half past one a.m here
we are efficient as a team yeah exactly
but for real then let's next do the
warden that's so difficult challenge
how did she do that how did she bring
him to her basement like I don't know
maybe yeah
I want to fight the warden
me too I'll fight the warden yeah yeah I
found a castle the other day
I could help you guys fight the war yeah
thank you woman yeah
[Music]
come on
yeah the warden isn't meant to be fight
but I think with our strong ass team I
feel feel like we're perfect I feel like
a good match for it hell yeah um
we have to first set off
the or I don't know we gotta find the
place with the Lord and then there is a
warden right under the spawn of the new
server really
is
he look wait how do you what what yeah
little tentacles on the ground they go
um
ourselves at it yeah what the
yeah
we should oh my God happy girls noticed
how in the Japanese server they all like
they're they're guilds now they're they
have guilds we should yeah too oh
they're cute what do we call it
our Guild are we construction or
fighting or both we're fighting at least
um fighting we're just I'll be the party
trick
sharks Karen
Phoenix
[Music]
oh
wait oh it could be strong
you stop
it's for what what's next
[Laughter]
oh but you have to separate it
I mean where is FM
radio channel
[Laughter]
shark
tackle owl nature Kiana I'm the only one
with the name shark owl what'd you say
taco owl nature piano
yeah I guess we're the stones wait which
one am I oh owl
oh what a song sounds like something
oh yeah we're making stonks with our
with the quests that we fulfill in our
guilds
it's true we have the economy behind us
like look at our fancy gear we have so
much stuff wow
we can do anything we're gonna make even
more Stones I did like I do like stonks
wait if we make it wait when we have to
make a guild base
oh good good idea yeah
should we make it in the new server
because I haven't built it yeah
yes yes
should be uh I mean if we're gonna do
something big we might want to do it
another time if we want to make
something small we could do it now I
mean we can at least like claim a ground
or something
ground
we should probably sleep
what
[Music]
who who
I can trust no one let me sleep outside
oh wow you cut it off
out there
a guild what uh oh yes oh yeah yeah
who's out here disturbing the peace
am I the enemy I don't have a bit oh
never mind
bring your bed coming
up
[Music]
okay I'm coming upstairs I'm putting it
down okay
it's ready for you thank you
thank you room service truck how long
was the weather arrived like three
minutes that's yeah I don't think my bgm
even looped once
every day that's an epic bgm I don't
think it even got to finish I was just I
was I was just like one of those people
who are like on their jogs with their
their earbuds in with like Luffy playing
except there's like the world is burning
and exploding around them they're just
chilling when the world's ending you
have to listen to one last song I know
but I'm just listening to some lofi
isn't it Lo-Fi loafy just like how It's
weekly
why people always read her name wrong no
the music
and and
um
leafy
okay
[Music]
what about little fish
although Wi-Fi is different right with
Wi-Fi what is Wi-Fi stand for wireless
internet if fun internet what is it
Wireless
it doesn't stand for anything would that
be called maybe why let's put down what
did we do
apparently it's wireless fidelity Wi-Fi
what is wireless wait we what's we in
does it mean wait no why why I'm fine
why why I'm fine why not fine why am
fight Wireless infidelity
[Music]
is that when someone cheats on someone
I thought that meant like an enemy
well it could be an Infidel yeah that's
the word I think of
Infidel it just means a traitor right
which is also someone who practices
infidelity the enemy
the wireless briefly is the opposite of
that huh
what what
weird ones
you guys remember
what there's a tower the red thing is
there a tower
over here it looks like a spine
look up look up
what look up where's the door down from
the tower Dome
it's in the woods
yellow ones
cool where are you second time I'm still
in the desert right because it's cause
I'm deserted
thank you
you deserted your sense of direction
where is she I'm in the forest now ah
now you're on the floor don't go very
deep it's not very deep in the forest
it's not very deep I'm going up oh is
that the tower the big red Tower yeah oh
okay I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
oh I see your name I see you guys
okay hello hello
it's right here oh hello oh sure it is
right here well
oh is that the mark of where the game is
oh
he doesn't care about no gold
that guy was almost dead inside to know
or want anything material in this world
and man
man
now chicken
get
chicken cow
are we just naming animals we know now
where do I think I'm thinking of
something but it's not
I don't know never mind
no it's something but I can't so it's
not nothing not nothing it's something
cat dog cat dog
no that's not that's a that's a great
thing to think about but that's not what
I'm thinking about cow dog it looks kind
of scary
what kind of shark are you in shark form
because I watched a shark tier list I
just want to know a hammerhead what rank
you are I'm a salmon shark
salmon is that salmon
no but yes it is a thing it's a thing it
wasn't in the tearless so it probably
isn't really relevant is it oh no it
sounds like whoever made your tearless
this is so knowledgeable about sharks
who is who made this tier list
level information about do they send you
the videos they're so good they just
chose generic ones because they don't
know anything they just go hold shark
yeah
specialty of a salmon shark what is the
salmon shark do it tastes like seven no
they look like tiny gray ones they look
really angry but they're really small
you can pick them up with your hands and
stuff they don't do much and they taste
like some shark they might I'm not sure
salmon
I know this but I don't know is
more of a salmon than
he's killing me
it sounds like a shark
what is this just like a salmon and then
it goes like
I want to be a shark so it's a salmon
shark no he's he's shark I promise you
it's a shark
that's all I have I have no other
information about this
she played silence it's you how how do
you not know what else you want to know
is it a salmon shark is it called that
because it looks like it's the size of a
salmon
I want to know yours your stealth your
intelligence your stamina your HP your
defense I don't know it all you've been
playing too much of that jrbg game
[Music]
the house that's on fire
part 300
is it three of them are I had nine years
Lord 90 90 hours yeah 90 hours of
reading the longest game you girls ever
played game with the most hours hmm
oh
God oh my there's a lot of them here huh
wait you guys wanted to fight more right
yeah
sorry jelly
[Music]
they're so tiny and really long slinkies
okay nice cleanup
clean it up somebody said fauna's DOTA
for sure
on Steam anyway
okay okay
I don't know if I would even count these
kind of like endless going games though
I mean
at what point do you count like MMOs too
you know like play time on those
[Music]
all right
yeah all right let's go to the new
server
I'm so excited
everybody has seen the new Sarah by now
right or yeah Inna hasn't maybe I have
yeah
okay okay that's where I found the
hoarding you know
oh did you just walk into it oh sorry
wait what I mean what type of owl are
you mume are you snowy owl
I I like to change my my type of owl if
I'm if I'm stupid I'm bar now
though
or wait or annoying
I feel like the warden wouldn't kill us
but berries would
and the berry bushes the berry bushes
will definitely kill me one day
so do you know where the portals are
It's tap beer
is it a mythological creature yeah no I
mean no it's just real it's real
[Music]
what would it be otherwise
I'll come back I'm not I'm not live Hi
how are you lost I'm not lost
I'm not lost I'm not it's lost let's
shoot an arrow for you Hugo I'm found I
was just lost in life not lost you know
understandable
you'll never find me
never find
oh there she is
that you
hello
she's over there she's gone
so about hitting those moving targets
I'm sorry ma'am
are you stood in front of it you stood
in front of it ma'am you stood in front
of it you have no gun safety your gun
safety skills are
I have sword safety but I'm gonna throw
it out the window oh I fell I'll forgive
you this time
and it's like a cross
oh
no mommy no no no no no no no no no no
no
you have things to do no there's some
suspicious things going on in this in in
here no there's there's there there's
you know team kill and you sound so
suspicious why are you stuttering it's
team building no I'm telling you
confidence here
say something
yes say something that makes us all come
together again we can't oh great leader
has anyone just be stink
hahaha
okay so we're together everybody
[Music]
holy could be something else
oh no hurry before the words I've been
playing too many crosswords this is
getting dangerous hmm what are you
thinking
any place that we should have it close
to for like the sake of what about the
tree the other guild is over here right
oh oh oh oh maybe we can cozy up next to
them yeah they have cameras
like the other girls this so pretty
yeah
bless you bless you do we have something
to claim the ground
or so
um
[Music]
where's the girl that they make the blue
building is a guild
the blue building yeah over here
so cool I know
they got cannons pointed directly cool
too I want to help
whoa Senpai gills
oh my gosh I don't know if we should
build it next to here because I don't
think
comparison might be
well
good yeah make something even better
that's one of them
we're just gonna make it out of wood and
then call it
no sometimes that's the party filter
check
though
should you build me on the ocean
oh God
where do you guys go
where's the ocean oh yeah we could build
like oh where's the ocean I don't know
if that's the ocean with just water
I see you I know there's I don't know if
there's one like nearby but there's like
water here for sure
haha
okay
I feel like there's there's a lot of
land taken over here though
let's go west
yeah
where's West this way
where is this one this way
okay okay
are those pandas there's a lot of pandas
wait when did they put pandas in this
game a while long time long time ago
actually what what it came with the
jungle right what maybe it's still going
west
around
what only a panda baby if you find one
with a panda baby you want to stay away
where where are you guys heading to
we're going west where are you West
where's the Guild Hall the blue oh the
frames they just dropped all of a sudden
you're aware
we passed the pandas yeah we passed the
pandas
yeah you passed them
there's like bathroom pandas pretty good
are you guys still at the pan
no we went past the painters they even
passed the pandas only a little bit
we're five minutes
another portal
what
past the surface
what is all this the beetle are you past
no not pass the beetle what where are
they where are they
oh frog
there's a different Panda place
can you come pick me up
wait I don't think we were going west
what is that noise
it's beautiful
[Music]
your mouth
what wait is it creature sound I'm doing
that well I am a frog partially so you
know oh that's the other pen the spot
okay I see can someone pick me up
um you know you know the blue building
Guild building
we saw with the Canyons no we're just
there if you if you look at the big
pecora building like let's not stand in
front of it go right the Big Pig but
like be further away from it no it was
not it was I'm going I see you
um you see me yeah we were going south I
think oh there there you are I thought
you got the skeletons I was about to
take out my bow
no you went South
yeah or we could build over a bike I
think fauna and my Trident we're kind of
close together we could build them yeah
I was talking about the ocean like
oh yeah
and I was like shocked that you built
something it looked really good
thing yeah wait what does that mean what
hit
no no I was shocked that it like it
looked pretty much like finished but I
guess then then I went inside and I saw
it really wasn't finished and then I was
like okay that's good
are we going to the trident
yeah because um
I'll be going in that direction I was
gonna build my house near there too
actually
yeah now wait I don't know where you
guys are
um
no go back to the go back to the I see
the pandas that you saw
we lost her again
towards the the portal
the portal the beetle the Giant Beetle
are we gonna make a giant okay let's get
another portal that you guys were
talking about with our anagram in it
what I'll come find you
I don't I've never been in this area so
I don't know what you mean when you say
like the blue Guild and stuff
oh no we went back to them
what are you near them or the pandas I
can go near the Nether Portal here I'm
just gonna go
Are You Gonna Save here
okay I've been I'm near the pandas okay
we're almost there but I'm almost there
I think I see you okay
inside
prism
kind of sounds cool
wait who's m
me
I okay so I've mixed them all up some of
those like first letter names some of
them are
owl and shark and ah
where where is everybody now oh we're on
our way
oh thank you okay are we gonna build it
around cura's place now yeah around
there has more space or open space
together okay
[Music]
allergies are kicked my butt what
allergy do you have every all of it
[Applause]
have you gotten that allergy testing
before yeah
they prick your back they put your back
they pricked my arms it's either back or
arms but you can't see if it's on your
back though Stacy but you win
a piece of skin they could take a
picture probably but I didn't really
want to see no they like Cricket and see
like how your skin reacts
they were like yeah you're allergic to
everything oh no
especially everything in nature
I was only scared if I was gonna be
allergic to cats but I wasn't so I was
like okay this is yeah the animal one
was the one I was worried about I was
like this is okay this is all that I
want to know thank you
thank you goodbye yeah this is a good
spot something around here right here
how to claim it
uh make like a like a square with our I
have some Red Blocks red sand yeah me
too yeah I have normal sand should we
ride like a big en or something oh okay
wait we don't like piss FM now
uh here's some signs that we could use
noise
where are we putting it here I have a
sign
oh yeah
thank you that's like this whole area if
we want to make like a big building
so from
I'll just hmm
uh
Guild
wait sorry
I'm writing an S oh
I'm writing an s from that side wait if
this is wrong yeah I guess it was like
easier to see
no they might be easier
if you want some orange terracotta
my ass is done
there it is that's an s
who wants to do the T
everybody's looking at this
oh my goodness wow
we might run out of blocks
[Music]
oh you can do it oh I'm doing the oh is
that enough room for your tea
oh I don't think so oh I need the
cameraman
um
sorry
your tea can go in between there yeah no
boys
oh it's very short tea
nice nice oh it looks so good with some
Builders wow
like we're in sync well wow oh beautiful
um
definitely readable
oh stop
you can just ride stop I was about to do
that
I was about to do that I was like
surely they will notice if I
oh no
I'm ruining it
is
STC
oh
don't
this is Santa I can't
if you wanted to be a p yeah
um
should they be an N yeah no no no stop
[Music]
right no stop
no why are you stopping
stopping
you know yes okay okay
wonderful okay
it's a clear message
there's like an exclamation mark then
yeah
oh
stop
in the name of the law this FM
for what what does it mean wait make it
even though get rid of all this
shrubbery
that's nice Mommy
beautiful I wonder if someone's gonna be
like but why
why you will see eventually it will all
make sense
we will surely we will build something
here right now
the next three months we will make
something here yes
[Music]
okay that's a good reason for me to play
Minecraft again
for something like that there's a whole
bunch of stuff around it that's useful
right now and maybe okay we can also
like eventually the first thing we
should be doing is like make everything
around it a little bit flat so we can
have a building oh flatten it you heard
the lady flatten it all
not all
I like the area where we're building our
lives here
[Music]
robot robot robot went bad do we have
Guild rolls
is there a sign up sheet for the guild
rules can I be the dog
look I already have a shark instead
we can have an owl too they can carry
letters
can I be the owl
[Music]
can I be okay so we got the ocean we got
the sky where's the ground one
the Phoenix
but I'm in the sky too
brain hurt you're in
cane walks on land
true she's the Earth Bender oh
wow Humane can be the stoat
stone is it a ghost it's the cute little
cute little rodent cute like it looks so
cute are they rodents
cute little
carnivorous
I Wanna Be I want I want to be the
ambassador for international Affairs oh
yeah it says good good yeah okay between
ID and Japan guilds Etc okay that will
be my role please I need to write this
down
I have no sign
[Music]
I can be uh I have a book it's a video
Aesthetics uh I don't know our
ambassador ambassador
I'm not very good at designing buildings
though
I can be that that's the I don't know
wait what are Guild rolls anyway what
are they I can be the one that turns on
everybody I can be the support Google
may I please know
wait
uh and the I'm the consultant of many
affairs
yes
what kind of building do you want to do
you want something like natural or like
futuristic or modern you know
minimalistic
fantasy like what kind of costume are we
going for here I've seen so far a lot of
like RPG fantasy style builds in the
server so you want something modern
minimalistic
no actually I like the fantasy okay okay
but which style of fantasy are we going
for are we going for like uh uh you know
like the classic in town look or do you
want more like uh uh you know like a
special area kind of thing like uh in
the forest kind of building with like
cute mushrooms or or
oh mushroom sounds cute that would be
cute or like a castle or oh or you know
with the gothic Castle or like a normal
Castle or you know I like wood like wood
yeah yeah what do you guys like
like in the woods kind of like cute a
little hot like like the hobbits kind of
design
yeah what are we going for here can we
have a Hobbit's uh hole like a round
Dome like maybe that might be a little
difficult but we can make it happen yeah
your your roof is already a dome you
know how to make it oh yeah the top of
them actually I'm quite proud of that
though
let's make a shire Hobbit Shire okay all
right
[Music]
I saw I saw fauna talking about watching
Lord of the Rings with everybody but
yeah you know kiwawa and gura already be
watching it I don't know about mermaid
Inna have you girls watched I've watched
it in theaters oh
either
oh but then it's about time I know
Florida rings
yeah oh I want to listen to that
soundtrack now but have you guys watched
the Six Star Wars movie back to back oh
I've never seen one
never say anything
it's fun though it's almost May 4th yeah
it's a good good time to watch
um two Star Wars movies in my members
and I've stopped watching them because I
I refuse to watch anymore wait which
ones did you watch which ones did I the
first like the the first ones that got
released the first two ones okay you
didn't like them
um
um well I prefer a Lord of the Rings
do you like sci-fi no yeah I do not like
do you watch anime uh my anime uh Alien
do you watch Aliens oh alien is good
well
depends which but I did I didn't enjoy
the news
I need to watch Avatar the blue one okay
I was like
I was like okay which one is there a new
one coming out it's already out yeah oh
it's already out yeah
I guess mama is probably not sleeping
that's because she's not here that's
because I I just said it's sleepy time
did you think it was me again I'm not
sure
that was fun that was fun
I don't know where I put my bed uh
oh let me see those
good morning did we just leave our beds
here might as well yeah we can do that
okay all right so we have our stop sign
we have some of them
I don't know we could change it it's
whatever you want to be
what's a stoat I don't know that's what
they said I had to look it up because is
it like it's not a rodent it's like a
weasel yeah yeah it's like a little
vicious weasel yeah you
okay well then that was uh way easier
than expected but we finally did it I
mean it's a warm-up you know for the
warnings yeah
[Music]
okay go in my basement you can hear him
oh did you see the woman's Castle
no it's actually quite nearby here comes
is it really or am I getting
yeah like a cross over there do you see
what this is the warden's Castle is he a
big tree
so did they just like build it on top of
it isn't that cronies the warden don't
think oh the word
oh my god
oh
[Music]
I love this soundboard okay all right
who's that
okay
this one is where am I put my guild
resignation
you can't it's written and it's sealed
and signed we have a contact for further
inquiry now you can't back out
you'll have to come before the council
before you remove yourself from the
guild That's the Law we're in front of
two of them yeah
and I say oh wait no we say what do we
say
we say hey stop we say you're trapped
here forever not listen to all the
soundboard and toot noises
okay I guess I have no choice
all right I am content
me too I live here now in front of the
stop sign
that's all we need to live these beds
okay then
I will leave let me get wrapped it up
today yeah
for us yep
[Music]
killed the Wither like it was uh never
pain in my neck
here we'll kill the warden like it's in
our garden
watches or else we'll all be very upset
please
that's cool that's fine yeah yeah
okay thanks guys thank you guys putting
it together thank you for organizing and
for asking if anybody wanted to beat the
Wither and for uh
flying and beat up the Wither yeah and I
learned what the Wither was and there
you go and yeah more experience in my
life yeah yeah
the stunks
goodbye
[Music]
it's on your cape
which one yours I have a key