[Music]
do
two check here we go here goes the chat
whoa
hey hello everyone can you hear cali can
you hear the game can you hear me on the
other side
i guess i kind of want the music to be
bumping a little more guys let's turn up
this banging music
it's been in the background for me for a
long time and i want to
bang it even high even higher here we go
the music is awesome
it's vibing it's like such a jam it's
vibing
we are vibing hey guys hey guys wow wow
well well i think i really well the
sound seems
fine okay okay oh
okay a little bit higher okay okay i'll
turn you down a tiny bit tiny bit
okay okay well welcome everyone
we are here today because we are playing
together as
takamuri bleach brave dolls
where they actually got a big big major
update with
a lot of new content including the arena
er so i thought that we should give it a
shot we together aren't we the best
couples to do this stuff together we are
i mean i guess it has been a long time
since we have
done a collaboration stream together so
i pose i suppose now is a
as good a time as any well you say a
long time but it was just last week
oh yeah i mean i guess it just feels it
just feels like a long time
yeah it does if we don't talk for a week
or like don't collab for a week it feels
like a long time
yeah it does well anyway i'm talking
about
all of english and who are you hi
oh hello there hi i'm uh mori callipe
from whole live english
um i'm i'm the resident shinigami reaper
hey what's up what'd it do i'm excited
to play this
this game must be perfect for you
i've been looking for it oh so
yeah guys you uh and uh we
i guess we start right off with telling
you guys that you have to download the
game
i think you can uh use the link in our
descriptions for it
and by the way there is free service
there is a japanese server there is a
cert
an asian server and there is the global
server and will be today
playing on the global server together
yup yup that's right and um it's super
easy to download
um and really easy to just get into
um you can just you can just go head
first into that bad boy
um plenty of tutorials to kind of show
you around
um the ui and whatnot and i get to feel
comfortable playing it so i
highly recommend you just jump right in
you guys super easy maybe you'll play
against one of us someday i don't know
i'm um i'm gonna keep you for myself
kelly
ah we're gonna work hard together today
and
and forever until eternity um
yeah i don't know i can't make any
promises on that one
can't make any promises on that one
listen
oh well so um
want to talk a little bit about bleach
yeah sure thing one moment guys i have a
qr code that i want to give you oh yeah
just to make it super easy
did you see it yeah let me go ahead and
grab that qr code
it's right above me i'll go ahead and
grab grab that bad boy
here we go trying to scan it guys try it
try it i challenge you do it just do it
just from your screen from your screen
you should be able to from the stream
screen the storm squad
scan the current
do it do it all right challenge accepted
quick and easy screenshot here we go
just to make it easier for you guys just
to make it easier for you guys
you can just go ahead and grab that bad
boy it's a luxury
yeah you guys hear me take that snap
here
it's taking a while from that oh
[Music]
what what
did you get the qr code on the screen
i did can you make it a bit bigger oh
okay i had this ish i had this issue
with it before
there you go is that big enough no
problem guys
take it it's
big now big qr code it's a bit blurry
now
i think it should be fine
just kidding i got it okay i wrangled
that bad boy
all right
here you go yes all right oh i got it oh
now it's on my face ah get out of my
face
there we go here you go guys don't cut
out your beautiful face
huh i'm shy listen
um you guys get it from here you admit
to get it
what no
it's okay i've noticed that before i
already know about it anyway
so are you ready yeah sure thing
okay yeah where'd you put yours by the
way i'll put it in my top right uh above
my logo
my own logo okay cool
sounds good i don't want to cover up the
name grim shady because it's so iconic
i love that name i i'm so jealous now
because i got
i came out with a really basic boring
name kiara hodo
and yours is green shader sounds so cool
pyramid real quick okay everyone you are
me
let's see
[Music]
okie dokie so and there we go
okay let's talk about bleach
please stand up yes a bleach um i know i
have a bunch of bleach fans
that are here oh i know that you guys
are really excited for me to play this
game
um bleach is just a whole lot of um
nostalgia
because bakken's a day and this is
actually
this is this is something that i just
recently remembered
um one of my first like christmas gifts
from my mother that i ever received when
she found out that i liked uh manga and
anime
was a volume one of the bleach manga
what
yeah so technically it's the first
manga volume that i ever owned um was
was bleach
wow then thank you thanks to your mom i
guess
oh okay ignored back in the day
lady death i think i was not active long
enough in the game i got kicked out
oh no that's okay no problem get back in
that bad boy um
but yeah so that's probably um why it's
kind of um very it's a very nostalgic
franchise for me and also because
um and this isn't so much back in the
day i did i did watch the anime and read
them
today um but then after that
it was kind of um a long while before um
when i got into
reaper college i guess um my roommates
were really really really into bleach i
had a friend
who was a huge fan of kampachi
oh and drew so much kampachi fan art so
like
that whole like arc um where like
kampachi is kind of like the
the the main i guess in that arc they
focused on i distinctly remember so
oh my watching so much of it because my
friend
really really really likes kenpachi oh i
wonder if your friend is running with my
daughter
i really hope that she's doing well
wherever she is she knows who she is so
i hope she's watching this and being
like hey
that's me i'm that friend
shout out to your friend to your
kompatchi fan friend
i think i also like uh kempachi's
bangkai the best
oh really really freaking cool sick
waiting a long time for it
a lot of anticipation leading up to it
how about you kiara who's who's um
or do you have good memories of bleach
well to be honest i i'm not the best
informed person but bleach was like well
because i grew up in a german-speaking
country
um on tv there was like barely any anime
on it when i was younger but
one of the few like let's say there was
a handful like maybe
five five animes on german tv
in in german language german dubbing and
one of those
five animes was bleach
so i kind of like when i was uh
um i think i sub um how do you say
subconsciously
watching it yeah subconsciously yeah
just like i watched those other
uh animes which i will not mention but
it was like i think i didn't even
realize yet like that it was
like what an anime is and all that but
from from back
in dad's time i do remember bleach a
little bit
um it's just been so so long because i
was a
really small baby phoenix and i barely
remember what happened back then
but it was one of those few legendary
german uh legendary anime that made it
into the german tv
so yeah oh my gosh long long long time
ago yeah and now
it's still here because it is so
legendary and we have a
super fun looking game in front of us
i'm pretty hyped yeah oh about the
bankers what would your bank i be
that's a good question bangkai being
like okay so like your ultimate freaking
freaking start and move myself around
signature freaking move unleash
the final the final form that you've
trained for ages
ages four i don't know i mean it's
already pretty obvious that like
my um my like my shinigami my sword my
uh
my zampa kuto i don't know how to
[\h__\h]
i'm so bad at the pronunciation would
obviously be ricky
right yes i would obviously use ricky
right so like let's see i haven't
actually thought super hard about what
kind of
sig bank i would have just something
really stereotypical grim reaper right
probably i mean i feel like for me but
it'd also be super cool
i think of course everything is
except actually little known fact
shinigami don't don't eat your souls at
least not where i'm from
not where i'm from you wouldn't eat a
dollar bill i've said this before
right we basically treat schools like
currencies so it's a little different a
little different i say i say i was going
to
compare your job to their job but i
guess it's
there are some there are quite a few
differences
i will say though i kind of do want like
the cool shinigami
robe look that's going on because like
my outfit's pretty dank but like
you should wear the outfit that ichigo
wears
i mean i kind of i kind of want my own
my own i guess kind of uh look
from the bleach universe i can't say
that those pants
yo i know they're kind of styling i want
to see it
a little bit by the way my i think my
move would be something obviously
phoenix
fire related so maybe like yeah it would
be called
maybe a turtle flame or something like
that
yeah uh yeah i can see that and
and it's already blasting the background
i already do have
my my weapon you know i have my sword i
don't know why i didn't pick it up today
i think it's because it would be
covering up you
but that's i think i'm already equipped
perfectly
that's my son eternal friend
don't come here don't everyone all of
you are true nebula
and cow you as well look at you your
junipero
[Music]
so i mean i guess am i really yeah isn't
that kind of an insult
no no no no no it's not what the hell
you know what juniper means
no can you explain to me because i feel
like i keep getting the wrong like
impression what juni
is a second second grade in
uh the thing before high school
it's officially in english i guess it
would be like a creative
schooler yeah yeah but in our system i
guess it would be eighth grader
syndrome it's like you know when you as
a child you you act like
if you have all kinds of magical powers
and all that but i mean we
we do it's not we don't act as if we do
you
you're a reaper i'm a phoenix i can i
can totally spit fire this is not just
my imagination
oh yeah is that a fact it's like the
edgy teen face yeah
edgy no oh actually i guess edgy preteen
face oh i see i see
yeah you kind of get it when you when
you phrase it that way it makes a little
more sense yeah
well anyway to go back to the topic
er bleach brave cells is as we talked
about
originally a popular tv anime and
uh it was also it's i think it's is it
still continued the manga
i wonder no it's it's ended i believe
it's ended okay
well and then and now you got this
smartphone game
uh but you can also play it on pc on
steam if you don't want to play it on
your phone for whatever reason
and then you can get all these fancy
characters you can build teams you can
fight together with them
and take on super super big strong
enemies and yeah also there's some co-op
uh things and arena and all that up to
six
people can play together with new
friends let's go have some fun like we
are having today
yeah exactly very excited you wanna
er explain how we do the co-op thing
um the yeah sure absolutely
eat some all right so let's see
uh before we do before we actually uh
jump into the co-op
we're going to need to um
it's it's that time everyone yeah the
gotcha
all right it's got your time you guys um
we all knew that this was coming
um let's see if if we can be lucky
because i'm not sure
a lot of um pools right so we're gonna
do all of them yeah
uh yeah i mean i'd like to but mainly
what we're trying to do here is
we're doing the uh the guaranteed
selectable six
oh is the main gotcha we're doing so go
to the shop summons
characters i think this shoe is a six
star summons so basically you get one of
five characters
chosen by you and now we'll try to use
that
exactly we'll use the character that we
get uh in the co-op
do you want to go for it sure
legs for free into the gotcha hell let's
go
all right into the gotcha how we go
and we get only one right uh yes
so basically you choose five characters
to use in the summons and
you can see details you use character by
tapping and holding on their thumbnail
image
my megane prince hold on a second sorry
i love this dude
i'm ready my dog i am ready
i'm gonna listen oh yeah you're gonna
probably be choosing completely
different characters let's see what you
end up with i'm going in
i'm going in this show has a lot of a
lot of cool mega names
and a lot of cool uh closed eye
characters we got we gotta start with
the homie
with my main homie though
santa claus only visits those children
oh that's all
i got let's uh she looks like a claws
i'm just gonna make this nice and big
for you guys um so i think you guys
everyone here um in in my
in my chat realizes
um who is your favorite bleached
character
now uh there are only two selections but
that's because the right answer is in
there
um so uh it is a bit
a bit rigged though uh because again
ichimaru lost the pole
um i don't understand how that could
happen possibly um
but it's fine also because uh gin also
won the poll again again is the best
oh my god i got them
i basically got it it's christmas over
here because i got
that so in the christmas santa claus
outfit
oh my gosh christmas in june my name is
really cute
are you pulling yet no i'm looking at i
want to look at the homies
i'll summon some others meanwhile i
guess can i summon those they got 300
scenes
just has like an array of just
incredible mega on a characters
that's another thing you can do so okay
i just want to point this out really
quick
um you guys can watch ads yeah and to
get character
is it i just thought that was really
cool is it bleach ads because then i'm
fine with it
oh i'm i'm not sure actually
i haven't tested it out yet
oh that's her again so cute i want to
try yeah
bless me um i will oh yeah bless you
sorry i was really engrossed in the
gotcha pulling
cool wait i can get two what the [\h__\h]
what you can get two
no no just know she wrote no no no no
it's just just toshiba
wait out someone again can i do that oh
yeah
yeah oh what is this beginner summons
i need to see my options there's too
much going on in my head right now
okay i want the homie
oh green joe
yeah grim jiao grim jiao is um i chose i
chose grim jio as my first free
character
oh but i don't think i get him in the
co-op unfortunately
i think these are the homies
yeah chad i remember chad
i got in the chat
oh that was used to be so taken aback
and i'm like oh someone said chad
why'd they say chad i'm like
you will receive one of the characters
you selected did you choose the the six
yeah i already got that i'm doing
different gotcha while
okay cool i got the christmas lady
that's it
nice nice good results i think christmas
ladies
can wait did you get gin yeah i think so
what
i remember getting him in in the other
godzilla that i just did
okay explain to me where the where the
gotcha is i just did
uh the beginners the beginners concert
beginners
yeah beginners kick off summons okay
yeah dad won that one
i got him i think i remember him even
twice no
what what oh freestyle free start again
oh wait can i add my team here wow all
right
level 200
cali they come as level 200. wait what
the six oh yes we don't have to worry
anymore about losing
nice what what else
look at all these cute cones
not enough spirit orbs no
[Music]
all right all right but we're not
fighting with this team because co-op is
only with one character
and i think we'll be using our six star
character
holy damn level 200. yeah i'll use ricky
yeah
oh yeah all right all right all right
first thing for kia
my poll still stands you guys know what
to do go vote
so for the for the co-op we're gonna
hide the screen for a moment but
uh yeah yeah okay
hide that hide that bad boy all right
all right um you guys aren't allowed to
see it's a secret
wait where's my screen uh
this one there we go okay i hit the
screen
are you uh just i guess write the read
the code to me and
in le discord and then i'll we'll do
we're gonna do the droplet trial
okay we tried uh by the way off
which we tried before doing the gaja
and we uh gloriously failed and died
two times two out of two times
but we didn't have our six stars yet so
now we have obviously higher chances
yeah exactly
and there's a there's a little
surprise i guess i'm gonna explain it
while you're setting up the lobby
yeah there is a surprise this time
during our playthrough if we can clear
the quest
three times which i am now hopeful we
will manage to do
we have got the permission to give all
players
20 spirit balls and 10 gotcha tickets
as a gift yay yeah
thank you caleb i know they thank you
very much hiding because of the matching
guys did you listen
yeah we have to hide you guys aren't
allowed in here it's our it's our secret
secrets it's our secret room our secret
room
just gonna be sarah are you able to are
you able to use the character that you
pulled
oh wait yeah i have to set that up
that's right oh
let's see no i am not
i'm also not but i do have hanatara for
some reason who is it level one
um yeah recommended level 120
um maybe let's not let's not do that um
i'm going to make a new room
and we're going to do um level 20.
how do we change i can be ichigo level
20.
i had this issue earlier as well yeah
yeah
i'll send you a new one oh damn i'm
making a new room but then
if we can't use the six star this is
gonna be uh
ah maybe it's fine it'll be a nice
challenge rarity descending
the right attribute all all it's all
them
all hit cancel choose the green tab
ah kelly
you figured it out get out uh when
you're like
when you had you you know that you did
the the the
you opened that window right where we
want to change the character
and even further on the right side
there's two signs for kokoro
in japanese right and in one of those
windows it should have
uh the character that you pulled for me
it was the the green one
okay me too actually okay we're
talking now we're talking now we're
cooking all right cool
thanks jen here we go making the room
thank you very much chad you guys are
chad's
okay you're making a new room right
yep okay level 200 woo baby now we can
just go right into it so we're going to
do
we're going to do the droplet trial
we're just going to do level
um 120. let's do technique droplet trial
that sounds fun create a room we got
that technique no problem
we do we do i chose the one that was uh
green for both of us so
all right and here you go here's the
code all right
and one three three four
just kidding i'm gonna switch back to
the main screen but i am going to go
ahead and cover up the uh
okay in fact i'll use the qr code
i am in it it doesn't
say the code anymore i think though once
we're in that room
oh it does for me so i'm gonna cover it
oh okay yep
all right perfect now we're gonna go
ahead and switch
okay cool here we go
oyster right we're ready let's go
are you ready to party kiara you're so
ready and
that's a perfect combination we're gonna
wrap
this exciting stuff here we go
on to the battle we go
kiara and the grim shady
the real grim shady get it right i'm the
real grim shape
it only says scream shady in your name
i'm flying all right look at all these
six special attacks i got
oh down you go rich money all right
wow what
that was so sick holy [\h__\h] those
freaking icy moves
you need my way with you i love this
strong oh wait my health oh no i gotta
watch it
i can't just go in ruthlessly like that
don't do it
i'm gonna should not overdo it we gotta
be saving those big moves
just kidding i'm gonna go ahead and use
my powerful move right now
let's go
damn goodbye everyone
yeah maybe i don't know probably should
have saved it i don't really care that
looked
sick no need for saving your special
abilities
ahead no no need for that you're right
you're totally right i have a bad habit
of doing that
saving my specials i love those aoe
skills i have like they're
all fire fiends is that a phoenix like
what the hell
that's really cool it's almost perfect
all of this was planned
yeah ice and fire conspiracy theories
all right i got him where are we going
all right where to next i'm not in bad
shape right now
i'm just gonna although otto is gonna
lead the way
there we go do it oh no murano thank you
lads
i don't need your help oh i'm dead here
use the spirit orbs to continue it's
fine i'll
i'll use my spirit orbs and i'm back to
life
it's cool leave it to me
[Applause]
we gotta win this kiara for the viewers
epic power where are you at
i guess i guess we still need to oh no i
have 40.
the viewers for the viewers i want them
to get the free stuff
we'll do it for you guys don't worry
should i use is there gonna be like a
final
boss that i should
it's okay we'll play it again we'll play
it again after this
we'll play a different trial i panicked
and i skipped it no
oh [\h__\h] i took it away from you guys
no problem holy [\h__\h] i want the viewers
to get the free stuff
i had one hp for the longest time oh my
gosh
that's kind of impressive though in and
of itself that is impressive
the clutch i am back
i will protect my green shading
huh okay
easy cool we're going
[Music]
that way ah the i think that everyone
shows us where to go
oh okay cool nice
okay party time lads
i think i really just figured out what
my like ultimate
final move technique would be
i like use my my scythe turns into um
the bass guitar from my roki cover
oh i shanned with what with one stroke
everyone just dies
that sounds dope
how are we doing it actually reminds me
um back in the day
papa reaper used to like watch a lot of
anime with me oh
um and actually used to watch bleach
with me as well
watkins a day and i specifically yeah
papa reaper
i specifically recall him saying you
know kelly
if i if i had an ultimate technique for
my sword it would turn into
a piano and and if i hit one key
everyone in the world dies and i said
i don't think that's i don't think
that'd be a very good move
he's like why not and i'm like well if
everyone in the world dies that's just
kind of
i mean it's not a great yeah
not really my parents did not really
have any interest in anime
oh yeah yeah i mean mama reaper didn't
either but
she she was happy to get me manga if i
wanted it very nice
my family from holiday presents to
gaming like we played world of warcraft
instead
yeah yeah you mentioned that yeah
they're big gamers but
not oh you died again you're not big on
that we're dying so
much yeah but the good thing is we got
some girls to revive ourselves so we're
not gonna fail
yeah i think we'll be fine yeah for the
viewers for you guys
yeah let's go
go go go wow
[Music]
for each other i'm surprised that
those are level 120 and we're 200 and
they're still
killing us so often yeah but we're also
killing a lot of them
is the thing i don't think we're really
we realize like how many people we're
taking down yeah
there's a lot
thank god for those aliens yes i know
right
and i love being able to attack from far
away that's super on brand for me
actually
my scythe can do stuff like this
yeah slash and then like a sick like
blast of what looks like air but it's
really it's the cycling extending
yeah oh oh whoa the boss battle time
party
give me this i have to break it okay now
give it to me
all right while you're frozen i'm gonna
beat you up
and here we go here we go we have to do
it
hey kiara do you have any accessories by
chance i don't think we've really gotten
into that yet
uh nothing added at least no i don't
know do we have fun
it's okay we're we're going it we're
going in just uh just raw like this my
dog no problem
it's fine we're fine no
problems don't wipe me no problems
hang on let me get out of here i need to
run i need to run no no
please okay i'll come back back to life
back to reality
oh my god it's a big grip
we can do this we can do this we just
have to be careful be on the defensive
oh oh my god i wish i still had my
special skill both of us we both wasted
it
yeah it's honestly it's my fault because
i chose like a really hard level
next we'll we'll go to the the medium
one okay
and there we go we're just not uh that
leveled up yet it's fine
oh my god the bus is there she's dead
almost i think
oh really oh sick wait that was no that
is a really different heavy
uh medieval flail oh my god no
okay i need to use more of my specials
where am i we're sheet
stamina jewel nice
phoenix finish yeah we did
is like a phoenix
all right are you back with the lady i
think i'll hide quest clear
oh no there we go
[Music]
oh should i should i send you a friend
request
i'll send you one i don't know did you
question
yeah send a friend request i'll send you
one
let's be friends oh
also a friend requested you are now
friends beat me to the punch
yeah let's go back so i know
yeah i just figured something out kiara
oh um
it's that the stage that we were on oh
was meant for four people
so actually in reality we are really
good at the game
were we good or where are our characters
good
that's a good question well that's very
one out of three victories we want to
get two more victories in order to get
those free
stuff for the audience exactly
let's open up vote and use one time
we're gonna go on a stage for two people
oh okay that's good
then it might also not take that long
but
this is this is actually a lot of fun i
know there's also
the arena right and which is the new
feature
and we wanted to try it out but
unfortunately the arena is a bit buggy
at the moment so we can't play that
today guys
i hope that's okay but you guys make
sure to check the arena out
once it's available once it's fixed
and then you're gonna have a lot of fun
in there i promise you
yes indeed i went ahead and created a
brand new room kiara so i'll give you
the code
okay this time uh we're going to be
tackling a
bit of an easier level um stage
this one also looks like it's for four
people though so let me see
hold on
all right so we're going to be doing um
like a lower level
stage if that's all good with you
yeah no problem i i did test the arena
in the tutorial though
so i i didn't see that on the street
it's
very interesting we do want to check it
out someday
i only did the tutorial yeah that sounds
really fun we should play it together
let's go with level 20. i think the
arena was for
three people maximum three people so
we can invite some more friends next
time
yeah exactly what did you write new room
code incoming okay
[Music]
there you go okay there we go
i recommended uh we got recommended the
accessory fusion trial
and it's beginner mode so i think we
might not die this time how about we
make it a challenge to not die at all
this time
i don't want to have to use them
challenge accept dad
let's go right let's do it at the quest
okay here we go it's in the city oh like
wow are we flying
oh we're just we're fighting flying
monsters oh sick we're fight oh on air
that's so sick
okay cool oh yeah these aren't much
easier they die immediately
leave it see your boy to pick a
professional shinigami mission right off
the bat
dying is just my eyes so it's okay it is
my instinct
wait aren't you level 10. i can't help
it yeah that is uh that is i think
that's why it's recommended level 20.
[Music]
if we do well on this one we'll go up to
level six okay
enjoy that trial oh missed some some
sparkly thing
okay we'll get them next time oh what a
waste why'd i use that then
fine
ho ho ho i am santa
too let me bring you some just leaves
you know what that fits really it's
this is another this is another homie
right here also i remember
really really liking back in the day
okay now this is
mostly because look at this
oh you are very elegant this is oh merry
christmas
i want him you have to do my food dirty
like
that dude is so short so freaking small
yeah yeah look at that nose you like
short people
chat knows they're calling me out kiara
i'm calling you
too right here at the spot hey you stop
that hey
hey listen well not bad not bad let's go
back to the co-op quest menu and i'll go
ahead and start up a brand new room and
this
time we're going to do level 60 kiara so
we might get just the right balance here
that's two out of three wings that we
needed
a little bit off balance because one was
super hard one was super easy but the
next one
will win as well no problem
all right let's see uh let's do um
accessory fusion trial
uh level 60. sound create a room
all right and here's the code i'm on
your way
three jag it's the first number
ready i am so ready
all right i got it i have received the
secret code
there we go all right
okay let's party
okay let's start ready up here we go
we've got to do this for everyone for
the kfp employees for the deadbeats
just for everybody what
yes this is for everyone what did you do
huh nothing this is for everyone ah this
battle
that's why we must win the presents yes
yes
yeah it's fitting that you're dressed
like um like a santa because it's like
you're going to be gifting the kfp
employees and the deadbeats yes
by winning these battles i'll get them
the spear balls also works really well
because my powers are super icy
iced ice baby
dude i don't i don't want to get
stricken
okay it's a big move
okay that's a big one oh wow
yeah get them knock them down we make a
good team
um
okay yeah i think
i think caleb knew that takamori
was unbeatable and perfect
perfectly harmonized yep
exactly of course now this
this level feels um like pretty good for
us
yeah yeah difficulty was
i did like the the first one though
because it was quite the challenge
it gave me it was i like the challenge
it gave me that
what's it called like adrenaline yeah
adrenaline
yeah adrenaline and we're gonna go up i
thought that's here
fun okay here we go
boss battle are you ready lost battle
give me some of this
we don't need the health until maybe
later so oh
you want to use your special skills uh
oh yeah i might as well huh
i mean it's time anyway here we go
show us what you got yeah here we go
we're a good combination merry christmas
mary curry
[Music]
three out of three battles all clear
what does that mean
that means what it means yes we're
giving everyone
20 spirit balls and 20 brave souls
actually no yeah it was uh supposed to
be 10 but we're actually giving 20 brave
souls gotcha tickets
yay got that we did it kissatory we did
it
for you guys free orbs
everything's very exciting you'll
probably just receive it so
in the game automatically at some point
look forward to that
yes so let's get out of that co-op
uh arena all right go back home joe wow
you got nice hair yeah yeah
wait who grim joe yeah
yeah yeah he got a name let me go back
to him and he got that kitty tail
wow yeah wow
cute wow it is quite long
another one of my faves um a real cool
real honorable homie right here do some
spins for us grimshaw do some spins for
us oh yeah are you looking at my stream
no no no i have i have my own little oh
you got him too
i'm spinning him around he's doing a
little dance for me
dance my little my little ring-tailed
lemur boy well i prefer
wow uh i think that was that was a lot
of
fun uh i think we had a blast with that
but unfortunately
it has come to an end
you like to make the announcement
of that actually first kiara i want to
think i want to do
i actually do want to i want to play one
more round if it's okay
oh sure is that okay okay okay
okay did you did did we miss something
no i i want to i want to play an upper
mid-tier quest
if at all possible is that okay of
course
why not ye
okay cool let's do it awesome i
i have the itch i want to play just a
bit longer if it's fine with you you
could even
if you won a bit of a challenge you
could change the character from your
level 200 character
to the
wait where um ah wait wait wait are
there yeah we could change but they're
level one
the other ones that we got like
let me see let me check out the trials
here because i want to see like the
recommended level
maybe like upper to maybe level 100
might be good might be a good one to
check out
100 the droplet plus yeah i feel like
that might be pretty good that's pretty
much uh like upper
i trust literally for mid i trust you
okay cool
awesome yeah level 100 might be good um
let's see how about accessory fusion
trial
um let's do the green one what's this
kanji
uh you're the expert the green one
i can't read i can't read because i know
i can read
coco
oh okay so cool like like special vasa
special technique
oh i see i see cool let's do that one
together and i'm gonna go ahead and
uh hide the password real quick and make
the room and this will be
our final go at it i have a good feeling
about this one okay
all right let's do it and create that
room going in for
an uh extra round uncle dude
conquer uncle cool
everyone say it
i could get one of those whichever one
you guys want just type it in the chat
let's go
okay i got your i got your keys
we got this one i'm excited to see how
we fare this time because this is like
this one i think this is perfect
more difficult than the last one we did
huh
oops this is this one's more difficult
than the level 61 but it's not as
difficult as the first one that we did
then let's go that one was like 120 or
something like that so
i think this should be fine all right
start the quest here we go let's see how
we fare
you ask for uncorru you get an encoder
here we go
all right here we go we're outside okay
all right hey guys it's a park yeah just
a little
a little sampo together osanpo oh my
gosh
it's such a nice holiday outside um
hmm could not be more fitting i'm gonna
burn this forest back all right a bit of
a cuisine
okay yeah this level is pretty good it's
about like challenging
um and pretty tense but not unbeatable
we're not failing the first second
that's good
where are you where am i
[Music]
oh okay you're under if you're under
attack don't hit that one no ah
i'm gonna have to use it early it's fine
just use yours for the final boss please
shaku
blast them away that's that's the way to
go
nice hit that hit it grim shady
cool yeah grim shady you can count on me
stand up yeah
okay the health orb i think we'll make
it out of this okay i spoke too soon i
spoke to you soon
oh no okay from here i'll get him from
here
attack from far away yes keep a safe
distance
save this that seems like a pretty good
technique
the damage will reach them probably
nice strategy okay
oh we're in the morning again by the way
my favorite place i might die
soon all right no worries i got your
back
nice i just rise again
is that that attack is that a fire manta
or a phoenix i'm not sure
i gotta revive once here i'll let myself
revive one one time me too me too
yeah okay i i feel like
we're actually pretty close to this one
i feel pretty good about it
oh there's another okay
nice oh you're still here hang dude
sorry i was gonna
i had to oh
all good in the neighborhood oh my
it is boss battle time lost battle
and i'm here for it yes use it just use
it right now
ho ho take this present i hope you like
it
thanks you've been a very good child
very good boy very good girl
very good i'm just gonna leave all the
stuff
oh then she is here that's my dude wait
no what are you doing my dog randy no
no it's my dog
it's so cool right i think we won yeah
we're done we're done
we're done
yeah quest clear leave it to us
like yeah oh damn i felt really good we
got usb
i don't know why but i got kicked out
again sorry but we're at the end anyway
so
it's all good yeah no worries got all
kinds of item bonuses yata
yes it's too fun to spin them around
like a dj
so oh man i can't wait to go draw more
characters we did
four of
for all the free co-op challenges i
think we have uh
done very well with that and that was a
lot of fun like i love
all of the the like fighting effects the
attacks that we had and for some reason
there must have been some
faith here because me getting a
character with all those fire skills
it is it is meant to be
yes i think so that was it worked out
almost too perfectly i would say but
there there were no forces at work you
guys that was just
that was just the god the gotcha gods
giving us all their luck
thank you gotcha thank you caleb for
sponsoring this and there's also
a currently running campaign as you see
saw see sauce
as you've seen the uh six star
received six six star characters uh
campaign
you get a chance to roll it that's the
same one that the same that we did right
yep maybe you guys will i don't know be
pretty lucky and get uh
your favorite character guin ichimaru uh
from the series bleach i don't know
maybe you'll be a little luckier than me
any possibilities can happen anything
can happen you guys i'm gonna probably
go back and try to get
to try to try to get my faith you're not
satisfied you must get more and more
from the gotcha
it's okay i understand i understand i've
been very addicted to gotcha games
before and it's just what happens but
we're trying to control yourself a
little bit okay we don't want to lose
you
it's easy to lose yourself there
it's okay yeah it's okay
a little bit more is okay you're not
that deep in there yet
i didn't realize like i always used to
be like ha i don't understand
the the gotcha thing and now all of a
sudden with these feelings of wanting to
plug in i'm like i'm
slowly starting to kind of get it i
kinda
there have been some in the past that
have similar like things like that but
not
it is my first like like really like
gotcha yeah
maybe maybe my second yeah and that's
like the best you could start out with
or like
get into because it has like all these
connections to you
i recently have started saying holos a
little bit
i can't stop myself i don't know where
that came from
oh hey listen definitely not my job
come on come on man listen
but i have a list of characters that i
want to pull actually
i'm going to read them out to you you
guys know obviously i think you guys
know who number one is
again of course um i got rukia yeah
go ahead and cross her off my list
little check mark
um we gotta get udahara
so the the the one big memory i have
of um of udahara is that at every single
um gathering of fans of
um of anime and manga always had
like maybe 500 people wearing his head
oh oh yeah mr keys okay
so i'm just picking up my free stuff
there's a lot of different stuff in this
game
but i picked up rip the band-aid off you
guys i also owned one of those hats
are very good hats are very cultured and
useful
usual who like this one
and then i did get gampachi and i don't
have
toshiro yet and i wanted to get an ng
and i have grimjao use grimshaw for the
next co-op
arena friend requests
sorry guys now you're getting a lot of
friends yeah yeah oh yeah
i'm sorry guys oh that's a lot of friend
requests i can't accept them sorry guys
you cannot accept cannot accept
let's see if we got so far we got campos
are you going for your list oh my god
i'm looking through all the characters
that i got
what's with all these coins there are
literally so many dude that's what i was
gonna say i was like really
should we make an army with them
you know what yeah who of the same
character cannot be in the same team i
see you
well then i just have to pull different
columns that's the way that you fix that
smart you put in chat you need chat
callie
i do how come you didn't get the chad
with the shades i don't know dude you
seem to get you
got a lot of the characters that i
wanted so i'm like i'm not salty or
anything i'm just you know you know
i'm just yeah whatever man
i'm sorry i took i took your look i
don't know it kind of uh
went over to my side it's not on purpose
oh man that's awesome
i you know what after this i i'm
definitely going to go get
okay good luck i do want to at least
see how playing the game is with the
homie because i just remember i used to
be such a big fan back in the day and
still kind of ammoness
oh the whole squad is here we got
grimshaw we got rookia
we got kenpachi yeah on the stone that
swivels as well
so kelly are you are you i'm ready to uh
say goodbye to you all you beloved
characters
no is it time already i want to play
i want to play with them more well
everyone will enjoy
the free rewards that you got through us
and i hope that you guys will enjoy the
co-op mode and the arena
you can already play the arena we just
didn't we weren't able to introduce it
today
so sorry about that but i definitely
should check out and as you see above us
there is a qr code or maybe cali
somewhere else but try out the qr code
and otherwise the links in the
descriptions are there as well for you
guys
to check out and download the game get
it today
or get it never or i mean whenever but
but today would be the best day to get
it
so have fun
have a good time and maybe maybe you'll
run into one of us i don't know
um who could say because i mean i i can
speak for myself when i say i i'm gonna
be doing a
couple more polls reliving my uh
nostalgia trip hey listen
i didn't think it was gonna hit me this
hard until now
i'll invite you to my circle of
anonymous gotcha players uh
to help you out later on yeah sounds
good
thank you appreciate it please behind me
really yeah you know it's part of that
circle
way no way heck yeah my dude please
please
i don't know if that's a good thing or a
bad thing anyway i just wanted to also
say um a big
thank you to caleb again for sponsoring
this stream
thank you so much uh for letting us play
your super fun game and for giving our
fans some awesome rewards
for our very valiant efforts we had lots
of fun
yeah i want to try it again maybe maybe
next time
we can do the arena
yeah i want to try out arena soon that
was that said
i'll say goodbye to my peeps in german
and in german we say
au friday and you remember kelly
i did i did and and for the deadbeats we
say
do you remember kissathoti what could
it possibly be is it is it
is it war is it battle or is
it maybe peace oh my
you're pulling my leg here because it's
sorry yes it's peace
uh bye everyone see you later thank you
so much caleb for sponsoring and hope
you guys enjoy playing
bleach brave souls catch you on the flip
side bye-bye
bye bye thank you for watching
goodbye
[Music]
do