[Music]
do
you guys
[Music]
attention please i'm pavlia rainey from
whole life id generation too and welcome
it is time to tally mushrooms everybody
and by that i mean it is time for
another practice mario kart stream what
is up i hope you guys are doing great
um i was streaming today earlier
um at uh miss tension kotone's place but
now we're gonna play here today and um
you know as you guys probably know the
tournament is nearing
mario
uh
game sound kind of loud are you serious
i don't know i didn't change the volumes
from last time though
i didn't change volunteer last time is
it really that loud
can you lower your voice please
[Music]
could you make the game speak more
quietly
yeah
but anyways i don't know dinner bath or
lower your voice exactly yeah this i
didn't change the sound at all
considering right listen i didn't uh i
didn't even play anything else
so the settings uh it's been like a very
peaceful week because i don't have to
actually change the settings of anything
because all i've been doing this week is
play mario kart it's
such a bliss
yeah
anyways
yeah yeah yeah yeah um we're gonna play
uh two i'm kind of nervous because
tomorrow um as you can see i retweeted
uh tomorrow is the you do
polo
cart
something something
beautiful a team card i think that's
what it's like um it's a casual uh you
know pre-event no i mean a lot pre-event
we're just um casually gonna do a
team
thing i think a collab um a lot some a
lot of the people actually over there
i'm gonna be racing them for the first
time
um so but anyways because it's gonna be
a team thing i just hope that you know
i'll be able to perform well and you
know let's just uh have fun together
with everybody you know
yeah yeah kind of like a warm-up race
exactly
yeah so i'm just uh yeah i'm just uh
i'm excited at the same time pretty
nervous too
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
7 out of 12 is d team so you can measure
your skill
looking forward to a new batch of
california girls
[Music]
how to come and valley girl exactly
i mean uh if you are if you are using
roy you are already halfway there
for some reason i don't know man um
but yeah
good luck in the you rule race thank you
castle
yeah it's like oh yeah um
california's latin
yeah so in indonesia there is actually a
region called southern kalimantan so
it's like
and if you abbreviate it and abbreviate
like make it shorter uh it becomes
castle
but you know kao is also the first few
the first syllable of california right
exactly you know that's that's where the
joke is but yeah hahahahahaha
inserts uh laughing track sample here
um let's go
um let's play um
online play
let's make the tournament
downstairs to cal cell
i don't know
how do you how do you how do you how do
you act like a calcium
tournament
oh we're good okay jj revival needs to
go i'm sorry jjj
i'm sorry jj you have to go
this is
[Music]
create a tournament yes
rip jj gone too soon but we got we we
got jj reloaded that is fine guys it's
only it's merely evolving
it's nothing
uh name for your tournament uh jj
jj reloaded
we're
loaded
it's gonna be the jjj trilogy you know
that
um no more no calm smart steering not
okay
don't shuffle uh code required okay nice
um should i hide this
well okay nice
jj reloaded
okay nice
yes
[Music]
jj revolution and resurrection
okay
shoot what's the code
how do i
how do i look at the code what's the
code i forgot
um let's remake
ah wait how do i check
how do i check the code
i don't know how i checked the code okay
let me disagree okay i'm sorry i'm sorry
guys
one person got it i'm sorry i forgot my
own code
um i'm gonna destroy jj reloaded gone
too soon truly
gone too soon gone too soon
sorry jjj reloaded
um jjj a new hope
jjj a new hope
a new hope
okay okay i'm gonna hide the screen i'm
gonna hide the screen now before i
forget
[Laughter]
oh my oh my oh my set your tournaments
rules okay it's more street now okay
uh code required yeah yeah yeah yeah
write the code this time okay yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay i'm gonna write the code
i remember last time i talked about
switches i think i'm just gonna try
mx like hyper glides or something
i don't i'm not i'm like i don't know
maybe it's time i try those out
um
okay jj a new hope
let's go join
what is you do team race like a casual
team race between
some of the holo memes hold on let me
just um
oh there we go game screen and this is
the coke by the way is that it is that
it i hope that is it
i hope that is it
anybody can actually get in
[Music]
oh whoa whoa good luck have fun guys
only one way to find out
i hope i don't i hope i didn't actually
i hope i didn't actually press cancel
instead of okay
it's right okay cool
it's right
and before whose phone number is that
somebody asks i guess that kind of
question is in every mario kart stream
the code looks a lot like a contact
number in the philippines plus one
number
[Music]
cool um i guess we can do cheese land
for an opening
hello hello hello good luck good luck
good luck
funny funny green message
cheese to me
[Music]
okay okay oh somebody chose wario uh
that's okay i think
okay
cheese
[Music]
cheese cheese
cheese oh somebody's in the somebody
here is in the yes let's let's do our
best
what's your favorite cheese
[Applause]
what's your favorite cheese is
cheese flavored cheese
cheese flavored cheese parmesan
i do i have zero i do everybody has the
cloud
why is it only me that don't have the
that don't have the
that don't have the mushroom and not
mushroom
a cloud glider
so sad yeah
[Applause]
yeah like i unlocked something you know
i was so happy this afternoon i unlocked
the glider but it turned out to be um it
turned out to be uh what do you call it
uh the ritu glider
it turned out to be the reason glider so
i was like oh no
false hope i was given false hope i was
given falsehood so sad
[Music]
i was given false hope i'm so
disappointed
i myself
were expecting more
[Music]
that was very
very awful
[Music]
not even
wednesday what's wednesday dale what's
up
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah okay um this is bad because i can't
open the i can't do this
more mushroom
not enough mushroom
not enough
[Music]
what cheese do i like i don't know
what cheese do i like i wonder
[Music]
what cheese i don't know i like cheddar
cheese i feel like everybody likes
cheddar cheese
blue cheese i like blue cheese not
everybody likes blue cheese but i like
blue cheese
that was fun thank you for playing
all kinds of cheese yeah like all kinds
of cheese there are some extreme cheese
you know like the one that's like
they make they make it so they're
uh practically infested with maggots on
purpose or something i've never tried
that one i don't know if i would like
that one but it's like try everything at
least once right
blue cheese with buffalo chicken yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
what's your least favorite course um i
don't know
probably
ice eyes outpost because i don't know
how to do it but let's try that at least
once a rain egg
[Music]
blue cheese it's okay it's like you know
some food or
[Music]
is like a kind of spicy sauce
uh like chili
um it's v it's pretty strong
[Music]
yeah the seashore you guys here
yeah
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my oh my
i
[Music]
foreign
i have no idea what's going on
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
mangosteen
we counted shrooms today i don't know
where oh sunshine airport is a pretty
chill one we can do sunshine we can do
sunshine airport
we're always counting shrooms
if you have um
oh hello it's a mirrored rain
it's a mirrored rainy
rain
[Music]
solid
rainy are you doing the indo classroom
for this month um it hasn't been settled
yet
oh nice the inverted r okay it's time to
go try hard guys i'm sorry
let's let's talk about mangosteen after
this match
[Music]
yeah
no
i wanted a full race
[Music]
yeah dk leggy
cat
they are very very shy shy cats
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah the thing is also
in mario kart i think we're all we're
also like relying on other people
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
okay
i don't
follow you
[Music]
uh
distribution i don't really know
and it's gonna be in the morning so
that's why i can't really play until
late
i gotta make sure i wake up actually
wake up early
[Music]
i i don't know what i know what i should
choose here whatever is fine
[Music]
not father papa
morning voice rainy during the
tournament i don't know i might try to
wake up like earlier so i don't have my
morning voice it's more like so i'm not
sleepy
i'm actually kind of sleepy right now
where's my coffee
[Music]
early morning or yeah early morning it's
gonna be
on like 12 noon in
western indonesia time
[Applause]
is this going to be the redemption art
or is something going to go out
awfully wrong
again
[Music]
oh no i missed all the
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no there's the i don't remember where
the coins are
[Music]
uh where is the
i want coins
coins please no i'm not getting coins
oh yes i am being points somehow
somehow i am getting coins
[Music]
now
oh no
and that's actually not bad
like it sucked but nothing really
happened to me either
it was okay
yeah i'm totally fine with like
placing whatever
yeah i need to learn actually how to do
baby park
[Music]
mario circuit
maybe rainbow road this rainbow road
[Music]
why is your car so slippery i don't know
it needs some anti-grip
yeah wiggler and bowser doesn't do well
in baby park yeah i think so too
i need some shuba shoes
super super super super super super
super sugar shoes
[Music]
yeah baby park's like really really
really simple
but
yeah
maybe i need maybe my build is wrong but
it's like whatever it's not like i i
have it's not like i know what track is
going to be chosen right so there's
really nothing i can do it's fine
[Music]
it's fine it's very very very very fine
why is it already practicing mario kart
because um there's a there's a big
tournament in two days
[Music]
and i also don't know how to race here
i'm just gonna be honest with you
[Music]
[Applause]
now
[Music]
oh nice dodge there
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
people are asking me like remember like
in the um
video
[Music]
like in the mushroom video people asking
like why i'm so mad that i got mushrooms
like oh it's not that bad it's not that
bad and i'm like they say what this is
what happens if you get mushrooms all
the time you don't have anything to
protect yourself from shells
[Music]
um
i feel like okay california let's go
cheap cheap beach
[Music]
cheap cheap beach cheep
choo choo choo choo
[Music]
why does she get so many mushrooms i
have no idea
it's like a mix of like distance and
placement and rng but also like why
right
sun on the beach
[Music]
oh we're gonna go dry bones that's okay
too that's okay too
so on the beach
sun on the beach
[Music]
this is sun
on the cliff
i don't know
[Music]
sun on the beach hey waluigi get the
hell out of my sight
oh my god
for real
[Music]
sun on the sand sun
i think we can do this i think we can do
this if we um if we just try our best
we just try our best
we surely can do this
we surely can
[Music]
we do our best
everything's gotta be dige okay
okay
[Music]
bananas and bananas
how
there's a
there's a blue
shell
there is a blue
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
can you believe it
now
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry i accidentally clicked it okay
everybody go go go go go go go go out
now no no go go
go
uh
everybody come in
i don't want it to be like a two people
match
no i accidentally
pressed it
i'll be fine
jinxed it
that's so sad
[Music]
accidentally
[Laughter]
wait let me
get back
[Music]
why is it starting
150 or 200 150
it's
150 big balloon
oh whoa
big baboo waist
[Music]
i don't know how to play here
santa bread
[Music]
oh god
oh that's so crappy
who did that
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god
that sucks
that sucks i can't even
[Music]
i wonder if i can rip
oh no i couldn't
[Music]
this is kind of difficult
this is difficult
[Music]
ah this is difficult
yeah it wasn't
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h] is that like an ink
yeah that sucked
i was um it's fine it happens it's mario
kart i got mario kart in the like two
most important places
totally no big deal no assault
whatsoever it's fine quote unquote
not crying i'm totally not gonna cry
after this dream uh what should we
choose
oh ollie ollie's
here if it makes you feel better only
goes last play at the end of doing this
map no it doesn't make me feel better
i'm sorry but thank you for trying
i feel you thanks ollie
what's up
[Music]
uh
that one show earlier was surprising
though lol well you know if only i
didn't get freaking hit at the two other
important places
so sad
[Music]
um
ollie was time traveling that man then
her viewers destroyed her now the thing
is i'm not really fond of time trial uh
for uh i guess because time travel
really gives you like okay fine like i
know this is the optimal route like you
gotta hug the edges or anything but
and you get all the shrooms and you can
use them tactically but in real races
[Music]
i do i still do feel like hugging the
edges all the time is really really
risky what if you're hugging the edges
and like somebody shells you and you
fall off the map or something like that
or like you're not gonna always have
mushrooms at your disposal
you know
that kind of thing
so i prefer online racing
and i feel like time trial is like fine
though to see if you can like okay i
just want to do a perfect run what
happens if there's nothing stopping me
[Music]
but yeah
i i remember like spending a lot of time
with time trial with this map though i
do remember
[Music]
i don't do this
oh why did i go here
[Applause]
[Music]
my stomach hurts i think it's because i
drank coffee without
because i drank coffee without actually
um
[Music]
oh no did i waste that
oh two bullet bills
[Music]
i would have um
i would have liked to use
this somewhere else
[Music]
i have zero points by the way i just
realized
[Music]
it's so slippery i don't know what's
wrong with me i think i'm just like
really scared of stuff and then
[Music]
oh yeah
we talking about about mangosteen how
often do you guys actually eat
mangosteen i'm asking
[Music]
mangosteen is sweet and sour
i actually don't eat a lot of those
but uh
well i eat a lot of strawberry i eat a
lot strawberry
[Music]
you have lychee in indonesia i think so
i think we do i'm pretty sure we do i
don't know if they're really important
or like local grown or what but i i'm
pretty sure we do
yeah
are you okay ready why the hell are you
guys asking me if i was okay that's
freaking annoying what what's that what
what does that mean what what does that
mean
i like oranges i also like oranges
lychee is um
like she is
i should like
like it in drinks i think
[Music]
that is also good you said your tummy
not feel good because of coffee oh i'm
fine i'm fine
[Music]
how about mangoes mangoes are good but
they make my throat itch a lot
you need to be more toxic rainy uh sure
you want me to be toxic i'll do it your
wish is my command one person says that
yeah sure i'll do that
i'll do that
and malay i only see let's use insane
mayhaps may have that that's what we
have i don't know
rainy is so petty no it's because like
you guys are um i feel like you guys are
really trained to like push my buttons
when it comes to like competitive games
[Music]
have you guys some industrial words in
this race no
[Music]
ah
i feel like traffic today is we keep
getting like half full races
i don't know
i feel like half all races aren't as fun
to be completely honest
at least like i want i don't know even
um i don't know usually they still fill
them with cpu right even if it's like a
halfway race
i just feel like the more people we have
the better it is
[Music]
because you know there's a lot of
there's a lot of i don't know
the more the merrier that's what i think
what the heck is going on
why why did i turn that sharp why why
was it even possible to turn that sharp
[Music]
join us to the dark side
it doesn't feel complete even with
what's true
[Music]
am i gonna get mushrooms are we gonna
farm mushrooms today
is that what we're gonna do mushrooms it
is it is mushroom day
this is what we're gonna have today
yummy yummy delicious mushrooms
[Music]
delicious
delicious delicious
[Music]
oh my delicious what just happened
wow
[Music]
i want to play what i have work
that's okay maybe next time
[Music]
rainy can you use your what
voice when you race oh sure
we can
we can use the oval voice when we race
of course
[Music]
what's the number on the screen for it's
the room code
it's the warm code of the
[Music]
waist with the jigsaw voice
oh oh my god sure
hold on wait please
hello
hi
tess test test hello yes okay there we
go
we are gonna race today
today we are going to be racing in i
have no idea oh my gosh i think it's
lagging
[Music]
i want to play a game it's mario kart
okay
it's time to play a grime
what are you
wait zero
oh what is this
it's
[Music]
oh that's a pretty cool helmet
what's this royal raceway i have no idea
how to play this of course
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
but here's what is
[Music]
do foreign
where is everybody everybody's so far
already
i really do wish somebody gets like um
[Applause]
[Music]
oh god
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah that sucks
first and second are so far away anyways
sniped but that's fine that's fine
that's totally valid
wow first and second they're so good
what did they do
yeah it's a decent race it's a decent
race uh i'm not mad
um that's valid the fact that you got
i was so confident like oh yeah it's a
blue shell but wait i'm getting it
[Music]
that's one
they were one with the drifts
yes they got a real good gaming chair
maybe i should invest in one
i need a good gaming chair
[Music]
i'm gonna go to sleep to rainy mom's
voice
no it's yoshi like what why why do i why
does it why do the tracks i actually
want never get chosen
um
[Music]
but it's fine i guess surprises
oh
avoid that
[Music]
i have zero coins actually
ow
why are so many
[Music]
why are there so many bulletpills
whoa
[Music]
that's actually pretty scary
so so so scary
now
[Music]
wow that's so chaotic
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah middle ground's fine i think
everybody just surprise upon dives you
thought
you thought
okay can i can we please have something
um okay i don't actually want anything
much here
um
[Music]
true which one i don't know which one
anything is fine probably probably like
toad's turnpike or
i don't know which which one of these
which one of these toad harbor or
toadster pike
is my card just racing rng yeah that's
why that's why there's a term called
mario karted
for
for you know if you're doing well and
then like you know rng screws you over
that's you know you just got mario
karted
the traffic jam sure
[Music]
chilled harbor for a mushroom but this
is also toad certified
oh yeah we need to practice weaving
between the cars yeah yeah true true i
haven't had the chance to do that ever
since i changed my setup
[Music]
good night hello
my kart is the mobile gotcha version how
do we call that what
double mario card
double mario card so okay i don't know
what i don't know what happens like
what communication error oops
oh let's check
let's check first let's check
[Music]
oh no
it's not the glider coin so sad bye bye
bye bye bye bye
[Music]
they got mario karted so sad
jjj a new hope i hope i can enter
okay join jj a new home
[Music]
let's see let's watch if there's a
if there's a match going on we can watch
then we can play after
[Music]
was that a mercedes yeah
oh my god
there are so many mario's and there's
also a dry bones
you will join the next available match
sit tight
let's go
mario i don't really i don't really want
to watch mario i'm sorry can we change
who we want to watch
but h actually guys i'll be right back
i'll be right back i will be right back
i'll be back soon
[Music]
hello
i bet mario had more coins than reigning
oh why you gotta be like that
mushroom soup anyone welcome back
wait wait wait actually no hold on i'll
be right back
no my cat hold on
[Music]
three three
do
[Music]
wow
everyone finish the race quick it's okay
[Music]
rainbow road
by emcee
[Music]
but i need to sit down i need to sit
down
i need to sit down i'm going to sit down
[Music]
there we go there we go
[Applause]
that's dumb why would you do that
[Music]
okay so i'll be safe
so i will be safe
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
down
wow
mushroom my mushroom i at least want my
mushrooms please
yeah i mean that is like the worst item
in mario kart like why would you do that
i just feel like
ow i just feel like it doesn't really i
don't know like who doesn't help
[Music]
who does it helps
how does it help
why why would you do this to me
why would you do this to me
[Music]
the one who used it i don't know where
where are they where are they who was
the one who used the community what did
they became did they become first or
something
[Laughter]
[Music]
god says coming out either side of a bad
person
[Music]
uh
what's next bowser's castle
[Music]
tick um clock
or
[Music]
bowser's castle
um
[Music]
castle okay yeah we can do castle
bunkeroni revisited
whichever you think you need more
practice on
um i don't know
tick tock is on your favorite map
oh i'm not in the same block as her
though
i was gonna be like let's destroy her in
her favorite map
[Laughter]
but we're on we're not on the same block
what's the event for tomorrow it's a
team it's a casual team match
i i'd like to think of it as a pre-event
kind of thing
[Music]
god says
god says what i don't know
[Music]
have you checked only all these fanfics
no not yet i'm gonna check them after
the tournament
after the tournament and then i will be
able to play other games
[Music]
god says with an uru voice
god says with an ubu voice that unless
you reconcile you cannot win the mario
kart tournament
god says yeah see look at that like
the rng is so bad today
it's like it's not it's not so much
about the race rng it's just like the
map selection rng is so bad like the
[Music]
yeah i haven't seen the fix i think i
would rather focus on the tournament
first
says
oh look at that i got all of the coins
aren't you guys proud of me
yes
aren't you guys proud of me look at that
look at me
look at me i got the coins
[Music]
yeah
look at that
oh i'm so proud of myself never before
having so proud of myself
and look at that even if i got is it
even as i got hit i still got the coins
look at that
ow
lost [\h__\h]
i remember i still remember the day
i still remember the day um we were i
don't know wait what you're not supposed
to hit those
you're not supposed to hit those really
for real
[Music]
coins
okay
okay i'm not okay okay if there's if
there's one positive thing about this
map is that
is that out
is that i'm not so bad at gathering
coins
in this map
why is there no item boxes why is it so
oh yeah okay
[Music]
oh my god i still i still do it anyways
i still do it anyways so sad
[Music]
i saw you i was like oh yeah i forgot i
shouldn't do that and then i do the
exact same thing in the third lap
i don't know why rainy no i don't know
because i just don't have a brain right
now
[Music]
i want to try please i i don't know like
like please
please at least get something that's
nice
like i don't know like i feel like
nobody
nobody wished for that track to be
chosen
but yeah
[Music]
um have you practiced drafting driving
behind people for speed boost um what i
have practice is not to throw my
controller every time um stupid stuff
happens
i thought you could oil your cart there
exactly right that's that's the exact
same um thing that's my train of thought
you know
barry's family rob brady and her brains
no okay listen i i haven't read the
bears one either you know i expect it to
be very spicy though but i haven't read
that
see like what the what
like who the hell wished for thwamp
ruins aside from like maybe those two
people like but who the hell wished for
it who else wished for it like nobody
wished for it except for those two
people
[Music]
the gift of fan fiction that keeps on
giving
[Music]
[Applause]
i missed it all
no
it's so hard to see to be fair though
to be fair it's really hard to see
looting your core because no it's not
lewd what are you talking about it's not
lewd at all
it's very very wholesome the stuff that
i make they're absolutely absolutely
awesome
they're absolutely absolutely
[Music]
absolutely
very very kawaii destiny
oh my god
[Music]
okay at least i got
the remains of my mushrooms
yes
ow oh my god why are you over there
nobody asked for your presents
nobody asked for your presents why are
you even there
okay
[Music]
okay let's go
okay please please please please please
please just
just let me let me let me be in peace
you know like just
[Applause]
just leave me alone guys
what if you wanted to be left alone but
god said
but god said
but god said yes sir you're right
[Applause]
[Music]
god says you must reconcile
a new boundary city i'm going to choose
new boser city
god says serves you oh god says
is this jjj and you hope i could uh yeah
it's jjj and you hope it's the same room
it's not a new room
um i got dc'd and then i rejoined
basically yeah
this is the mario kart content we want
ah
the mario kart content we want
[Music]
oh my goodness
an alternate rainy that's orange orange
rainy
[Music]
oh there's baby rainy too oh yes hello
new bowser city
[Music]
fried rice
what i want items how come i don't have
items how dare you steal my items
how dare you why are you like this
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
oh god this is so brutal
please like
oh no i keep failing when it comes to
getting the items
[Music]
so sad
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
so sad i fell again
[Applause]
did i just like did i steal a coin of
somebody
sorry
wow
okay listen
i spawned that and even i don't even i
think
kaminati shouldn't exist
i i believe community shouldn't exist
it's um
it's it's broken
it shouldn't exist
yeah it's just naturally like kill the
joy it's not even like
it's not even like there to like it it
doesn't bring joy to anybody like i
don't feel joy like blasting community
to people it's just like it doesn't even
have like a satisfying like thing when
you shell people you know
[Music]
randy you have become very famous you
swore to this story i mean to be fair
like it's random right
i didn't ask for it
i have to use it
so it doesn't spark joy
electrode
[Music]
so it's satisfying when you shell people
oh yeah especially when they're like
mid-air
hmm
[Music]
when are you supposed to leave if you
join uh immediately like immediately and
then you can come back but as long as
you don't go like so and so in a row
[Music]
i having a satisfied when people are
mid-air as well but then you you can't
see the impact
you can't really see the impact
oh gosh there's so many people
leave immediately don't even play
no you join immediately leave not even
time for a race
[Music]
good luck have fun everybody
yeah if you leave before the race starts
you can't get hit by kavinadi true true
true true true
that is true it's like
one no a surefire trick not to get hit
by kavanaugh to avoid the kaminari all
you have to do is not join the race
there's somebody called why bully me
expo
[Music]
if mk had bone boxes like in ctr ho ho
ho man
[Music]
you can't actually use the d-pad to race
i didn't know that
[Applause]
i accidentally rested my hand on the
d-pad and then
today i learned you can still move
[Music]
oh no
oh no oh no
[Music]
whoa that's so scary
ah oh
oh my god that was so close that was too
close for comfort
too close for comfort oh my goodness
why
why would you do that
let's go
[Music]
wow
yeah kaminati
yeah what sucks about karma is that you
know
it drops your items it makes nobody
happy
yes and we both have fake boxes so wait
what do the fake boxes do
[Applause]
what do they do
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
so slippery
[Applause]
[Music]
oh bananas said they look like item
boxes oh my that's so evil
that's the most evil thing
[Music]
trolling ctr leave tnt before after item
box no but that's so easy you can just
like
chanting before or after adam box you
can just like to be
to be careful you can just like
touch the edges and it will still give
you the item
[Music]
they were bananas that look like boxes
and they also did block shells
that sucks
[Music]
item box shaped kaminari
so sad
hmm
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
draw fate i embossed on top of the reel
i am boston wait for the rage
man i wish i played that though
sounds sounds sounds like
cool uncle fun
ah sounds uh fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
is there a phone number and no it is the
code for the tournament if you want to
join us please please do join the join
the room for the mario kart
online on the wii was interesting to say
the least yeah i was never like a wee
kid so
i don't know
[Music]
excito
oh still not too late for uh for a turbo
then that's good i was spaced out for a
little bit there
[Applause]
it's
[Music]
what's wrong with you
oh no somebody's doing the thing
somebody's doing the thing i'm scared
[Applause]
yeah i feel like i don't know there's
just a lot of um
i mean exciteback is kind of like baby
park in a way and like oh it's a pretty
straightforward but i still feel like
excitebike is
whoa
[Applause]
i still feel like
excited bike is kind of
more interesting
for some reason because there's just a
lot of more jumps and more things going
on
oh my god
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no
yeah for some
[Applause]
[Music]
bad yeah i got hit in mid-air there that
sucked
but it's fine
can you as much room mid-air yes you can
[Laughter]
if if excite fight is the baby park for
adults
why is it not called adult park
[Music]
dc
jj new hope
[Music]
nintendo didn't like that question i'm
sorry i'm so sorry
[Music]
i'm very very sorry
the server can't handle the jjj maybe
mayhaps
um
yeah we're spectating again ah
[Music]
oof
only like five people
what
oh that was so creepy when the music
stopped i thought it was like wait what
happened four people and a bowser
okay let's go shy guy
go shy guy go go go go shy guy go go go
oh oh no
[Music]
yeah they just started
oh come on go go go go
[Music]
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go
oh yeah that's the glider that i just
got oh no
shy guys too shy to be spectated by you
come on shy guy you can do it
go go shy guy go shy guy go go go go go
go rain how's it going um i got kicked
out of my own room
[Laughter]
i got kicked out of my own room and now
i gotta spectate people uh until i can
play again
hey kiara what's up well how's your
training going how's your private
training training going
how is it
yeah
i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm just gonna watch
and then
press a to change pov oh magics no i
want to watch shy guy
guys second let's go
no
jinxed it i'm sorry shy guy oh no no no
no no no i'm sorry i totally jinxed it
i beat my gem mates but yesterday heck
yeah
let's go
holo bird strong
yeah commentator's curse i'm so sorry
shy guy
i'm so so sorry
kiara number one and hollow myth let's
do that
i'm i'm excited for the reality also
kind of nervous because i know people in
team d are really really really strong
too
you switch the shy guy he got all the
mushrooms
i know he's last cause of you oh shut up
no don't say that
i'm
rooting for him
no shy guys number one in my heart might
be number five over there with number
one in my heart okay
um
shy guy take my energy
[Music]
don't know uh rainbow road i'll choose
rainbow road or whatever it's mine
whatever it's fine
[Music]
you gave all your bad luck to shy guy no
you should do better no don't know don't
be like that i mean it is
i don't know
uh i've been i've been doing okay
[Music]
i've been doing okay ish
are you ready
yeah oh they they have swamps everything
has swamps
i really want to do cheap cheap beach
though
animal crossing of course
who
who must
who mr
[Music]
let's go animal crossing
let's just race casually we can do this
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no i didn't get items i'm scared
oh god what is this
i don't know what happened there
i don't know what happened there that
sucked
[Music]
oh no
i don't know how to
oh no i should have protected myself
with that
[Music]
yes of course
of course it hits me when i'm about to
go
yeah i don't know i always is it is it
because like it's texture weirdly the
road
is it because it's textured weirdly i
always get
[Music]
oh
my lyrics
here's the blue shell
[Music]
oh i'm hugging the outside edges
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah that that that i always do the same
thing what is wrong with it
is it the way i drift or
there's something wrong with the road
[Music]
oh god
[Applause]
the river pushed me what river
what river
the small water waves is there what
there's water i thought that was sand
there's water flowing where i didn't see
that i don't have eyes maybe
i want to try big blue again please
please pick big blue
[Music]
the starfish there's a starfish
it's both water and sand
i can't see
your brain's probably used to scooty
i think so
[Music]
i think i'm just like very used to mr
scooty and i have to get used to well
wiggler now and it's like okay
i'm trying to get in
[Music]
yeah i've never tried to get into uh get
into a stream
of mario kart's room street i can't
english i don't know
do your chances increase if you join
through friends list
[Music]
is it better to keep on dropping out
when in the wrong room or is it better
to wait i have no idea
it's all random okay
[Music]
hmm
oh
what happened there
[Music]
oh
that sucks
yeah i feel like it's fine
[Music]
i really never get lucky at the end it's
always like uh
it's always so messed up at the end
i don't know if there's like
like it's it's
i've only raced twice
but two of them had this the exact same
outcome
[Music]
sorry about the bullet bill ready no i
will not i will never forgive you
uh we can try music park
[Music]
wow
they will be cursed
god said
unless
everybody reconciles
you will never be able
to
uh i don't know
to be continued
[Music]
oh no
i'm in are you in
[Music]
is she in
nice
is that her
[Music]
is that the wheel the absolute wheel
kiawah
[Music]
let's go
i want this to go easy on me it's fine
even if i warmed up um
oh jeez i don't know how to do this map
i don't know how to do the shortcuts in
this shortcut this map
[Music]
fish
um
here there's that little ramp over there
[Music]
oh let's go oh no there's a blue shell i
didn't see that in time
i didn't see that in time oops
i didn't see that in time i wonder if
kiara's in front of
nobody really wishes for
nobody loves coming nobody likes it
oh no
nobody wants it
nobody wants to call me nutty
oh my god did somebody fall
did somebody fall try to try to get the
shortcut
[Music]
so sad
oh no i missed that
i missed the thing
[Music]
i missed it
i missed the thing
[Music]
more mushrooms
ah oh stupid bananas
oh and i didn't get the i didn't get the
item
uh
just my luck oh just my luck just my
luck
[Music]
oh just my luck
[Applause]
[Music]
oh that blue shell was you
can i say of course course course yeah
stay stay stay stay safe yeah please
stay here please stay
yeah yeah yeah
yeah please stay please stay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah sure
[Music]
do you wanna
i know
if you want if you wanna call too that's
fine but if you don't wanna that's fine
[Music]
yeah
god said one person
one match per person except for
that's what god said
i'm on my phone but yes
sure okay um
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
hi
oh
welcome well i should
yay i should get your tatia but
i should get your tattoos
i'm so sorry for low quality but i'm in
my bed uh in my bedroom with my phone oh
okay nana no worries what is this
dolphin shoals
oh look at that somebody's got the exact
same setup as you
baker
bye gang i switched this setup because a
lot of people a lot of people in this in
the tournament is probably going to use
the exact same setup so i was like okay
maybe i should learn this thing
[Music]
yeah and i'm doing uh just a random one
just with daisy because i like daisy
daisy is cute daisy is cute oh my god
i'm thinking
everyone with the same setup
yeah i know
but i was like i don't know i've been
going so far i wanted to go dry bowser
and mr scooty like the one i usually use
but
i felt like that setup it's just really
difficult for turning it's not very
versatile in certain maps
[Music]
yeah i'm just trying um i'm liking this
one but i'm thinking of waiting rosalina
rosalina's cute
maybe after the kingdom i'm gonna switch
go for it yes yes yes
how are you doing
i'm doing okay how about you
i've been playing mario kart only
15. you've been doing well oh thank you
just try my best
yeah
she's supposed to be in auburn because i
heard she's dropping out oh really
[Applause]
maybe
okay
that she was inverted so we have one
less rival is that good
[Music]
that depends
i'm really scared though everyone is and
everybody in team d is um
strong i'm scared of especially like
there's you there's also ina there's
also there's also a lot of people that's
i think you know i i've never raced them
before so it's like i think we're all
just kind of decent
yeah i think like also like we're all
decently good right like
nobody like the skill level is the skill
level is like kind of like
yeah
ah stupid bananas
[Music]
i like bananas i don't like banana peel
as much
whoa
i was behind you for most of the race ah
yeah
five
oh the daisy is behind you too
yay
yahooch
there is also marin and luna chad
says there's two there's someone that
looks like
is that oh yeah
there's somebody who looks like her
that's very high quality me
yeah cheap cheap beach or moo moo
meadows or baby part which one would you
like
i think all of them are fun
oh her name is mata
he's the puns the japanese puns with her
own name yeah yeah yeah that's also what
she said right i think that was like her
first tweet or something yeah she says
that and many other puns
very cute very useful name she has yeah
so cute my cats are watching uh mario
kart right away hello
they're protecting us from afar oh
that's cute my cat's outside
because you know when my cat's here she
always climbs on the keyboard and you
know
she disrupts my work the cats won't
behave why did you not did you not raise
them to be behaved children
no not exactly i'm not exactly the most
well behaved either so i guess like they
just um looked at their role model
yeah apparently cats take after their
mother
i guess
oh and there's another
there's a french
person that wants me to come to
france oh
in the name
let's all go to france let's all go
let's all go i've been walking
um only once or twice oh
was it paris
paris paris did we go to disneyland in
paris
oh no i went to the other theme park um
they had another theme park right um
i forgot
the disney one
yeah the non-disney one
it was asterisk i think asterix or
something
yeah i don't know that one
ouch
yeah i went there but i don't really
have memory much memory
would be really nice if we could have
like a whole live you know trip
somewhere yeah
guys
it would be so fun to travel through um
for europe with everybody because in
europe it's like so easy to travel from
country to country and you can see so
many different places in a short time
oh
yeah yeah yeah i would want to do that i
would definitely want to do that i love
traveling
like i don't know just seeing new stuff
like with
friends
yeah
oh what placement are you right now
well i'm tense i'm not doing well at all
oh
oh god
i'm not doing very very well
[Music]
when i asked you a question i was scared
and now i'm
[Music]
that happens a lot
oh god are you serious
[Music]
you made my bullet bill go away how dare
you separate me in my bullets
when you're in the bullet bill and you
get a thunder you get kicked out of it
oh no no no no um i was gonna use it and
then like i got kaminaried
oh so sad oh i'm sorry about that i just
had to use what i got i need to save
myself
but maybe maybe we will be reunited in
the uh next um
are you gonna stream your like
participation no
like that's the thing i want to but
after like seeing like the rundown and
everything i'm like how am i supposed to
stream this
oh why because there's like breaks in
between yeah like there's breaks and and
yeah i don't even know and then like
what happens like if i get middle and i
get eliminated or something like that
means i don't have any more streams to
do right then i'm like what am i
supposed to do
that's when the stream ends too
if you don't get into the the good cup
or the bad cup then you get into no cup
yeah yeah we get yeah and then
like what am i supposed to do i'm just
like okay guys i'm going to end my
stream because i'm not getting anywhere
well
i think you know i i've heard
from most of the holo myth girls that
they're also including me that they're
also not streaming it so i think at
least some people should stream it
probably
maybe
i feel like i don't know if i if i'm
streaming i feel like i'm gonna like
mess around
i'm just really bad i'm just really bad
but you're streaming right now and
you're doing pretty well but like for me
i have a huge debuff there's a big
difference from how well i play when i
stream and how well i play when i'm not
streaming
it was a huge difference
i was just like i don't know i want to
stream but at the same time
yeah
but you know imagine imagine you would
do really really well
and you would get into the winner's cup
but then you're not going to stream it
and then it's gonna no one will have any
proof of how cool you were on the race
no i can record myself
i'm thinking so too yeah but now i'm
getting so comfy and bad i've been
thinking i'll just uh participate while
i'm in bed you know i'm also considering
that i kind of want to just be in bed
you know
yeah
blake that would be so nice
why why
why would you do that i thought we were
good friends
you know how when
back back in
back in like elementary school when a
boy liked the girl they would tease the
girl yeah
it would make the girl like really angry
and the girls wouldn't know like that's
why he hates me doesn't me
okay that's what happens that's all
happening really really
let okay see
[Music]
what do i have what can i do
oh no no no no please i thank you
you guys don't need to hit me to show me
that you love me
please
[Music]
so scary
i'm so sorry
i'm so scared
[Music]
i don't have uh i don't have a shell or
like a mushroom oh okay that's not bad
at all
what
why on earth
did the blue shell go to me when i was
fifth place explain that oh because
everyone else was already over the
finish line yeah that happened to me too
i was like
blue
what the [\h__\h] that
as a fifth placement that is not fair
but okay it came to be on the finish
line it's okay oh okay
yeah that happened to me like i was
third i think and i was like oh blue
shirt bye and then wait what why is it
spinning on top of it it's messed up
that is
so have you just been practicing in
private all this time
yeah but not that much actually
push a little bit uh like for me like
the thing is if i practice offline
it's like i won't be disciplined you
know i won't price i would be like i
want to watch movies
yeah yeah i've had the luck that like a
lot of other people
have been streaming their practices so
yesterday i joined ina and today i
joined you oh that's nice that's nice
oh where oh that's funny that's cute you
cute kid
actually i'm doing a practice tomorrow
so if you awake you can join too oh what
time what time what time
um i think
uh
jst it would be something around 9 00
p.m 10 p.m
9 p.m 10 p.m okay i think i will have
time for that if i can join i will join
okay okay okay okay
i could be wrong though it could be like
11 p.m i don't know i forgot
oh okay okay okay i'll see i'll see
okay okay okay okay
10 p.m jst they said
i think i'm right behind you you are
yeah
do you see me honking
no no
no that but that was you i didn't see
you honking there oh maybe it's just not
there
it's like client-sided what do you mean
like you know not server-sided
i didn't get an idea i didn't get an
item either
oh that's fine i guess they stole it
from us
it's not bad it is not fair it is not
fair i got coins though which i'm
probably gonna lose soon
i'm probably gonna lose them soon
oh do you know any shortcuts going on
shortcuts oh yeah there's like a pretty
hard to pull off shortcut in um in this
place
there's like uh you use a glider
and you just like ride on top of the
bounds of those i don't know
what
yeah that's basically how to do that uh
theoretically yes but in practice i
don't bother
you can try it and practice it if you
want
i'm just like i don't have enough
um i can't do it
yeah i was thinking about learning some
short cuts but
i feel like i won't i won't have enough
time to practice yeah that's what i
thought too
i was like oh even without shortcuts i
feel like i've been doing fine enough so
i'll just focus on you know trying to
nail the maps as much as i can yeah
just gonna roll with it
yeah i get you
oh i'm not getting items
so sad
again
items love me but not in the way i want
them to
i just got green shells
so
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's not
bad but i i do think reyna that
generally the the viewers are
on an average better than most hololive
english whole life girls all together
i think we have uh stronger
rivals right now than we will have in
the race but
you'll be wrong
i think so
maybe
if you're 10 year then i think you will
be
seventh
in the tournament
[Laughter]
very reassuring yeah maybe
let's just let me there's there's only
one thing to do right like we have to
train as much as we can i mean not as
much as we can um
train smartly
fake kiana looks exactly like me
oh there it is
as well i think she looks very angry
angry calliope
not a muse not amused there's a dinosaur
[Music]
a green green dinosaur
and there's the shadow person
darth vader
nice and nice nice
[Music]
there's there was also like a fried
rainey
[Music]
there was a fried rain and she's like
orange with orange here
where is their respect where is there i
was like huh
[Laughter]
oh i barely practiced this one although
it's this is really hard i think
[Music]
me honking and still getting a turbo we
winning
oh
this is so
this map is hard
[Music]
really
i think so
oh green reaper knows how to use that
shortcut i don't i don't know there was
a shortcut yeah there was a shortcut i
need to practice that one i've never uh
i haven't really practiced that i will
need i will need to
hmm
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
no green reaper stop taking my
[Music]
slippery slippery
slippery slip flip victory
i forgot that there was still one yeah
very cold in winter over there or not
there's no such thing as winter in
indonesia
yeah it's just like um we do have like
rainy season as well as uh
rainy day season
rainy season
it rains all the time right now it's
rainy season until like probably
february i think if i'm not mistaken oh
no it's too late for me for the short
cut oh
and then i think like the hotter seasons
are
aside from that exactly
[Music]
wait what about over there
and we have all four seasons all right
now it's pretty cool okay hey
that's cool
i don't know because sometimes even
though it's raining it's very very humid
so it's like uh
yeah i hate that
in certain countries where it gets too
humid like in japan
like wait i don't know though i thought
like japan summers would be
more
i don't know piercingly hot i don't know
if that made sense
it's meaningful piercingly hot it is
like it makes you like go into like heat
strokes and everything too right yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you might ever
remember when i
when i first went to japan like a
million years ago
um
i it was summer time and i remember
throwing up at a cat cafe because it was
huge oh no that's awful
but don't worry i made it to the toilets
okay okay okay that's good
that's good that's good
yeah i was i really i mean no matter how
many times i i went to japan and even
when i lived there on a longer basis i
still couldn't get used to it i i don't
know the summer it's too much
yeah the summer i never got used to it
the winter glow is easy for me
the winter is easy just don't ever go
outside
no no no i feel like the winter in
at least in like tokyo uh-huh it's
barely
week compared to the winter in austria
but like in hokkaido when i went to
hokkaido with cali
i realized oh okay japan can have some
freaking ice cold winters as well gotcha
oh i've never been i've never been to
hokkaido i need to i heard that they got
delicious food
perfectly fitting the theme we're now a
race on mount wario exactly this is our
mock uh hokkaido holiday
yay
we're gonna get to hokkaido for a while
we're gonna can you ski or
snowboard no
snowboarding so cool can you where can
you
i can i can see
like literally every austrian can ski
that's so cool no i feel like you know
because we're just not we just don't
have the season you know so i feel like
not everybody
almost
yeah not a lot of people can do that
from indonesia
if you look at like olympics like winter
olympics and whatever then you see that
for the snow sports oh yeah austria is
actually winning some things oh so i'm
pretty proud of that we normally we
never win anything where we suck at
sports but when it comes to winter
sports uh-huh that's the only time when
we can
show up what we got oh
i think that's indonesia with um okay
what do you call
it's like tennis but it's uh it's like
tennis but not tennis the one with the
uh soft
thing
you only use a racket what is it
yeah
uh i um what you mean badminton
badminton okay
really indonesia is good at bad news
yeah for some reason
yeah i i am not good though but like i
think if anything i think there's a lot
of indonesians who are pretty good at it
[Music]
yes yes yes
okay i'm usually better out on this map
um i don't know what's going on you know
you know the forest thing like i
i played here and against cpus
uh because you know i wasn't online and
then for some reason when i get to the
forest somebody has always somebody
always does the squid thing in the
forest
when i'm in the forest
more difficult yeah
oh gosh this is awful this is way more
awful than the previous runs i did so
sad
i'm nice where are you kiara
[Music]
don't mind me i'm 12
i'm 11 no
oh no i don't have items either oh no
[Laughter]
yeah we both sucked in that one
that sucked that side i know
it's embarrassing
it's fine
that's why it's practice you know so
we'll be better in the real deal exactly
right
which one do you want i'm fine with like
any
of
ah i think i want hyrule circuit okay
yeah let's choose that not anything is
fine
anything is fine
what are you drinking coffee
[Music]
dana is a coffee drinker
nice just like
it's just like sweet
milk coffee like i don't drink black
coffee or anything
getting comfortable oh okay
you should you should my cat is right
next to me
she's my cheerleader hi
no she doesn't want her
okay she doesn't speak on commands no
okay my cat doesn't meow at all
it only meows when she's complaining
when we like ask her to get off the
keyboard and like we just carry her like
okay you go outside she's like
okay but that's that's um i think
good a lot of people complain about
their cats being too talkative and too
annoying
pavoli anya
what
[Music]
i like cats i don't know yeah like other
people's cats they're pretty talkative
but not mine
i think it's just too chill
[Music]
mine like in the morning one of my cats
will like terrorize me with her meows oh
my goodness i don't know like lately
only in the morning in the morning my
cat would just sneak into my room and
wake me up like paw at me
i fall in the blanket because i sleep
with a blanket and then she's gonna be
like
trying to wake me up
or like try to she thinks my body is uh
something to sit on like furniture okay
yeah is that that cool i wish my cats
would do that
i am certified cat furniture
and yeah my cat it's just like my cat is
the owner you know i don't know why i
keep forgetting the turn
in this place
[Music]
[Applause]
wait was that you that's not you right
no no but they had the star
uh
[Music]
bad luck i keep losing coins
i keep losing coins for some reason
[Music]
okay justice
smokey huh
huh
i got my mushroom stolen so sad
i just got like three mushrooms and then
the booze stole it i don't know who who
that was
[Music]
what's happening
right i can't hear you wait you're still
there what yeah i am i am
you can't hear me
now i can i know you can okay
probably been playing today right now
huh uh i've been playing for
uh one and forty five i started the
stream at
uh
i i don't know no actually i started
this no i have playing for like two plus
hours
oh how much longer are you going for um
i don't know i'm i'm i'm fine
i feel i don't know
i don't know how long are you gonna play
me um
i didn't eat breakfast yet so maybe like
two or three more races oh okay then
i'll i'll stop playing when you stop
then
really yay
yeah
no because i planned this to be like a
two hour racing thing
oh okay yeah because we played more than
two hours anyway so it's like are you
doing another one tomorrow um
i'm not sure may i might just join you
but it depends
okay
okay i'll be waiting for you dana oh
[Music]
people are like kiara skip breakfast
please why why are you telling her to
skip breakfast
it's almost 4 p.m what longer
yeah
it's it's indeed almost 4 p.m but i got
up very late so oh that's fine it's okay
it depends breakfast depends on when you
woke up right so it's not cool
that's why there's a you know those
things called all day breakfast
yeah and it doesn't say morning clothes
it says juice breakfast yeah exactly
there's no there's no morning in
breakfast
i don't know
yeah
you get what i'm trying to say
i like this right here so much
[Applause]
i like this map this map is really
peaceful but also
oh no i'm gonna get chilled
i don't know i didn't get killed that's
good
[Music]
[Applause]
oh god i wasn't my eyes wasn't on the
road
[Music]
my eyes wasn't on the road
i have no idea what was going on
the the whole train just
yeah i don't know what happened to it
oh no i'm 11.
i'm 11. can i recover from this
situation i wonder
i hope i can recover from this situation
i just want to be
[Music]
okay
um i ended up seven
ah it's okay we're close we're close to
each other it's fine hello birds i was
doing much better yesterday
yeah
it's all right we have those days i've
been having those days these past few
days but as long as i can keep up with
you they know i'm happy
[Laughter]
then i would love us to place a little
bit higher
let's do our best
sweet sweet canyon or rainbow road or
the volcano
oh i don't i don't mind
oh my god yesterday i played number one
on the rainbow road against amen ina and
akura oh
nice do you want this rainbow room
i oh this one i hate with all my heart
why
i think this one i i don't um i'm not
good at that one yet but i guess that
means i should practice
true the one i actually don't like
the most is the the other one not the
one inna likes not the one you guys did
it's the one with the that looks like
trains the one the one that has trains i
don't know
do you guys know oh
the course is really short i feel like i
just can't measure like how long the
course is
oh
what it's gonna be what's it gonna be
why is there a purple rainy
oh
[Music]
oh sweet canyon i think
the game is yeah the games
yeah
no no a communication error please oh
please oh yeah
oh it would be so sad if like if there's
a communication error
you got that when
you were
in the enid tournament right yes i did
that's all i hope it won't happen too
much this time for all of us yeah
especially because like the host is
probably going to be in japan right
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
oh i like this smell yeah it's pretty i
like it
[Music]
oh
there's a star coming in
yikes
a caminari an uninvited cabinet
what happened
i don't want to say anything because i
don't know i was gonna be like oh i've
been fine but then what if i get unlucky
in the third lap or something because
that kind of thing always happens
that kind of thing always happens so sad
[Music]
doo doo doo
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god
collision
there was an accident
with three people affected
[Applause]
[Music]
this is so scary
wow
what happened oh no i'm like sick i was
like third for like the whole race
except
except third lap
oh i finished third
[Music]
so i have my cats to cheer me it's okay
you got cat
support okay look they look they might
be first or second but they don't have
cat support
you're winning you're winning you have
the cat support that's the most
important thing
so is this always last one oh maybe yeah
you can choose which one you want
[Music]
mario circuit okay
i have no idea how to do the shortcut
for this one
you don't need to know we don't need
such a thing
oh there's hacha machama too
yes
[Music]
have you ever tried hatching an egg
before
like in in pokemon right
no in real life have you
we're birds after all of course i have
oh
can you explain to me in detail um your
experience when it comes to like
hatching eggs for science well i mean
you i just want to make clear
i haven't uh
i haven't laid an egg i've just hatched
an egg many eggs
so basically
you sit
on top of the egg for a while
and then when you warm it up while
sitting on it
then eventually it will crack open oh
and then you get a little baby bird baby
bird that sounds nice the only things
i've been doing with eggs is cook them
for breakfast that's it these days
[Music]
then i got dripped even harder yeah
it's okay
everybody can drift but not everybody
has cat support
oh no there's a shell now don't show me
please i beg you
what's
shell
we got shell no i didn't get shell
thankfully
i still have zero coins i'm really good
do you know what i'm really good at with
mario kart well you know what my
specialty is mario kart not getting home
exactly
avoiding cool we said that yesterday and
i remember oh yes no
i got sheldon midday that's so sad
that's the saddest thing since me being
avoided by coins
i'm so sad
so sad no okay i see nobody's actually
trying the insane shortcut
[Music]
oh
good for us
good for us good for us good for us
i i should be doing so much better today
maybe your viewers are just too strong
[Music]
i don't know
but i think
i think everybody is
i don't know my viewers are pretty
trolly at times but then i think
everybody's viewers are like that right
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no it's already ending
it is
one more dana one more one more okay one
more one more um
revenge revenge okay
oh you were third damn elena
yeah i got lucky with the last item
last game season two
congratulations
thank you
last one absolute last one i wanna do
bowser's castle okay okay we'll choose
bowser's castle
delicious that person is also everywhere
everywhere when i play mario kart
everywhere everywhere
yeah i think you know sashimi was also
there last time i'm a little nervous oh
no oh no need to be
okay
oh my god okay i see it
kind of cute
no i think yeah no there's a there's a
chance that it's like the hands you know
because like stubby heads only like
boobs to me oh oh okay
migraine oh my gosh there's somebody
called migraine
oh
i don't want my greens
do you get headaches this is like really
cool
not really no oh okay
this is like really weird small talk
like do you get migraines
[Laughter]
i wouldn't mind if it wasn't my training
[Applause]
i yeah i fell because i got too much
dokies when you said that
[Music]
okay i'm just bad
be careful i will be careful okay
be careful
okay
[Music]
yes
please everybody have monkey on me
why is everybody using a bullet please
that is so lame
i want one foot i agree
i agree also like why why does everybody
use stars that's so lame
star should be i don't know
disabled why is there bullet bill what
did the bullet will just pass me get
bullet bill out of the game
hi
pikachu
[Applause]
[Music]
wow yikes
oh it's the final lap
[Music]
it's the final laughs
i am very very scared
[Music]
[Applause]
come on
[Music]
we're on the same level i like it i like
it
wait where are you
i was uh behind you you were behind me
but i see i i saw you earlier in the
race
oh you're sick yay
i practice more i'll practice more too
probably yeah when you can
did you know that i got a new controller
because my i'm so scared i'm so scared
that my old one's gonna give me like
drifts
that's and then i just bought a new
controller oh there's kiawah's gf
anyways yeah last match thank you so
much for joining me in this stream today
thank you
thank you to have fun i'm gonna let you
say goodbye to your viewers then okay
okay oh there's another fiona
maybe maybe you're asking you tomorrow
then but no pressure oh yeah of course
of course of course yeah have a great
day evening
have a great breakfast bye-bye thank you
thank you
okay yeah
we ended we ended the voice
yeah bye here i hope you have a great
breakfast that was fun that was real fun
um this will be my this will be our last
race
our last race for today
we stream for
two and a half hours
last
because you know guys i need to i i need
to rest well because tomorrow morning
remember we have the you do uh mario
kart
[Music]
you know i really really want to do like
at least like one big blue like okay
probably like not today most likely not
today i really really want to do one big
blue that's not scuffed you know
[Applause]
i want to do a big blue run that is not
scuffed
so sad because all of my big blue runs
are very we're very very scuffed
especially towards the end
very very sad distance
[Music]
oh my god i got bananas
bananas bananas bananas
oh blue shell
scary scary scary blue shell
[Applause]
i'm sick oh my god i can't believe that
i'm sick
[Applause]
so so so so scary
[Music]
oh
oh i actually have 10 points
oh my god
i spaced out
how is that possible
[Music]
i spaced out
i spaced out is there a chance for me to
redeem myself i hope so
[Music]
i hope
i will have a chance
to redeem myself
oh maybe not because after this is the
last segment
i don't have enough items
oh
[Music]
god why does this always happen
oh that's fine
[Music]
[Laughter]
very nice all right um we're exiting uh
we're exiting the match we're leaving
[Music]
uh leave this group yes
oh let's see let's see what we got let's
see what we got we got two 400
the coins
why
i just want my clown glider please
i want my cloud glider
[Laughter]
so sad
oh well that's okay that's okay that's
okay
that is okay desire sensor mario karted
truly thank you so much guys for joining
it has been fun um i love uh you know
kiara joining was a really really nice
surprise um
it was really fun yeah because i'm just
like very used to uh
playing alone i guess and sometimes like
we did we did have some godot and shoes
but we never really had
um uh
ones that we didn't predict
[Music]
it's just really oh it felt really nice
and wholesome oh we're gonna be in the
same cup uh which is d you know let's
just like do do our best
let's just do our best i don't know how
i i would definitely want to stream but
yes
[Music]
guerrilla collabs are always a blast
yeah i had a lot of fun um
we're gonna switch windows uh just give
me a second
give me a second i'm just gonna
[Music]
i want to switch windows but i need to
um fix the chat
okay thank you so much guys um game
portion is over because we played for
like uh more than two and a half hours
but that's fine after this we're gonna
be reading donations and as well as you
know talking a little bit
uh i wanna set up
something for tomorrow too and yeah
let's
okay
there we go oh let me just close the
game
okay nice ah
that was real fun
that was really really really fun what
does mean you do you do is like um
i don't know casual it's like a casual
team match thing wait let me actually
check the members list somebody said
that oh yeah it's like few members for
like from like
the
you team
wait how many members are in one two
three
four
five
yeah
wait one two
three four
five
six
i can't count holy crap
one two three
four
five six people
six six people
are from
the d block or seven
[Music]
i i don't know
yeah there's a lot of people from d team
actually
what is their math on rainy stream
[Laughter]
seven from d
yeah yeah yeah oh my gosh
gorge
seven including me that's why the math
was off yeah most of us are from the
detail wait what
[Music]
oh gosh
team d dominates the practice game
exactly
counting is technically math yeah hold
on let me just like turn on my air
conditioning real quick
yeah that was super fun
yes it's gonna be like the real thing i
know it's like a mock match uh but no
it's not gonna be like the real thing
because it's gonna be a team based match
you know most of it
yes yes ooh funny green message ike's
all good luck on that club later thank
you
thanks for the race and happy 10 months
of royalty very nice to play with you
and kiara yeah
i've never really had a
joint practice with kiara before have i
i don't remember so you know especially
uh
it's really it's just really nice i
think it's really adorable that she's
like was she in bed i don't know well it
seems so comfy though i would want to
just play like that
with cat support that's so amazing that
sounds amazing
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
i have a very good feeling that d team
is so close that anyone can be first in
the last lap
yeah that's what i that's what i think
too like
d team like everyone is really
competitive and everybody is like
yeah i feel like it will be like the
most the more unpredictable
the more unpredictable a cup i feel like
cats are the secret ingredient to
success yes
in bed with cats playing mk what a lie
yeah
gotta be up to r jesus exactly well
that's that's what's so good about it
you know everybody's gonna be trying
their best then it's like yay
i trust that it would be like uh
you know whatever happens in the match
you know everybody gave it give their
all and yay
is your cat as fluffy as kiara's i don't
know
i have no idea this suit
hmm
just get serious though for tomorrow so
that you would know you're standing i
guess so
maybe
i'll try my best
[Music]
what is this
ah i understand though
okay is mc still bald
she's not bald shut up
um she grew her hair a little bit she's
not as fluffy as before but
she's growing her hair
um okay we're just gonna read uh super
chats from mario kart
the funny green thing says the
tournament is so close good luck thank
you
old emcee oh no i gotta wake up early
i gotta wake up everything i wanna sleep
so bad i wanna sleep i need to sleep
wait having coffee is a bad idea i think
[Music]
hey rainy about rosalina bill what about
comment that white weak any
glider i have no idea
let's try that after the tournament
is it decaf no
[Music]
oh we have um
we okay we have muno grow oh no my game
crash from mowers from france
yo
is it espresso no it's not we have bare
bear gaming chair fun by the way give
back our reigning please what do you
mean give back our rainy what does that
even mean
we have mary dude i was the dk i saw you
bump me in the fall off the stage the
next day i knew i heard screaming for my
computer speakers am i bad from the
stream
what what happened i don't know i forgot
i feel like the second half of the
stream you know like uh because kiara
joined and you know i feel like it's
just nice to have somebody to talk to
um while racing
[Laughter]
i mean it's just nice
hello burb i feel like i haven't been i
haven't really been streaming with her
lately i think our last collab was what
i don't remember so it's just really
nice to be able to talk to her again
yes
[Music]
yes yes yes
we have achieved
is a separate word it means we dance
[Music]
yeah last collab it was like worms right
yeah
i think it was the warms collab
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
happy rainy best rainy i i legit had a
lot of fun
the verb trio collab
um warmest collab is for yeah super fun
it was my first time playing worms too
and i had a lot of fun with it
doesn't feel that long ago
way
[Music]
my bullet bill with the ghost uh no
get mario carded
uh okay we have nina's apostle reigning
i played for two rounds because i didn't
know the rule here's something to make
up for oh that's oh that's fine
yeah i mean like generally the rules is
like you know you play once and then you
get out to let everybody else join in
but you know you can you can get in
after too that's why it's not like an
absolute only one person only one time
per stream no nothing like that
but yeah thank you
in your defense your mushrooms were told
exactly i needed that mushrooms for like
cheesing the shortcuts and everything
but i couldn't do that you know so it's
not really my fault okay
um
i really stole a golden mushroom while
being fourth
true true facts but you know mario kart
things all right
[Music]
we got
doomsday dan just the juxta were driving
in january getting jolted by jolly
jarakians
[Music]
very nice
ah when you're already in the grass and
the boost steals your shrooms oof
yeah oh whoa
[Music]
we have female ghosty chan thank you for
the race thank you we have orchard 61
thanks for the racist reigning i had a
lot of fun thank you
let's sit on cafe astronomer just join
the kfp kiara will hatch you
okay
the only things i do with eggs lately is
cook them for breakfast that is it
i just had like an egg burrito the other
day
breakfast burrito to be precise
um it was okay i had the mail at 4 p.m
[Music]
we have
purple dragon
when you got the blue shell launcher we
could feel the feel of my wrath i'm the
one with it this time in it
yes
yes this is not often i i actually get
blue shell shells i'm like yay i got the
blue shell breakfast burrito at 4 p.m
sounds legit yeah exactly we have a
place that serves all day breakfast and
i'm very thankful for it
[Laughter]
just um just whole life just whole life
things having breakfast at 4 00 at pm
we have deniven good game rainy thank
you thank you so much
i make them with rice beans eggs and ham
mmm delicious
delicious delicious delicious
and now i'm hungry get some food get
some food get some food
[Music]
we have joe fu
fun stream also thanks for teaching
kotone english that was also super great
oh thank you for watching yeah i was
earlier i was um
uh doing an english uh stream uh with
miss kotone on her channel
it was fun um we chatted quite a lot
before and after the stream too
yeah
uh
i really really wanna you know i mean
it's obvious with this stream too but i
really really wanna do uh like a whole
trip thing like together with whole life
members you know like also like what
kiara said like oh yeah let's go for
like the europe trip they'll be so nice
miss kotone ready to become the god of
bali
[Laughter]
don't you know i'm god
what is your occupation
oh god
yes
[Laughter]
go to bali to become the bali girl
bali valley
god or goats
god said
yeah trip would sound really cool i
would love it i i really really like
traveling so you know i mean i'm not
you know like i really like traveling
and like you know it's like a good
change of pace to like what you're used
to especially if you're like me like i'm
i'm always like indoors i'm always in
front of the computer of course um so
traveling's like a really good break for
me
to just yay
you know
occupation
yes i am god
courtney
god gonna go to hawaii for those famous
hawaiian pancakes i've never been to
hawaii i would want to go to hawaii
we need a whole live rl beach episode
yes that is absolutely correct
[Music]
if any menu
i always got 12 today i don't know who
to blame i'd love to blame the azure sky
but maybe because i was too nervous of
rain and kiara oh that's fine it's okay
if you see no listen if you see my past
mario kart streams i um
i constantly i've caught i constantly
get 11 or 12 it's fine you know if
you're 11 it means you know you're one
rank one but twice double one
did you know i'm the g in lmg
um
if valley is a gonno ghetto is jackson i
didn't get it am i getting now actually
i kind of
wow
just jackson jammer january yes
twitter space episode with holo in
europe let's go on why i really want to
go to europe
really nice
i just really want to go to different
places you know i feel like you know
[Music]
it just adds
i don't know
when you go somewhere
that's different from what you're used
to it opens up it gives you
a lot of inspiration it gives you like a
fresh vibe it gives you it just makes
you feel really good i don't know if if
if every literally everybody feels that
way but i sure do
[Music]
change the scenery always nice exactly
yes yes yes yes
definitely have a bit of a travel itch
for after the past couple of years yeah
true true true
and cultural awareness exactly it's
always interesting to learn new things
you know
switzerland now switzerland's nice
uh i don't know switzerland for me they
have like okay listen and like
i i don't know anything much about like
countries because like most of the time
i'm like just a tourist right but
switzerland always has a peaceful vibe
for me
yes yes yes yes yes
rainy i want to sleep also rainy keeps
talking
travel is expensive exactly that's why i
need to like keep like a separate
like a separate
what do you call it like i save money
but then i then i separate it from the
other expensive
expenses because okay this is
money
for travel you know
[Music]
business ex business trip expenses you
know if it's with hololive then it
becomes like a business trip sort of
yes tourism budget exactly
exact mom
what does that mean again what's exactly
what mean
yes except for saving a call account
maybe choo choo choo choo choo choo i
want to learn french i wanna go to paris
and learn french
yes
um
[Music]
yes
sure thank you for the fun stream
looking forward to the whole cup thank
you thomas for watching
i'll do my best in the holocaust
tomorrow to tomorrow morning or
okay i need to sleep then
uh there's a you do you team
yes yes yes go to spain and impress them
with the cucaracha yes yes yes yes which
country you visited before
um
which country you visited before uh
yes i don't know
here i just went to france i i guess you
did a stream right like i'll revolve
friend from
paris or something
i want to go i would want to go
yes
if you post at least one voice clip of
you with any other holograms then it's
automatically contact aka business
expense exactly you're absolutely right
she went to disneyland oh that's so cool
that's so nice i've never actually been
to the disneyland in france
did you visit the philippines i've
actually never been to the philippines i
would want to visit one day you know
um it's actually it's been
it's been one of the places that i've
been wanting to visit uh because of like
yeah uh but i don't know i just had a
time to
and
yeah you want to eat jollibee yeah
that's what people always say like yeah
i want to eat the jolly bee
exactly
misses worldwide exactly i want to be
mrs worldwide and just travel i can be
like oh have you traveled here yes i
have have you traveled here yes i have
purple dragon here is a small french
mess a sentence bonjour je m'appelle
named je vous al i don't understand i
perrier pep apologize paris yes
rainy changing her name to pitbull
am i a peacock no i'm a pitbull
welcome to the royalty let's go they
have jollibee in canada are you sure
um pit pal
yes yes yes
[Music]
daley exactly
yes yes yes
[Music]
doesn't taste the same i think
i don't know
isn't it always that like that for
example like franchises never taste the
same
like
in japan famichiki tastes really good i
could live off okay this sounds really
sad but i could live off on michiki like
i would buy the microwavable rice and
then put famichiki on top of it and eat
it for like three times a day
but the famichiki you know that
indonesia have amitsuki too
it's um
yeah
it tastes different
[Music]
yes yes yes
that's smooth oh okay
well variety maybe no not every single
day but say like in one day
i would be able to like eat three
three times a day for how long well not
well not not absolutely every day
subway is different in mexico and sea
wait how different is subway mexico
like mike d in the us is different from
my dnc from what i heard yeah i think so
too
[Music]
i see the taste of disappointment oh no
that's so sad
michigan is on my bucket list i see acid
the bread selection
i want to visit south calimantan why ccc
that's
complicated you want to be uh
a cell you know castle people
you gotta try the coca-cola ph
mcdonald's legendary wait what what what
what do they do with it
um
um milk was the biggest difference
overseas for me huh really
meg did indonesia serve nasi uduk well
okay
[Music]
yes
there are foods in jollibee in the us
that are not available in ph no like
from what i heard like in uh for example
like in southeast asian countries
say oh no no no i know the kfc and ph
like has gravy
has so much gravy and that you guys
abused the gravy so much
in the philippines um i think in
indonesia we don't have that
[Music]
yeah
unlimited gravy is soup
gravy abuse
[Music]
[Laughter]
so much gravy carrot basin
oh gosh
yeah they got unlimited gravy so sad um
i don't think indonesia has it i don't
think japan has it um i don't know which
i don't know what country has a gravy in
their kfc other than um
philippines
you bring an empty plate to the gravy
dispenser then go to town on it
i think id no id ph gravy equal to id
sambal because we abuse sambal a bit too
much fair fair fair fair you know like i
think like when traveling like a lot of
indonesian people would just like bring
a lot of like sambal sauce like chili
paste with them with like the in the
sachets and everything and even though
they go to like a really fine restaurant
like for example like okay um you have
the tour you're in a tour like the tour
guide takes you to like a really fancy
restaurant and then they still get out
there softball and it's like
[Music]
you know
i feel like you know there are some
countries that are really strict with
that like
i heard
because like you know it means that oh
if you're like seasoning re-seasoning
the food in the restaurant you think
that the food doesn't taste good so it's
just like uh okay better be better be
careful right i don't do that
but you know a lot of indonesian people
are crazy about spice so yeah
you can't do that in france exactly the
chef will like get out of the kitchen
and be like hey what's wrong with my
food and then
[Laughter]
i guess
i used to carry a sriracha bottle
everywhere oh my gosh really
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes
every fancy restaurant indonesia is
forced to have sambal exactly like the
i don't know like even the most fanciest
restaurants they definitely if you ask
is their sambal they would say yes like
oh and then it's like you know it's just
an indonesia thing i guess
just see things
i got my brother the world with the
world's hottest hot sauce for christmas
and he almost died oh no
u.s portions are basically two full
meals want to eat here one take home
exactly yeah u.s portions are really
really big
and rainy what's your favorite sambal i
like sambal
you know it's um it's made with a type
of fish
like the the fish is called laroa that's
uh that's why it's called samurai like
it's like
it's sambal but mixed with that fish
it's really really good
yes
and i just use it like really really
really sparingly because i'm not really
good with spice but it just tastes so
good
yes yes yes yes
it's not really
it's not really fancy i think like
indonesia is just like famous with like
mixing stuff in their sambal
[Music]
samba is the soul of indonesian food
it's very common and i don't know
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
i prefer sambultrasi i see
is more spicy than ali's mata um whether
something is spicy or not depends of the
amount of chili
um sambal mata is just um tastes
different because you use like um
um what do you call it shallots you use
shallots and everything
um
so it kind of tastes a little like
shallot tea
i don't know
shality and like sweet ish
and spicy um it's not too salty i feel i
feel like the roa the fish the fish kind
of stumble that i'm telling you right
now is more off on the salty side
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you have the
fish ground into the sambal
yes yes yes yes shout
do you watch indonesian dramas
uh no not really actually
um no not really
is there anything good these days in
indonesian drama in indonesian cinema
electronic or cinetron
yes yes yes yes yes
not really okay
i don't know i don't watch either oh
okay
[Music]
you
how often do you watch indonesian films
and series as opposed to foreign ones um
i don't watch too many indonesian films
but occasionally there are indonesian
films that are like oh they're so good
so i watch it there there are a few
indonesian good illusion movies i can
recommend you for example
it's hard though
um
and i would uh if you guys like
fighting
um even though it can get super violent
like the raid is really good it's action
scenes
and stuff
um
[Music]
oh my gosh
[Laughter]
oh my okay
indonesian fighting films are crazy good
yeah it's because um
it's because of indonesia's like
traditional martial arts thing i think
that's why um
the raid and everything is very very
good because they're like mixing
um
you know
okay they have like guns and everything
but they kind of mix it with
the martial arts kind of thing that's
what makes it really really good the
choreography and everything
uh-huh
yes yes yes yes
indonesian ftvs are kind of cheesy but
it's surprisingly interesting when
you're bored isn't that all isn't that
like also oprah
tcu
cinematic universe
[Laughter]
yes yes yes yes went from symbol to
martial arts well it's not it's not
every time we get to talk about um you
know indonesian films i think
you have a region martial art yes yes
yes yes um
i think like i'm not very familiar so i
can't really um
i can't really say like how much we have
but like one of it is like oh yeah we
have like something like pentax or
something it's kind of like you know a
type of martial arts
yes yes yes yes yes
um
pancake is the most famous one yes
yes yes
amazing
[Music]
fighting fighting
writing free thoughts are fun because i
have to keep a google search tab open
the whole time now that that's called
education right no i usually do that too
whenever like i talk i like i have i
have google open i'm like wait
which one was it again then i
[Music]
ours in the ph is arness with the twin
sticks let me see
[Music]
oh
oh i know this okay okay okay
aside from weapons arness also
relies on the use of your bare hands or
weaponless technique as its main focus
oh
i say
[Music]
i see high quality educational content
ready free talk is really talking about
whatever chat leads her to exactly
like everything is just a big free talk
with me
oh
anyways yeah um i have to prepare for
tomorrow
i'm gonna
see you guys at
in the morning
[Music]
oh for the you do
you do holo
cards i'm very very excited there's
going to be a lot of people uh in the
team
i'm kind of nervous too
but it's fine because you know there's
nothing to do aside from you know just
doing your best right
[Music]
early morning at noon
but yeah that is it thank you so much
guys for uh coming today and it's truly
been a wonderful time um and i'll see
you tomorrow all right three magazines
thank you very much for your attention
and assalamu alaikum everybody let's
wait let's anticipate for the tournament
it's coming very soon bye bye everybody
yay
[Music]
do
you