do
[Music]
hello
yes bring your license
ah a bit too small nice little okay okay
okay
wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
oh
and then we'll show everyone the code
okay
and everyone can join us this is a
warm-up okay this one doesn't count it's
a warm
up chaotic it's driving here we go yes
oh we're going for the ice ice
i was never on that road before i think
oh
that like oh i've done this a couple of
times
okay here we
[Music]
number go how do i use items again i
just like this
i keep on forgetting yeah i'm so slow
and white though
excuse me oh no
why why are you faster okay now i'm
faster i think
oh no oh okay
i've been i've been practicing this
isn't how it's supposed to be
i have not been practicing by the way
i can't even see
okay
i'm gonna show you the german driving
skills that i learned on the german
autobahn
i'll show you the power of taco
i don't know if octopus or taco is
allowed to drive but
don't worry about the details they're so
far away
why are you so far away it's it's
my training i i went through the
training or kiara
yeah i actually i just took a nap
okay this is fine this is mine that's
the sign this is fine
no i can't lose this
by the way we're
we are driving against each other and
against the people who are going to join
the room right yes yes yes
not just us we're gonna give you the
code in a bit
after this one this is a warm-up we
gotta warm up
you're using the power of the ancient
ones no
i'm doing the square and square
i don't believe you i don't believe this
is why you gotta practice
kiara why can't i drift
i can't drink anymore
oh my god initial taco yes
gas gas
[Music]
it's uh four zero six zero five
one one nine zero three one five
if anyone wants to join us feel free
feel free feel free okay this there you
yes yes you know you and me together
okay yes we gotta
gotta win i'll get the crowd
because they're so strong we don't have
a chance against them if we also fight
each other we gotta work together
okay okay oh here they are
okay what's a good good
no god no not rainbow except
that's the worst road ever
don't do that to me i mean oh no oh no
rainbow road is the majority what are we
gonna do
i'm gonna fall off the cliff at least 50
times
okay i believe in you believe in me who
believes
oh by the way if everyone could be so
fair to
to leave the room once they participated
one time
thank you so that as many people as
possible can join
oh [\h__\h]
i drifted i tripped it i did it
[Laughter]
oh why didn't we choose this road
it's cause i went too fast i went too
fast
we're done i should have saved my shoes
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
i'm coming
i saw someone's mushroom but i'm still
i'm still
waiting
we're dead last that's why i told you
not to choose this road
i mean we would have still
gotten you know
ah this was the majority of things on
this
one oh you never know
hello
oh i gotta start
i need i need driving lessons oh my god
same
no no no i'm literally
driving off every single curve the sun
is hard honestly
[Music]
i believe in you what
i believe in you oh really
oh wait i can't i can't tell which one
you are there's like there's like
multiple of the same character
well why are you so
okay not bad not bad not bad i feel like
i should
um make this
a little bigger number 12.
come on oh by the way uh well i want to
give a shout out to an artist called
nino maya
she literally speaks you did it in what
an hour or less
40 minutes or something right after my
previous statement
she
oh right the people actually left except
two people who are sleeping or something
yeah but i just can't see everyone left
yes
i'll put this right here okay that's
better good people
mm-hmm next time please leave
you two people who hated hey what's up
right here
gamer you little oh it's just someone
oh hey yeah
you look cute
like such a little why are you so few
maybe not everyone should have left
where is everyone
you guys can join in again later okay
everyone who just left you can join in
again
[Laughter]
mario circuit yay
are those npcs yeah i think so
oh okay i can't win against npcs
or can you me
i don't know i lose against nbc's a lot
of times
sadly
yes i should be using control price
uh i'm not
tilt controls are better are they
tilt controls are superior are they
they are yeah
who left their winter wheels here in the
middle of the road
[Applause]
[Music]
tackle drift pictures
i thought you were bad at this game i
practiced
i told you i had to people said i was
doing bad so i practiced
him
oh
npcs is the real challenge
oh this blue shell i got him
oh kiara you're in front of me
wait no that's not you that's kfi your
employee
my employees i i mean if my employees
win i will take that as a win for me as
well
no even though they're driving against
me but i'll take it as a way for me
i was thinking so well you aren't very
good aha thank you comments that's
i'm not good what do you mean i'm number
10 okay
no as long as you're not last you're
okay not last
what the hell behind me me
two of my own gear workers
are behind me they actually i think i
saw them stopping on the road
you i love come on hello come on you
are you gonna lower their race i mean
your their pay
if they are in front of them
they're fired if they if they don't let
me win they're fired but
vgamer and kfp you can stay in the race
you're doing a good job but i have a
feeling that now that i trust them
next next race they will they will um go
behind my back and win against me again
okay don't don't let her win guys
we gotta i mean i mean uh let's let her
we got a we got a um
yeah cooperate kiara yes
uh yeah yeah of course of course
of course i'm using tail patrols
[Laughter]
let's see let's see okay
you chose the airport oh this is a
random one
oh what's this
twisted mansion well that's basically if
i remember this one
and it's called komori taco
forest coffee tacos
[Music]
where are the taco nashes
[Laughter]
oh hello thank you for telling me damn
it
we got a clock remember not
very much indeed
oh my god
oh that store must be you yep
not anymore though yo two items again
how dare
[Music]
it's so slow yeah you know
the big plant yeah it's useless
everyone's bumping into me
it must be the kfp workers
yes you're supposed to throw your shell
forward not backwards friends
oh there's a blue shell coming but not
for me because i'm not
[Music]
this is okay this is okay i can make it
out
which which which uh
which i can't speak english every time i
i
play mario kart i lose all my english
weights
don't worry i do too
we need to stay i just gotta be careful
we should go to england uh english
lessons oh yes
definitely
no i didn't
come on let's see the number one rta
soon
okay who gets number one first
oh kiara where'd you go
oh i got did you get this seat i got
kicked out
eh oh wait i think it's the settings
oh oh oh hold on
let me edit let me edit the room let me
edit through
oh wait i can't edit that one
coming up okay i'm pretty much back in
again i think oh okay okay
i got one right next to me
are you in the room uh i'm going in now
ow oh i'm spectating oh i mean i'm
in i'm in but you're not there yeah
scared i think we're good should we make
the room
maybe maybe i have a room called speed
speed you want to enter the speed i made
it before okay
everyone let's let inna join first
[Music]
how about you write it down for me and
then i will
enter it i will like
0 9 7 5 9 3
wait you're saying you're speaking out
loud
they can they can follow some rules they
can obviously not follow the rule to let
me win
but they should be able to follow this
one group
i'm joining it's currently closed
do you want to what
yeah whatever join speed yes okay
oh yes
[Music]
this is fine this is fine
okay i'll change the code in my stream
um
could you please drown me too in the
swimsuit okay if
if you win against me i will draw you
in the zooms okay oh you gotta win again
in the next place
wait where are you kiara are you in yeah
am i i'm in
i don't need oh god you're in like a
different room
no you're in the same room but in a
different
dimension yeah yeah it's because you
know because there's so many people
yeah we're in the wrong timeline
student isn't like oh no no
yeah okay we'll do it one more time i
will make a room
and then okay i can join before
before everyone else hold on let me
uh-huh
yeah you can leave okay i will make a
new room
um sorry about that um
we know nothing about this game
i literally picked it up again because
of the stream
uh of your scene before
before today's stream like five minutes
before we were like wait
which mode we use multiplayer online
wireless what it's all the same
maybe there's a different way to do it
oh god how can i leave
this race oh you can play a game while i
make this
okay okay okay then
then i will show you my road rage
show me your german road rage
this is it
[Music]
[Laughter]
that sounds silly
hong kong wait ina do you have
a driver's license like for real like uh
i have a learners i can drive
i can drive but i need someone with an
actual license beside me
okay i will let you know the code
[Music]
okay
how how to drive oh my god
wait i want to watch
it's a horrible race between uh
some some nice people who are trying to
stay behind and me
oh god they're so nice
there's no way that those people are so
as bad as me so
they honestly they respect
this majestic phoenix they're following
the speed limit
had to stay behind friends oh finish
okay need to get out of here
someone here is called watson achillea
watson what's that
what's in i can't wink anymore for some
reason
oh one i don't know
i'm drawing i used to be able to wing so
well
okay i gave you the code uh
okay let me know everything that's
faster me or the viewers
okay no i didn't i didn't update the
code yet on
my stream okay okay but they're seeing
it as
i'm typing
did you change some settings uh i
changed it because like last time it
like shuffled people after a few runs
but now it's uh yeah
you okay you leave voluntarily okay
okay okay so they were forced
to leave yeah after four runs yeah
but now people gotta leave by their own
will okay
well wait i mean yeah
okay okay one more good
here we go again here we go
now okay i will win this race and if i
win then
against you against you yeah
well i mean anything that i'm wearing i
will make sexy just because of my
put you in the chickens
no please no
[Laughter]
weren't we talking about like wearing
halloween costumes and then everyone
kept linking you like a chicken cozy
[Music]
i saw someone uh do a halloween costume
fan art of me and kelly though
and they threw me as a as a devil like a
red devil
why does that keep on happening to me
anyway it looks so good
ah i played some of it oh i really want
to play
breath of the wild i haven't finished it
oh i i bought the game like ages ago but
i never started playing it
yeah i'm uh i'm really bad with like
open world games because i'm
directionally challenged
i'm just like where am i supposed to go
you seem to find your way today um
well there's only one way to someone oh
it's true
no well sometimes there's other ways
like no
it's i'm so proud of me
i gotta fight for that swimsuit
oh no don't do that everyone's going to
come get
it think about it who doesn't see it
damaged
no no applesauce what the hell don't you
want to see me in the swimsuit
yeah sure don't we all want to see me
i don't really want to see inna in a
swimsuit
if i win i get to draw myself
come on
please mercy who left their banana on
the road who was it
sorry i think
oh that was almost bad that was almost
bad
[Music]
someone else that looks like me a bullet
in poster oops [\h__\h] no
speed no my my seven
no i used to be doing so well not like
this
no oh no
my dream of my clothes
oh no i'm not doing this
on purpose by the way i'm not thriving
for that on purpose believe me
they're waiting where's your
where's your german driving skills um
i love them in germany okay how about we
do this how was it
you win any of the games today on this
stream
any of the people any of the i'll make
it easy for you okay
[Music]
do you mean win them against you right
now against me against me
and you have the game
you have a lot of chances you gotta make
it count okay
yo not everyone has to leave because it
feels like not everyone
not it's not filling up that well but
let's see okay everyone's getting silly
controls
um that's it what a shame
[Laughter]
health controls
isn't it sad like uh at least um
in the land where i currently and which
is by the way uh it's public now so
don't
don't worry japan oh thank you apple
sauces thank you for the super chat
the summer ended so quick quickly this
year oh
and that made me really sad so i would
love to see myself on the swimsuit
well if anything you'll get yourself in
the skin suit
no i refuse no please no
if you can't win you're gonna be in a
chicken suit okay
why does this keep on happening how do
we speed in the beginning again wasn't
it
that starts beating on number two yes
why does it not work anymore
it hasn't worked all day someone has
hacked my cart
someone has walked into the gate
who did this with my with my with my
what it's not a card though it's a
screw what is it uh what is it
called uh what's the thing on two wheels
uh bikes yes
wow english stills always on point when
i play very hard
you know how about we speak some german
uh oh no i fell yes
[Music]
bye if i tassel yes yes keep on going
that's what means
you're close to me i see you i see you i
see you oh
you all catch me
um actually this might be the race this
might be the race oh no
is that bullet you yep
nothing fun
[Music]
yes yes yes yes i want to draw you in a
chicken suit
well you can do that too if you really
wanna
can you make it like cute actually i
noticed
that in today's thumbnail art he gave me
a helmet
that kind of looks like a chicken head
anything you got to say about that i
mean you saw chicken right
yeah chicken burgers
[Applause]
[Music]
what happened wow
swimsuit here i come
okay you can you can do it like in a
drawing stream
i don't know about youtube can be nice
when i chose
since you're not getting banned and
you're showing so much
non non-existent cleavage maybe
maybe if i draw a chicken suit kiara
youtube come won't tell me chicken soup
yeah
i can't believe this is shoes this is
not what it's like no
i have one swimsuit not not chicken
sauce
chicken swimsuit huh
oh no
[Laughter]
i want it to be sexy or cute
chick sexy okay fine turkey
i know you love me you're not the type
to bully me
flamingo flamingo
the bird i like flamingos
but i mean it can be it can it can be a
swimsuit with a flamingo pattern
okay what about kitchen
oh pigeon well i really like pigeons to
be honest
but i don't want to be in a pigeon suit
i want the swimsuit i want this favorite
square
okay i mean the chaos yeah you did you
might have helped they might have helped
but
no my items
oh i like the music on this race oh
there's
dirt everywhere my employees
well i did hire a lot of people much
more than i
actually needed to get the store going
now i have so many people working for me
that i just sit back and look at them
working
okay of beer
workers are strong i turned on the the
friend request receiving
uh just to add ina and now turn it off
our relationship is different it's uh
it's your boss
and it's employees okay yeah would you
add would you add your boss
on mario kart
could you add yago on mario kart i would
say yes
i think everyone it's an argument
we need to play against diago oh i feel
like y'all will be really good at mario
kart for some reason
nah i doubt it i doubt it you know he's
really good at puppies
he's only got a tetris
did you see him patriot skills
oh when he was playing against you see
something yeah yeah
i think so he's like
wait what what's going on nina what's
going on
[Music]
channeling my inner cali with my gods
god
[Applause]
[Music]
why are we the only two ones if a
japanese flag even
like i mean i'm in japan
well well two swimsuits for me two
swimsuits
no okay one is fine what the hell is
that face on that
on that on that paccola fan standing
next to me
why not it's beautiful it's beautiful
and beautiful
i think i saw that one before and in
pekuda's stream
because
she's she's not in here right i think it
was up her name was i think
mario kart
is streaming at nine o'clock today so in
15 minutes so they have
[Music]
after all we're a team right right
sorry uh
i'm just driving safely
huh did you put your seatbelt on yes
i have my helmet my seatbelt okay
everything very good
oh i feel hello i'm like right next to
you pretty much
hello i don't know i apologize
why oh
huh what's happening are you okay i was
like named and now i'm 12.
what's up
i thought we were supposed to be friends
like work together though that was your
plan all along wasn't it
let my car down aim for number one
let my guard down
hong
[Music]
you're a bit far behind no
okay
i'm getting better i'm getting better i
was just in the beginning i was back
because i didn't practice before
if it was one-on-one it would be a
different story
oh you want to do a one-on-one you want
to do one-on-one huh huh
that's right let's take it outside
enough you want me
right okay our last game is gonna be one
on
let's one let's see what you can do
without your workers
no don't take my attention working
something for me they're all i have
okay
[Music]
i need to go on another training arc
which one do i go oh i want wario's gold
mine i like that one where's the pain
text
you can say so unfair
i'm using total controls yeah that's
right
i'm blaming the tall controls
yes yes blame everyone
it's the penguin oh pink
what's that painting choose your wrist
the paint question oh i chose red
okay okay the pain controls
they're not working
[Laughter]
let's see what we get tilt control is
more like tilted controls
funny
your workflows are really really like
mario kart
yeah i told them to change their names
so i can recognize them
oh i did it finally for the first time
in today's stream i've managed to
speed up in the beginning the first time
how was it that time do that
everyone's just vlogging me i'm joking
i can finally hear kelly playing the
kazoo
what does it sound like give me your
best kazoo
[Music]
no you're impressions me don't do that
you asked for it
i am kazoo why am i going so fast
i'm not feeling bad at all i feel like
something
what left the uh left the map was it you
kiara i saw kate
yeah it was me
i'm ghost
well i just gotta do what a ghost gotta
do
you know it's just the job of a ghost
spooky spooky
you know by the way yes did you see i'm
having a
off collab with nana tomorrow i saw
i'll do my best to watch
yeah really i'm going to be awake maybe
schedule ever yeah don't worry about it
oh
kiara yes
[Music]
don't leave me with that thingy you got
in your hand no
that's right you gotta go fast
[Music]
on my my gamer gamer brain cell
that's right i even beat your tfp worker
thank you
kfpq for stopping right at the at the
finishing line to let me become number
11.
not at last oh here we are
baby pike here we go hey
it did laura go well for you why don't
you do this to yourself why do you
choose rainbow road
you know what if i'm gonna suffer if i'm
gonna suffer i'm not going down alone
i'm bringing you with me
baby around baby world baby road
rainbow road everyone you guys want to
see kyra suffer
yes yes you do yes you do
kfb workers it's it's your chance to get
back at her
for all the time she threatened to fire
you
[Laughter]
the thing is though i buy them i fired
them already so many times
do you retire them though yeah i keep
coming back so
i think i enjoy it
oh according to plan
god damn it
[Music]
this is the sixth race
yes i'm
i'm going to set a record
oh well it's going all right it's going
all right i'm not falling off yet
stay here and stop i'm just okay i did
i spoke soon why is it so slippery today
and again number two
[Music]
do you produce ink uh
no i'm human oh really
dad is counting how many times i'm i'm
falling off i already lost count
[Music]
well i could have totally taken that you
cannot be friends with your boss don't
send
drug requests
oh please let me go
who's holding you back you know myself
ancient ones would have been a better
answer but i'll take it oh
hey alta is okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
well this i'm i start when i get into
the finishing line thanks guys
thank you thanks for waiting
i was hundred percent kind of number 12
but but admiral and item is waited for
me
come on you gotta make yourself for not
12.
it doesn't even matter because like
i'm already so bad it would be higher
i would be like sixth or fifth or
something that would matter but but if
i'm this low it doesn't even matter
is this your favorite it's so much
bigger
sounds easy oh it sounds easy baby stops
baby chicks
[Laughter]
okay kiara i think after this one is it
gonna be our 1v1 race
you ready yes okay okay
thanks for the super chat thank you
[Music]
i don't know how i deserve them but
thank you
well they're paying me my salary
this is unfair now they work against me
mostly so don't worry about that are you
sure about that
only like there's only like two people
who waited for me at the end
was it
oh i love this music oh this is the the
seventh
one fun
oh my god not fun i'm not very good at
this
[Music]
he slowed down to hit me with those
spells or maybe
maybe he was not trying to hurt me
i'm going too fast
and ghost boo hoo
spooky spooky halloween
[Music]
i'm turning too fast so it's going too
far
let me get let me go let me get
already went in i got sports
those four that are behind me they all
waited for me
dude
okay how are we going are you ready okay
yeah yeah okay
bye guys thanks for the games guys
thanks how do we do one on one
to our friends and rivals is that what
we need to do yeah
i don't know what to do hey
i think yeah is that what
yep oh no maybe not no no that's not
i'll create
one okay i'll make a room and you can
come in
go to go to like friends
and then you'll you'll see my name
and then you can click my name and you
should be able to join
ah nice
okay um chat do you have any
recommendations for a wheel
oh i think i need twice something
how about monster wheels 100 or 150
cc one 150 okay 150
normal items no come all vehicles
oh 48 races four races i guess okay
yes
i'm explaining the rules
but what's slim what is slim god damn it
i'm taking this okay
it's random again no teams normal items
no cpu
okay vehicles four races out enough
oh we're doing four races okay oh okay
well we can just do one and then
caught
which one do you want to do i i just was
random so it's fair and square
oh oh yeah okay oh okay okay
what will it be which will it be you and
me again see today
[Music]
super mario 64 uh clock thingy
i love that one okay here we go here we
go
hey i'm number two wow that's not bad
two out of two i have the legs
huh
how dare you no one is safe from the red
shell
[Music]
i know
i have to keep on holding that if i want
to have it on my ass well what
hey guys
[Music]
oh i'm out there
oh i'm waiting i'm ready just gotta be
careful that's gonna be careful just
gotta be careful just gotta be careful
just gotta be careful scotch gotta be
[Music]
covered
speeds list
[Music]
energy
people are gonna doubt if i really speak
german now
we're so close no are you trying to hit
me with that boomerang
that was close that was close
i slipped up there it was close
i think we are 50 50. yeah we are
both bad drivers let's be real yeah yeah
i agree with that please
well thank you for driving against or
with me
in whichever way
oh my god i never thought of that i
never that you want to collab with me
kfb and taco bell um depends
we gotta figure out the details in the
in the back
you know how many coupons are we talking
about
all the cute coupons lifetime coupons
yes
thank you very much for today and
i'll see you soon yes um do you have any
awesome
yes number one
swimsuit chiara coming soon chicken sit
[Laughter]
here
communication error between us two now
something like that would never
never know uh in exactly
uh 19 out hours okay
no i it 18
18 hours from now
at three o'clock for three o'clock
japanese standard time uh i'm having
the i think everyone already knows but
i'm having a collaboration with nana
where we're doing an off collab karaoke
concert
yeah we are the we are we are
orange
everyone has a free entry ticket but you
know how
you know free entry kfp
people still pay me my salary thank you
just kidding anyway every everyone is
welcome too
but nina you you're gonna get a vip seat
yay
did i get a backspace pass yes yes yes
[Music]
um i just like to say uh
thanks for being with me today uh
we just did uh 400k
during the streaming game yay
come on during that stream
i feel like every time i hit a milestone
i'm with someone
i'm glad that you're here
[Music]
maybe i can be there for four years too
we can we can we can drive off
have a drive off there
oh yeah okay
[Music]
can i say my german bye-bye yes
okay let's say in german
[Music]
bye
you