[Music]
no one's gonna buy this [\h__\h] i believe
you cute it's all hell in a literal
sense
saying that i like so much more is along
the lines that you reap what you [\h__\h]
say so gotta know in so could you let go
of your soul for me
i'm not asking for much do me a favor
[Music]
human nature
um
[Music]
okay
all right
[Music]
oh
hello
is
modern day killers really must hate
fun more often people
take in lives rocking and knives and
guns the real murder
connoisseurs in the ruins
of hell got used to
luring the audience with moe
that sells cause to my surprise
snatching lives torii
zoo something
nice try stopping the [\h__\h]
of da vinci erasure can't
stop the pace sir make sure when
standing
[Applause]
who is in the rules
[Music]
is
do me a favor
[Music]
is
why why why
uh uh
[Music]
streamlabs you're fired they hear us
you hear us you can hear it
oh hey i can hear them what
you guys can hear us wait really it's
okay
huh we can hear we can hear
we can hear i can hear but it's quiet
okay that's better than nothing that's
better than nothing okay
wow um um it's not showing up in stream
labs um
that's funny it says the mic isn't uh
making any noise
anyway um
[Music]
i hope that hurt all of your ears i'm
sorry
let's start let's start is it okay
everyone
yes it hurts okay good good okay
wonderful sound is good
bgm ah
can you hear the bgm bgm also is not
showing up
kawaii bgm okay okay they can hear okay
no no no i'm the only one talking i'm
the only one talking right now
it hurts it's okay okay good yay
wonderful
bgm on fantastic we gucci we gucci we
gucci
okay let's start let's start
okay anyway hello everyone hello
hello thank you for coming to the stream
for all of you who entered remixes thank
you so much for entering
and we really look forward to talking
about your remixes today
um but first let me introduce my
special guest we have two guests today
first of all
um as you can see um next to me
next to me um to my to my left um is
kusatori
um kind of freaking out going crazy as
per the usual
yes please can you just try to be a
little
a little calm this time today actually
i'm in serious mode because i'm
translating so i will be calm i will be
serious
yes kiara is special helper today um
very kindly offered to come help
uh with translation stuff so yeah it's
gonna be fun
um and then to my rights we have super
special guests
uh keiz kokorovic aka
[Music]
[Applause]
that's right very nice
good yeah can you guys hear mr case
yay yeah space all right okay good good
yay chat says yes
okay good hello mr case hello mr case we
can yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh let's talk a little bit about the
remix contest
okay so we received
over 800 yeah 800 entries
uh oh my god you are crazy deadbeats
you are crazy crazy crazy crazy humans
why
i mean i'm happy i'm happy i i really am
i'm so happy
thank you very much but um what the [\h__\h]
like you guys are amazing and it made
gosh it was it was really really hard uh
to choose
our favorites uh so i might have picked
more than 10 maybe more like
15. sorry sorry sorry sorry i can't help
it
there were so many good ones and and i
have i have some good news
for everyone who isn't chosen um
so i decided that um so before
in my streams um my kaiwa
before super chat right superchatto
yomunomai
i have a standby screen right with me
chasing my friends
but because all of you entered so many
wonderful entries
i want to play um the top 200 top 200
um for every stream during that the
standby screen
um for you guys so yeah i'll choose
one every day for every stream to
introduce and i'll talk a little bit
about it
afterward so yeah uh thank you very much
everyone
uh we couldn't we couldn't choose
everyone and it was really
it made me sad i wanted to choose
everyone because i love you
oh i'm guys but i'm gonna make it up to
you
i promise don't worry you don't need to
make anything up for
anyone but i feel like i have to though
no no no
no
okay i'm chilling i'm chilling i'm
chilling
well with that being said um
i guess my opening remarks would be
thank you everyone
you are amazing and i can't wait to
share with you our favorites um
next uh mr k's do you have anything
you want to say yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
804 entries
you know
[Music]
yeah every remix was really amazing
there were some funny ones there were
some cool ones in between
and while he was listening he was always
very excited
and they also laughed a lot and danced a
lot while listening to the reason
me too yeah it was wonderful
so i hope that you will enjoy them uh
you haven't
heard the top 15 right so some are yeah
i only heard like
the funny remixes that you played in the
beginning which you already saw that
were already so good
yeah especially uh i like the the google
google voice one yeah i started crying
actually
there were a couple where i started
crying when i listened to them
where they tried really hard to make me
wrap this
up i also cried but one day one day i'll
i'll wrap it for real okay i'll show you
my rap god skills one day
i'm waiting i'm waiting try to impress
me why is your head on my shoulder huh
but i'm looking forward to the godly
remixes that are coming
today they're very good they're amazing
the best of the best and
it's sad because even the the best best
top tier
i didn't make it into the top 15. uh i'm
really sad
um so but like i said you will see them
you will see them and the results the
final results first
place and second place is next week
next week's next week's live stream okay
um
second place today not today no we need
to think we need time to think about
so let's just play the top okie dokie
well i guess
let's get started let's get started um
now everyone
um we've been having some audio
difficulties
right technical difficulties so if you
can't
hear the videos when we play them please
let us know in the chat and we will
figure something out it should be
okay though let's find out okay
lights out it's dark okay
first the first number one
here we go
[Music]
sir make sure
of your dreams
[Music]
do me a favor
we decided to turn on the mic so you can
hear tiata spazzing out and all of our
reactions
[Music]
[Applause]
ciara's having a lot of fun tiara's
having a lot of fun
he's so excited
amazing yay and you can hear us now
right it's okay i hope i didn't break
everything
that was so hyped so this name
wow
[Music]
um
i thought it was amazing and i actually
heard
a while ago the work in progress work in
progress
w-i-p work in progress and i thought wow
that's amazing so the finished version
is is wonderful and it has
swing vibes right i love like the kind
of very
subtle right swing vibes are amazing
amazing
it made me happy kelly should i
translate would you say for caisson as
well oh sure eh if you want to
know
[Music]
i will speak a little more slowly and
clearly it's fine okay thank you
and now just translate what ksan says
leave it to me anyway that was the herb
shop
the herb shop yes you can find the links
to the playlist for soundcloud and
youtube uh in the description
of the video so please look please look
there
yay wonderful um and if you just look up
uh the herb shop remix
with the hashtag you should be able to
find it
number two this this is a really intense
one
let's go
[Music]
i feel like i'm about to play guilty
gear i'm so excited
yeah calliope guilty gear theme or
something
i love it's amazing
[Music]
up
we got this
[Music]
so much more
amazing is
yes
really i mean you know this method
um
[Music]
uh usually this uh turbo song
the turbo sun usually makes uh eurobeat
songs
[Music]
something else yeah
yes this is very neat i love it it
reminded me of um
of yeah guilty gear i would say because
it's one of my favorite games i love
i love that game especially for the ost
so that was awesome
i loved it and it felt intense and the
production
quality was very very good very high
everything that the tempo
was in sync and it sounded good uh
together
my vocals somehow sounded good on a
completely different genre
that's amazing amazing amazing i must
agree
yes yes
thank you very much for your wonderful
entry yeah it's fantastic
now the next entry is
someone that i think is so cute so cute
oh i can't wait to show you her entry oh
i love it
it's full of positive vibes my exact
opposite of my song
from me so let's check it out okay here
we go
next entry
[Music]
first i have to be gangster
watch this watch this is so cute
[Music]
hardcore [\h__\h] ass
high five i miss you
[Music]
my face
okay
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
she did a really good job at like
battling between cute
and cool style but the balance wasn't
ruined because she makes those two
styles and the range quality was really
top-notch
as well as the video and her voice is
really really adorable
yes the flow was really nice and and
when she
switched from being cute and cool it
wasn't uh like jarring or shocking it
was good it it flowed well
yeah it was amazing i love it anyway
daisuki
yeah i know that's interesting i never i
never heard of her before i want to
check her out now
yeah me too everyone everyone check her
out she's so cute
cute voice and hard worker so please
check it out
[Music]
next next another very strong
very strong competitor ah yes
all right here we go with no context
let's watch
and listen well here we go
uh-uh
[Music]
is
do me a favor
[Music]
on your keyboard go ahead and be slow by
the way
[Music]
is
i didn't want to talk actually i didn't
want to talk because i was so
i was so invested in the track i was
like why do i say this is just so good i
just feel like jamming out right
so interesting
you know
they put in a lot of different sounds
made it super super cool
but even though there were so many
different uh kinds of sounds it did not
like ruin anything
it did not like it it harmonized well
with each other
yes yeah definitely it all blended very
well it was nice
really amazing it it it's really and
that's hard to do that is very hard
it's very hard to beat he's in the chat
yes he is in the chat
welcome welcome and congratulations
welcome welcome and thank you always for
your support
but and the amazing amazing remix
yeah that's that's something you need to
be really highly skilled
to do that you can't just pull that off
by doing whatever
sounds so original yeah like something
completely different that you would
never expect if you hear the original
absolutely and that's what i was looking
for uh for this competition
i chose uh some very original ones right
because there are so many wonderful
artists that that make great music
but in this kind of competition i'm
looking for
some a little bit of originality right
yeah
yeah ones that are different from each
other so yeah anyway
very very good amazing amazing
now oh lights out in just a moment the
next one what's next let's see
uh i need to do that one last um okay so
the next
is um i'm just not gonna say i'm just
not gonna say anything
uh you'll you'll see here we go
[Music]
already
oh party
[Music]
i'm jamming
oh man i want to go running
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my gosh i can't i can't take it i
can't take it
[Music]
[Applause]
that is some top notch wow oh my gosh oh
man it was yeah like a roller coaster
get the ghost
that was fun i couldn't help but dance i
want to dance yeah
that lifts your mood up so so much jeez
fantastic i i have nothing to say except
just
amazing
one
[Music]
me too that was so much fun wow
seriously so amazing oh i need to take a
deep breath
oh i'm i am so excited to listen to that
again later
on
next is another amazing um
female vocalist entrant um and hurt the
vibes
the vibes are so
so different right from mine
um again cute style yes
you'll see you'll see cute cute but also
you'll see here we go lights out check
it
trigger seizures nice be careful
don't watch if you can't do the flashing
lights guys
it's so different from mine but i like
it very dark
[Music]
of
oh
[Music]
foreign
is
okay listen it's hard for me to
listen to a lot of how do i say this
nicely
some kinds of rap are it's hard for me
to listen because i'm really
i really zone in on the lyrics a lot and
the lyrical word play
word play that kind of thing so it's
hard to impress me with that kind of
stuff but in the second verse
when she brought out her original lyrics
i was kind of like oh okay
okay you thought about this you you
thought right
ma like yoku kangai you really thought
hard about these lyrics
she makes it herself which of course
gets big
[Music]
her voice was really nice to listen to
and the harmonies she
fought off really well done they really
were um harmonizing and mixing was also
really good so everything was top-notch
yeah she really paid attention to the
the feeling of the music the feeling
you know uh yeah i was impressed so [\h__\h]
bye-bye
very good different wrapping style from
yours cali
yeah yeah but it made everything so
mysterious
i liked it i like that it's different
from me because
it makes the world interesting right
with many different sounds
life is interesting right so i'm happy i
think it's wonderful
there's so many kinds of atmospheres in
these
thank remixes that's right thank you
very much for your entry
now let's go to the next entry without a
moment of delay here we go
it's all next
[Music]
i actually um this is the first one that
i went back and listened to a second
time
[Music]
no one's gonna buy this [\h__\h] i believe
crazy i love that
[Music]
you'll dance anyways
attention to the melody
[Music]
like i said i really you guys should go
check it out till the end because i
i was listening last night and i was
just like yeah
the the melody it's so melodious and
they really put a lot of care into the
sound the feeling of the sound and how
the melody interacts with the sound
it's so good i love it amazing
[Music]
yeah this was amazing the original song
compared to this remix turned out to be
a completely
completely different key or chord so it
turned out to be something
like so different from the original yeah
it was very
very very different completely different
something new and fresh
yeah i love that i love that so much
when it's just something completely new
yeah fantastic i love that yeah thank
you
and it's
i guess so maybe someday i can sing in
almayope yeah
i hope fingers crossed okay
well punch punch patch and great job and
good luck in the contest
[\h__\h] yay going on to the next one
without even a moment delay oysha here
we go
this is this is my personal one of my
personal favorites
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] i
[Music]
oh
that's my favorite part
[Music]
so with this one i thought i thought it
was good
right in the beginning i thought it was
good but
then the hook with the vocal chop like
that's what that's what made it five
star for me i like to say
yeah yeah that was just wow
amazing amazing damn mad respect for
vocal chopping skills
right there excellent gunshots
[Music]
heard the first drop he was still like
maybe not completely
impressed not completely sold on it but
then kelly tells him to
listen to the second draft definitely he
has to
and when he listened to it ah he heard
those chops
yeah and he immediately fell in love
with it he was immediately sold after
that second drop especially
yeah i felt like i personally meet kiara
i felt like i was in a party
a party right party
yeah yeah it was really quite amazing i
must say
so big ups and well done thank you so
much for your entry it was so cool
yay all right oh boy
i'm excited for this one here we go
[Music]
it is
is
[Music]
oh he started original lyrics too right
yes of course they're all original rep
amazing amazing so this song was i think
it's a fan favorite
right everyone in chat was like ah yes
boogie
yeah a fan favorite um phrase rap is
just
top top tier and i i all of you know i
am a long time
uh fan of japanese rap right so i i
listen to a lot of japanese rep
and so in the beginning um it was easy
to impress me but now not so much
right um he is psycho psycho
amazing fantastic thank you so much
and that's that's
[Music]
was very funny and the rap was really
excellent very
entertaining yeah it was great
it was amazing well done well done and
they submitted very early too they
they made it very quick they did good
work very fast good job on that
punch clutch nice well done really good
rap
they work hard i think hard workers
good job thank you nice to see nice in
that
[\h__\h] thank you very much boogie box may
we meet someday
in the underworld and they're also from
the underworld
probably not no but they're undead right
so that means i have to kill them at
some point probably i don't really like
i don't really like things that
listen death sensei says dead things
should stay dead okay don't come back to
life
no no no no no no no no but
but i like them i like them very much so
it's okay
it's okay they're special they're
special so it's fine let's be friends
let's be friends
without any hesitation let's go
oh this this one has some really nice
vibes listen
it's a house mix
oh yeah get ready to bob your head again
here we go
i want to drive through the city
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh man i love that i love that yeah yeah
i don't know i love it it's so good
maybe like a pluck or something i'm
it was so good i was really impressed
because i
always i i pay attention to how everyone
handles the one part hold on a sec
deadbeats listen up it's what you want
me coming in the night for ya
that part that part is always kind of
sometimes at that part
it can be off tempo right sometimes that
happens
it it it gets this time was good this
was good this mix was good but i pay
attention
and he handled it very well the track
um it like fit it fits with that
change that change that happens right
there it fit well
it was nice good job i pay attention i
love that
i look at the details
he was surprised because he didn't
expect such a mellow feeling
yeah yeah driving i want to drive
through a city with
lights everywhere beautiful lights
[Music]
was amazing really amazing well done
fudge pudge watch amazing thank you very
much for your wonderful entry
next up let's see oh a very interesting
one
this one's definitely a little different
from all of the other ones so please
enjoy here we go
[Music]
[\h__\h] it ah [\h__\h] it oh
cycle [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[Music]
perfect
it's a completely different sound
[Music]
nice that was cool
super cool right i think so yeah i think
it's the same person
wow and very very well very well done
very well done that takes a lot of
effort right you have to play the song
four times four times you probably
played mine in four times
yeah probably right more like ten times
or twenty or five million
five million right well anyway um
i can't play instruments um except oh
i can rap you can totally play
instruments hold on a minute
the instruments of hell
[Music]
wow
no wait hold on i don't know how to play
the harmonica
this is easy this is hard anyway
um yeah that's that's all that i can
play but anyway
i have so much respect right respect
for people who play instruments yeah
amazing me too also kind of playing
i can't imagine and if it really is one
one dude
like playing those four different
instruments holy [\h__\h]
but it might not be needs to do some
research but seriously amazing
wow
there's
hey every single instrument that was
played here
was really really highly skilled very
skilled and the reharmonizing
he would usually probably not come up
with a harmony like that
and so he was very moved by that it was
so different
i love that wonderful nice job good job
good job thank you thank you for your
entry yay
all right we have three more we know
four more
well this is i like this guy's name but
here we go
the vibes pay attention to the vibes
on please pay attention to these vibes
don't sleep on them
[Music]
believe another super bad apartment
[Applause]
is
[Music]
ah
special guest based wow
that was wow nice
i'm impressed he really like like built
it up right
and like got got me wanting to listen to
it i wanted to hear more
and he the build-up was good right and
the drop was just
oh amazing and it's hard to tell
right um from here just from listening
to my video i guess because i took the
video
from youtube right so the audio quality
it's probably better on youtube right
than from my downloaded video but the
mixing and sound design and production
quality is very high
very high so go listen to it please
[Music]
wow
and the sound making was very very cool
very impressive
but the drop made it even better yes uh
he says
we're very very cool yeah absolutely
fantastic dope [\h__\h] bro yes
i'm dope [\h__\h] i'll say i personally i
don't listen to this kind of music
at all but it's really impressive really
cool it gives me like the chills
yeah it kind of scares me yeah
absolutely
fantastic stuff wow amazing um by the
way everyone
just so you know um ato that later i
will post the
names the names of the top 15 names of
the songs
uh so that you can go listen to them
yeah
fire super lit dope bro
ah that was a big surprise big surprise
but i love it
yes well done amazing thank you very
much
the wonderful entry thank you thank you
three more
yes that's right next up now this one
this one caught my attention kind of in
the middle i was listening to it and in
the middle i was like oh that's good
and then i went back and listened to it
again i was like okay this is really
good one second if i
when i imagine you callie listening to
800 goddamn
songs no k has helped me so much how can
i even pay attention to it i don't know
ah they both listened of course you
switched in between probably but
oh my god that's like so we talked a lot
that you also invested in all of this
listening wow
yeah we went through all of them um
yeah and listen to like listen when you
have 800
you listen to as much as you can but we
listened for a while um
we listened to all of them i listened i
did listen to all of them
yeah let's see what you got yup well
anyway this one
this one is fun so let's check it out
here we go
it's fun you'll see
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] i believe
a
[Music]
still the killer better your dreams so
much
[Music]
crazy
what
[Music]
hey
if it's that speed if it's that slow
then i can also wrap it right
you know what really impressed me about
the slowness though
is that sometimes when
when people slow down my vocals it's
distorted
right like it sounds kind of like it
sounds like it's stretched out but this
time
this time he did a great job right of
really
it didn't sound stretched out everything
was
was the tempo was good and the vocals
didn't sound
ruined or anything it was great it was
great wonderful and the drop was so sick
damn really fantastic
[Music]
wow yeah he he's kind of
lost for words because it was so amazing
but
he really liked the part that uh the
fact that they mixed in some like
japanese style
sounds yeah it was very impressive but
he's like lost for words yeah
yeah i really i really love that i love
that the japanese
uh sound is very i'm gonna i'm gonna
practice
your this song this rap with this slow
motion version
good yeah and i think i can learn it if
it's this slow i can learn it
perfect perfect yes someday by all means
by all means cover myself
if you want if you really want to okay
do your best now next um
let's see next up we have two more left
oh no and i wanted to end no right
the next one is yet another one with a
completely can you send me all 800 songs
yeah we'll send you the list no problem
all right here we go let's check it out
[Music]
you're going crazy over there
[Applause]
[Music]
those horns are so good
so much details
[Music]
yeah so much attention to detail detail
right
but it wasn't too much right they didn't
yaris
no no it was perfect perfect with the
detail nice job
[Music]
he found it very funny that they were
able to manage to keep the whole
atmosphere
throughout the song because the original
uh has like a really spooky harmony but
in this case they made something low-fi
out of it so that's how they
were able to keep the the yeah the
atmosphere in something really cute and
fun and poppy
yeah yeah it was really well done oh my
god amazing
i think out of the i mean i think
there's one more song right but i think
out of these 15
this might be my your favorite because i
just feel like fun
fun vibes right so i mean the other ones
are really cool too but i guess this is
just by my
personal preference cool it really was a
lot of fun i was like very
going to my to the most extent
of my uh you know right and left
energetic and bubbly and cute yeah yeah
well
it's like that white square yes
let me explain set to mishmas so this
last song
um i want to share with you but um i'm
worried
because the mv um
has maybe copyright material
it's a little dangerous the mv that they
made it's a little um
i don't know i don't know what's going
to happen so um
you'll see uh just for now um but i
recommend you go watch it afterwards so
anyway
this last one um i want to say a message
first to everyone
um for those of you who didn't make it
into the top 15 there's still a chance
you have a chance because um like i said
before
the my standby screen i'm going to play
your remixes i don't want
so many amazing remixes to not be seen
by the world
so please don't feel hopeless or
anything uh i love all of you
i really do i love you thank you daisuki
it's okay and
good work you are you are mr tired or
mistired
you are tired person most honorable
tired one
good job let's go to some of this okay
and um
i did i listened to all of them and i
love all of them even the troll ones you
all have talent you do
the troll
um but please i wanted to tell a little
story
mr k's listen to one one troll entry
um and his eardrums his eardrums they
died
i didn't have to listen to it
yes so let's all thank mr case for his
honorable sacrifice thank you
thank you thank you giving us your
eardrums thank you
yeah some of you in chat were there nice
yeah yeah
anyway let's listen to this last one i
think it's super cool and i was really
impressed
i'm not usually very impressed by these
kinds of songs but this was very good
so let's give it a listen here we go
here lies the track for which we are
about
to kill may it repent for its soul
let us show them calliope how it's done
grim reaper's rappers coming for the
death peters never get away cleaner soul
leaders with the size goliath be looking
nice i'm
[Music]
i'll see you later battle any master
debater on who is the greater goliath
well a trainer to make the paper and rap
yo now these animators getting jealous
over cash flow
i'll bring you through the light when
you're about to take a nail with my desk
no writing welcome to your health if you
want to try to fight me
you should save yourself so you don't
need a white knight purple soul to sell
you'll be living the only deal trying to
run away can you tell we'll be getting a
million different residents
[Music]
we're not asking for what's the favorite
is
you'll dance anyway cause it's human
nature
[Music]
[Applause]
i know right go listen to it it's
[\h__\h] amazing is that the one where
you said that he's a better rapper than
you hey
don't tell anyone i said that don't tell
don't tell anyone i said that no listen
no you're a best rapper
i don't often conceive like that don't
tell anyone
no i mean listen this is really i pay a
lot of attention to lyrics
right and that kind of lyrical very much
like thinking about
thinking about um your lyrics like he
thought so
much he really sat down with the pen and
was like i'm gonna make this clever
it reminded me of some of my favorites
like for example eminem
or even even dell to be honest like i
was like
hell yeah i don't know just lyrically i
love lyrical rappers and he's
he did a great job he fought words yes
yes
it was a very high level rapper ranger
he has that sound that i like my taste
my taste
[Music]
i kind of do like you know like a little
like what is it not really higher
pitched but like
mid-tone and like how do i explain like
really punchy flow
and um and really well thought out
lyrics uh just
and also i want to say you you wrapped
your rap went so well with the track too
the backing track was so intense and
just
yeah it really the two of them together
um
were just a psychonaut combination
track arrangement was uh very it's
amazing
very cool big ups to you as well my dude
thank you so much both of you for
entering it was two people a team
a team team entering two people
yeah it's okay no no no uh track maker
and
wrapper so yeah fantastic job
yay good stuff amazing with that um
i guess no not over no yeah it's over
it's over
yeah i mean not yay but yay but no yeah
it's sad
[Music]
but so do you mean that out of these 15
yes there might be first or second piece
yes that's right two out of these will
be chosen
yes oh my god that's right who could it
be i wonder we'll get the results soon
but
for those of you who didn't make it like
i said you have a chance
and and not only will i share your song
i'll talk about it too uh it's not like
i'm just like hey check this guy out
anyway
[\h__\h] done with that onto the next
[\h__\h] no no no no i will talk about your
song
so yeah you have a chance and there are
so many amazing entries
thank you very much everyone i
i didn't think that this would happen
i can't believe did you think you would
get 800 entries
no i thought i'd get like 200. 200 tops
200 maybe
so when when kay said oh my gosh we have
entries i was like no way 100. amazing
amazing and now it's like yeah 800.
what that's nuts man
congratulations callie on your success
thank you
congratulations to you as well thank you
kids as well for everything
you two made an amazing song and
everyone loved it so much that they just
had to make five million remixes out of
it
yeah it really shows how how good the
song is and how skilled both of you are
thank you so much i wanted to choose
everyone even now i'm so frustrated
what's the word what is the word i'm
frustrated
why i want everyone to win because so
many
talented people you are so talented
my deadbeats are the greatest
amazing amazing well i guess i guess
that's all
that's all everyone that's that's it
as well kiara thank you so much thank
you so much
professional live translator it's my new
job
but you did so well i mean you were
amazing oh thank you thank you i'm just
glad i could help you somewhere because
you always helped me so much
i love you well i mean what's the saying
eye for eye for an
eye eye for an eye tooth for a tooth i
want to help you you help me i help you
it's like that
okay if you take my advice anyway
anyway i guess
[Music]
you're coming soon i anticipated
that's all so anyway everyone thank you
so much to everyone who entered
thank you to my guests
[Music]
and he know this because he also streams
sometimes
and he noticed that many japanese
listeners also really enjoyed the song
and this whole contest this whole event
and so really having so many people all
over the world enjoyed together
made him feel very moved very very happy
and he noticed that
the power of music is just so strong
and so so yeah i don't i don't i can't
i can't think of enough but um yeah he
felt that everyone
even though the original song was
already so good of course
but everyone made this song into
something even better so he wants to
really
thank everyone from his height yes
[Music]
all are very thankful to all of you
thank you so much everyone hi
and well done let's go to some of this
and with that i'm going to end with my
kazoo
okay oh hold him what kind of tune
should i end with
[Music]
it's me i'm the winner of my contest see
you all later thank you so much for
coming bye-bye
yeah i can't i'm not moving my hands but
i'm i'm waving i'm waving just believe
me i'm waving to you goodbye
yeah he says is moving too he's not
dabbing forever
it's different it's constant dab state
that's right
bye everyone see ya goodbye see ya
peace out always take a [\h__\h] break
i don't feel like it here we go
did this get there we go you guys can
end with this anyway
[Laughter]
bye guys peace
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[Music]
my