[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
i don't wanna
um
[Music]
no
um
[Music]
hello
everybody
good
[Music]
ah
evening
good evening
i i hear vtmo the medium is really okay
right the btm is okay right
sometimes it's not
okay
but
good evening
good evening i think i need to like move
into that
so i can like going up
yes
good evening so today i'm gonna solo i'm
gonna doing a solo uh so
how's my recovery my recovery is
[Music]
i can do solo now
so
i'm gonna like check it's the beginning
okay
it's the medium okay
museum okay nice
nice
okay
i'm supposed to be going back to my team
uh
[Laughter]
huh
why
[Music]
boys recorded
what do you mean
thank you
thank you so much
oh
this one
[Laughter]
i'm gonna cook in here
up
insert a cassette
and play
except accidentally record audio with
left mouse right mouse to record new
audio
so i can i can use this cassette
i can use this
yeah
what should i record i want to record
where it's very spoken by please
hmm
i just realized no
polka sorry
have it
i used to be
people like telling me
[Laughter]
it's a habit where people like you tell
you me my my my koha is my senpai i just
like
i'm used to it
i have two now
okay
i'm gonna put it randomly
hmm
[Music]
want to move it
hmm
i just realized i have lots of machine
gun meshing
i have this
rocket launcher and the rocket but i
need to get a lot of scraps so
that's what we're gonna do it now
oh the ammo is
oh this
[Music]
foreign
i want to make a fishing spot
first i actually forgot how to make it
is it in
here press it on
unreal
crafting
others
so
the source
here
i want to make a lot of survival fish
traps so
i'm gonna fishing for scraps
i want to like fishing for scraps so i'm
gonna make a lot of a lot of survival
fish straps
um
we need a lot of wood and clothes i have
a bunch of clothes
and wood stripes
hmm
i need to find a lot of a lot of stone
i need to find lots of stone i just
realized
i will do it later real quick
so
no i don't have a jackhammer and
chainsaw yet
i'm gonna buy it later
donations thank you
thank you
just a good one
here
i'm gonna i'm gonna put
the passage
five seconds
yeah i do need to bring rifle ammo i
don't need this
my my weapon is only thompson my thumbs
only my thompson doesn't need to use a
revel
why thompson doesn't use a ripple why
they use just like a pistol
baseball pistol
thank
okay
how
yeah thompson doesn't use
it
sorry
i'm shocked
but thank you
oh well
where is
the wood
i want the one that already down
ah there you go
[Music]
i will i will buy
i will buy a new one
what's this
this is a celery
she's got ribble
that is
hello
we gotta get a lot of stone and wood and
after that we will find another
sorry we need a lot of food too
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
you know
so
donations thank you
and
i feel like the graphics a little bit
bug in my place i don't know
i feel like so
like there's a bug or something
put him in container chamber
good idea good idea
hey who's place is that
there's someone living in there
that's new
okay
now i'm going my last
[Music]
um
just need a medal now
[Music]
i'm gonna cook them all
by waiting
before the night comes
fighting for the nights
they come
i don't want to change it
uh
night i become a chef
yeah i want to go to
i'm i'm dressed as hello summer i'm
dressed for hello summer look at me i'm
using this coconut
already
nice right
nice
coconuts bra that i'm using now with the
little uh
skirt that from the tree
it's the coconut
outfit i'm using now
i hope it's good for solo summer
cause i don't have bikinis don't have
bikinis i
changed to coconut you suck up the nut
become coconut bikini
thank you aloha mona aloha
okay
here we go
yay
my
so
eel
[Music]
need to dream though
i'm gonna drink
i'm going here
going here
[Music]
to like going in
it's like a free loot
isn't it
[Music]
why you can only make one
cannot make it side by side
[Music]
hey can i take it
um
same
this is water
and one i want food i want food i want
food
okay
in my foot
you
foreign
okay
now
i need to get the baby
[Music]
baby
bye
my
[Music]
um
there is like someone who wants to join
me
as well
eh
i don't wanna say it
let you guess it
this is better surprise
[Music]
we need this
i need a lot of
you pickles
know where can i buy a pickle
i won this video
as we chilling
[Music]
hmm
i think i make a lot
i think you'll make a lot
but i i only have like few
please
so
[Music]
now what
and we wait
wait
we can use
me
[Music]
i can't i can go right
i mean i can just go right
and just like
leave them right
yeah okay
now
i'm going
back
i think i need to mix another shotgun
right
click on ammo
it's really good for like this
i like that one
[Music]
metal fragment and gunpowder okay
what do you even have
one powder
well
we can we can make one
you can make one
[Music]
all right
now what do we say about the one bite
oh yeah
so far right away
didn't
um
charcoal
we're making a gunpowder
i don't think it's metal
donation thank you
all right
i don't catch a stream when i miss you
so much i me shoot you
how's your day
i thought we got a lot
lots lots lots
[Music]
and don't have enough support
you have
so for yes you have okay i'm gonna
borrow which i mean borrow is for me
it's a senpai it's okay
oh yes it's okay mona you can take it
whatever you want this is our
our place yeah
yeah you can take whatever you want
moona
oh thank you thank you so much kyla
uh do you have another silver
oh you can shake it probably i have but
i forgot
so
let me take one by one
oh it looks like i ran out of sofa i'm
gonna make
make it for
you yes
donation thank you
thank you
it's batman my dream uni reject me
could i please have a case
uh your uni uh the universe is that that
you want to go is rejecting you if
that's so don't give up
that's mean
um
got my my uh
[Music]
might tell you it's not your destiny
you can try again if you if you want to
try again
uh you can try again later uh maybe
next year or you can you can move to
another university
it's up to you
[Music]
me
okay why should i kiss
why should i kiss
give me a reason to kiss
speeds to 1
000 thank you
wait 100 and 1 000 what's
serato strategy
super chat thank you
androids
oh is that sound
um
what's he missing
punch
[Music]
64. thank you
64.
ammo
wow
not a lot
[Music]
foreign
thank you so much
i will read it later
i heard like like donation thank you and
then i i accidentally
i didn't see it
hi
now we need to go to this place
um
i think it's around here
[Music]
it's one of my favorite
little
[Music]
it's one of my favorite places
hey this is neo this
house is this
who house is this this is new
this is new but it's not
new
wow
[Music]
i don't have i don't have a horse i
my horse died
because
because i didn't feed him
[Music]
mm
i'm sorry
well there's a lot of
[Music]
nine
nine donation thank you
don't worry i'm gonna keep on trying to
get in uni i'm i'm spending my
application email good luck
[Music]
let's remind me the old days
where i
i go to a lot a lot lots of place
and go to a lot of a lot of university
to like you know
yes
nice
it's really hot
well i don't know
is it hard
i think most most of the university that
i went that i tried to went
i i got in but i didn't choose it
most of the
university
i
want to like it's really nice university
it's really nice university and
i
i got i got like rank three
it's the international
international one
international university
i got i got like uh i got like rank 3 uh
for the whole
application
and
but i didn't take it because because my
mom said it's too far away
i'm really mad about it at that time
donations thank you
oh
yeah
it's like that
did i just miss another donation
i think i did
your mom the right choice if only you're
going abroad for university we can't see
you as muna now
perhaps
might be
but might be not
but it might be not probably i'm still
as i am right now
because
those university it's have the same
um
same same not really the same it's not
even
it's just the changes
i'm not gonna be a designer
i don't think that i'm gonna be a
designer
that's that's the only one problem
i still love singing um i i still love
singing i start singing i start singing
since i was in the
um
i think
primary school since i'm on my primary
school so i think that might be still
possible
to join
wow i have a lot
i don't know what
[Laughter]
no i don't i don't have a plan to get
another degree
no
it's not it's like it's not like i don't
like school it's just like i just want
to focus on what i am right now like
i still have another things to learn
so i don't think i want to learn the
same things i want to learn another
things
[Music]
okay
hey well well i have lots of it so i
think
i'm gonna give it to her
i'm gonna feel like pilots
i want to i want to like
maybe learn
language
i want to focus on
idol
hey music
so
i i don't want to like continue my
degree
i want to learn other things
[Music]
i want to learn how to make an actual
music
[Music]
i think if
i think if i i really want to
i think if i really want to
[Music]
have
you know college thing again
probably rather than continue to make um
i think
what is possible
i think i want to like go to the music
theory or something
mr terry
manchester yeah
rather than magister i want to like
getting another
but focusing on music
[Music]
donations thank you
i'm happy to meet you here my your life
and my darkest day
actually
no
i'm not like you are
like
without you guys
i can't be this bright
as a fact
and
hey i haven't i haven't really tried to
kill this one
what it tastes like
thank you
oh it's
oh it's like this it's just like a
chicken
it's like the chicken
whenever we're in the dark i like being
on
uh kyla's house
yeah i don't think that oh
i see this
okay
[Music]
better
then what's it oh it's a wolf oh this
one is wool okay
okay
i think it's time to clean this mess
a lot of things to clean wire like this
[Music]
oh ella
i feel like a mother who just like you
know cleaning off my
my kids
stuff
come on
[Music]
well you are now i'm not
foreign
what i heard it's like a school
like a high school or something
um
should i put it
thank you
unless you've been to candy mountain yet
it's a line of happiness with joy and
joyness i even get so mad at you no i
haven't what was that is that even
a thing
oh
[Music]
i think it's like playing this one
good morning
[Music]
all right
sun is nice
it's already morning it's a really
morning
it's morning already
helicopter
me
all right we can first kill
[Music]
yeah i want to go this way
this way
hmm
yeah
yeah yeah
thank you nice
i'm gonna make sure that i am
free
[Music]
so i'm gonna go back to our place or
listen here
you can find scrap as well yeah
[Music]
so
no nails on
[Music]
nothing
can we like this one recycle this one
i haven't really
do we recycle it
i should have put it on the car
will put it on the car
[Music]
it's not great
no
[Music]
do
and where is my scrap over
here um
didn't i have a composer or something
no
too tarp
and wood i got i got tarp somewhere
i can tell it's not
you don't need much of it right
isn't it
uh composter for this
no
[Music]
is
i'm gonna
get my scrap
my
wrap i need i need to buy
[Music]
read the lie
oh my scrub is already there
my scrap is already there okay
yeah
okay
was this a shop
a shop
what shop is that
[Music]
uh
is
[Music]
okay
it's so rare oh wait do you guys know
where can i
walk a horse
because i i don't know where is it like
outpost or mining
or or where
[Music]
when it has two different voices
what do you mean
um you mean like my talking voice and
then my singing voice then yeah i
probably can say yeah
yeah how like a different i i don't know
how is that possible
yeah
oh we go let's go let's go let's go what
is this
i still like want to know what is this
shop thingy
look at that a horse
it's a really nice house it's a really
nice house
but what is this
[Music]
nothing
i'm gonna go here
oh it's a player shop
okay
[Music]
goblin voice when she talking lady clean
voice when she's singing like probably
goblin voice
dolphin voice really
really
my voice looks like a goblin voice
uh uh
[Music]
if i talking like this if it sounds
still it'll still sound like a goblin
voice
i don't want being called goblin or
something really
and where should we go
[Music]
wait
i
uh
i remember that
oh yeah this one
not in this one
i better go to this
online shop
oh we can we can buy
huh
all right
let's put markets
put more cats but
i want this one donations thank you
this is jack hammer
my own jackhammer
and then
um
[Music]
this one
else i have a small throat right
oh this is harrowing
this is hairy it's not
i need to get
shot
super chat thank you
yeah we can buy them directly on a mess
and something i think
just take a delivery free
it's like a delivery fee okay um
literally
okay
food market
what makes sense i'm doing do i need to
accept
i need a lot of pickles though
thank you
and then
where where should we go again uh for
the fishing
but it's the stop no
grab exchange no
i have no idea where it is
should we do a class
uh
wait
okay
[Music]
has this fishing spot where
where is it
oh you're a lumberjack
[Music]
are you dough
where is it huh
this one
produced extinct
i'm gonna go there
[Music]
okay
oh my going this way
maybe that way
i might go this way
up here
weapons
huh
[Music]
what weapon what kind of open it
hmm
okay
near windmill
it should be in here right
oh here
so corn
okay okay so corn
cloth
fertilizer
small truths okay
i have this
pairing
hairy
okay now i got it um probably i'm gonna
go into
this
with this water bucket
like
some mulch
um
you guys know where i can get
a horse
because i need to
go for like a lot of place
where is it
branch
the one from someone awards
that's not fair
i'm going back
yeah i'm cosplaying as kyla right now
let's pretend that
yep
i didn't get a lot of porn actually
what
wait a minute
so
you guys you guys know right that i
just
buy something on delivery
where can i get it where
[Music]
where can i
take my delivery item
oh this
[Music]
okay let's get into it
foreign
okay
[\h__\h]
[Music]
nice
hmm
that's so weird using this one
that's a nice one
is this one needed
for phillip workbench okay
okay
[Music]
when i first don't fall
the guys told me that
luna's voice is
what like
like what
okay
[Music]
thank you
hmm
i'm going back
i'm gonna take my
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
do
yep
[Music]
foreign
low grade
oh great flunia
because
[Music]
we
okay okay
[Music]
you know
me
[Music]
on
so
foreign
mercy
[Music]
foreign
i know
[Music]
donations thank you
foreign
[Music]
um
rainey
mia
[Music]
foreign
ah
[Music]
foreign
amy
[Laughter]
me
okay
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
he's like the one who told her is
youngest child
maybe
i haven't fall i haven't found any horse
where can i find a horse i want a horse
i want a horse
[Music]
it's been like a couple of days i play
ross but haven't found any horse
mashina
first vashina mahashima
anything
yes
is
um
my
amalus
thank you
[Music]
there's
okay
which place is this
is
i see
do you guys know where is
um
mommy
booming place
i think i want to put like a like a
voice writing recorder prank to muy may
play
i wonder where it is
i don't even know where's we'll look you
stand by place
i think it'll be great if i look like
hmm
what kind of songs i report
okay
my love
oh
good idea
my evil mouth
i think
evila
i know
i'm gonna do this though
okay
thank you
ugh
[Music]
yeah
going back
um
yep
[Music]
maurice
okay
i'm gonna put it in here for a while
thank you
keep
[Music]
i think most of them is
stone
[Music]
yeah
nice
i kept making like open clothes like
this in case that super chat thank you
i want to
you know
[Music]
upgrade
the upper side
so
yeah
i was making it later
[Music]
most of them
it's just most of them is good
we're going to build skyscraper
eventually
perhaps
no i need a lot of scraps
i'm gonna put it in here
if kyle is needed
she know where to go
right nowhere to go
[Music]
i'm gonna take it in here
put it
here
[Music]
okay
right
[Music]
now where we want to go is
i want to go to this place
around
here
i get the corn
to get the corns
yeah hopefully we'll find
a horse
hey
[Music]
why you want corn i want to sell it
i want to sell it
[Music]
and maybe i need to like making
i think it was better if i made
some
tests in here
later
[Music]
first car spread
donations
[Music]
train
hopefully no one say uh corn juicy when
they see the corn one
you
already already
glowed my little fragment low gradual a
word full
ease
animal fat and cloth
animal fat
and
i need to make a lot slot of it
guru made announced this morning with
corn what happened with corn
i like corn
don't you like corn
and we are killing each other and here's
monaca actually going about our day in
wrestling just losing with a what a
great day to be alive
they really play
rust
i'm not really playing rust
it feels like like a living simulator as
long as i leave
that's good
more like
that i'm sorry
but i really like chilling over killing
i know that's not how to play this game
but that's how i enjoy it
donations thank you
i look like lame since but online
which i like
hey
didn't she meet oh all right she just
ah
donation thank you
rainey
[Music]
foreign
money
[Music]
foreign
donations thank you
[Music]
you're gonna shake have you look some
water already moon
i haven't
thank you for checking up
i'm gonna drink after this
where is it
nothing nothing no
i'm gonna
bring you up
okay
[Music]
well what is sewing kit for
i'm okay
are they still like like you know
talking about the horse
i don't know
but i don't have any food
[Music]
dang it
foreign
that is
i'm gonna get
i'm gonna get my
chainsaw again
if looking farm you won't make farm you
can use her farmer's information
uh where is it can you tell me where is
the farm is because i have no idea where
it is
yeah my chainsaw i need a lot of
me
foreign
[Music]
sorry
thank you
so
and that should be enough
[Music]
should i go to the lucky crate
yeah we're just like waiting for it
waiting
for winery
i want i need refinery too as well
but i'm so poor
okay
a refinery
a refinery is for the crude oil so it's
not for this
that makes sense now
oh yeah
look at that i'm making it
thank
you i want to eat something
i don't have a mixed table
anyway do you know that a couple of
hours ago i bought
a little toro round
but it's it's it's gray it's half a gray
skin it's not it's not blue one it's not
a purple one it's a gray one
and
and i have something in the bag
it's cute it's like
so small
it's a little little one i think i want
to buy it again
it's only 69
rupiah 69 000 rupiah
it's a good one right
well now why are indonesian woman so
powerful what's the secret what do you
mean powerful
what do you mean powerful
i just realized that i also have lots
that tell
me
um
what
me
anything like this
the secret is msg
you give msg
your woman will be
um
really really good at everything just
give msg to every food that you can find
[Music]
so um i put emma's in my coffee it will
taste good doesn't mean you are stupid
amazing in in a drink
i said food not drink
yo this woman is amazing i want to marry
her
does anyone's on eggnog
it's already late
super chat thank you
[Music]
and this is just like a magic just like
um
like
like a
listen um
like a portion like like um
like a medic potion
like a magic magic dust magic dash
[Music]
i put energy in my eyes no i cannot see
that's your fault
[Music]
did you know that this um
probably
the secret recipe of a crusty crab is
actually a crab
yeah
like
are you thinking secret formula
it's probably like a crab because the
crystal crab is just half the shape of
the
crap
a trap
right a crab trap
and
yeah
and there is like an episode where
i forgot
there is like a tear theory about that
no it's not the treasure chest
it's a crap
crap
so
that's why there are no other cracks
like mr crap
exactly
super chat thank you
we made luna all the best and how she
can play family with her favorite hollow
man bye
meet you
it's well in bikini bottom only pearl is
well where are the rest becoming free
i didn't know about that
i like crap
i love brad
i like crap very much
thank you
i want to get refinery
what is this low quality carburetor
okay
i'm still right
flamethrower
himself
you like any indian food
uh
i haven't really tasted indian food i
think
i think i haven't really tasted indian
food before
what is indian food
the name the name can you like
curry is indian i think it's japanese
i i think it's like japanese
maybe
it wasn't in
i see
india i see
oh i like kari
indonesia of curry too
roti prata i like roti prata rodi prata
is the best
i love roti prata
man
i want roti pop roti prata right now
my mother made a roti prata is really
good roti prata
my mother really good at making prada
especially paratha with blue light
that's the best thing i've ever eat
best food
[Music]
prata with with gulai
that's the best thing
[Music]
i am
got
[Music]
i think you gotta do something
man i'm so confused
do
[Music]
oh well
look at that moon it's red
just like what i am right now
how did you know that the moon is red
right now oh my god
nice
russ no
should i eat
or
bear
i'm gonna
spark
hey
super chat thank you
next month is my birthday it's happy
birthday to me happy birthday
for you for next month
it's funny
thanks mom but you're asking now
but okay
i'll give it
that is early but okay
donations thank you
thank you
let's
see someone box
our
skill right now is
put everything
while we're going
here
okay
i didn't have uma
i lost my donation thank you
hey for the stream when uh i need to do
deadlines once again please do your best
i can't give much but i'll be supporting
you what
thank you
i only like reading health
[Music]
for a sign what do you mean resign this
i can
i
wow i didn't know it's possible
i didn't know that's possible
okay
thank you
drop
and this one too
no this one cannot
[Music]
i haven't really been here
i want to see what's in here
i can just take ours with the crane how
oh there's recycling
this is for cycle middle pipe
this one too
eh laughs
okay
oh that one cannot
this guy
nothing is possible
can i do it
hey what's this
i'm gonna take this one first
can i can i
try
oh
left movement key
[Music]
so
can i
move on
can i walk
how to walk
please leah
i use w wsd but it's only like moving
like this
oh
hey that's hard
and then
eh
oh this is
[Music]
it doesn't need anything right
oh okay
okay let me let me try let me try let me
try let me try
how about this one
no
idea
why is so hard i just want to go
oh
bang
i just
um
oh okay
okay
ah
oh it's not moving
[Music]
oh
eh
[Music]
how many scrap
it's going to die only like that
[Music]
so
eh
i do
i know
one
i yo
why is so hard
now
up
okay okay
uh
okay
[Music]
come
on okay
yes
must
subscribe
[Music]
now
we still have this one
and this one
[Music]
that makes
three
and that one oh that's that's a lot but
i'm really bad at it
[Music]
so
right now
it's like i trade uh the
the fool
into a scrap
which is okay
but
i don't know
but i can i can take it home
will it respond another
will it respond another one
eh
where is it
and where where is
this one
[Music]
so
okay
we have another one
even go this way
the risk i'm just gonna use this one
this one
i'm gonna take it home
it's mine
[Music]
so
this is my horse now
oh i cannot go from this way
i think it seems
i
i think i can drive it now
we're gonna change it into scrap
thank you
nice one
i have to like
flicking [\h__\h]
okay
hey
yes
[Music]
where is it
oh there
thank you
okay
can i have like
two
uh
no
only one
ugh
donations thank you okay i says can you
give me a leave home
no
before i leave you home you're gonna
beat that head
dang it
come on
hey
okay
ah
wow
yes
[Music]
thank you
yeah
one more
and we go home
one last car
and we'll go home
with the crane
eh
hey
oh okay
it's a free real estate
[Music]
i'm gonna take it home
feels like i'm playing time's on
okay let's go back home
i don't know how to get back home
i think
we're stuck
so
okay
follow the way
oh
dang it
i got sand moss
[Music]
thank you
one
[Music]
i didn't read the whining
i didn't read that warning
i'm sorry
[Music]
nah
we're gonna
need a mushroom
[Music]
i think it's gonna be mine it'll mean
this will be cool whose house is this
whose house is this
it can still imagine you from your job
place
but i won't steal it so badly
[Music]
ah
that is so sad
zen lose
ah
okay
[Music]
but i prepared
i mean
[Music]
yeah you could have fun to use it near
home like showing off the kayak kayla i
have this and she was like
oh my god it's so cool imagine guys
imagine
now i cannot do that
[Music]
flying
hmm hmm
i do have lots
of items in my
[Music]
layer
thank you
[Music]
okay it is
time to go back i guess
[Music]
but you can bring car back home what do
you mean by that
[Music]
it's going back home
oh the repair car but i don't have the
items to repair
i think i want to keep it for later
raining tool appears by
what is that
well that is the car that's
buy or make them yeah i want to like
make them
to make it a really nice car
i haven't found any horse why
it's been a while i haven't found any
horse i run a horse
you're still caught from both i don't
want snow
hmm
uh
foreign
thank you
i'm a horse nate you don't even have to
feed me
so you want me to write here
you want to be right
i see
dump it
love it
um
wow i have like lunch
okay
[Music]
donations thank you
what
west or east
there is affection
there's like there is a fashion in here
i don't even know
i don't think i'm gonna go into war
[Music]
because
before before i think
i'll play ross again around maybe at 25
perhaps that's gonna be my last time
playing rush
and
maybe
after that
maybe after that um
i want to use all my scraps
to
get another things
you know
last time last time of the month
last time of the month
[Music]
because it's it's reset every month
right
so i'm gonna use the scrap to research
before the reset
[Music]
too hot
i think war for season 2 at 9 9 2022 is
that so
i heard bear
no horrors
um
to do it's like a lot of things to learn
i'm not logging routes every day
it's like
whenever whenever i log in ross there's
a couple of times i met
a pecora such or maybe a mikko senpai
he always
who was that
they always online it was like grinding
well i'm not using that
i'm not like them
you're addicted
they're just like an npc of the game you
know
whenever you find
yeah
did you know that the rust actually
a live brows actually have uh like a
rules
where you cannot
you cannot um
rate
people
or people house
if they are
offline
and
they also have rules if you want to rate
the person's
um
house if they they are offline
you have oh mixes table nice you have to
oust them first on this court
[Music]
it's not like i don't want to like
join
the end of the season too
[Music]
but there
probably
i cannot because i have other things to
do
that's why
um
oh your hair
already hey
someone leaving here
who is it
unicorns
[Music]
made it
ah
wait
it doesn't look like my house
[Music]
i forgot to bring the
oh anyway i'm gonna reveal it again
i need to get another one
we'll need to go in here again
[Music]
donations thank you
my house have a lot of resources and i'm
almost on when you can read it anytime
who
are you are you hollow life members
what i really like about this they
almost respond
so you don't have to worry
[Music]
that's why i like it
it's like a free real estate
[Music]
oh minnie porn
okay
this way
donation thank you
thank you
[Music]
i'm hallo and genwa nice to meet you i
see
but i think we are on different branch
so i don't think that i want to do it
because i only want uh to raise someone
with
polo not hallow
thank you
can i sell the pumpkin though
[Music]
hmm
sorry
i think the corn
over you
[Music]
don't blow
i can do this all day
they just like respond again
in
oh
[Music]
less
you god bless
us
from last
let's go back
perhaps i'm gonna make a house in here
second house perhaps i don't know
it's not even possible
[Music]
foreign
well there is no um
[Music]
i cannot make bed yet
foreign
[Music]
i haven't had the helicopter yet
don't yet
[Music]
and after this we're gonna see i um
hey why are you running
and what a surprise
you know the reason why
[Music]
there is no um
no horse
where are you when i need the most
the horse
i'm gonna go in here again
i don't want the muna surprise
wait running
[Music]
i hear a bear on my left
what's a really good thing is when you
hear the
bear
it's just like
you can really
hear the step and it's like don't don't
like that
you know
there's a telephone
[Music]
there's nothing a heart beating faster
not really
[Music]
i don't know
okay
um
should i do the mixing there
and then
okay
oh what else
and i'm gonna put it in here
we need this one we need this one
i'm keen also cannot put it in here
[Music]
i don't
so
[Music]
it feels like a harvest moon
i don't know where is this table
i don't know where's the stamina
actually
[Music]
yay
don't mind me
look at me i'm just like literally
someone who
will become a fisherman and then
perfect man
i'm gonna sell this material wow
okay well the other side i'm just gonna
become a farmer
what a peaceful day in ross
i mean after all
okay now we go
this is
i'm a passive player
this is not rose this is vlog game we're
4k i'm sorry i enjoy like this
i mean we need
we need to be a farmer
and in some place someone needs to eat
right someone needs to eat
survival doesn't need
oh i can't i can just go from here
living in a survival place doesn't need
to wear um
farm
if we can go in peace why not
why not
right
possible remember when you meet anya and
found her with an ass yeah me neither i
don't remember that
definitely not remember that at all
that's probably not me that's probably
yoshi
hey what's that
what's this
wow
thank you so much
lucky
lucky fireman
inviting zeta was right at least you
have an fps layer
let's say zeta and kyla is my bodyguard
they can they can literally kill someone
while i'm chilling
that's me
yes
can i make this do i want to make this
one too
like i want to sell something
yeah maybe i can make like a ropey
thingy
you know
hello
i'm here to sell things
hmm
hey let me see
i forgot
so
yeah proud of that kings we need to go
to the produce exchange
do you guys know where the produce
exchange is i
have no idea
it's it's supposed to be around there
that one right
this one
go to harvard skater horse
where is harvest
this is
stuff one is stuff
oh yeah
okay okay
time to sell team
bye
ah
that's not much but okay
at least we have like 76 crabs
donations thank you
okay i'll probably take your wife till
someone like it only in
hello
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know
i want
okay
oh
[Music]
cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
no gambler
is
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
oh i have a really nice
[Music]
donations thank you
i'm gonna run it
[Music]
wait
well let's have this one
i don't remember
oh yes
oh oh yeah yeah yeah
let's get the crate
just activate the crate
farm i want to see for the reference
you guys see it it's good
q8
q
g
oh
so far
[Music]
eight so far
okay
where should i find a horse
[Music]
dang it
i am
[Music]
a lot
foreign
[Music]
it
oh battery
[Music]
hey someone ready
someone already done it
[Music]
is that
it works
[Music]
your hands
me
lock your hands
up your head
[Music]
hmm
where is it
oh i'm using a thompson
[Music]
i'm gonna wear this one wait
it's nice outfit though
it's really nice outfit look at that
wow
look at a beautiful lady
look at that
[Music]
now we're going home
do
[Music]
okay
come on online now play with me
i still have uh
two hours
i'm gonna end this room probably at two
so yeah i still have like two
hours around that
come join
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
so chocolate but not actually choke
yourself
[Music]
accelerates it
machine gun machine gun
two of these is a machine gun
i literally have a lot
machine gun
let's open this and wonder
[Music]
so
i don't have a skull
i am
[Music]
do
i got a lot
[Music]
me
my sniper
[Music]
armor
oh
hey mom
[Music]
okay
you wanna discord
you need to discord i have a lot
a lot of things
i think i'm gonna put it in here
ah
[Music]
hmm
okay
know
[Music]
wow
like
[Music]
do
hmm
[Music]
i like you
metal chase wait where can i make the
metal just
workbench three
white bench tree
that's why you need to make it
uh
string
is
[Music]
the sun
[Laughter]
foreign
the different
this one here
carpet
think
[Music]
m
foreign
empty air
do
[Music]
i'm back
okay
i'm gonna get another scrap
[Music]
um
and go to junker
is
this this whole
uh
this whole week probably i'm gonna do a
lot of raws
hi
hello
[Music]
us
let's go
[Music]
all right
forgot
fertilizer
[Music]
and ring
huh
[Music]
i drink a lot
okay
[Music]
foreign
what's up
[Music]
did you visit the wiki farm not yet
ah
like me
[Music]
on
indeed
um
hey salaam
gift
[Music]
uh
guys
[Music]
is we're going to the hello route uh
amanda
[Laughter]
ah
spoiler
oh my god
it's allah
so
come on
okay
[Music]
oh there
unbelievable
it's home brown
so
okay
let's grab
is it round here
let me see
there's a scrap over here
i'm inscribed
you're searching for
the kai
might be somewhere around here
i don't know if they can
go
from here
i don't think we can
it's it's raining right now
but that's fine
but still
hopefully
good
um
[Music]
yeah an inside car for like 15
scraps
it's a good deal i think
i think it's a good deal
[Music]
oh
oh yeah the oil
i'm gonna take the oil again
[Music]
i guess
i don't know
[Music]
you have another place
have uh
where is
another place i think i think it's good
so far
[Music]
ah
um
okay let's go back
hello
[Music]
so
it's raining right now
i need i need little rain uh you know
the water that have a rain just like in
a
stylus place
[Music]
you mean
gonna assist with this
yep
[Music]
and we got enough
got enough of
scraps to get a working table tree
finally
that's a good one isn't it
[Music]
all right
awakens three let's go
let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
in this stream
this is the only stream that i can get a
lot of money
even it stays for like a long time
but i get a lot of money a lot of crap
so
it's a good sign
it's a good one
i'm gonna put my things in here
[Music]
hmm
so
[Music]
yay
okay
middle fragment 100 times high quality
metal
okay
hey hold on
my
i'm
gonna make the white pantry and after
that
the gamble
the rest of the scrapped me to the
gamble
if we have spare
if
we have spare if not we don't
so
um
[Music]
one man's three
yay
[Music]
she
yes my outfit is nice right
because the only one who need a hat is
not only my head but these these and
this need a hat too
okay
baby
nice
it's unless it like before our
[Music]
now
what i really want to do is
[Music]
i want to see
it's really like
really really
long wait
[Music]
i got a c4
and i want to use it
and i'm gonna sell
c4
[Music]
for my research travels down there
gimbal time
gable time mikuza
let's go
gamble time
with all this honey sweet
okay
we don't need an honest work
[Music]
it's honest working money
well well well
okay
ah
maybe we got an altitude turret
projectile
projectile weapon i don't have
projectile weapon
do i just need an ammo just like a
regular amount or can i
[Music]
electrical
um
turrets
do you think that i made
the
thing
[Music]
indoor oh it's like indoor
dongle
can i put it in here
right here
i'm gonna put it near the chest
i'm gonna put it in here
oh
oh okay this is
your shotgun
that's makes me realize that i actually
haven't researched a shotgun yet
i cannot
[Music]
oh yeah i don't know
we have on in here
see look at that like we have a lot of
things that i haven't
updated yet
i'm gonna start something
i think
incendiary i noticed more damage insane
theory
hello book a workbench study books
books
[Music]
gone
things
oh the hell is still in here
[Music]
actually
i don't know
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna
understand for like a couple of hours a
couple of hours
no
what i mean is
a couple of minutes
okay
so
we'll wookie farm
now
yeah we can go to the fubu farm
yeah yeah yeah we can go to this public
farm
let's go
q8 right
q8
is
so
[Music]
honey
i am
healing
hey
hello
so
okay
one more
[Music]
gimbal
me
it on
foreign
fun
[Music]
is
on there
um
[Music]
so
come on
[Music]
mana
the
[Music]
find another way to gain scrap rather
than gambling well i mean it's the end
of the stream it's the end of the stream
already i can do whatever i want
not at all
last time we'll be all in
[Music]
making excuses
i'm not
[Music]
so
there you go
whatever
[Music]
i don't know how to play this one
foreign
[Music]
so
okay
foreign
[Music]
yes tomorrow i will stream ross again
around 8pm
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is this
wow
wait what there's a candy in here
and this is this is
um
[Music]
new
oh
sorry my mind is not working right now
oh it's a steam problem i have those
problems too
you have to check your steam
microphone
hey uh mina senpai where's your house
is it my way my house is around
f 8.
oh
uh nearby the junkyard
yeah
is that careful
you had another
[Music]
your microphone looks so so so
far
i somehow it's like nearby to each other
is this your really good spot
wait guys where where where should we go
again
um
[Music]
do i sound better now
yes and better yeah you sound better now
really yeah you still literally was the
ps5 controller
[Laughter]
oh wow yeah i was building her house
yeah
yeah but it won't place on this side
good luck this side it doesn't place it
i don't have it could help if you're
oh that one
is that the farm
i want to know that one
i i i gotta go thank you bye
bye bye
bye
that's my very first super chat when i
say bye thank you
i need i need to make a lot of this one
is this this one
you know
to make your house so beautiful
thank you
[Music]
in here
this one
wow
[Music]
oh my god
it's really nice one
[Music]
is
what's the name
[Music]
oh
oh this is like water
[Music]
oh my god
wow
what's this potato wow
[Music]
technology
everyone
[Music]
foreign
i love it
[Music]
m
it's a good one
we got a small shirt oh my god
yes
[Music]
everyone says up there what's what's up
there
[Music]
hey i want to make it like this exactly
like this i want it
[Music]
yeah this is a good reference thank you
guys i'm gonna go back
take all your i can't take it
really
i can really take it for free
[Music]
i want
a potato
and it's like i think too
thank you
wow
i'm gonna follow that i'm gonna make it
look exactly like ain't nobody have
really taken this one
yet
[Music]
oh my god
yes
[Music]
what's that
who's house is that
it's a cute one it's a cute
house i mean
[Music]
you hear it
sorry
it's a cute house can i come in
can i trust you uh yes
uh here uh before the trust uh
i will give you these a round pork for
you to cook
oh admission fee
yeah okay okay
excuse me
i'm incoming oh my god wait
do you have a friend with your soul
wow
yeah
[Music]
wow you make electricity
you make electricity
[Music]
wow
yeah it's small
and there's stuff on the roof
[Music]
[Laughter]
well then i have to give kiara some food
or she's gonna starve all right
yeah could you close the door
if you're still here
oh my god
wow
what
[Music]
wow
oh they make it like this
i still have no idea how can i
do this kind of things
is it connected with this one
[Music]
okay
i cannot close it
[Music]
i'm gonna tell her
hi
i cannot i cannot close your door
i kind of look okay i'll close it it's
fine for now i'm sorry
all right
thank you
[Music]
yes
potato
i'm gonna go
do
should i help them
they need my help
i'm gonna get those things
i think
there's ami in there
it's gonna be okay
they'll be fine
[Music]
i just don't get any [\h__\h] like i
cannot find any horse in here like i've
been like walking for like a couple
well
some place
there is still no
need a luxury also in your house i guess
thank you uh yeah i can make elixir tree
i like tree city
i mean in season one i've already made
electricity
but i think
but i still don't have the items behind
us
like
um my items that i got is already like
i'm looting from somewhere
so
yeah
does anyone tell you about the rules of
the rest
so
in rust
it actually
um
[Music]
everyone like need to like uh
on voice
so that's that's the reason why i'm on
voice this whole time like i'm not
muting or something
what what's really uh
not recommended one is
of chat using a chat
for global chat because it will show up
in somewhere
someone's
streaming i'm anna
see there is no horse
there's no horse
huh
[Music]
what's this
what's
this this is
what
oil pump
looks like an oil plum
wow okay
oil pump
around here
is
well i guess
oh punch the top opposite the top what's
the duck is okay
i think
nobody really talking about the talk
why is it like open voice
open voice is the right dominant one
i need this what's that
mcdonald's
okay
[Music]
he didn't expect we'll get another
rocket launcher
i want to
have you play it
small january
i'm gonna
i'm gonna see
how long how much
five
one two trading
that might be possible
i'm gonna save each
tomorrow i'm gonna play with tomorrow
what should i do tomorrow
okay
[Music]
today
i will not i will not streaming at
20 uh i think
i think i cannot streaming at all
[Music]
around
to 27 perhaps i cannot stream at all at
that time
so the last time that i can i can stream
i can streaming is 24
that's the last day
for me
yeah
i'm gonna make another one
did i add in here
oh this is hostile yeah
you know what
while we're waiting
i'm gonna build
another one
yes
[Music]
wood metal fragment and carp okay a wood
middle part
omani
[Music]
that's before i end the swing
gonna
gather
lots of woods
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
oh yeah
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
me
and also we need to make this one too as
well i'm gonna open all of it one by one
at the end of the
so i'm gonna like gathering a lot of
scraps uh for the
research
kind of thing
mm-hmm
yeah
i want i need to like unlock after
after i saw
from the season one i realized that
scrap is missing
and but we still can't have the
research we still have the research it's
not changed at all
which is good one it's really good it's
really great
so
what i'm thinking maybe
maybe i can make like i don't know
you don't make it around here
[Music]
you can make it around
so
[Music]
where's
uh
hmm
oh
what
so
[Music]
it's a little weird
i cannot
[Music]
okay
this one is for that
i hope it's working
[Music]
oh i can't take this one
the face strap
clothes
goodness
[Music]
uh
huh
[Music]
okay
it's like a simple one right
[Music]
uh
do
[Music]
how can i change it
is it going
huh
i cannot press r
[Music]
honey
or press f1
the wall
you mean the wall
[Music]
and i'll write the wall
ah
it's still the same
so the same
[Music]
so
uh
what should i
[Music]
bye
um
[Music]
sit like this
looks so weird
now
[Music]
come on
five
[Music]
hmm
i'm gonna delete
[Music]
ah
i think
it's so hard to use in mouse only
[Music]
so
one flying
hey
man fine
the part
it is like coloring it a little bit
am i coloring the whole
i'm gonna make another one
[Music]
i've got onset
it's so big
it's shall be good
hey
heart blah
[Music]
come on
come
hmm
[Music]
ah that sounds
that looks great
[Music]
on
one
[Music]
donations thank you
i don't like it
i like this one better
mine
i'm
[Music]
one
yes
i don't think i like this
so
yes
okay
come on five
one five
[Music]
mona slime
one of one
nice
one of mine
i need to make some other dish
i've got lots
that's not the one that i'm searching
for
wait look around
requesting the raw files
well i try my best
thank you
try my best
[Music]
really
i needed grammy you were using mouse
yeah i'm using mouse
[Music]
oh yeah
um
[Music]
me
i think i know what i want to be
this is for you
[Music]
foreign
wow
[Music]
foreign
manga
item crap faster when you stand behind
beside workbench
well well
ah it's not
[Music]
foreign why
why
today
[Music]
oh yeah
i think it looks
no
i don't want it
[Music]
wait wait wait
oh okay i got i got an idea i got an
idea
so
and it's
[Music]
me
so
[Music]
okay
i can't read
i'm sorry
i cannot read
um
[Music]
and another one
thank you
the moon is beautiful isn't it ah
i don't know
i haven't looked outside yet
do
hey
okay
so far
[Music]
huh
okay
now
super chat thank you
[Music]
i'll make it like this
maybe i'll make it like
okay you know it's so much it for me
today
[Music]
ah
run
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
they're just like chilling in here
yes chilling
so
[Music]
is
me
something
inside
[Music]
door's like
still looking like that
you're so weird
wow
can i change it
i wonder why
this one was almost only like one side
it's all the same
it's still like that
this is
like this double door
[Music]
like this
you cannot rotate it
okay
i think this one okay
yeah
that's more like it i like it
i like it
good night
okay
why this one a great blog
bottom wood
i need
this strap
uh
try to remove one
yeah
okay no one's gonna destroy the floor um
well i believe that
if it's all alive but if it's npc i
i don't think so
i think we're gonna continue
it's um
tonight
so i think for now we just like end and
now
and now we can end now
yeah
and now i'm gonna just stay here
am i stuck
oh yeah
okay let's and now thank you so much
everyone i am muna hoshino from whole
life indonesia
we're gonna
[Music]
for the one who already donate me thank
you so much for
watching
[Music]
donation that i haven't read to be
honest
i'm so sorry but
oh that's okay
i am
indonesia generation one awesome
[Music]
you