[Music]
hmm
my
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
you
do
[Music]
my
hello
[Music]
sorry for the
one hour delay that's orange juice by
the way mmm orange juice
[Music]
that bitter sweet taste mmm yum
how are you doing everybody we're
playing a new pokemon game
oh my god
oh my god there is a new pokemon game
it's a new craze it's a new arc
[Laughter]
laugh with me come on
a new pokemon arc
how's it going new pokemon
enough
thank you thank you thank you
um today
i shall
catch them all
i will
i will use this arm today with all my
power and maybe i will also catch you
you want to get caught
thank you for the
for the new arm actually there's like
versions of
um
all of my outfits for this specific arm
thank you skye
skye made this one yeah even for my
kimono but unfortunately even if i move
a little bit up you see my other hands
gonna maybe move myself even lower than
that
um
yeah yeah that that kind of works i
guess most of the time small kiara
although i make my face bigger then
okay
okay are you guys ready for
a new adventure
i have not spoiled myself yet like i
mean i know roughly from the trailers
what it's about but besides that i don't
know much how about you guys
yeah me too basically
yeah
i'm going in very blind me too me too me
too what you play the liver
is that pokeball our new user
no no no no that you're making sense if
pokeballs were really really terrible
places to be in but as far as i know
they can be pretty comfy
i've been playing it since midnight oh
did you pull up
did you wake up all the night i can't
speak english
did you stay up all night yeah sana
gurgaon cali already uh started playing
it and now it's time to start my own
adventure
uh we're also playing it tomorrow so
yes
uh
let's get right into it
cool
15.
okay gamefreak show me what you got
oh espanol espanol
or uh korean
no no deutsch of course deutsch
no i have a goal obviously english the
logo might be german but that's just
because i had troubles finding an
english
logo for some reason google i'm sure
there's
english local pngs out there but when i
you say i don't know when i was looking
for it i couldn't find it only the
japanese one and the
german one
so
whenever you see now saving on the
screen your progress is being
automatically saved you can disable all
the stuff but yeah okay
okay
is that what the pokeballs look like in
this game
pretty interesting design
oh
well welcome to my realm located beyond
both time and space
it is well that though art here would
oh
i am that which humans call arceus
now i wish to know fine appearance
oh
[Music]
i see yeah they once again give us uh
a weird looking blonde that looks so
like greenish
it's such a greenish blonde like a
greenish yellow
um
can you later change your hair color to
orange with revenge any chance
you can change the hair color later
ah
and
then
and what about the eye color
you can change the eye color as well
not sure about orange okay but um
yeah yeah okay huh well for now i'll
i'll go with this one
tori is according to but how much later
is later i hope not too late
what is thy name
but wait as always
um
i need to
quickly whoops my finger slipped oops
uh oh
okay no problem they
they don't give
they don't give any suggestions
so we're good we're good we're good
we're good key last time i was kiawa
right
in the last pokemon game did i call
myself kiara or
in any case i think a weird keyboard
what's weird about those letters here
huh huh
you don't like my b
kiawah
the last time was kiawa okay i will
continue with kiawah this is a
an ancestor of kiawah
um kiawah and the last pokemon game that
we played was kiawah the 216th
uh this is kiawah the first
kiawah
ikuto
[Music]
when it's written like that it seems
very
weird
soon though shalt find thyself in a
world strange to see
don't talk like that
a world inhabited by wondrous creatures
that humans call
pokemon
yes what is it
[Music]
what
seek out all pokemon and those shall
find me once more
okay okay wait what how many how many
how many all of them what what did they
say
what did these say
want me to find all of them or just do
one or how many i need to know
nice nice t-shirt oh [\h__\h] i'm falling is
this a nightmare
is this
me playing
uh lynx awakening
oh no my phone
[\h__\h]
get my phone
[Music]
oh is this the legendary
[\h__\h] phones we don't use that stuff here
[Music]
oh
but how else will i check up on twitter
and uh youtube man
don't worry about that
okay
except we do we do okay uh pokemon
legends i see us yeah
[Laughter]
yay
did i get isakai so she actually comes
from a different world
wake up
oh do wake up won't you
pokemon
[Music]
are you alive my girl who's talking to
me
daddy
ah
you have a funny face
and a cow
holy [\h__\h] that eagle is on fire or
whatever that is what is that what is
that supposed to be
wait audio is like really low man
turn it up
turn it up get it up
fire it's a mouse
yeah i mean i mean what is it original
an eagle
oh i i think i think i want to say
hedgehog because then in german it's
eager and i know eagle in english is a
flying verb okay never mind holy [\h__\h]
there's a black hole on the top left you
guys are [\h__\h] can i go back to sleep i
want to go to my original world or did i
come out of that black hole
here you know
[\h__\h] black hole
an ant either is it an antheator
never seen a cinderella no i don't know
i've seen a pokemon before but you know
you gave you
uh uh
uh
you gave me quite the shock wait why am
i still like going
you gave me quite a shock falling from
the sky like that
this doesn't even sound male what the
[\h__\h]
i have the gender all the way pulled
down
but frank gordon you seem unarmed
uh
yeah who are you
i'd like to ask you to say
i mean you fell out from the sky you
understand like a [\h__\h] angel no this
is not meant to be a pickup line trust
me come on now who in the world does
that
what the [\h__\h] are you wearing
your clothing is so weird did you buy
that at uniqlo
you wouldn't happen to have an
acquaintance in these parts would you
uh she i like how
how
she has that pikachu face she's like
she i mean that's probably the default
face but it fits perfectly because she
looks very shook like what is going on
i don't know
i see you seem to be in a bit of a
pickle
yeah you could call it a pickle i guess
might i offer some directions do you
have it somewhere around here you could
stay
dude
you don't get it i don't know [\h__\h]
very nice of him to try to help me
though
look at her
devastated oh no
oh no
so you don't know anyone here and you
don't even know where to spend
tonight well
what if what if the you falling from the
sky was a pickup line after all
never mind uh this is a proper pickle
indeed do you like putting pickles in
your sandwiches then maybe we could get
along well
[Music]
[Laughter]
are these um
are those starters
one different starter from from each
like a different generation or am i
going crazy
because
yeah right
i thought so okay cool
i mean i thought it would be cooler if
they
would have brought up new
completely new starters but okay
i see well no gentlemen would have
abandoned the person who such needs
[Music]
cool
oh
my completely forgot to die i just
called up those three wondering pokemon
when they when you tumbled out of the
sky what
what they didn't tumble out of the sky
with me they were here right it's almost
as if they know you'd appear here
[Music]
oh but do you even know what a pokemon
is
well that i know
my that's her oh [\h__\h] she's wearing
sandals
on the beach
she'll be like [\h__\h] sand it's everywhere
it's coarse and rough it's [\h__\h]
everywhere
that's a relief you should maybe change
your shoes or take them off completely
your sand is going to be everywhere
after it is yeah just walking a few
meters and you'll be so annoyed by it
yes well these three pokemon belong to
me mysterious creatures that they are
oh yes and what might your name be
[Music]
so you called kianwa
that name has quite a ring to it i
imagine it must have some lovely meaning
oh but i do apologize i haven't even
introduced myself
my name is lavinton oh that sounds
british to me
i'm something of a pokemon professor
that is to say i'm a scholar seeking uh
to even our understanding of pokemon yes
pokemon such as these three here which
ah why are you really really
oh blast and butter
is that something they say in the uk
my darling pokemon why must you run for
me again
again
i'm terribly sorry but do you think you
could help me round them up i beg you my
back is [\h__\h] kill killing me a match
i tried to lift the mattress this
morning and then uh
the mattress fell on top of me and i
called jerry seinfeld but he wouldn't
come to help me so i was just lying on
the ground for ages trying to get
someone to help me but oh boy no one
gave a [\h__\h]
where are you there wait
hi
what uh
what a intro
let's look
at the beach
okay
little fishing boat that we can use to
escape immediately because we don't
wanna
we don't no we don't we do not
we do not want to be in this world i
think no no
no no this is not where i belong to
prelude beach
pre-pre preluding
at least in german the
beach in um
uh in wind waker and at the beach but
the the the the village in windwaker is
called prelude
no no i'm not not thinking about prelude
and thinking about uh uh
uh the legend of zelda links away and
then like some links awakening
uh uh
wind waker
oh
did you see that hmm
[Music]
okay
what is this oh what's this
[Music]
yeah like a prelude mm-hmm
there's a glowing beeping object over
there oh
whoa whoa whoa what is that
what is that that looks fancy take it
take it investigate yes call the
investigators
that looks very fancy indeed you found
something that resembles a phone it's
just a phone with a fancy phone case
trust me it's probably your phone with a
strange shape i feel you feel strange
power emanating from it yeah they don't
know what the phone case is i suppose
a message appeared on the screen paul
did you see your face again i bestow
upon the this arc phone and dimension
seek out all pokemon oh okay all of them
apparently
all of them say no pokemon
who not
if i have time
you gotta give me something back
gotta give me something back if you want
me to get all the pokemon
[Music]
he's cute
he's actually kind of cute with his
weird face
i lost yet another miss oh
i'm glad you've come to my rescue my new
friend from the sky
i tried catching my little runaways by
tossing some pokeballs their way but i'm
not the best at this sort of thing you
see
[Music]
i would love to give you a go at it but
perhaps i should tell you a bit about
these three firsts
what just did i just see that
now that one is roller roulette roland
rowland i guess rowlet can
photosynthesize like a plant and
apparently it battles using its sharp
feathers
oh it's so cute it's so [\h__\h] round i
love it
so wrong you can use it as like a
bowling ball
[Music]
which one did uh good asana and cali
choose
tell me
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
sana usa what kelly chose what
[Music]
wait they didn't choose the boob
they did not choose the bird
can we pick the cinder quail
they i thought the bird would feel like
super popular
was a what
oh what
cinder quail that one over there is a
cinder coil
that fire burning on cynical's back will
flare up whenever it's surprised or rate
you know what to do with that right you
just stick it in the toilet to make it
cool down
[Music]
now pokemon unicorn is also what i know
that's a horrible name
so what knobs while floating under water
and it can't battle using the shell-like
object on his belly
cute is it's pretty cute though what
oh i never forgot to cover the most
crucial thing how to go about catching
pokemon
oh
that's my ball
here you go my girl poke balls throw
these at the pokemon to catch him
fifty holy [\h__\h] that's a lot oh
okay
[Music]
thank you a pokeball a mysterious ball
that can be thrown at wild pokemon in
order to catch him these bones can be
crafted by hand if you gather the
necessary materials
oh
well that's sweet a crafting system
or only for balls i wonder for pokeballs
[Music]
yeah i guess i don't have to catch them
all
um
one of them
hey yo
now but that won't do for an explanation
will it i do apologize let me be more
for it
now i have mentioned already that
pokemon are strange marvelous creatures
what's so strange about them you ask
well each and every pokemon is able to
shrink itself down to minuscule size
and that's where pokeballs come in
pokeballs are a recent invention you see
throw one of them at a pokemon and why
the pokemon was ringing down and fit
inside the ball comfy as can be and with
that you've caught a pokemon
yeah sounds nice
i know we've just met and this is crazy
but here's my number so call me late
late
baby
i'd be awfully grateful if you could
catch me in my free runways
now the proper technique is to take aim
at the pokemon and then let the ball fly
it's quite simple
no far beat from me to say so i suppose
give my own dire lack of skill in this
area
[Music]
well well is that our where is that
that's it okay
uh
you can keep moving around as you do so
use the right stick to adjust your angle
and carefully aim at your target pokemon
oh
release that eye button to throw the
pokeball if it hits the pokemon you may
be able to catch it if you've ready to
poke a ball but do not want to throw it
press the b button to cancel for okay
that's easy
uh where did the burp go i want the bub
i want the boob
[Music]
mum
how accurate do you have to be with that
i wonder like if i throw it like here
will still
like catch it
sheet you see it okay that didn't work
yes yes
oh my god i have to pick it up
tiny little fireworks
pew
oh wonderful you've caught a pokemon
it seems you've quite a knack for this
pokemon casting business piano
catching a business oh jolly gently
useful skill to have around here
only two of my darling runaways left now
still this is the most unusual i have to
catch all them anyway okay you don't
seem fearful of pokemon in the slightest
hmm
we have pokemon in my world and uh
we have
we have uh
what are you doing
that's good
we have taken control over them
[Laughter]
okay
that one was in the water and
you my little fire friend
take this
whoa
oh
[Music]
look she looks so disappointed oh yes
i'm afraid that can happen pokeballs are
hardly 100 foolproof give it another go
old gold girl did you call me old girl
[Music]
hi
all righty all righty
okay there we go
what what's yeah what is old about me
[Music]
thank you very much indeed oh what a
relief to have them all back
you see the three pokemon you called
have only just arrived at the village to
help with our research they won't yet
listen to anyone
and as i mentioned they voted from the
village almost as if they knew you'd
come falling
but i must say kiawah i was taken aback
by how well you use pokeballs
an old-fashioned british thing ah
[Music]
how is it that you catch pokemon so ably
when you've only just arrived here
one can't help but think there's a
reason you appeared here and now
[Music]
why
wait
oh
[Laughter]
seek out oh all pokemon
uber what's this
that object is an arc phone you say yeah
new phone who this
is she's just flexing her phone at
him what an odd device could it be
guiding you somehow
if you'll indulge me for a moment
there's something i'd like to share with
you
he actually
he doesn't really look like he's from
this time either he looks like he's
also from a modern timeline
weirdly enough
i have a dream i have a dream to compile
this region's first complete record of
its pokemon
we in the field call such a catalog of
pokedex
yeah a proper pokedex is a wonderful
work of research containing detailed
records of all the pokemon to be found
in a region
but in order to properly document
document pokemon one must of course
catch them all
darren lies the robe i'm afraid
pokeballs have only just been invented
and not many have mastered the skill of
using them
and to you
a person with a clear talent for
catching pokemon
your goal is to seek out every pokemon
and mine is to have all those
pokemon so you're not gonna lift a
finger aren't you
minus travel
situation right for teamwork don't you
agree
once again it's the children doing all
the work yay
[Music]
sure
yeah
um you totally 100 percent
convinced me
i i'm not even gonna think about how i
could get back home that is apparently
for a 15 year old not the priority right
now right no no no no no
then reverend from wherever you may be i
welcome you with open arms
[Music]
what the hell
man we've a pokedex to complete yay
first things first let's get the pokemon
back to the village and then we'll sort
out your lodgings and find you some
proper clothes in the mail and all that
jubilee
[Music]
yo he really might have
um back problems the way he looks
yeah so what about this black hole
with some uh
rainbow reflections coming out of it
oh
thank you for your tyler's work keeping
us safe my good guardsmen
this young lady was of great assistance
to me and my pokemon so i hope you'll
forgive my bringing her into the village
for a bit
[Music]
her look
she's terrified
[Music]
finally i'm back in japan
can you just show me that scene
this way if you please
okay i'm coming
super live village it's come a long way
thanks to what sorry what
this road we're on uh now is known to
the locals as canal avenue where you
from i don't know the village was built
scarcely two years ago there's much to
do yet you're too fast what the [\h__\h] i'm
not even pressing anything and since we
know it's only lovely to look at pokemon
people associated with
not supposed to talk to strangers yeah
well stop talking to me
oh botheration i've almost forgotten
oopsie doodles
i need to go and report that we
successfully recovered the escaped
pokemon
might i ask you to wait for me to
continue
okay you just uh we'll past this bridge
here and then to the left the wallflower
it's called
the wallflower
[Music]
is arceus talking to me
someone seems to show where you need to
go next oh thank you
use the minus button to view the map on
your arc phone you can consult the map
for guidance to your next destination
and information on your missions and
requests
you'll also see guidance markers when
you're out exploring of uh or running
around the village uh-huh if you're not
sure where to go next then just look out
for that
sounds good thanks arceus for the back
seating hell yeah
what's here
[Music]
well um the design is cute um
small
the houses are cute though you're coming
to the village yes that's me
hmm
yeah yeah
yeah oh they're working over here
um already making grapes for all the
dead pokemon that i'm gonna kill thank
you dude for your hard work
i'll bring you the bodies later
[Laughter]
oh okay oh can i run in between oh
oh i can
almost okay well i mean that's that's
actually
didn't expect being able to run through
here
okay so
i like this part with the little river
at the the water machines thingy
you want to talk
back in my hometown i've got an older
brother who's gonna inherit the family
farm and all uh but i'm gonna make my
own way here in history
oh you were not supposed to talk to me
this weekend
and there's lots of delicious pokemon
tomorrow you came here anyway how come
cause i'm not scared
nothing scares me
oh here i can't run through
oh they're working they're working on
this building apparently
oh i like that that's that's very uh
yeah yeah yeah
traditional
japanese store that's cute
with like it's open doors
and laying out the stuff to buy in the
front
no design oh
that's a nice scissor
yeah old clothes maybe clothing store
for later you're gonna sell me clothes
she looks fancy too
i've never seen clothes like your son
where might they be from
i'm gonna go shopping here later oh this
is the hairdresser
i'm not sure if i want to trust him or
her
with my hair
that's your birthday emily happy
birthday
happy birthday to you
wow your hair is so green but only the
the the front um
beard
is gray and the rest is green
well no i don't chew it off are you
awfully uh suspicious
the wall flowers for galaxy team folk
only we don't have seats for outsiders
move along
well your beard is strange
what hello
who in the world are you and what's that
bizarre garb you're wearing
a pokemon could slice right through
those flimsy excuses for clothes
for you to get in here someone must have
vouched for you
yes yes if only if only this protagonist
had the power to talk then we could all
communicate and misunderstandings would
not happen
was it professor lavinton do you two
know each other there's uh he's from a
region a long way off
not the most reliable sort though
letting pokemon run off and give him the
slip and all
three more of them got away just a while
ago
if i hadn't been resting up after some
pokemon dropped me with a move called
thundershock
i'd have corralled them for sure but the
professor will
unfortunately it's just as it says i'm a
clumsy sort of fellow to put it mildly
[Music]
but everything will be quite all right
now
kiawah here has agreed to help us with
our pokedex
as in she's going to join the survey
corps
what
what makes you think that's a good idea
we can't just take in any misfit who
wanders out of the wilderness
allow it
is that a
[Music]
a lady
gah
hmm
i don't know what voice to do lady okay
assuming the individual can contribute
to the survey corps status
i am the captain of the galaxy team
survey corps you may call me sil
celine
cylene cylinder sullen
cellini
i don't know
cyrus
oh
[\h__\h] oh it's obviously a reference huh
because of the name as well
oh
professor 11 10 has told me how you
helped secure his pokemon when they
slipped
his control
and now it seems he would like to feed
us uh would like us to feed and house
you in exchange for your ongoing labor
you look to be 15 or so
quite old enough to work for you keep
thank you feelings for the rest of the
time thank you
well we can't simply take on the
stranger who understand among us without
any of their any idea of their skills
and origins
tomorrow we shall see if you can prove
yourself worthy
oh the most reasonable decision captain
now would you care to join us for a meal
i'm sure you've got plenty of questions
for a visitor
ah that's quite all right
i prefer to eat alone so i might
appreciate my meals without distraction
[Music]
all right okay and it seems like an
important character
a love as always i see
well no matter
the rest of us can share meal and some
pleasant conversation than a
shut
benny old chamber the usual potato mochi
if you please but make it for free today
yeah you potato mochi
potato moochie he's shaking is he
shaking
wonderful stuff then you're much obliged
your potato watch you never fail to
place
hey but that's cute i like the the balls
and the umbrella above us
uh where'd you find the stranger in the
first place professor
oh well you know of that right hole in
the sky and when the one people called a
space time rift
our new friend fell right out of it oh
[\h__\h]
oh was that a joke
[Music]
he nods but
is that not true
come now i'm a scientist my job is to
observe and explain any and all
phenomena
i concerned myself only with facts
[Music]
now you already know there are many
pokemon here in the history region
sure they're all over the place in the
grass in the forest in the ocean it's up
to us in the survey corpse to study them
and figure out what kind of creatures
they own
well we know this much
pokemon are terrifying creatures
[Music]
it's all but impossible to know what
kinds of powers they might possess so
what sorts of wondrous things they can
do
but that's where kiawah will come in
she successfully caught free pokemon
three of them in quick order you
understand
nani
nobody in the galaxy team is capable of
feat such as that this means we can
finally begin our pokemon research in
earnest
[Music]
that's really something we count
ourselves lucky when we manage to catch
a single wild pokemon while fending off
their attacks
oh well to be perfectly fair the pokemon
that fled to the beach weren't on the
attack but the key to catching pokemon
is getting close enough to aim a
pokeball well and it seems our new
friend is fearless enough to do just
that
one second
[Music]
throwing is apparently a skill here yeah
i'm
i'm perfectly comfortable here
i'm very good at throwing games
so
yeah
i'm good at brewing
in some way
does the serving corpse we have the
leeway to be enjoying a leisure
leisurely meal with this outsider
oh captain just ordered 10 whole
portions of potato mozzie you know the
slow progress on the pokedex of yours
clearly has your own edge
i'm sure we'll start the terrain in the
good captain stress eating soon enough
now have your fukiyawa
i think thank you i think if you make it
into the galaxy team you'll never have
to worry about a meal again
the team provides for all its members
needs even if said members fell out of
the sky
[Music]
i have some food here as well in case i
get hungry
in between
some snacks i hope you guys have some
snacks too that was quite delicious
quite delicious indeed
oh the night sky is pretty nice
i like the the sky
that looks pretty
prettier than the ground definitely
you're you're awfully relaxed about all
this you don't know that we don't get to
have kiawah join the survey corps unless
she passes the trial
not to worry i have complete confidence
in key our skills
thank you he has confidence that i must
have confidence too
let's hope it is not misglaced
pia what was it
for tonight at least we'll provide you
with a place to sleep you may use our
quarters here
thank you where may i sleep
but if you fail to pass the trial we put
to
put to you tomorrow you must move on you
will be expelled from the village to
meet your fate and perhaps your death in
the wilds
what
well that's uh
drastic
captain celine's like history in a way
they're both plenty harsh
now now she simply puts on the stone
fronts to help keep us all safe
at any rate i think it's time we turn in
for the night i it's a good thing one
can't fall out of the flu tones we sleep
in here i imagine our new friend has had
enough falling for one day
and with that i beat you both for good
night
oh yes
thank you for welcoming me holy [\h__\h]
that is
very very worrying i don't know if i can
sleep with that above my head
still people falling from the sky that's
some kind of story
yes i totally did not arrive with that
little fisher's boat
no um that is not
that is not what happened i i fell from
the sky that is the more realistic
option so that is it
baby
[Music]
all right well i have to say the the
lightning lighting
sets the atmosphere and the mood pretty
nicely so
that's just good
that's pretty
good we should open a kfb branch in
these parts and show mr potato emoji how
proper restaurant is run hell yeah
[Music]
oh
what a room
ina
oh
[Music]
beautiful
i hope there's no cockroaches though
[Music]
chucky server tips server tips contain
all sorts of useful information to help
you carry out uh your survey work in the
history region to read them at any time
simply press the up button to open the
menu and then go to the help screen
huh handy tips for team members don't
wish your toys to be forgotten nice
movie diligent record keeping will save
you from such fate
a safe wink uh-huh is that a hint
there's cockroach pokemon oh no
there's no animal in the pokemon world i
guess that's true yeah there's i guess
there's really only pokemon any animal
is a pokemon basically
uh to save your progress press the up
button to open the menu then scroll with
zlr button until you reach a safe screen
there is also an all the same function
you can use to have your progress saved
automatically you can enable or disable
all the safe by scrolling to the help
screen
sure
very helpful notes in here
that chest is nice to investigate it's
addressa of a very solid construction
where extra sets of clothing can be kept
can i change
investigate a nice fire in the sunken
heart can help keep the entire room
heated
[Music]
that's really cool
and they even have a garlic up there to
keep out the vampires
shoes hanging up there as well and
tomatoes is that tomatoes they look kind
of uh
uh
old but sure
oh
i'm a ghost i can't see myself in the
mirror
[Music]
what is that
there's some lovely stones that someone
must have found but they are just plain
old stones okay well full length mirror
okay but i don't have any clothes to
change i guess
i'm oh i'm a vampire not a oh well then
the garlic must be thrown out if i'm a
vampire and i can't see myself in the i
am a vampire
[Music]
[Applause]
is that that's it do we sleep
oh
happy dubs what are you doing here
oh what the [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
wait was that tree there before
or did the tree just get created by the
thunder for some reason
wha
the next day
and are you awake there was some white
lightning last night right
it was hella wild anyway if you're up
come on out
okay i'm coming
i do like my room a lot i do like that
we have a room
and no mommy no mommy no pokemon mommy
in this game oh my god is that a first
oh is that a thirst
is that a first
oh yo i like how she actually i was
about to say because i saw her wearing
shoes like yo does she not take off her
shoes in this room that's that's
inconceivable but she does
you
[Music]
what's that by the way a jug used to
store drinking water oh it has a lid on
top to keep diapers from falling in um
no no i must i must say
i like how you know they explain what
each item in here is used for even if it
does not actually have actually have any
proper
use in the gameplay but they
explain it and therefore like foreigners
who don't know much about japan they can
also learn
about some traditional housing in japan
yeah i think that's that's that's nice a
nice detail
my chest looks like you could store lots
and lots of items well we know that okay
yeah nice detail
gotta say some good things
did you sleep all right i know it's not
easy in a strange new land
we'd better not keep captain
celine waiting let's hurry to the
headquarters
celine is my pokemon
yeah but it is the first time right
how did you meet the pokemon game
[Music]
maybe we meet our mom at the very end of
the game i don't know maybe we get
teleported back into our own world i
wonder
whoa
the inside does not look very japanese
here we are galaxy hall what do you
think ever seen a building this grand
before
[Music]
oh don't give up keep those eyes open
um the wild pokemon day they were
everywhere attacking from all sides i
send out my partner pokemon but against
the whole pack outnumbered
this is what this is what happens when
you go so far afield but the medical
corps will put you to rights who's
talking
you uh do realize that if you fail your
trial and get flung out of the village
you could well die out there well you
might die even sooner than that if you
have to take on this trial without a
pokemon to be your partner
[Music]
yeah i haven't chosen chosen my star yet
captain celine ma'am
uh i've brought
foreign
[Music]
oh she has a
abra
opera is it an uproar
let us get straight to it
if you wish to join the galaxy
expedition team approve yourself capable
by going out into the obsidian fitlands
and catching three different species of
pokemon uh beethoven staley and shanks
shanks
three species right away but none of us
have ever managed that
losers absolute losers
did this stranger not catch three
different pokemon only yesterday
my trial should be simple enough for her
if the professor wasn't exaggerating
things that is
the galaxy team does not have the means
to provide for those who only take
without giving if you wish to stay you
must prove beyond any doubt that you'll
be an asset to our cause
[Music]
yeah easy no problem no problem for me
i'm not complaining
i will lend you one of our cervicorp
satchels to carry whatever you may need
in the field
[Music]
that whatever it is you're wearing
doesn't suit our satchels in the least
hey
i'll expect you to step in if anything
goes all right
ori all right
yeah my gucci bag
checking missions and requests press the
white button while consulting the map on
your arc phone and you can check the
tasks you have waiting there are two
types missions and requests mission must
be completed our requests are optional
yes
oh opportunity i will come with me a
moment
are you gonna give me a starter
no they're not only good morning to
everyone
what did you need professor
in order to complete our pokedex and
well simply survive in this unforgiving
land
he our absolutely must pass the trial
and as a professor of pokemon i've got
just a ticket to help accomplish that
[Applause]
[Music]
pokemon that strikes you fancy well you
already know what i was going for
yay
[Music]
let me
how come no one has
chosen this this cute precious little
round
ball of love and fluff and ah cuteness
huh
cool
we can we can also you guys can imagine
that this is a chicken if you want
another owl
if that helps you guys
do you want me as your first partner
hell yeah
[Music]
oh you surprised me
oh it's your first attack bamboozle
could that be a bamboo
and without one of the pokemon you
caught that prelude beach for me will
now be yours to keep good show i've
tucked roll it back inside the pokeball
for you so take it as yours
[Music]
baby
what a baby wait from which which one
from which game was rowlet a rolex
originally from
because i think
whatever game he was from i did not
choose him sun and moon yeah yeah okay
well then i did not choose him back then
i chose the fire cat actually when i
played it um
privately
[Music]
i'm not sure why because you know burp
versus cat
it's a tough choice
the verb looked cuter but a cat is a cat
you know yeah
[Music]
i know
yes yes
but this
with this choice put in front of me i
think we need to go for the
cute bib
a word of advice my girl pay close
attention to which pokeballs are empty
and which ones contain a pokemon when
you're out in the field
look at those two cheer on their pal
vernon adam's cute
and i know buddies like from
kindergarten nintendo
or maybe they or maybe they just wanted
to help kiawah with her trial
that could well be they did go dashing
from the village when kiawah fell out of
the sky off the wall
well not worry you too i'll have you
assist with my research for now
i don't wanna you disgusting
i always go for water or grass pokemon
as a starter no no i don't really have a
preference and
element to be honest i mean obviously
fire i'm biased but when it comes to
pokemon
i
rather go for the looks because
obviously every one of the three
elements has
strengths and weaknesses that i once
again will have lots of trouble
remembering and you guys will have many
many times where you can help me out
with that
what
what uh well that's smashing all three
of those species can be found in the
obsidian fitlands
let me give you some pokeballs to use
during it i already have 50 dude
pokemon
if i move
yes definitely you may backseat me when
it comes to typing and
what attacks i should use and what
attacks i should let my pokemon have and
all that and last time
um
i don't mind at all having you guys help
me with that
[Music]
what i didn't keep the 50 pokeballs oh
what the [\h__\h]
ah
these pokeballs may be handcrafted but
they work as a treat as you've already
seen
you'll have to strike cleveland no time
let's be off i'll show you the way to
the obsidian field lens meet me at the
gate to your left as you leave
headquarters
left okay
all right
this game needs a lot of pokeballs yeah
i've seen i've seen in the trailer
you tend to throw a lot of them
and maybe also miss a lot especially if
you're running that will be tough
wait a second what
oops
wrong way
i felt left after after that gate
machiganda
i'm coming
i'm coming i'm gonna be on my way
oh wait that's where it came from
no i'm not sure
not sure anymore a bit confusing
[Music]
here i am with my ninja clan ninja clan
yes we stan who are you
oh what a curious get up you have there
i can already tell you quite the
character
you too sir
i'm well of the ginkgo guild the go-to
choice for any of you bears and doll
leads here in history
i've heard uh talk about you fell from
the sky didn't you now that's certainly
a tale i'd like to use it
oh and you have a pokemon you're
certainly full of interesting surprises
well
investigating the odd and novel is key
to any good merchant success so what do
you say how about you when i see uh how
a pokemon stand it
in a battle
is this my uh
rival
sure but that doesn't
i'd like you better and better what a
delightful find
i've also heard about this trial hero to
attempt let's have a quick battle to get
your blood pumping before you head out
though i hope you know you'll lose if
your pokemon hp reaches zero
i know i know i don't have a rival
whoa our first battle
ever challenged
pogba baby
baboo bubble that's cynthia's ancestor
yeah
oh i like the interface
wait it's moving what the [\h__\h] fight
gus
oh you can run around doing it i love
that what if i go like in front of my
pokemon am i gonna block the attack
that's so cool
[Music]
dead
battle decided oh
wow okay the battles
are looking pretty fun the music was fun
and uh the interface is fun and being
able to run around like that is really
cool as well
i can't get hurt oh [\h__\h]
a new feel to it
oh
new move
it's always good it's fun to have your
pokemon do battle don't you think
and as they gain experience through bad
till they learn more moves and grow even
stronger
look at my moves pokemon sometimes learn
new moves when they level up
if you want to change the moves your
pokemon can use in battle open your
satchel choose the pokemon you want and
select change moves option
what
does that mean you can change the moves
whenever you want and when you unlearn
something you can always relearn it like
whenever
oh wow
[Music]
okay that that way you can at least like
try out a lot of moves um
especially if you're kind of new to the
franchise and you're not sure yet what's
a good move and you may maybe want to
make your
your own opinion about it
and yeah i don't want to make any
mistakes
but yeah also want to try it your own
way
i mean it makes it again i guess a bit
easier but it's cool i i think it's
pretty cool
oh but so few people who have their own
pokemon if only more new how to use
pokeballs
at any rate let me help our two battles
battlers recover from their little
experience thank you for the healing
and to you my sky fallen friend i
present some potions in thanks
five potions
oh
i like the links of those two
a topical medicine meant to be applied
to pokemon it can be used to restore 60
hp to a single pokemon
you can use them on your pokemon
whenever they might be worn out from
battle i'll be hoping that you're
successful on the trial of yours more
galaxy team members means more customers
for yours truly after all
bye-bye
[Music]
if you can battle that well i've got a
feeling you may have your trial well in
hand even if it's more to do with
catching than battling
now that obsidian field lands let's go
whenever you leave to the left village
you have to pick a destination from your
map and let rest the guardsmen know
where you're off to
that way someone can come collect your
things if you go wrong
is that a typo that's a typo
[Music]
you mean my body my corpse you mean
someone can collect my my corpse if i
die is that a nice way of saying that
i hope you make it through this i will
i'm i'm going to outside i don't know
where i'm going
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh oh the map looks cool
i like the way the the clouds are drawn
in that traditional style
yeah
[Music]
cheese yep yep my unconscious no my dead
body
no need to
no need to change it up like that let's
be real
i said that is it like a picnic
thingy in the back cute
[Music]
oh it's hokkaido i didn't look at it
like that
oh that would be nice
let me let me take a froat candy
candy candy
this is our base camp it's where we
start and finish our service
now remember what you've got to do
different times of catching free species
of pokemon bidoof stallion chinks
i'm curious to see if the professor's
stories about you are really true
oh professor something wrong oh [\h__\h]
uh well you see
captain celine got hold of me after you
left she impressed upon me that i bear
full responsibility for whatever happens
to our southern ghost
she doesn't let us let up how exactly
are you supposed to help out here
professor you're useless
to be honest my dear boy i don't intend
to lift a finger i knew it
keanu's talents are the real deal
she'll pass with flying colors you'll
see yeah that is true but i find it
ridiculous how you are never lifting a
finger at all
so in other words i'm still the one
bearing the responsibility here
not my ideal state of affairs
space
let's just get started you'll be more
than an equal to this kiawah
let me go
catch a badoo the first pokemon spaces
you need for your trial
okay
oh look at that sunflower
aspiration hill
[Music]
i've been over
yeah i'm not gonna say it but you guys
know what i'm thinking
[Laughter]
you may be some sort of prodigy but just
in case here's what captain celine
taught me
hold down the that l button to focus on
the wild pokemon set l
focus you can focus oh
and to keep it in your sights as long as
it's nearby this technique comes in very
useful when aiming pokeballs at the
target or when dodging pokemons attacks
okay
i'm looking forward to your thoughts on
it oh
are you well
i have a lot of thoughts
the duve is a mellow pokemon which means
it doesn't tend to run away when you
approach it only wants a hug that's all
at once
i would love to give it a hug
all righty what i what i do think is
like um
maybe it's only me as a streamer but uh
the music is
currently a bit lacking like um
maybe
you know as a non-streamer it wouldn't
bother me maybe that it's so quiet
um but especially at the beginning of a
game to build up the hype and excitement
i would have expected more music like
right now there's no music at all it's
just like ambient sounds
um and in the village i would have
expected the village music to be a bit
more upbeat
because like you literally just arrived
and the new game is
starting oh maybe they did take
inspiration from breath of the wild yeah
it seems to be like a bit um calmer in
general probably on purpose
but
i don't know i
for pokemon you know it's a it's a
childish game usually and i want that
childish excitement so a bit more poppy
exciting music would be cool as a
streamer especially to get everyone
hyped up in the chat as well
but it's been very calm
the whole time so what this is focus oh
there we go
uh
x
what
wait no no no ah okay okay
[Music]
yeah this is serious business we got the
video easy
luxury
yeah yeah no i mean in general you know
in general pokemon games are obviously
more like for children so i mean that
anyone even adults play it so
yeah that's i'm not saying it's just for
children but you know what i mean i just
kind of want more like
let's go
yeah yeah
yeah but it's okay
uh the battle music was awesome though
one big dude god no only match let's go
where's the next one
a starling right
you have to catch us darling next
the second pokemon species
yes good
a boob we had uh didn't we have a
starling in our team
um for the last pokemon game we're
playing oh is that a different bird
wasn't that a starly
and crouching down press the button the
crowd to make it harder for wild pokemon
to notice you
yeah
that was a stylist so i'm not sure if i
i want different pokemon in my team so
even if we catch one now it will not
stay in our team unfortunately even
though it is very cute
kawaii
and if you creep into the tall grass
while crap slow you'll be even harder
for wild pokemon to detect
i say
stealth
oh
it's
bouncing so cutely can i still focus
okay
wait
what is this
oh
well yes that is kind of that i felt
like i'm in breath of the wild just now
that's cool
that's uh for crafting later maybe
[\h__\h] i'm stupid no no no no no nothing's
there no
mate
wait
let me hide oh is that a are those golgi
go not gold oh were they called golgi um
berries gochi berries
that's so cute
ah okay i have to
hold it
it does not see what's coming
[Music]
oh happy birthday
dudes that makes the comics on reddit ah
you're tattooed yo
i haven't been on reddit much uh these
days but i always enjoy looking at your
comics
happy birthday to you you guys know
the comics on reddit about my minecraft
adventures
they're always so cute
and that's charlie caught two i admit
i'm impressed so far let's go to the
next one
maybe if you will um i don't know why
you owe me a reddit maybe there's a
reason for that but if you
upload them on twitter as well
then i would at least not miss them
but maybe you don't like twitter
i forgot to share another smidgen of
wisdom
yes what is it
oh oh holy
uh
boy of the tree what is your wisdom how
to throw your partner's pokeball
to quote captain celine's wise teachings
have an item at the ready but want to
send another pokemon press x
what
an item at the ready but want to send
another pokemon i have a pokemon at the
ready but waterfall ah i already did
that okay okay
wait i just want to switch it out okay
then once you've got a pokemon ready try
aiming for certain rocks or trees like
this one your pokemon will hunt for bit
oh
the pokemon will do it
yes shanks okay oh
so
go rowlet
oh
[Music]
cool
where are you going i don't know i
wanted to look for more berries
mommy wants berries i can't help it
oh and i can wait how do i how do i uh
oh
[Music]
what if i just throw it at like nowhere
what's it gonna do
she's chilling
it comes back if i go too far
[Music]
okay that seems like it can be quite the
fun gameplay
especially because the world already
looks pretty big
there it is shanks
we had this one in our team as well last
time um so far many repeating pokemon
is so unfortunately until we find
something better
it might stay until we find something
else but
yeah
um it has what
an aggressive disposition
don't worry about it just focus on the
pokemon around you you'll figure it out
quick enough
the same reason
but but
i can find an eevee oh [\h__\h] i'm gonna
get the eevee then
but at least since it's not two games
but one game there is at least no um i
suppose there is no nothing like oh this
pokemon is only available
here in this game and this is this
pokemon only in that game right because
it's only one game
once aggressive pokemon get wound up
they'll knock away any balls you throw
whoa when you use that l button to focus
on the pokemon you can see how easy it
may be to catch the more arrows you see
pointing up above the pokemon the easier
it will be to catch okay
oh
now
okay well at least i would definitely
want an eevee i don't know on twitter
because
they're gonna have too many pages ah
well you could make a friend
you could make a new post i mean
yeah i know i know you would have to
make a lot of them but still
you could make a thread an x icon will
appear above a pokemon if it has picked
a fight with you
oh be warned pokemon display in this
icon cannot be called unless you engage
them in battle oh sheet
not uh but not to worry i'll teach you
the trick to catching them
you draw them into battle once it's
caught up in the heat of a battle you
can throw a pokeball and try to catch it
you've got a few pokemon of your own to
use now don't you
take one of their pokeballs and vary
that what pokemon you want to battle
use what you learned in your battle with
volo get out there and make your last
catch
[Music]
it's easy to start a battle against a
wild pokemon simply throw a pokeball
that contains one of your own pokemon
added if you can see that you currently
have an item ready to throw not a
pokemon press the x button it will allow
you to toggle
okay so before
throwing an empty pokeball yeah
he's coming at me
brown pokemon
uh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wow that's just
stressful
um
holy [\h__\h]
and when do i catch it can i catch it
before killing it
[Music]
wait oh no
ah
yes
how about now
well at least now i don't have the aim
[Music]
put it in oh we got it
he shook
whoa did you really you really did it
you did it
that's three species of pokemon caught
you really are some kind of prodigy wow
that's fun
it's it feels very fast paced and i got
to attack three times in a row what the
hell
you must give it you must have given
professor levinton the shock of his life
first you fall from the sky then you go
and catch all of our escaped pokemon one
after another
i honestly didn't believe the
professor's story until i saw you in
action for myself
and here you are with free pokemon cards
you've complete completed your trial
hey
yes i did
ah if i'm fast enough then i can get in
multiple turns oh
if i think too much i might only get one
or not even one turn i wonder
your speed stat dictates attack speed
excuse
and the pokemon users turn silk around
yeah
fast enough meaning your pokemon is fast
enough
cool cool cool
whoa i said you would pass the driver
flying colors and it seems you went and
did just that
congratulations kiawa
you've taken your first steps towards
seeking out every pokemon this calls for
a commemorative photographer
with that old camera
put some filters on that unbelievable
[Music]
oh thank you thank you chad
i've got to admit it it's true you've
got a real talent for this
now then uh with best reporters captain
celine
time to head back to jupiter village
let's go
i want to see her face
i want to see her surprised face
um
but that painting
a picture
eventually you should be able to have
pokemon your card go live in the village
pasture pastries
the most pokemon a person can have with
them while out exploring is six
apparently not that we have anyone who
can manage that
wow they're all beginners when it comes
to pokemon huh
come now you too let's not dilly dally
captain celine awaits our report at the
headquarters
i'm on my way
[Music]
well let me look at the menu by the way
oh no that's something that's on the
menu what's the menu where is the menu
this is the menu oh
mario
i see
looks pretty good
looks very organized and tidy yeah
no problem with that i got something in
my eye
okay
yeah what is that what is that person
doing there
what are you selling
eggs there's an no that's not an
aggressor it's all cute wait what
the garage team is made up of several
clips let's see there is the security
construction and agriculture crips
and a few uh others besides
nobody are you gonna sell me something
later i don't know it looks pretty cute
i'm curious
[Music]
yeah we had this music before but even
for this one i i felt like it could have
needed a bit more pop and maybe a bit
more
japanese sound to it as well
but all right
so what do you say
i've got uh four pokemon now
[Music]
it seems we won't have to leave you to
die after all
congratulations i suppose you've passed
your trial you can hold on to that
satchel
i must admit you've impressed me i set a
high hurdle to judge whether a stranger
like yourself could be worthy but you
cleared it
this is yours the official uniform of
the service clubs
something cool to wear let's go
[Music]
yes
i will get changed present yourself in
uniform to our commander this is your
first official order from your captain
wait i have to use the one in my in
in my room right
or not
yeah okay
is that my room is that my house
but i don't even see myself in the
mirror how am i gonna properly dress
myself huh
i have a problem
[Music]
but okay i'll give it a try
huh
oh yeah
that looks
amazing
styling i
i do like the design of the clothes
very very much
um but i'm also excited to see
what other
clothes this game will be giving us
what are those
yeah the shoes look interesting
[Music]
wait was there supposed to be a hat
i'm not sure
i don't think so only the clothes and
the shoes i think
now i can go club shopping what
look at you in the survey club's uniform
you're rocking it better than i am but i
do wonder when the captain decided to go
ahead and get a uniform ready for you
hey she already she didn't admit it but
she had a feeling that i will need it
yes i say you've changed regarding your
accommodations you might continue to use
the room you slept in last night
you may wear this as well
[Music]
can someone make this so i can put it on
my head
maybe with my straight
hair you've changed kiawah what do you
mean
you may have changed my clothes right
not my personality or so right
good
now present yourself to the commander
all my bangs are gone
oh frick i love it
i love the character design
i think that might be
my favorite or one of my favorites
wait where's the commander
[Music]
oh above
but i mean out of pokemon uh
character designs
[Music]
second floor oh wait what's in these
rooms
[Music]
a maybe we ought to build some spare
logins in case anyone else falls out of
the sky
[Music]
yeah i guess so you're making a joke
are you doubting that i really came from
the sky
i i don't know where the hell i came
from
i'm not the one who's saying i did that
i'm not claiming it
soundcloud is pretty oh you look cool
[Music]
hello
nice um mustache
wow
i've been waiting for you
[Music]
i am uh wow okay what the [\h__\h] i am
kamado commander of the galaxy
expedition team
[Music]
you know you're madness at least
you've been briefed on your situation
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] including how you fell
from the river to the sky
now then come here come here let's see
what you're made of yeah face me comment
try to throw him charged at him uh
bad i am bad ideas all of them
[Music]
[\h__\h] idiot
you got some fight in you
your sumo needs work but i do see some
potential
[Music]
don't expect a warm welcome from
everyone naturally some will be slow to
trust an outsider who literally fell
right out of the blue
the superstitious humongous might see
your arrival as important of disaster
[Music]
but you passed the trial that was put to
you
no matter how odd you may seem you're
part of jupiter life village now
dedicate yourself to the work of the
galaxy
expedition team and complete the pokedex
please
but i want your kiawah
pokemon are terrifying creatures
keep your wits about you as you work
okay
complete
[Music]
are there
are there by the way already like
reports on how long this game is
how many hours for like
the gameplay
[Music]
i would like to know that
uh pretty long 70 60. holy [\h__\h] what
60 that's pretty long isn't it
30 40
40 to 60.
yeah
[Music]
14 hour speed runs huh
don't trust early estimations
it seems like longer than other pokemon
games though
i'm gonna wrap my blanket around me i
bought a new blanket
i bought a new blanket it's pink and it
has a
um it has a
a hood with um cat ears and a cat face
on it
yeah
soft blanket
wish
[Music]
also
and it has inside pockets or am i
wearing it wrong no it has inside
pockets i think what
[Music]
maximum comfy
cats everywhere
hell yeah
[Music]
okay
i look really weird but for some reason
you guys are not able to perceive it
you are not ready for this nerd look
that i'm rocking right now
so the commander has also accepted you
oh but understand this you begin as a no
star recruit among our ranks in other
words you have no rank at all
perform well as a member of the survey
corps and you will move up through the
ranks indeed engage you see the more you
add to the pokedex the higher rank will
become and working on the pokedex will
also of course bring you closer toward
the goal of yours
so seek out every last pokemon that's
not my goal that's your goal dude
i just adopted it because you forced me
to
here you will need this
pokeballs yay a recipe oh
a recipe one apricorn and one tumble
stone yeah
so i suppose i'll be mostly
um
crafting them and not buying them
oh 3 000 poke dollars
thank you
for the charity
i guess
uh okay you're an expert at crafting
yourself teach on your recruit what you
need to know yes teach me please
[Music]
oh you're you're wearing the old cat
kiana shirt thank you
my arm now my arm is feeling pretty sore
yes ma'am captain
get ready for a lesson for crafting
crafting means making items from scat
scratch
that's right whatever you need in your
survey work you'll mostly make yourself
some things you can buy at the general
store but it's good to try to be
self-sufficient oh
this way we can even catch pokemon with
pokeballs we've crafted ourselves
eh
but listen to me prattle on let's go to
the craftwork so you can try it yourself
wait what can i do it anywhere or do i
need to go somewhere
ah
crap i have to go somewhere
[Music]
are you almost cut merch is finally on
the way you're up oh let's go
got my cappy shirt and honey thank you
well done earning a place now team my
name is and oh
you are cute
i like her design she looks old but
still cute
my name is anthony i'm the local
clothier
the professor i said i read you a change
of clothes so here you go i do hope they
fit yeah
a change
every thank you mono and apparently
i hope you'll avail yourself to the of
the village's humble shops
i want to i want to
i hope it's not too expensive
hey hey this way to the craft works
i want to change wait
wait can i look at your um
inventory
a special parcel has a raft for your
name on it what
monojet
wait am i getting this for playing other
pokemon games so what's happening what's
happening what's happening
shaymin
what
i just you don't have to give me
everything for free i'm trying to see
what you sell
yeah yeah okay uh buy clothing
huh
no no no i wanna see
[Music]
oh i'm looking at
what am i looking at it's not changing
is it changing
what i don't see it changing oh it
what
[Music]
when i click on it it's
oh you can't worry
ah
i guess it's covered up by the cap
ah the hat is a hairstyle
uh no i don't want to buy it i don't
want to look at clothes
oh
that's the i got an everyday kimono
everyday trousers uh are we gonna get
more choice later on
some sandals
no no so far everything looks pretty
glasses cool everything looks pretty
similar
uh yes
a lot more
okay thank god
but i do wanna i don't wanna change
i wanna see uh what i got
uh-huh
oh modern jacket
looks
interesting
okay where why did i get this one
from what did i get that
oh my god that is hella adorable that's
from pearl diamond
is it from pearl specifically or
oopsie [\h__\h]
no
how i am
the colors are so cute yeah
um i think the sandals suit best
oh i can change my oyka oh let's go i
don't even have to buy them i have every
contact available to me um do you have a
purple or like
yes that works that kind of looks like
mine i suppose
or i mean it looks pretty gray actually
mm-hmm
ah right here's purple there we go
for sword and shield
this is for sword and shield
that's that's some kind of pokemon isn't
it
uh
yes
i mean the other outfit is cute too but
this is even cute every day kawaii oh my
god what about hair oh my god tell me
tell me you're also going to give me
something for free no
500 i pay ahead of time
cheat what if i don't want anything
afterwards i'm just gonna i just want to
go window shopping
[Music]
uh-huh
that's cute
um i think i like this one what about
this one
okay well hopefully we're also gonna get
different choices
later on but yeah what if i cancel this
looks kind of like a mom style as well
what if i cancel will i still get my
money back
gold black
white
chest ah i look like a mom
yeah
she's
the service corps does look best
uh
but
but yeah maybe with chestnut
see the gold is the gold is so greenish
that it almost is as green as my clothes
chestnut is nice though
where's that
oh
eyebrows
white
[Laughter]
you were eyebrows
okay well
i guess i'll go with that
for the hair dye what extra 500
oh [\h__\h]
oh well
well
worth it uh just a slight change but
hooray
no that looks very cute i like the
chestnut oh
yes yes cute
all right where were we supposed to go
we were supposed to go here excuse me
for the little break
i love this table it's cute
what a deal
this here's the craftworks and that
there is the that there is the workbench
it's where your craftings ah that was a
workbench so when we go out we will
always have a workbench with us
[Music]
when you step up to the workbench uh
i'll supply your materials to make some
pokeballs call it a present to celebrate
passing your trial thanks for the
membership welcome
mystery gift is more fashion what
[Music]
okay
workbenches
let's give it a try we want to make a
poke ball
and we see the necessary materials we
see that we have 20 each
so um i'm not going to make 20. i'm
going to make 15.
okay that was well very simple
okay
[Music]
of sneezing today good morning good
morning
uh-huh now that's some fun craftsmanship
hard to believe this was your first time
stepping up to the workbench my girl
you'll recall of course that pokemon
possess the odd power to shrink
themselves down with the pokeballs we
craft we can make use of that power to
catch him
also also that more pokemon species can
be duly recorded in a pokedex
and on that note here you are
oh thank you
what does it look like
a pokedex it's it's a book
it's literally just
paper
old-fashioned
a volume for compiling the collected
results of much pokemon research
professor levington continually adds to
it with each report made on a new
pokemon species
okay so these are i've seen the pokemon
i've seen so far
and
these
wait what is the difference ah these are
this is the regions
oh
well that is very very uh detailed what
the hell
how many times you've seen it uh use
certain moves
uh-huh
thank you for giving that to me
um i preferred this volume just for you
i hope it ain't you well in your aim to
seek out all the pokemon there are in
this grand region
it'll take plenty of research tasks to
help the professor complete the pokedex
i've got to get going on those myself
i'd be all too happy to explain more
about the research tasks i could use
your assistance with
come join me at the field lance camp
whenever you're ready my good kiawah
alrighty
okay time to time out uh that spamming
dude please
[Music]
bones are you here
excuse me i couldn't help but over here
if you're going to the field lance camp
would you mind taking care of a request
for me
what's sleepy
i'm standing guard so i can't leave my
post but i'll be here at the
headquarters if you want to talk about
it
[Music]
people who have something to ask you
will have a request i can display above
them if you fulfill a request you may
receive a nice reward
okay what is the quest you would like to
give to me
right on it
well okay
[Music]
i'll do it myself fine i'll do it myself
hey so there's this pokemon called
wormpole have you heard of it
you know
well you see i was having a chat with
professor lavinton and he told me that
after a pokemon gains a certain amount
of experience through battling and like
it will sometimes change his appearance
and become stronger
it's called evolution you said it was a
phenomenon called evolution exactly i'm
smart i'm smart
[Music]
evolving pokemon
some pokemon can undergo evolution which
changes their appearance and stats if
one of your pokemon has met the
wait a second is evie called evie
because it evolves into so many other
things does evie come from evolution
no way
no
way what
[Music]
[Laughter]
well
what i mean i've
in my childhood i played the games in
german and it doesn't really make that
same
um reference in german
and
wait what what the hell was the name
again in in in german
what was the name again in german
[Music]
and when you're playing a game in german
then you're not
you're not gonna think about the word
evolution
because in german the word evolution
also is a different word although if we
is even closer to evolution than evie is
um
yeah yeah
oh evolution
well okay
[Music]
clung no no i mean of course we have
some
english words that we pronounce in a
german way but we usually call a pokemon
evolution and vita and speak long no no
you you should agree with me on that one
yes
we the game uses the word vita and
victor not evolution
get out of here
[Music]
i have to stand my ground
okay you'll be able to select the evolve
option when viewing the pokemon in the
satchel what
i choose when it evolves
[Music]
so for everyone who you know usually
presses the the x button or whatever the
b button or whatever it is because they
don't want them to evolve you don't even
have to do that
because it just stays what it is until
you decided
wow i wonder why they did that
i wonder why
i i honestly i do like the surprising
moment of after a battle having a pop-up
that your pokemon is evolving that is
that makes me go doki-doki
but okay
okay i guess
because it's annoying but i mean
i mean
who how many people are there that don't
want their pokemon evolve
all the time it's not that often is it
you want a wrinkle sure if i find one
i'll give you a worm ball
neither hold on
okay where are we supposed to go
there's another side quest
shanks ears
you want the shanks
i can give you my shanks i'm not going
to use it
yes oh i can show you
i have sinks
oh do you want me to
throw it at you
be careful
[Music]
look at look at it
no
ah this way okay
would you look at that ah you're looking
at his butt cute foot
[Music]
i look so happy
yes it looks like a star yeah yeah
um what a bone stuck in my throat only
the throat's my brain and the bones of
thought
what are you talking about
i'm late and i got potions out of that
that was worth it
okay
uh
wait what's our main quest right now i
guess we need to go outside
[Music]
uh
this one
in order to complete the pokedex you'll
need to come accomplish research tasks
speak to lovington okay
so he's waiting there for me i suppose
[Music]
oh
let's go explore
rydo let's get to it then shall we in
order to complete this pokedex of ours
there are great many research tasks i'll
need your help to carry out my girl
the details of these tasks can be found
in the pokedex for you to reference
anytime
aha
research tasks are the tasks you need to
carry out to complete uh the ones i
already looked at like how often it uses
a certain attack and so on
yeah yeah
when you are focused on the wild pokemon
in the field using the set l button you
can also instantly check the research
tasks for that species by pressing the
down button to open your pokedex right
on
right to that page some pokemon have
some unusual research tasks so be sure
to check them out okay
okay
thank you
now there's one more chimpkin nugget of
wisdom i've got to share camera
share do tell wild pokemon may attack
you at any time when they do dodge like
your life depends on it are you going to
tell me how to dodge oh
look just watch me would you then you'll
be able to copy what i do
do a backflip do a backflip here i go
eating a front flip
[Laughter]
nice
a timely dodge will keep you from
getting hurt by the fierce attacks of
wild pokemon and that's key if you'd
rather not end up blacked out in some
field like i did
when those things got me with under
shock i might have been done for it if
the security corps hadn't come and saved
me
oh man that's scary
but hey no need to worry you've got me
here to give you tips i'll teach you
plenty
thank you
now what is the button to dodge um
excuse me
i'm using a controller
why thank you
bro what about what about sprinting boy
i'm coming
aspiration hill we are back
done
get ready for some survey corpse wisdom
focus on the pokemon of the dead l
button and then press down the down
button
okay
did you see that your research tests for
b roof include one about how many you've
caught
what
catching one will do it you've gotta get
two and four and more [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] ew
but do i really need to do that ew
that's not fetch
when it's time to battle pokemon
remember the captain's switching wisdom
if you have items out press x to read
your pokemon
give it a try now if you want i'll go on
ahead
why do i need somebody
that's not fetch at all
you are
don't quite understand the focus yet but
okay
[Music]
you are cute but i don't want so many of
you oh wait i forgot to
push the thingy do i have to do it again
wait let me focus on you
sir
uh-huh what is that how you're supposed
to look at it
uh
number of heavy specimens you've caught
heavy badoofs away
what what do they want from me
number defeated
number of different forms you've
obtained
okay
well what how how
how do i know how many they want
uh-huh
chunky
they want me to catch a fat one 25 what
kill 15
oh shit's coming at me
the numbers mason what do they mean
you
what
[Music]
at least you're not fighting back
and you're gonna make me use up all my
pokeballs
what that's what am i gonna do with so
many poke uh with so many b dubs
what are you gonna do somebody can i
sell them can i sell them on the black
pokemon market at least come on what
corny
i can release them oh will i get the
balls back though
make a big doop soup
[Applause]
i like exploring this though
oh yeah this is starly so this is
charlie's
i know i'm laying it on fake but don't
forget to open your pokedex when you
focus on the pokemon to check your
research test yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah dead l down alone
[Music]
styling next
one task is to catch starling without
being spotted ah
is that so
okay
we'll try to be stealthy as [\h__\h]
all right we're quite careful
quite
ah
let me take a look
number you've caught without being
spotted oh apparently one already number
defeated wait but
it's not like just the ones that are
marked red on the left side are done
right
or i don't understand
because like the first one number caught
four is marked red
but i only call it three
do they really need me to catch 25
is in progress
but why does the the second one not have
the red mark
important ah the red ones are important
for progress and the other ones are
voluntary
uh-huh
so for the starling
they just they don't even care about the
one being spotted
you only need to do one tier of them
okay thank god so i need to defeat a
bidoof
and i need to
defeat uh starly as well
but they
but for the progress don't they want me
to evolve one as well
red is more progress
okay i don't really understand this so
well
for pre-orders oh [\h__\h] no i didn't
pre-order the game i just bought it
today
only the red one
what if i don't do it will i not be able
to progress in the story or
hm
rain rat is my main objective no right
is side objective
i know
but okay he told me to not be noticed
even though it's not a main objective
okay bunk
i don't think it noticed me
oh [\h__\h] they noticed me though how about
we fight one of those
so
what if i
throw out the shanks
and we fight
starly is keeping his card up starting
with what you little [\h__\h]
your little [\h__\h] wasting my time not
even letting me attack first
huh
[Applause]
go get me some berries
thank you
does he want to talk to me
oh [\h__\h]
look at that was that a hello
was that a starling or
[Music]
what do you mean i didn't pre-order the
game
what is that i said shanks
it's it's typing something right oh [\h__\h]
uh what's strong against you here fight
fight this i have too many of these
doesn't matter if they die yes
[Music]
they look so happy about seeing the
videos like their friends ow what the
[\h__\h]
uh no uh hi uh
roll out
go
nice
big is fixated on the roll up
we defeated the [\h__\h]
you know we didn't have big doof in our
team um in the previous game so i
wouldn't mind taking bidoof in our team
this time
see i'm already getting lost because
it's
quite fast tonight
you don't get me some berries thank you
apricorn that's what i need for um
pokeballs
it shanks from xbox lobby telling me
mean stuff
mommy
mommy the doof is so mean
go get him go get those berries
good boy
who's a good boy where's where's my
quest over there that is far away uh
what do you want uh me to do with the
shanks
don't attack me
no no no
no
no huh
could i please
huh
there you go
uh
number you defeated with ground tap
moves was that not the ground tab
sometimes you've seen it click attack
number you've evolved okay so i need to
evolve a shanks
freak
[Music]
on the screen oh god i'm not using it
oh
[\h__\h]
we're all on this rock nada hoda
ouch
are you good
i can tackle now
oh [\h__\h]
it's gonna die
jinx he's looking around oh
maybe uh time to uh no uh
[Music]
no
wait
go
yes switch to the other videos
what do i have a video for me for
if i'm not gonna use it
go go
[Music]
wow okay so i don't have um an hp
showing but when something hits me
the screen kind of um
breaks i suppose
uh but now it's gone so does that mean i
i'm healed
basically
three hits and i'm out
okay but is it back to normal now back
to like default
i suppose
what should i network
uh
what
i need to defeat one i haven't defeated
one yet already
um
[Music]
how about chinks
sneak 100
ah the last one run away right right no
why you run away what is it with you
what's the matter of y'all
there's two over there one of them will
fight me right
oh they're so cute
they're sleeping
you caught stallion underwear well now
you have to fight me
now you have to fight me find a shot
[Music]
we've gotta catch the worm ball i don't
know if he went for if we want one for
our team but
oh [\h__\h] let's run it's not running away
don't run away don't run away
what is that about the signs above its
head
showing me
how high the chances of getting it but
oh well i guess so
yeah we got it
we got it
the only thing that's bothering
bothering me right now is that i can't
cut down all this grass i come i come
straight out of playing lynx awakening
and i just really want to cut down this
grass man
oh that's tough
yeah yeah i know about the era's meaning
but i don't see any arrows above this
pokemon's head
it's sleeping
oh you're so cute
that is so cute
wait so what uh what if i um
what if i
uh okay
oh want to change
wait how do i get how do i get the
others into my team
do i have to do that in the city
can i not switch it out now ah for this
i have to go back to the camp okay
[Music]
although i might turn on bgm in the
future whenever we are out in the field
it's a bit too quiet for my taste oh
there's a fireplace over there
i know my quest is somewhere else but oh
no it's not a fireplace it's just uh-huh
maybe the next area
[Music]
what btm are we gonna use i'm gonna find
something fitting
oh there's one of
those ah
what are they called also can i get this
stone
no probably need a tool for it okay
okay let's catch this boy
there's nowhere to hide really
oh [\h__\h]
you wanna oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
panic move
what
attack
oh it doesn't show me if attacks are
very effective
huh um
that was very effective
nice
oh
i should have maybe caught it
should have maybe caught the pokemon um
okay anyway i need to talk to this boy
he wants to talk to me
i'm a big girl now yeah i don't need to
gain the game or you guys to help me
that much anymore perhaps no
no i don't need your help but uh this
one i remembered electricity is strong
against the water yeah
around here you can find the pokemon
called boise
i just met it i know about it oh it
respawned nice now maybe now i can catch
it thanks for respawning it
just like shanks you'll need the belly
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh nice flex
if you take too much damage within a
short time you'll be in danger of a
blacking out you can tell you're in
danger when the edges of the screen turn
red damage goes away over time but you
won't begin to recover if you're still
being targeted by a wild pokemon if you
take further damage after the edges of
the screen have turned red you'll become
overwhelmed and blackout
that is a cool feature
and speaking of which your research
tasks for breezel include seeing it use
a certain move you gotta see the move
and battle for it to count towards the
task so battling's extra key here oh
no
all right let's try to get it to attack
me well not me but my pokemon
okay
[Music]
let's not kill it too quickly
i also want to catch it
but i also want to see and attack me
do something
[Music]
do something what if i wait
will it eventually
[Music]
how do i skip a turn
how do i skip again
it's distracted
[Music]
no i wanted to use an attack man
oh well i'll throw a pokeball
[Music]
was it just replaced by a leak oh did it
did it drop a leak
what is that
i'm supposed to use oh if i use it
myself that comes to it too
ah
oh look at that sleeping boy
oh now that works
change focus i'm pressing a but it
doesn't work
ah
it's making a cute sleeping sound as
well
so cute
okay wait where do we go next
where's the
uh
ah here he is
what's up
it didn't do anything to you just the
berries good boy
wait you get exp for that
you're doing pretty well for a mystery
stranger from the sky
mm-hmm here a little reward for keeping
up with me your own crafting kids
crafting cake
what do you mean crafting kid
what is that
crafting kit a kit containing everything
you might need for crafting even when
there is no workbench around however you
can only use the materials you have in
your satchel
ah
what so on the working bench i can use
materials can i buy materials or is it
just like things i have in the storage
or so
craft anywhere nice
hey
here's a recipe for potions too
thank you that goes i don't
obtain the recipe for crafting potions
or on varian medicine week okay i have i
have those
with a crafting kit you can craft items
anywhere using whatever materials are in
your satchel as long as you've got an
apricot in the tub so you can make a
pokeball anytime i'm running out of them
soon
or with an oranberry and a medicinal
leak you can whip up a potion
that question
research going all right you can see if
you've got tasks ready to turn in on the
pokedex cover
what ah
task of unreported data
how do i turn it in do you have to go to
the professor
uh okay okay
report your research as you request the
laminar sufficient number of pokemon
research punch alrighty i guess we're
already ready to go back look at all
those burps staring at me
you want some berries too
oh it's running away
he doesn't even care for me
[Music]
wow
this these pink flowers are nice
is there a way to uh quickly
quickly um
go back
maybe not now but maybe later
what i convert pokemon at the ore to
mine is
really
well yeah
there is fast travel later uh-huh
but i'm gonna have to walk around this
way
later there's a mound
i've seen it oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
i remember seeing that in trailers
true okay looking forward to the
mountain is there like only one option
or can you
like an mmorpgs
get different kind of mounts that would
be cool
hello
i've been i've done some tasks
yes i got a craft okay yeah
[Music]
give me some rewards money
how much how much
yes
one thousand six hundred oh
okay if i'm getting money for those uh i
don't mind working hard
[Music]
oh i see most illuminating i love the
pokedex of this new data
by carrying out research tasks and
submitting survey reports you'll raise
the research levels of the pokemon
species you encounter
if you raise the pokemon's entry to
level 10 that entry will be considered
complete
and you will have unlocked all of the
detailed information to be had about
that species
oh as you can carry out tasks and
complete the pokedex entries for
different species you'll also gain
pokemon research points which you can
view on the cover of your pokedex
once you've earned a certain number of
points you'll be able to move up for the
ranks of the galaxy expedition team
oh good luck at work thanks for coming
uh what are we looking at now research
over two
six
ten
shanks is complete
species newly registered are updated six
more points points
i'm so close to the next rank
not quite there yet you'll need to
complete a few more tasks before you're
ready to grow up a rank i'd recommend
you work your way through b dupes and
charlie's test oh thanks for the hint i
suppose
okay he wants me to continue
uh all right we doof and starling
let me see
i think they wanted a heavy-duty
change your team oh can i do that at the
headquarters wait a second let me drink
[Music]
i can find evie now
talk to the guy in red okay
but first let me go back
if i can do that at the camp then i want
to do it
because i got too many bidoofs in my
team
i think uh starting from the next
episode on i will also do um
um
oh no no no resting no no no no no
i will do okay
i will do i will do the thing that i did
in the last um pokemon gameplay i will
show my team on the screen
at all times
like the little icons because i just
think it's cute even though it's uh
not really necessary but yeah which one
do we want
oh
i'll go with this one
and get rid of
this one
and now we can also get boisel
ponita is here as well
whoa
okay
now we have all kinds of different
pokemon
okay
let's go
i suppose if you can like rest here
what is that
oh a berry
apricot i'm guessing that depending on
the time of the day
i will be able to meet different pokemon
um
what are you gonna tell me galaxy team
member wasn't there like a team galaxy
in a different pokemon game and wasn't
weren't they evil
yeah okay thank you
jump
ah
so it do be true oh should i have rested
because there are like some of my
pokemon are
oh
okay i should have rested sorry
we're going back one one more time one
more time or should we not maybe not
we'll be fine
it'll be fine
we're just gonna try to not use them
we just need a few more details about a
few certain pokemon but for some reason
i'm not meeting any at all
there are shanks but jinx was completed
there's a bidoof
let's see
uh
nope
[Music]
okay what do we need uh we need to def
what we have never defeated abidoof
okay
uh and uh number you evolve
every specimen okay let's defeat a few
what's strong what's strong against
bidoof
hello
probably everything
he's so cute
fighting attacks oh [\h__\h]
well
the fight
i don't think i have fighting attacks oh
that's very weak
[Music]
um
let's try wurmple
let's see what wormple can do
[Music]
how can you even see whirlpool it's so
tiny
poison
[Music]
it's so small you can't even see it
you learned a new attack
and there it is
it's dead
nice
we killed it
so
the top all around the badoof can
uh get these minerals
you can start us and dumbbell stone oh
good job
thank you badou
very useful
wait i'm not sure do i even what do i
need with you
no i want to see
[\h__\h]
can i look at the
damage
when i'm already in battle can i not
look at the the the goals
[Music]
shocking well we did that already but
maybe it's good to do it more often
good job
noise
okay maybe we can also do something with
the another worm ball
[Music]
we can catch more we can
i can't try to catch a light specimen
um
catch him without being spotted but
we've already been spotted on the feet
we have never defeated one
okay
wow
i shall fight
i don't know what's effective
not a little doll
wrapper is looking around you think you
got time to look around you're gonna die
[Music]
all right
move mastered new move oh shanks has a
mastered move what does that mean
okay so uh
you i want to catch maybe
still gotta get used to
the right buttons to choose
you already noticed me didn't you oh
[\h__\h] hello
[Music]
oh we get xp for catching as well now
i just noticed that now
oops [\h__\h]
don't run away
[Music]
okay
get
and then we want some berries as well
oh
what are you thinking about attacking me
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
uh
i think starly hmm
if i catch another one
that would be pretty good but it's
running it do be running away now
this one's running away too
i'll try it anyway
he wants to fight now and it runs away
yeah we really gotta do the stylings
without being noticed
okay okay okay
[Music]
i don't see it
i do see it
[Music]
come on come on steli come to me the
mother of birds thank you
good boy
i'm a good mommy trust me i'll i'll
treat you well
meaning i'll throw you away later
probably but
what about the doops again
no
[\h__\h]
they didn't want to catch you
by accident
okay okay
i will kill that one
wait that's a new pokemon what the [\h__\h]
it's a new pokemon
uh shall we attack it first
maybe we shall attack first
it's a baby pokemon isn't it
uh no no uh
look at that let's see how much damage
that does
oh quite a lot
[Music]
[\h__\h]
but we've at least seen one
oh [\h__\h]
i think i see a pokemon on me
i feel like
[Music]
looking cute over there
i will it's probably aggressive right it
probably will attack me anyway
it's looking pretty good in this game it
looks uh very young
hey
i caught it unaware hell yeah i did
quick attack i um yeah
i don't have a water attack yet
that was a rare find really the mime
junior damn it
[Music]
i think i wanna it's too strong to move
i shall give the pokeball a try
[Music]
go come on come on come on come on come
on come on
but
as i said we're not gonna use pokemon
that we used in the
in diamond pearl
um
so
unfortunately as much as i love konita
it's not gonna be in our team
yeah
[\h__\h] i can't stop collecting [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
shall we defeat you
again huh
[Music]
the sunset yeah the sun is setting
the time is changing
i'll crunch it let's go we learned the
water attack
[Music]
check out
dead
shiny i don't really care about shinies
let's slowly make our way back because
we're so far away
it's getting dark
oh
he got what's done
where are the pokemon huh
where are you all
where are they
man
ghost pokemon is this the night music
it's triple
oh [\h__\h] scary oh [\h__\h]
wait with that music
and then appearing them appearing it
sounds it's pretty scary i gotta give
you that i don't know what to fight it
with
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] it's coming at me
shall we catch it
confusion i might hurt myself huh
[Music]
i want to catch it yeah
go back with more points
[Music]
okay
i hope this is not too strong
[Music]
okay not very effective
is it not gonna fly away i hope not
okay time to catch it
my introduction to pokemon uh one of the
gameboy games but i don't remember
i played a lot of them
in
junior high school
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
it did not want to be caught
oh
it's enraged
[Music]
that's it
okay that's making it into my team i
don't know what what i want it to be
i don't know what i wanted to turn into
but i know i want it
[Music]
um
shall we first pick a fight with it
let's use uh starling maybe
oh my god oh my god
we will choose according to what we need
like element wise i think no no not new
not yes you
evie
maybe we can um
let's attack
if i'm in a bush
i can just tap i can't shoot oh
oh well
i hope that's not true if that [\h__\h] is
level free oh well
that did barely do and what it runs away
oh no no how rare is that no no
give me another one
i should have i should have gone for the
catch right away
ah
oh no
[Music]
how fast do they respawn
oh wait
oh that's a bit of
you have the same color you look like
eevees
oh
evie is really rare
[Music]
all right said adios amigos
resting recesses ones
i wanna find my ear
yeah
[\h__\h]
oh
well they are so the punitas really glow
nicely
um
we caught one right but we didn't defeat
one yet
i think we wanna
try defeating one huh
i don't think it noticed me
oh [\h__\h]
oh boyzilla's already pretty oh damaged
but i don't care
this is very effective
hell yeah can i take another hit
[Music]
not bad
what about evie
evie
evie maybe if i catch a badoof then
instead of the bidoof an eevee will
spawn
i have potions
i guess i could use a porsche how many
do i have eight okay
there you go
badoof becomes an eevee well hopefully
[Music]
we can try to catch another one
maybe
maybe we'll get a heavy specimen
[Music]
are you heavy
is it a chunk it's not a chunk
no it is a chunk it is a chunk
oh [\h__\h]
oh okay okay that was a that was okay
we got a chunky one yeah
hell yeah
wait no evie i will come back and get
myself an eevee
sooner or later
what about the drift loons man
while i have one here
oh
what
no i wanna look at it huh am i just
using the focus wrong or am i too far
away i don't want to get too close it
will notice there we go
no
not
huh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i want to look at my goals there we go
am i using it wrong
[\h__\h] man call it night number defeated
uh number you've defeated with ghost
type moves times you've seen
confusion hypnosis
investigated wherever draperon truly
does play with kids method unknown
side quest oh
okay well this one we want to defeat
oh
driftling you're actually pretty scary
in this game to me
i don't know what you think about water
attacks
uh
you don't care much
[Music]
but we'll go with it
oh
um
[Music]
i know i know i know i know
i know about the pokedex entry
what is this left right thingy
what
what the [\h__\h] is that
strong style
angle style
why did the game not tell me about this
nanny go dance
oh that was pretty weak though
[Music]
does that use up more ap
or what happens when i do that
ah
freshening very threatening look
tutorial later okay okay
well
nice silk
oh and the night has passed
and no evie
good morning everyone
good morning
i wonder if the eevee only shows up at
night though
or was that just
lucky
oh
the music
uh i guess the music only plays when
another time um
starts to introduce itself because now
it's gone again
that was a nice music what do you want
oh
[Music]
let's try this
it does ah it's okay
[Music]
it's okay
thankfully we're
high level enough
oh wow that did do much less damage than
the strong style
[Music]
learning by doing
without being told by the game
[Music]
here we go
good
job well it picked a fight with me so
what can i do
yo if you guys see an eevee go crazy
go crazy chat if you've seen evie i want
it
[Music]
mary's
yes i don't need tutorials i have my
chat to tell me everything
okay if i don't get a new rank now then
i don't know what you want from me i did
so much now
i i saw so many new pokemon
hell
i'm gonna read him normally for now
because the male voice is killing me
i see you caught six pokemon card and
report yes
[Music]
next doll
yes yes what only 884
what
but rank up please
most illuminating i'll update our
pokedex
uh huh
oh oh oh here it comes here comes
yes
by far
rank up oh but i'm still no star not a
hotel
you've made good progress on these
research tests kiawah i do believe
you're ready to move up oh i am ready
let's head back to the village yes
it's time for me to get a star
hell yeah it is
uh
oh oh yeah we can give i think one side
quest uh back
i did
but wait i wasn't the ramble guy did i
run past him
huh
wasn't the wormful guy somewhere here
you want a starling
see she got the mom hair style
[Music]
stylist darling
here i'll have a i have styling what
[Music]
what
oh you mean
after i completed all the starly goals
is that what you mean
[Music]
what okay hoof uh i don't know how close
we are to that
um
let me see
[Music]
oh wait what is down here
no no it doesn't need me in order to
complete it it doesn't ask me to do like
25 catches it just wants me to do an
evolution right
okay so once my evolution evolutionize
evolute uh evo evolve
evolve it above
[Laughter]
then we can come back here
okay probably
where's the whirlpool person though
hello
how's it going can i catch this pokemon
opera
[Music]
pretty cute man
english is hard yes
have fun thank you thank you
are you looking at this
[Music]
you have made progress it seems you have
earned yourself stuff
for this you have officially attained
oracle first star in the galaxy
expectation team
hell to the yeah
is this the
badges
are we not gonna have badges are we just
gonna have stars
i guess i mean it would make sense that
there are no arenas because literally
they just started out
catching pokemon
that would make sense
wait so there are no arenas but i'm sure
we will have enough battles anyway
there are no gyms
not you can now use heavy balls pokemon
of up to level 20 will also obey your
orders reliably okay so this is really
like a
gym badge in terms of it will give me
these options
they will be more generous now okay have
these as well there are favorite recipes
you'll need for crafting whoa
[Music]
episode
oh i will need that
that a stranger like you should fall
from the sky and yet flourish among us
like this is a testament to your native
talent and hard work
most people prefer it when things are
simple enough to be judged on face value
alone
and proving your worth by moving up for
our ranks is something anyone can
understand
keep at it and even if you did fall from
the sky people may be more willing to
accept you
working your way for the ranks will also
be a help if you wish to make a life for
yourself here a higher rank will grant
you access to more types of pokeballs
and greater rewards
yeah she does not have eye brows and
that makes her very sense
for today at least you've earned
yourself a meal at the wallflower and a
good night's rest
[Music]
oh messy da gohanda food time
oh it's the same food is that the only
thing i can order here
so kiawah my girl
i believe a jolly good congratulations
is in order well done on learning your
first star wreck oh yeah
our usual order of potato once it tastes
even better when there's something to
celebrate it does look yummy
why is
hey by the way have you taken on that
request
what
which one
most people here don't know much about
pokemon you've noticed right so it's our
job as distributors to take care of any
issues that crop up because of that
we're basically pokemon problem solvers
[Music]
some people will ask for you for help
when you talk with them without the
requests you will need
to be claimed from the blackboard i keep
in my lab
that one might be a bit a better fit for
kiama than me i don't think i'll be able
to pull it off unless i get better at
pokemon battling first
oh he has no confidence guys
oh yes your request came from maya of
the diamond clan diamond clan
that sounds dope
the people of the diamond clan have
lived here in history since before the
galaxy team arrived whoa
they might have more experience
[Music]
but we can discuss all tomorrow okay
yummy
nice
the next day
yo
what
up hey camera before i go meet my about
that request mind showing me how you're
doing bad oh
wait do i not have a rival in this game
wait i can say no
they gave me the option to say no
[Music]
bit busy here that was the other option
i wonder if we would have really not
fought then
oh i do not i do not get the okay
okay i mean it would have been pretty
cool
if we because i think a lot of people
are annoyed sometimes by these battles
it's an illusion oh man
what pastures you want to fight me
somewhere else not here okay
lewis and i'll
they gave me the illusion of choice and
i didn't even choose it
[Music]
oh wait [\h__\h] uh do i have to fight you
with my starly now what your plate's
full what
i'm going to be straightforward review
about something
uh-huh
[Music]
i don't understand how anyone can handle
taking on pokemon in battle i know i'm a
survey corps member and i've even got my
own partner but i just can't do it
partner
that's right take a look at my very own
[Music]
he got a [\h__\h] pikachu and yeah that
was a weird sound
that's a pikachu sound oh maybe maybe
it's a ditto what do you call it in
english i think it might be ditto as
well
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] you don't deserve a
pikachu you don't even know how to use
it during things attack i should have
had my pikachu fight on my side you know
what it wouldn't even have been that
helpful because electro versus electro
is just a pain in the ass but okay
um
why should this thing be able to fire
electricity
you're stupid so you don't deserve it
give it to me give it to me
but watching you while we're completing
those research tasks convinced me
if i want to do my survey corps work
well my partner and i have got to be a
team
and our first step toward being a real
team is to battle your team
[Music]
quite skinny only because
[\h__\h] i'm using charlie i don't know
what's strong against uh [\h__\h] i don't
have ground
whatever we'll we'll do it this way
i'm paralyzed let's go
oh [\h__\h] okay
what's coming at me
[Music]
[Applause]
don't make me say
[Music]
oh well well this is not a nice look
we're good
um
let's go
i don't want to purple potions
i don't care
oh my god
we're paralyzed
i think a good tackle just need one good
tackle
[Music]
man
it's time for shanks
he took my whirlpool and he threw it on
the ground
and
what about bite how does bite work on
your pikachu
oh hell yeah [\h__\h] you because you should
have done this from the beginning
this could be ash from the past you're
correct
that's maybe that's why he has a pikachu
because he's the ancestor of ash
oh
you seem so in sync with your pokemon
but what if i chose the the male
character then wouldn't this be a girl
and then it wouldn't quite make so much
sense i mean i guess it's a female
ancestor then i guess so
um that was amazing
i killed like wow a brazilian of your
pokemon oh i feel so strong now i'm
confident now
damn you're pretty strong aren't you
i feel like you're gonna be like a super
famous pokemon one day because you're
that strong i don't know i just got this
feeling in myself you [\h__\h] rocked it
man
[Music]
all right uh anyway i gotta think about
how to make good merchandise out of this
pokemon and then make a build a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] um
huge uh emporium about around it make it
famous and make a lot of money out of it
become a millionaire
oh this one doesn't stay in this ball
yeah i am
i guess the first step will be cartoon
me might be getting a little friendlier
with one another empire yes yes that's
what i mean
by the way the professor said pokemon
have these things called types which
apparently make a big difference in how
battles go pikachu here seems to be an
electric type for example
take a screenshot
take a [\h__\h] screenshot take a [\h__\h]
screenshot
oh thank you
[Laughter]
to the [\h__\h] screenshot taking i'm
going to take a snip snap snippy snap pc
screenshot
snapping tool snipping tool
my cheat sheet they give me a [\h__\h]
cheat sheet
no other game ever gave me a cheat sheet
before like this
hell yeah
thank you
both pokemon moves have types
yeah yeah
what what is this what's the difference
what is it what is this
what is this what's the difference
[Music]
uh-huh
wait this is where we're confusing this
is confusing it's easier to just ask the
chat
it's the bottom half oh
i
just want to ask the chat to be on this
but okay uh
cheat
one let me save
uh
yeah and then number two
super shock
cheat two okay
[Music]
thank you game why did you do that man
um so you're the one that you recruit
everyone's talking is this my rival
you are now my rival wow uh
hmm
you look strong
you have an interesting character design
i don't know if i think you're cute or
intimidating
you got a cute face funny hair
red is good tall yeah big big woman tall
woman so your soul
voice
the name
captain of the security corps
[Music]
oh cute
i see you've got some fighting you
figured i'd stop by and give what advice
i could
captain caesar is a master of an ancient
martial art where you guide pokemon in
battle
now listen if your pokemon truly
mastered its moves it can actually use
them in different styles
holy [\h__\h] she's big
on the one hand you can choose to
deliver a move in an ah strong style
the move will deal more damage but
afterward it will take longer for your
pokemon to act
[Music]
on the other hand you can choose to
unleash a move in the agile style or egg
such a move will have less power behind
it but your pokemon can act more quickly
afterward in truly favorable conditions
it might even get out two moves before
the opponent can act
strong style moves agile style moves
agile
and of course regular moves choose which
is right for a given situation and
direct your pokemon with a little nudge
[Music]
this is more pp than usual uh-huh i
thought so
oh but the agile one also uses more pp
raises the user's action speed but only
for that one turn right
[Music]
oh one for your mouth
and she's like me she
look at us
would you look at us
wait let's take a picture together
wait a second
[Music]
she's got the same spirit it might be an
uh
an ancestor of myself
oh one more thing if you want to teach
your pokemon some powerful moves just
let me know
alright
well that's certainly handy to find out
about before going to tackle mice quest
you remember i mentioned it earlier
i'm supposed to meet her down past the
foot of aspiration hill you should come
along too okay
let me check in with pokemon you bring
maybe even teaching news
should we do that i don't know
i don't know
should we teach
do i have to pay for
[Music]
i them new moves maybe
i mean who really needs an extra move
right now i feel like they're gonna
maybe it's not really necessary now
they're still keep learning new moves
anyway
um
i don't know right now it's looking
pretty good
new moves your coverage yeah i feel like
it's too early
but i do want to see what she could
teach so actually let me take a look
what do you have
oh are these
are these attacks that rowlet would
learn
anyway eventually
ariel ace
false swipe a restraint attack that
prevents the target from fainting the
target is left with at least one hp
huh
what
restraint attack that prevents the
target from fainting
so i use that when i wanna catch pokemon
that uh
but without killing them
[Music]
what if i use it once
and it's down to one hp and i use it
again it was
why would i use it again
okay okay but if it's a two hp and i use
it again it will not go below one hp and
i don't know
[Laughter]
yeah i guess um
[Music]
here we go yeah
yeah
thank you
rallies full of moves ah i mean we can
still like switch it out and then always
take it back right because we we can
like have um a [\h__\h] ton of oh yeah right
now it doesn't even have it in its skill
set i guess i have to
uh
[Music]
how do i oh
how do i give the move to rowlet
where the [\h__\h] am i
how do i go to my pokemon
here
uh can i like uh there we go
no
what
how do i give it the move oh yeah
someone
huh
oh
i did give it to rawa didn't i
ah there we go ah
wow
yes
i mean if i have a spot open it would be
nice if they could just add it to that
open spot i feel like that would make
sense but okay
all right
we got full swipe
i thought that was a chicken food
oh it's a little shrine a mini shrine
and they're giving i think is that mochi
oh
there are some like small trends like
that um as well not only the big ones
that you know with the big big big uh
gates
around it lucille sells various
protective challenges that come in handy
when you're out exploring the wilds i'm
here to give thanks to the guardian of
this shrine who watches over all in
juvenile life village
and you child if you're here with the
prayer for the shrine perhaps my champs
can help tell me what is your wish oh eh
[Music]
stay in good health
oh you have a charm for that
oh
we can buy like literal like shrine
charms yeah that's cute because like
they have similar like good health and
good study
and uh good love or whatever charms and
shrines that's cute
i don't know do i want it i guess i'll
take it do i have money yes i do
this job is imbued with the mysterious
powers of the shrine guardian may it
serve you well
warning charm r
i'll kill a mysterious town that holds
the power to protect the person from
being afflicted with status conditions
ah this type of can i give this to a
pokemon this type of charm comes in five
different colors
[Music]
interesting
that's cute
or if i have it in my inventory text
effect i'm not sure how it works
but no status effects
if
it protects me not the pokemon
[Music]
is that so
what do you sell by the way
oh you do sell pokeballs and revive
or revive would be nice but i wait i can
today i get the recipe i got it right to
uh make revives let me try to make
as many as i can
oh i can't i only have livy jokes
not a little then wait
let me um
craft some of these though
because i have a lot
let me craft
a few of these
okay but we will buy some revives
baby jokes
vivi chucks
is this cake lure base
a type of field provision that enhances
the flavor of other foods it is mixed
with
uh-huh
okay but i want a few of those
five for now
thank you
[Music]
let's go to the next
mission i don't remember what it was oh
yeah we needed to meet someone i guess
but what is that over there
they have a wormhole over there
oh is that a farm where i can leave my
pokemon
oh oh drift wait is that are those the
ones i caught
and
uh don't have them there's a lot of
yeah it looks like it
that's my pc oh that's cute i can see
how they're doing there and that's a
nice area to put them into okay
i will give you that positive point game
and item storage
pokemon
of the diamond clan let's go
time to milk driftlets they look
milkable hmm
did i surprise you i bet i did i was
trying to anyone
there's a secret technique to catching
pokemon you know
it's what i call a secret backstrike
technique hitting a pokemon's back with
your pokeball will surprise it i already
did that i already did that i don't care
i need a backswing
now working to create the pokedex as
they all are you might end up meeting
every last pokemon here
hi
hi hi hi hi
i need to rest my voice so i will not
listen to your
baby baby
bippity [\h__\h]
[Music]
no it's not root
i need to take care of myself it's a
it's called
uh prioritizing your health
go away sally oh i might accidentally
kill you
[Music]
oh sheesh
uh
come on you want to fight okay
[Music]
why not go look for evie first
i guess i could
i feel like we'll eventually meet one on
our way anyway
strong critical
[Music]
shanks is always so energetic and happy
about murdering you it is
i don't even remember like
where where i need to go where i found
the evie i think it was probably that
way
but
we're gonna find it
oh there's a baby relaxer
ah sorry it's not relaxed so it's uh it
was again what was again in english can
i jump into the water oh
oh my god wow it's such a deep water and
i can oh
never mind i can't i can't
nobody warned me about that i died can i
learn to swim
the [\h__\h]
okay we're already back to normal
drown is
pain what is it
strong pokemon
okay i'm rank one
yeah i'm strong enough
which way this one
hello are you mine
cute i have a feeling she's cute oh
she's cute over here oh she's cute she's
cute guys she's cute oh she's cute she's
got style too look at her leggings
this is kiawa
my my
a new face in the village
not that it matters to me if you knew if
you're here i assume you've prepared to
be of help
i am one of the wardens of the diamond
clan you may call me my
i suppose you might not even know what a
warden is if you're new to hissui
but such talk and wait right now i
travel we get straight to the point
i have a problem that i need to help
solving so the more important question
is this
do you feel confident that you can lead
your pokemon in battle
your face
i don't look very confident but i
at least have words that are stronger
than my heart
that's good to hear
that security corps of yours certainly
wasn't up to the task
she also has a weird face man
this here is my partner munchlax
it's a baby isn't it cute bubble bubble
we were raised together like siblings
her battles at my side by choice but he
battles at my side by choice without
needing any subtle silly little balls
like you use watch and learn
well i'm just trying to stay organized
you know
[Music]
[\h__\h]
sorry um what about if i fly yeah he's
coming at me
he's coming at me
fighting no i don't have that
what if i use my boob
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
she's super effective well that was not
a good idea um how about
um
help me chance
[Music]
uh
yeah
oh my god oh my god
it's gonna kill me next turn
i can't catch it she owns it
hold on a critical at least we're fast
oh my god don't attack me
what a [\h__\h] strong baby
oh my god
[Music]
maybe
damn
battle decided
all right
move mastered can't evolve rubble can
evolve
come on oh it's cute the way it looks
down
stop wait
[Music]
you really aren't one of the usual
galaxy buffoons if you could defeat my
partner
well [\h__\h] munchlax
i'll take care of the pokemon that
battled for us
oh thank you are you reviving them too
and i'll let you have these
you people make all kinds of things with
your crafting don't you this should
prove to be useful materials
[Music]
very chokes yeah
i needed this
you and your pokemon fought well
together you practically acted as one
wisdom
rather like the legendary hero of old
the one we tell stories of to our
children
i think you're indeed the one for the
job
you see i need someone to deal with an
alpha pokemon causing trouble upon the
deer track heights
it is large fearsome full
like any alpha but you'll come won't you
to deer track heights
let's go
your arc found us by bam
is that strange thing to me what of you
is telling you where to go
yes i think so
my my that is some curious sort of map
is that one of those galaxy team
inventions i keep hearing about
it certainly does it certainly does seem
to show the way to deer track heights up
ahead of us is that one get my mount
is that where that big thing is
i'll leave this bit to you you shouldn't
have any problem handling an alpha
yeah we'll probably move fine
it seems you're quite the asset to the
survey club's new one
that mount and that tree keeps on moving
you see that tree in the back
though
before we continue i must ask do you
already know about almighty sinnoh
no
i know the cinna region
almighty what now
i suppose that's to be expected alone
allow me to sketch out the basics
the almighty sinnoh stares at stairs all
time
wait a second
[Music]
it's said to have created the very
universe using its power over time's
flow and this land of history was born
in the process
it's by the grace of almighty sinnoh
that pokemon can live and thrive here
we of the diamond clan are descendants
of a people who crossed the sea and
settled here in the history region to
venerate almighty sinnoh
however it stole away from the world
long ago hiding itself from our sight
almighty sinner has only rarely been
seen by any human if the old tales are
to be trusted
but there are still pokemon here today
in history with a connection to almighty
sinner
[Music]
and it is the duty of wardens like
myself to attend to their needs
the pokemon that grace's dear track
heights is one of those honored few
it is directly descended from a pokemon
that was blessed with almighty sinner's
protection
follow me and you may understand
coming
if i don't get distracted by something
it's running away what is it
what is it
oh it's a beetle pokemon
i need to catch it it's looking at me
isn't that already an evolution
and apparently there's a pokemon
oh [\h__\h]
come on
in the tree
now i understand the reference oh [\h__\h]
y'all
what about the tree
that is that not how it works
tamaka
i can't cancel the tree
[Music]
don't kill it
catch it
[Music]
[Applause]
i got it and we got the berries as well
go get them big boy
there are a new pokemon here and this
boy he didn't want to find me apparently
oh he didn't want to be caught but what
about fighting
yeah
no
okay i need to catch those
when it doesn't notice me what is that
is that a vivid choke
[Music]
looks like it
oh
hmm
um well breath of the wild definitely um
looks better
[Laughter]
oh but yeah
to be expected i guess
[Music]
[Applause]
can i throw that fire is she able to do
it
[Music]
it's like an fbs shooting game now
stop walking always coming at me
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
i noticed
it run away
that's stupid beetle but actually i
wanted to check something else
uh
uh i wanted to evolve there we go the
hebrew emperor wants to be evolved
evolution
our first evolution wow
wow
that was a very dramatic evolution i
like the animation and
very fancy very intense yeah
it's so intense but it just turns itself
into a [\h__\h] cascoon
man
and you're getting dust ducks oh is that
like one of those that um you know comes
out two different ways depending on like
what the gender is i guess
ah
that stocks
what was the other one that i could have
gotten is is this gonna be like a poison
butterfly or something like that
so cool then costco
is random
the other one
beautify
50 50. okay i don't know i don't really
care
got the idea for a new move well go for
it go for it buddy can i evolve anyone
else no that's sad that is sad
yay
[Music]
okay i'm gonna catch that stop it
stop it beetle
how about you look the other way
that'll yes that'll make it easier for
both of us oh [\h__\h]
where are you going
[Music]
yes okay well now i'm satisfied
because
i'm level up oh
another shanky tree
is it the same yes it's the same pokemon
well we caught one so this one we are
going to kill
kudos
[Music]
i love that you can run around
that's really an amazing feature
i feel so free
the [\h__\h] did you do bear me you little
[\h__\h]
unbelievable
so much for killing it
[Music]
sorry man
there's a klein stein
small stone
and a weird flower that i've never seen
before
what do you want
burn that's that's not a very japanese
name man
oh there i might helping a guy out i'm
after some cherry berries you know them
are shiny red ones they corn some trees
can you give me some
how many do you want man
yeah you shut up
when you do one
he has a sweet face though
thank you
pokeball oh
okay
uh
is is it showing its back to me
what is that wait that's not a pokemon
is it not the pokemons on it
i thought it
[Music]
um
it looks like a pokemon but i i should
have i was wondering like why did i
never see that one before
was this effective or wasn't ineffective
it's super effective
okay maybe not run around too much um
even if you're excited
i was too excited
[Music]
that looks like a [\h__\h] pokemon
we might want to catch this one
oh
already in red so it's time
[Music]
i don't want to use it though
i don't think i want to use it
revive back piece oh yeah okay
okay i guess
[Music]
oh man
there you go
decent rock starter i know but
i don't know
i'll see what else we we will be offered
how the hell i don't mind fighting you
again
it's better for my oh
it's good for my steps
[Music]
[Applause]
he left us some mud very sweet
i should maybe heal
[Music]
be careful rowlet be careful
can you get that for me thank you
black cumbersome
don't care about those verbs anymore
unless
oh wait
ah okay i just need to evolve
one
and then we'll be good
i hope violet will be prophesized that
would be sick ah
interesting
oops wait um let me see
uh
you feed it with watertight moves oh we
can do that
number of heavy specimens
okay let's try to get it down with water
and then maybe oh no i need to defeat it
though
okay oh
[\h__\h] scary man
okay
destruction
how about we fell
[Music]
did i miss
now i did not
[Music]
how many are we fighting
[Applause]
only one okay but that was pretty strong
they all are looking at me though
is it like a swarm but i only have to
fight one
[Music]
oh and now i have to do the next one oh
man holy [\h__\h] that's tough
[Music]
at least they're fairly weak
free at the same time
oh don't stop using wrong ah okay okay
that's probably gonna give me a point
still
[\h__\h] i'm drowsy but i'm not sleeping yet
right i will sleep next turn
oh [\h__\h] no i'm too drowsy after all
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay then we have to change
it
uh
can i look at uh
i want to look at i want to look at what
pokemon has a strong move
why there we go is this is it this one
no
[Music]
okay
oh for a pokeball oh
true
[Music]
[Applause]
oh this one we should be able to catch
no problem
[\h__\h]
nothing
[Music]
do i wake up from sleep after a while or
is that one of those that stays until
the end of the battle
[Music]
oh wait wait wait now yeah yeah okay but
it didn't want to be caught so
yeah
ah
there's too many pokemon attacking me
now there's only one left but still
okay
one thunder shock
oh it kills it okay i would have tried
to catch it again if
if that didn't kill it
oh
damn son
holy [\h__\h]
that was oh what's this
is that a frog pokemon
oh wait it looks familiar it looks
familiar what is that supposed to be
looks like a frog but it's not
wait is she gonna battle me
should i be healed is she gonna heal me
[Music]
oh well i'll heal blazell
at least
okay so what's up
what's up here
tell me about it
yeah i suppose i have to battle a
pokemon
oh so even your professor decided to
join us
um
i guess he did
oh thank goodness i got here in time i
had a pokemon researcher i could hardly
miss out on a chance to observe an alpha
i suppose that is your business fine as
long as you stay out of the way
where is it where is it i don't see it
this is dear track heights
this is where i've long come to pray
tribute to a special pokemon a pokemon
descended from one of those ancient
blessings by almighty sinnoh
[Music]
okay
that's only a travel maker here to
disturb the piece of its racket
it looks kind of
mad though
looks crazy
and that's what you hear for kiawah to
drive the interloper from this place i
want to show your pokemon already oh man
didn't need to heal myself
very strong and made know moves that
others if they can't do not they're not
okay
yes i'm strong yes i am strong
no doubt this alpha is a powerful and
hearty foe
the way they're hyping it up feels like
it's just gonna be like a tiny tiny baby
pokemon
oh no it is an alpha pokemon oh
hey i thought you're looking for
something else
okay
wait um
what what pokemon do we want to use
it's a it's a beetle beetle pokemon so
[\h__\h] oh focus
yes just look at me look at me
[Music]
he just said hello
you didn't take it as a battle
invitation yet
are you gonna take it now
[Music]
very interesting the action order mm-hmm
okay that's the cricket tune let's go
holy [\h__\h] guys
uh
what do i have to catch it by the way
[Music]
is it from the shock am i doing fun to
shock
i can't catch
[Music]
it's talking so much
i'm gonna die
[Music]
um
is this gonna is this gonna kill it i
hope not nah
we're about the same level oh no i
killed it
[Music]
even when it dies
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i killed and is that really bad
or do we not care
cool
[Music]
i wouldn't be able to catch with anyone
really
you really are an impressive one aren't
you
seeing someone best an alpha like that
it truly reminds me of the legendary
hero of old
we'd best make sure your pokemon are
taken care of after facing oh thank you
thank you
oh he comes here comes the real deal
[Music]
what in the world
yes
nice beard is that santa claus is dear
it's the great we're dear why do you how
do you guys say it where do you
stop
it's gorgeous can i ride on you
are you gonna be my friend
he's looking at me
[Music]
he looks upon you with kindness kiawah
mm-hmm
which i'm like what what do you want
oh
it it left
i say the great white here we dear has
taken the liking to you
that is fortunate
he's an esteemed pokemon that can dash
across the expanses of history while
burying a human on his back a human he
deems worthy at least
he's a blessing to us all
i want it i want it i need it
remarkable truly outstanding stuff
a pokemon letting someone ride on it why
it's just like the ride of right pokemon
of alola what
professor i take professor i take it
things went smoothly
i'm here on captain celine's orders
she said we'd be able to set up a base
camp here once kayla took care of her
request oh
yeah what why do they know about alola
i'm confused too
oh
about that i know this was a joint
decision by adam and the commander but
still it is truly
fine is it truly fine for us to set up
more base camps like this
the history region is a land created by
the almighty sinner for the sake of its
pokemon
as long as your goal is to coexist and
thrive together with the pokemon then i
imagine you should also be allowed to
use this land
the great winger has wider i don't know
has taken liking to kiawah as well this
is a good sign
you have my thanks for what you did
today our clan leader will hear of how
you aided us
i'll come to show my appreciation with a
proper reward as soon as i can
the professor has been everywhere it
seems yeah
uh well if we're to coexist hashtag
coexist
and thrive with pokemon we'll need to
know them better and the first step
toward that is completing the pokedex
the construction club should be here
soon they'll have our new base camp
pitched in no time hell yeah
nice new camp
we have traveled quite some distance so
it's about time
oh comfy
here we have it our new base camp upon
district heights and call it the heights
camp
from now on when you set from the
village you can ask to be escorted to
this base camp to start your excursions
directly from here nice thank you
having more base camps ought to make our
survey work easier huh
indeed indeed
well that's that how about we head to
the wildflower like usual
oh
i feel like i barely did [\h__\h] man
oh 1200 okay
do i get a star probably not
[Music]
oh yeah yeah but next time next time we
should get a
rank up
this game really encourages me to catch
a lot of pokemon which normally is not
really my style but yeah
benny or the usual potato
have you heard all the great news the
front seat cleaver from the rumors it
ended up mauling some of our galaxy
folks who went out to investigate it
this morning the medical corpses had a
hard time getting
all the injuries back on their feets wet
feet
and it's clever that was really struck
by powerful lightning yeah i did his
here he's been behaving most erratically
since then
so the third investigation is in order
to serve a corpse will of course step up
to the task a certain amount of danger
is inevitable when researching on family
unfamiliar pokemon but i'm sure kiawah
he can handle things just fine
of course i can
but that cleaver is said to be much much
stronger than even an alpha pokemon
isn't he
now now you forget that the strengths
of pokemon are key items of information
that we of the service groups are duty
bound to research
and since the parent perilous work of
ours calls for clear head and fighting
fit physique i do believe in good
night's sleep is an award after this
fine meal hell yeah i agree i also i'm
getting tired
i didn't sleep that much today
because i realized
i kind of lost track of the weekday i
thought tomorrow was friday
i thought my doctor's appointment was
tomorrow and i realized when it's
already when it was already like three
a.m
it happens no i'm a bit sleepy
knock knock who's there
rise and shine
yeah
the boss wants you oh [\h__\h] calm down
come on
okay
no no i have to read super chat so
we'll talk to kamado
but then probably
probably then we will um switch over to
the office and read subjects yeah
or should we yeah then we'll talk
[Music]
uh yeah i guess i know how to name the
pokemon but i was just too lazy to do it
yet
did you get a good rest
yeah yeah
locals being look who's being punctual
finally you realize you're wasting money
you see this precious time by bowing to
a champ what
ah
[\h__\h] cute
there you go again insisting on your
false image of almighty sinnoh as a
ruler of time
my people follow the true almighty
sinnoh the font of all creation in rural
space
you could have all the space series and
still not know what to do with it
excuse me are you really suggesting that
you make better use of your time than we
make of vast history space
better than some
this dude reminds me of
uh uh
someone
it's a miracle you showed up on time
almighty leader of the pro clan
no not crony no no
[Music]
no no no no
i think some uh
jolly
jolly's art
i worried you'd get lost in the
pointlessly burst space
i
i might be confusing things right now
[Music]
it's not chrono
it's a little bad space though you're so
fond of and never show them
me get lost and almighty sinnoh's great
gift to the pearl clan in our world's
very basis
you wish
let's tell him girl tell him
i like those character designs they both
look nice but you know i'm always on the
side of a cute girl
i wish that i hadn't let myself get
dragged into arguing with you almighty
no forgive me what a waste of time i'm
off to commander kamado's office
i believe it was you who started this
she's so cute i like her dress thingy
what what
that man is named adamon he's the leader
of the diamond con ah they put a lot of
importance on time as you could probably
tell
and the girl is irida leader of the
burial clan
they're all about space we're diamond
brew we're done bro we're done bro we're
diamond pro
it's same region
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
whenever they run into each other those
same arguments flare up seems like
they've inherited some bad blood from
their predecessor's strife
ah well not our problem but you'll have
problems if you don't get yourself to
the commander's officer at officekit
i'm on my way
am i gonna meet the cute girl again in
there or should we keep that for
tomorrow yeah start off on a good note
how about that
that sounds good to me
and suzuki
wait why do i stay up here no
they're safe
save toko
[Music]
nice okay i kind of thought i would play
longer today but we have tomorrow anyway
and uh yeah we have a lot of time
we're gonna be playing this a lot this
month and my voice is [\h__\h] so um
yeah i'm a bit in pain
oh
yes yes we'll play more tomorrow
uh i hope you enjoyed this today we're
gonna read super chats in a moment i'm
gonna take like a two minute break make
some tea probably
and
yeah but i hope you had fun today the
first look into this new pokemon game
a new ark
arceus
thank you thank you
thank you
thank you for being here today
if you want to play it yourself the game
is out now
go get it yourself and then enjoy it
okay i'll i'll see you guys
after a little bit of an intermission
nina
thanks for the stream
thank you for watching
yeah
[Music]
mine is literally on an amazon truck on
its way here or did you buy a physical
copy oh
woman
well i hope you'll enjoy it then
okay intermission let's go and everyone
who's leaving thank you for watching
avidas and see you tomorrow hopefully
thank you
but if you stay then you're welcome to
stay just give me a moment everyone can
take a tiny break
yes
whoop
[Music]
hello
hmm
flip away
[Music]
i'm turning off super chat right now
i'm big
i'm running out of honey i need to buy
honey
[Music]
okay
uh
let's change into
something more casual
okay
hello kitty
i'm back welcome back everybody
i'm back back big
big back back
cardigan
let's
update the chat
i already have the super chat window
open as you can see
because i'll be showing the super chats
uh like this
instead of uh like reading the messages
but i will read the names that is uh for
the time being a new role in order to
save
my voice a little bit um
the weird thing is right now for some
reason it cuts off here
um
stupid window so i have to scroll to the
side
in order to see the
rest it's kind of lame
but okay and we will cut it like here
so
okay
uh could be worse yeah
could be worse it's all good let me get
some music hey michelle
[Music]
um
how about since we just played a game
that was kind of like traditionally
japanese or at least it had the elements
of it in it
we play
something that's kind of wafu
loafer i used this before
you hear it oh that's oh
that was too loud sorry
[Music]
oh sorry
well why don't we have a kkk emoji the
greeting one is kind of a kikiri but do
you mean like you want like the actual
letters
hmm
why there's no particular reason why i
just felt like the greeting one is
like supposed to be used in that way
like saying hello or yeah even the
chicken one or my own
with the hand up
need a yawn yeah yeah that's true and we
need that too
anyway we gotta go
down
let me see
pokeman pokeman
unloading loading
[Music]
loading loading
oh yeah
[Music]
wait
come on
come on youtube
i think i have to hmm
okay okay and then the members only have
already read and where do i have to
start
whole talk right oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
damn
[Laughter]
this will take a while
uh mia reading these will take a while
[Music]
this is what you get for not doing your
homework here we are hold up
squirrels
go i got to go to the left side
otherwise it doesn't load it in
[Music]
oh what are these
uh sawdust
nothing before holo talk though right
i think
hello
oh it's getting really omoi
it's getting kind of laggy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
dun dun dun
are we there are we there yet are we
there yet drink
let me scroll to the side please
[Music]
there we are okay
let me fix something
[Music]
uh
vegetable we're not reading super text
from today we're reading
[Music]
is
oh [\h__\h] wait
[Music]
okay
are you guys able to read this
uh
i guess we can cut this off
you guys don't need to see that
okay is this big enough it's kind of
small isn't it
why a bit
i i changed the size oopsie doodles
[Music]
cut it here
i cut it here
um
i mean
i read i i kind of read it anyway but
yeah if you really want to read it you
probably need a big screen for that
i don't worry there's nothing really to
leak here i mean
there's
public records anyway
here here here here
okie dokie oh
here we go that one that one was uh the
last one uh that that one yargla fire
that one came in like when the stream
literally already ended like i even
already turned off the stream
and
you came out of nowhere thank you for
the red super chat i don't know if
you're listening to this but
thank you
you're surprised with that what a weird
timing that you had
thank you soon
your glue flag
[Music]
thank you
so now what i will do as i wrote in the
pinned comment
um for the meantime meanwhile i will
read the super chats just by like
highlighting them so you see what i'm
reading
but i i won't really react much uh
and i won't read it out loud okay
it's kind of awkward
[Music]
oh thank you you're gonna get the
tickets only one or two are you gonna
watch both days hopefully both days
yeah
you gotta watch all the hollow myth
members it's a special occasion after
all
thank you hope you're excited for it i
am really excited as well
it will be a very very special concert
oh both of course oh
good choice good choice oh i just
realized i have a cat hair in my teeth
i got it out now
well if you watch the first day then
we'll be able to do a watch along
together
um today i want to inaudible
first first why i call it first
i guess because the first appearance in
a
concert but it was just like uh like a
2d like cut out right
what did they do did they sing more than
one song i wasn't watching it it was uh
i was not available
but i could watch the archive
how much did they sing did they only say
that one umic song
one song ah
2d portraits just one song
yeah it sounds like a screenshot of it
and i thought so that they would only
sing one song
yeah they um
for the people who don't know
um akua senpai had a concert today
or like yesterday depending on your time
zone and um she had marine and ina and
kuda as a guest marine was in 3d
but the other two were a default png
pose apparently
we were laughing the whole time
it was it was it only like was it not
even moving left to d was it just like
the p and g really
[Music]
i thought they would at least
they were moving okay okay and that's
that's thankfully the minimum
oh yeah they were singing that umi song
i suppose
that's nice good to hear
um
kitchen
[Music]
thank you
yes um
i mean
uh it's not on i would say you know it's
not only jaco who decided to hire me but
jungle might have been
one of the decision making people i'm
not sure actually if yago decided on it
i don't know
i i don't know but let's just say
yago represents the people or the person
who decided to take me into the team so
thank you
thank you i am also very grateful
thank you for your sweet words book book
pudding channel thank you
is this
what's what's his name adapters
mechanicals thank you for the red super
chat
[Music]
super excellent thank you
hope you enjoyed the
whole talk i was wondering if this was
another car name but i guess not
thank you for the support
very generous of you
[Music]
yeah as we heard in the interview he
himself said that nowadays he's not
really
um in the audition process
not really part of it
uh anymore
and i mean especially for ian you know
you know that
we have like
a different management and all that
anyway i have another cat hair in my how
does this happen
oh this is happening
typhon thank you for the red super chat
as usual thank you for doing hotel oh
wait i'm breaking it out of reflex
so awkward
[Music]
i need to read twice
i'm glad you found
someone that you feel like is worth
supporting
in me
thank you for choosing me
yeah
indeed many many
many many lucky videos have uh
made it into
hollow
live and um we gotta thank
we gotta thank whole life for choosing
such awesome people man i'm also really
glad that like thanks the whole life of
i've got the chance to
um
become acquainted with so many lovely
girls
that
normally if i weren't in a whole life if
they weren't in whole life if we weren't
in whole life we would have never and um
got to know each other but they're also
talented and fun and
it's it's really nice also like you know
not only japan but also indonesia like
making acquaintances all over the world
actually or australia for example
yeah it's pretty cool
to be able to connect to
the girls and have friends
in so many places
would be nice to have even more
international members that live like in
places where we don't have anyone living
yet
that would be nice
tyrell's might thank you soon optimus
prime vancouver
center
sundance
[Music]
what's
happening oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
i'm walking for myself
quite a funny way of cooking myself
[Music]
yes thank you i hope you learned some
things about him um
i've i've read some
um
i've read some feedback
uh that even the japanese bros
learned some new things so i'm glad like
even though there were a lot of topics
that we couldn't talk about
uh and a lot of topics where yago
didn't go much into detail
it was very difficult to get in get him
go into detail about anything to begin
with
um but yeah i think still we got some
knowledge out of him yeah thankfully
thank you for the insanely generous
donation felix
you're crazy thank you
[Music]
the man's tight lipped is that what you
call it
i think you controlled him really nicely
i don't know i don't know
i mean personally personally i wanted to
get even more info out of him but
it was inflammative really
you got a typical work day yeah wow i
was surprised it goes running like every
day holy [\h__\h]
oh how wow
when you already work 11 days 11 days an
hour
11 hours a day
you must be exhausted
yo and then he has a family right so
that's also exhausting gotta get make
some time for them as well
oh my god and he probably even like
works from home as well
sometimes
even after coming home
fidiago yeah
men
damn
[Music]
he probably doesn't sleep much
but he didn't seem so sleep deprived to
me
maybe he just doesn't maybe he's one of
those people who don't
need who are trained to
go
on about their day without much sleep at
all maybe he's one of those people
he's probably used to it
so what
[Music]
probably used to it yeah very
hard-working man if he weren't just
hard-working then
uh cover or whole alive would have
probably not been such a success so
[Music]
actually now now that i say it like that
it shouldn't be so surprising
someone like
him
you know
it makes sense if you think about it you
know making a company so successful
is only really i think possible to
someone who can work hard
[Music]
a businessman just like i'm a business
we mean
very passionate definitely yeah
[Music]
really want to read it out loud
oh yes thank you
he has 20th episode
yeah i i said i told you guys before
that i wanted the 20th episode to be
something special as well
so thank you for
celebrating together
you like the music kyle
i'm glad
it's pretty cool huh
thank you anton and a kiss from me to
you
look forward to the 30th episode which
will probably be quite some time but
yeah
um
i i already know
who the guest will be for the 30th
episode
[Music]
wait
translated
[Music]
thank
by the way i wanted to say because
people were saying
that um i
um
i was i was saying so doesn't it quite
often myself well yeah but partially
that is
because uh
wait but so doesn't it maybe he he was
like kind of uh
leading me into it
it's not it's not me
he was baiting me i got i got uh seduced
into saying so this net
[Music]
let me try to drink some tea one moment
oh it's still very hot
but i don't deserve to have a sodas in
it counter i didn't say it as often as
he did
[Music]
but it was fun like also calculating
uh when he didn't quite say so this
never but he said so this yone or he
said so this got so this corner which is
a question
questioning it
by the way so doesn't it means yeah it's
like that
or it's it's um
or like um literally translated it's
like yes it's like that
but um
yeah
it can be used in many
ways
um
[Music]
so we were joking about um
i don't know if it came across
quite well in the subtitles um as well
but when we were showing that clip of
marine
um senpai talking
she said that fubuki standby noticed
that yago was wearing something new so
she was like oh new outfit but like not
not only new outfit but new outfit you
know in a sense of you know youtuber new
outfit did that come across the way we
wanted it to
the way it was intended to
and then we we i asked him like what are
you wearing now is that a new outfit as
well and then he said only the t-shirt
but we got a freaking 3d debut out of
him
someone else told me like yo that's not
3d i mean
yeah you you might not need 3d goggles
to look at him but it's still 3d as much
as you know let's say miko senpai
is 3d um
yeah you might not see it like
it's coming out of your screen but it's
still 3d
yeah
hey don't take that away from me
yeah he could move his arms yo
i can't move my arms the rigging was
wild yeah
so realistic
such detail in the finger movements and
you know in the
in his expressions in his face
very realistic
[Music]
i don't know who is the rigger
i don't know man it's not really it's is
that really like
for 3d i mean someone made the body but
there's no rigging right you you are the
ringer the one who wears the body is the
rigger no you decide how the character
moves but i guess in some way 3d models
have to be rigged as well
i guess
big props is mom and dad yeah okay
that's a good argument his rigor is his
mom and dad
[Music]
look at my look at my beautiful kaijan i
recommend this to anyone like i can read
this but
um
yeah this is a really good chrome
extension
[Music]
you know it
see you can say oh daisuki
oh you don't see the whole thing but
you can even just translate this part
for the whole part
and here you see honor or n you see all
the readings
[Music]
yeah it's also on firefox
superdashi i wish i had something like
this for reading um korean
why
does it not exist i was looking for it
but i couldn't find something like that
at least nothing that also gives me like
i saw something that gives me the
meaning but not the the reading
i mean this also doesn't give me romaji
but it gives me at least hiragana
at least it gives me hiragana
maybe someone maybe the person who made
a hyper chat could could make me nah you
must know korean in order to make it huh
yo hyper chat person if you know korean
can you make me a rikaitan but for
korean
that would be really helpful
[Music]
hyper chat i'm using a chrome extension
for the youtube chat that's called hyper
chat in order to make it run better
and so far it definitely crashes
[Music]
a million times less than the normal
youtube chat i can report on that
yes yes
yeah we had to pester her for it a lot
yes she had
philippines
and so doesn't it
[Music]
you almost challenged you should have
challenged yourself man
why did you not do it
so listen
but your
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
yo this is oh [\h__\h] don't read it don't
worry the quinoa
[Music]
i did feel
very pressured
because you know him being
very very high up
this is the one thing that
i i
i feel like i'm like
some people
especially now after the after the
interview some people like to compare me
again with coco senpai which honestly
this is this is one of the few
comparisons that i don't mind being made
because it's um i i would like to be
um
as entertaining
and creative as she was
um
but yeah when it comes to
teasing
uh um jago i was i was very
i i was holding back but especially
because i was told beforehand you know
these questions are
no no
uh gotta be professional you know i was
told that before and i didn't want to
get in trouble if if i wasn't
like
you know specifically told that
beforehand i might have i might have
been messing around a bit more
during the actual stream but i didn't
wanna you know you know how it is with
uh
better to apologize after doing
something
uh wait what was it like better to
apologize after doing something then
asking for permission and then getting
turned down and they're not doing it at
all you know what i mean it's kind of
dead mentality
i did kind of
did it
in a in a more careful way as in i
yeah ask for forgiveness the information
exactly that's what i wanted to say
i do
um
the ask for forgiveness
style more often usually
not not saying that i need to ask for
permission for forgiveness a lot but
i just
often just go with the flow a lot but
in this case i couldn't
[Music]
oh
if your boss don't do the forgiveness
thing with him
i mean if coco was able to do it i
should be able to do it
[Music]
foreign i just said in japanese i don't
wanna i don't wanna be exactly like coco
senpai but some people have been
pointing out similarities and and hoping
that i will kind of like
spread
um
spread one spread
spread my wings just like coco senpai
did
within her life and continue building
onto what you started building
[Music]
and that's what i do want to do i don't
want to i want to do it like um
while being inspired by her but not
completely turning into the same person
obviously i think i can definitely take
inspiration from
her and and
i mean honestly even
even before when i wasn't really
wasn't really quite feeling
like
like i needed to
[Music]
take inspiration from her even before
then what i was doing before already
came close to it you know building
bridges with holotalk and all that
so i was already doing it on my own but
i'm glad that
people see it in a way that
um i can
build onto what she started building
[Music]
yes
which is one red one
[Music]
five what
500 days
wow what another coincidence
it was my fifth ton of days uh you
didn't see that part huh
today marks your fifth hundred days
since debut
on on whole talk
really
[Music]
people were so focused on the 20th
episode and jago that i guess that
didn't really make uh its way into
everyone's brains but is that so
[Music]
wow
how did you how did you even count that
yeah
how did you notice that
so doesn't it
500 days of kiwawa wow thank you for
your kind words
um
i will continue to do my best and work
hard patrick thank you so much
founding chickens
[Music]
so this is
so this
is now well we gotta
um some people try to
figure out the exact number
um
also even including my own sawdustness
so if you're interested in that look it
up
so this is
seventeen b-forty two down d play one
two three four down so listen
foreign
[Music]
thank you
for the pinky
[Music]
you need
rest of the day
yo yo yo let me read
[Music]
so what is yeah
so it is now i'm glad you liked the
episode i was feeling very nervous about
it anxious whether or not you guys would
like it because it was obviously lacking
the speed talk around and and the
singing part the singing performance but
you guys still uh were praising it so
i'm really happy thank you
oh you didn't read it oh [\h__\h] here
oopsy sorry
someone just knew
[Music]
yeah i think we're i think we're already
glad to have a a ceo who is so
um you know
approachable i guess i don't know i mean
i don't really approach him it's not
never like oh are you approaching me
um
but
he's just um
he doesn't at least scare people when
he's friendly yeah
down to earth yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah
it seems like he's very popular with uh
the other employees as well
so
that's a good thing a good work
environment i suppose
thank you for the pinky
thank you
yeah i specifically i requested them to
organize the green screen for yagu
and they did it i'm so happy they did it
otherwise it would have been not so
special it would have still been fun and
i think uh i saw a lot of you guys uh
expected it to be
something else
um as far as i know a lot of you
expected it just to be an image
a png
but bamboozled and i kept it secret i
wanted it to be a surprise
[Music]
it i think it made it a lot more
interesting so i'm glad we went through
the trouble of doing that
[Music]
yes
he might really be the most say so
some of evil duncan random collusion
thank you for the red super chat
hmm
yes yes yes
i'm glad you guys think so it is uh
definitely in good hands
thank you for watching and supporting
random ghouls collusion thank you
[Music]
foreign
yes yes
more episodes
thank you guys
you are you are what motivates me to do
these
holo talk
episodes even though it is a little bit
of
um work and preparation every time
why i censor it because he wants me to
say i am a chick
and i'm not gonna say that
he knows he knows it though he knows
how i will say his name
it's his destiny
[Music]
and
mary pippen stone cushion cuckoo and
thank
[Music]
oh i had nine really
thank you
i had nine soldiers so this
apparently
[Music]
i wouldn't say 61 though for him because
um i already rounded up quite a few
after
uh
yeah around the end so that one so
doesn't it after that i didn't cut add
that
you were on the stress understandable
i think it was you who was doing this so
this neck hunter no
i have a feeling it was you
so i understand that you were stressed
out
sometimes it was also not so good not so
easy to hear whether or not he said it
or not or how he said it
[Music]
yeah it's probably lower than 16.
but someone someone i mean it really
depends on how you want to
count certain
phrases but
someone ended up with 69 i think
including my own so thisness
[Music]
and that's just wishful thinking i think
but
[Music]
nice yeah no that's wishful thinking
that's how you want to hear it
eternal dive part
[Music]
one of the two
ah i see the other one oh
thank you thank you
oh
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] wait see the rest is uh here
and you see that there it is
ah you got caught off there it's already
paladins
oh but you you uh you followed up even
though you could have said that it's the
end of the stream i'm not gonna i'm not
gonna send the rest no one will
no one will remember but you still did
it yo you're true to your word what a
chad
[Music]
thumbs up thumbs up just go your own way
thank you what the hell ollie thank you
for the insane donation
did you did you
imagine that he would say it so often or
were you sweating every time he was
adding another
uh saw this nettle that you were like
looking into your wallet like [\h__\h]
please stop saying it for [\h__\h] sake
stop it y'all
or did you think that he would say it
even more often maybe
a man of honor
saw the snare
so this i think i saw him in the chat i
think he's here
[Music]
i saw this man
so this name is
[Music]
he's not there maybe he's not there i
might have seen a dead person a ghost
it's a deadbeat so
his ghost probably after donating all of
this he might have um
not had enough money to buy food be
careful of that okay
i hope you can still buy food
[Music]
60 is beyond any expectation
really
i mean
i feel like it was pretty realistic if
you think about it would be like a at
least like one hour conversation
well thank you so much
very crazy of you but i respect it thank
you so much for your generous donation
uh
maybe some of that will somehow go to
yago
black fruits and donkeys
wait it almost is over here at cocoon
fire trap danke should naked chicken
need this soul
you don't see it but wait
[Music]
his face is turned upside down
now we are at paladins yo we're done
with holotalk
[Music]
that wasn't so bad was it i don't know
if i really saved time to
i didn't save time but i don't know
maybe i saved some
some of my voice at least a little bit
probably not a big difference because i
still feel like i need to make up by
talking
but yeah maybe it helped a little bit
so the snare
at least 98
no but i think it helps i think it helps
i feel a bit um better i think
[Music]
and the tea helps as well
yeah i noticed today um
you know what it's it's crazy man i
don't know what um what was happening i
have the humidifier on i've been having
it on throughout the night as well and
now i have it standing right next to me
um
but like after
like already half an hour
of the stream today
already already pain in my throat man
without fruit candies and without tea
it's
really pretty bad man
[Music]
i will go next week probably i'm talking
to my friend about it
she said she wants to go to
yeah my vocal chords man
[Music]
yeah as i said i have the humidifier
right next to me
i don't know if it's really like
it is pointing at me like i'm getting i
have clouds around me
i have um all the mist around me
um it doesn't really feel much more
humidified but i suppose it is getting
humidified
um
yum i'm sorry guys that this is
happening
but
we'll be careful
we'll be chiara full
yeah recently i don't know maybe it's
because i screamed like literally out of
the top of my lungs so often in the past
not that i did it on purpose but it's
like the games made me the games made me
yo
recently in like death loop and so on
i've been screaming so much
[Music]
yeah yeah they were pretty back to back
it might have been
damaging
[\h__\h]
but it should if that's what what it was
and it should be able to heal i mean
it's not like
non-streamer people there's more than
enough people who scream just in
everyday life
like that
out of pure anger
now
[Music]
zelda was nine hours yeah but
but even it was before that and recently
honestly that that nine hours from yes
yesterday
was um
the day before
was the first time in the wild i've
streamed that long
mostly it was like five six hours
recently no
hmm what did i do yesterday
[Music]
memphis only was yesterday
we haven't had such a long stream in a
while
which is good
which is good however it did it honestly
it was so much fun yesterday
um
because all those nine hours were
not yesterday the debit wasn't it all of
that nine hours was gaming
and usually when my streams are that
long it's gaming plus super chats
but all of this nine hours was gaming
and i had a lot of fun
i have to say um today
my honest opinion with pokemon
it's fun
but
it's
not as
um addicting
and like motivating as for example
link's awakening or diamond and pearl
was to me
it's fun but
and i definitely want to play it again
but i don't know i think it's really
partially the music the lack of music it
might just be my personal preference
but it's it feels very calm
and because of that it doesn't really
motivate me to play as more than three
hours even if honestly at the mark of
two hours i was like
i feel like ending it for today
and that's at the beginning of a game
that's what surprises me
like the game is fun and and interesting
and all that the gameplay is fun
so if it's not the gameplay's fault then
it's i think for me it's really the
[\h__\h] music man
the lack of music really has done
something to me
the whole atmosphere is so calm
um
i didn't expect that i thought i would
be
i i thought i would be unstoppable today
i thought no one could stop me from
playing this game today
i don't know i did not feel like it was
overly tutorialized either
[Music]
i don't quite think so
i also don't feel like it's so
repetitive no
not yet not yet at least even the
like in the beginning i was like what i
really need to catch so many pokemon but
after i started like exploring um
around it was actually fun
to
it started becoming fun
like it's weird like it's fun but i
don't want to play it for too long what
is this feeling
[Music]
like i enjoyed uh
collecting those uh
materials and then finding the pokemon
then i found an eevee and i found a
dress blue and it was it was fun
um
[Music]
it's too tedious no i don't think it's
too tedious either
not enough immersion
yeah yeah maybe maybe that's one of the
things
it's missing sparks dream spikes hell
yeah
it's more pokemon than you've played
that a lot lately
what maybe because it's more pokemon
what
ah no no no i don't think that's done
it's way too different no no no no
[Music]
no
no pokemon go
[Music]
a complete different gameplay than the
normal pokemon we normally play
yes which is cool which is exactly why
it shouldn't feel repetitive or so at
all
[Music]
and i also felt like you know catching
pokemon
and getting into battle and all that a
lot of it felt way quicker than the
previous pokemon games
um like the whole
selecting
pokeballs and all that i feel like in
previous games it was uh
way slower
and it was tedious
so it's actually a plus for this game as
well
it's faster to get into battles exactly
that's a plus for me too
[Music]
well
it's not the graphics faults
[Music]
it's actually probably good
that it doesn't
um make me want to play it for hours and
hours and hours
because it will be bad for my throat
anyway
it's better this way okay let's continue
we're now reading um paladin super chats
which was a lot of fun i want to play
paladins again
i want to play paladins it was fun it
was an fps online game and it wasn't
wasn't as hard as i thought it was man
[Music]
you know what it's been five oh so this
person noticed how did you find out
spent 500 days since
davio i want to be with you for a long
time as i know you're late the same goes
for a whole myth whole life fruitfest
homemade second anniversary i try to be
with you until the thousands day oh
wait i write it out loud
[Music]
here
thank you it's [\h__\h] reflex man i
can't stop reading
oh thank you
yeah yeah yeah
um a lot of the korean bros that
recently joined may have joined
a little bit late to this whole
experience but
there's still so much to do together and
honestly
you can see you can see my first um
let's
say 200 days
it's kind of a warm-up phase
or at least the first hundred days so
you didn't miss that much from the
beginning
um but you always there's archives you
can always go back and watch the
archives if you wanna
that's always an option it's not like
gone forever
i joined late as well but i'm glad i'm
here now thank you i'm glad you're here
too
yes i know about the pinned comment i'm
the one who wrote it
don't miss the mario 64 archives
pain
[Music]
thank you
die 971 thank you for the red
[Music]
well
it was more difficult to do headshots in
this game than it was in uh def loop
because in this game people were
actually moving much more
and i wasn't really able to do stealthy
[\h__\h]
yeah but
but uh yeah my aim was probably pretty
bad but but but i tried and
it was bad but even then uh i was doing
much better than on um a controller i
would say hmm thank you guys
why am i reading it why am i reading it
thank you
you've repeated oh i thought you
repeated yourself but you said hi to um
as well that's so sweet of you
my channel
you for the red super chat
[Music]
it was your birthday exhausted here are
you here now probably not
sorry i couldn't do it on your birthday
but
let's pretend it's your birthday now
[Music]
oh you are here you are here
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear exhausted hero
wow
congratulations
better later than never right
[Music]
my team is getting cold
man
thank you for your support and
it's okay that we broke man it's okay
you don't need to donate but i'm glad i
was able to uh apple able to say happy
birthday to you
thank you for your support please
continue supporting me
1.32 million let's go thank you
subscribers
thank you
and
apple
i'm apple
i'm so i i'm so apple to see you all
today
an apple a day oh no that's really
what you're supposed to say
[Music]
apple
before whole live did you ever send
super chats to pick her up
maybe
i do still also have her uh her
membership but
um
i never i never sent a super chat after
joining her life because i thought it
would be um
awkward
but i do still have my membership which
i don't really i don't honestly i really
don't didn't have much time to watch her
streams anymore ever since i had joined
but sometimes i do
[Music]
an egg a day keeps susan away
hmm
oh free membership messages no no i'm
not gonna do that no no no no no no
no
no no no
especially she's also not gonna read it
anyway i think saga
[Music]
hmm
thank you you got my merch
it sounds like it's all of it
and you get all of it then i think
that's all of it thank you
again you're the
best thank you so much
yo
i'm glad you like them i hope you get
some use out of it and yeah
looking forward to having you cheer me
on
during the concert
glory to kfc thank you
[Music]
mine just chipped okay well it's on its
way
just gotta wait a little bit more
[Music]
stealth super chat that's not very
stealthy
remember dad let's go green wave you got
reminded you were like oh right all
right that was something haha
that that's something
[Music]
yeah right that was a thing
who uncruised
[Music]
thank you
oh in japanese even
she must but what does this mean
have a great day
a nice red super chat just telling us
that they're going to work
apparently that means damn it
are you angry because you have to go to
uh you have to go to work
[Music]
oh man
it's okay you can watch the you can
watch the archive maybe you did
[Music]
it's like crap like [\h__\h]
well thank you for saying hi though i
hope you had a great day at work thank
you for your lovely support
uh fighting do your best at work
daylight night thank you soon for the
pinky
oh
yes thank you you're welcome i am i'm
always very happy to play with ammo i
i was actually i asked her so
spontaneously i was making my schedule
and i was like [\h__\h] there are no collabs
in this schedule
i feel like recently i haven't been
doing many one-on-one collabs it just
happens and it's not on purpose just uh
happens
so i was like yo ahmed
you wanna collab
maybe fps game
and they have anything anything that you
feel like
i i would i could do learn easily
and amen was immediately like yeah let's
do it sounds fun
yeah
i'm i'm happy
happy she said yes so quickly
[Music]
i love you one-on-one collabs thank you
but i i
i'm glad you guys liked that collab but
i felt like i was um
i didn't manage to do as much small talk
with her as i wanted to because i was
uh you know
i
i had like before the stream i was
thinking about the collab i was like we
can talk about this we can talk about
that but then the stream starts this
happens so often and suddenly my mind
blanks and i don't remember the topics
that i wanted to talk about with her
i don't remember anything i literally
need to write down anything all the time
[Music]
but i guess it was still fun
and honestly
so sweet of ahmed trying to explain
things to me but
she was talking so fast and so much uh
when she was explaining things that
literally only five percent of what she
said
entered my registered in my brain
but it was nice hearing a voice it's
just it didn't register
i listened i tried to listen but
you know how that feels right
you know how it feels yeah when you
can't soak it up
[Music]
man
i do write down topics a lot of time on
my phone
um
but i didn't have my phone with me on
that uh collab i think and also it was
more those were more topics for like
solo streams yeah
yeah yeah
should have turned on subs
yeah that helps so much
like when i watch netflix i usually also
always have english subs on while
watching it in english
just because it's so much easier for me
to register
probably this is a thing of like you
know when when english is not your first
language yeah
same same oh
oh
[Music]
but then i noticed that i focus too much
on reading sometimes and i don't i don't
really look at the picture much you know
and then i feel like maybe i should turn
it off because it's not like i really
wouldn't understand it it depends on the
show though with seinfeld i realized
because the writing is so fast
that i need i need the subtitles
otherwise like sw should swoosh but with
other shows
like i finished watching the great i
finished watching it and for that
um the last few episodes i did not watch
with uh with subtitles and it actually
worked pretty well
[Music]
i did i was able to appreciate the
beauty of the scenes more
holy [\h__\h] was so gorgeous but
i'm not sure if i'm happy with uh
their decision on how they changed up
the history
uh for the shell
[Music]
i mean
they don't claim to be accurate but i i
they have been led astray and i'm not so
happy i understand why they did it
because
that character is just
so funny that they didn't they weren't
able to kill him off
because he's just like
such an important asset that if you kill
him off uh as as he would normally be
killed off in reality in history
[Music]
um but if they kill him off then the
show would be lacking quite something
we're talking about the great it's about
um russian history of catherine the
great
with peter
the emperor where
in history
she takes the throne she takes the
emperor role and then eventually we
don't really even
even like
um
like there is no real like proper proof
of what exactly happened but like how it
really all happened
uh but eventually peter gets killed or
dies whatever but in the show they seem
to have decided to
go against that keep him alive and then
make
like first of all
she's so disgusted with him she hates
him for most of the time
but later in the show spoiler alert she
finds an interest in him even though
he's a [\h__\h]
idiot
absolutely a freaking idiot that is i
don't know how she can love him
but he did change a lot there was
there's a lot of
growth in his character
in the second season
um because
he wants he he realizes he's in love
with her and then he
tries so hard to make her love him and
it eventually ends up working which is
just not realistic he should be dead by
now
yeah
but it is quite the character
development and as i said i understand
why they did it because he's he is a
[\h__\h] funny character
without him
the show would be lacking so much
[Music]
yeah anyway i still recommend it it's
just like you shouldn't expect the show
to be accurate at all
yeah yeah
[Music]
really
really i was i wasn't
when i was playing tyra i was like not
even
properly aiming
i wasn't even trying that hard with tyra
but um
yeah when i was playing the sniper in
the beginning i was i had to try to aim
properly
yeah tyra gave me more freedom to just
like [\h__\h] around
that was fun both characters are fun for
me
i want to experiment more with it but
thank you greenwilder
that's the trickles we don't properly
aim oh you just go
[Laughter]
understandable have a nice day
[Music]
i got a lot of kills with the ice cart
are you kidding me no i did not no
[\h__\h] way i didn't do [\h__\h] with her
you mean the one that they said is
really hard to play no no i didn't do
[\h__\h] with her as far as i remember
spray and pray ah
i learned something new
i i misspoke i
stumbled over my words i wanted to say
something cool
and sound like an fps gamer but
sometimes i just don't know what the
[\h__\h] i'm saying
i i wasn't even when i was saying that i
wasn't even sure if that's really a fps
term and i was just hoping that it is
it would have been even more
embarrassing if it wasn't man
thank god
[Music]
360.
this is the one from yesterday right
from the day before yesterday
hmm
[Music]
hmm should i hmm how much is that
mama help me
mama help me look at that oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
i'm going to read a bit
not all of it
okay
[Music]
yeah let's go let's do this let's do
this
thank you for the no wait the first one
is cyndaquil oh oh
please pick me no sorry oh man i'm sorry
the burp is just too cute
yeah oh you don't do you see it
no
it even has uh cinderquillas the profile
picture
i'm sorry
someone else did though in hollow in
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
oh
no
see the thing is i may have chosen
coronal but chrono is has yet to choose
me back so
don't worry it it's not not happening
yet um
but i did want to talk about
why
um why i personally thought that
certain
members go best with certain
ministry members do you want to see or
hear my reasoning
yes you do of course you wanna
okay so i said
i said let's start with um
kelly and sam
which is uh most obvious i think first i
i was thinking of shipping sand with
gouda as i said because
good eyes small sana small i feel like
it would just be weird if coulda had
someone to big
um but kelly
has before many times i think uh
expressed a preference to
small people such as gouda and and i
don't know just i don't know you
probably have more more um samples if
you watch your streams you probably
always react to smaller characters in
games
so and um
uh and and not only i i
did not only think about the visuals i
also thought about the personality and
we've seen recently that i think kelly
and sana get along quite well they've
been
through some endurances together
giving each other company uh
through jump king and through pokemon so
i thought that they're actually getting
along pretty well um that combined with
the smallness is perfect yes so i think
you got to give me a proof stamp for
that
100 where's my do i have it here
i'm going to prove myself
if i find my stamp it's in the other
office
oh my god what a mess
uh
where is it
oh it's not i can't find it
[Music]
is
is it here
oh my god hello
[Music]
looking for my layers uh
um
[Music]
approved a broke a problem a problem
let me take that with me
hey
sorry was that loud
no it should have been fun okay okay i
don't know where the night is though
it's been a while since i used that
and no i do not want to fight the mice
again
so and then moving on um because san is
now with cali i was thinking
[Music]
i was looking not only at the visuals
but also at the personalities
um
you know i thought
it's hard to explain
but i thought i just thought you know
out of the ones that are left
it would probably be best to ship good
out of bales
i know she gets along very well with
fauna and mummy as well but this is not
about the girls this is not about the
girl versions about of them
this is about the male versions of them
yeah
and
yeah i don't know i thought it would
also be cute to see good i was someone
who's a very opposite type of her like
good eyes is cute and all that and
pretty energetic and then
heiko
was like
just maybe just because he just had
woken up but he was like very much like
but i feel like together they would work
very well
and she would like
and
like be very very
amazing
how do i say this in english
i want you know i i just had this vision
of them of course being like hey guys
i love you and hey guys would be like
all right come here i'll give you a hug
and i thought it would just be so sweet
likes to be doted on yes yes
[Music]
i just had this vision trust me
are you gonna approve because i'm i'm
approving
[Music]
and then i thought ina
with uh
mo man
because
san san was already gone
and um
i thought ina needs someone who
is fairly intelligent and moo man
i think moomin is less forgettable than
mume
i don't know but the movement looks like
someone who likes to read books and [\h__\h]
so um
yeah i don't know
that one was tough shipping enough with
someone was pretty tough but
uh
visually i think it fits better than
someone like fawn for example another
option would have probably been a
cronull
uh but but then again when i imagined
them those two personalities clashing
together in a relationship then i can't
say it so much anymore i think uh
women is nice i think inna needs someone
who isn't to
to
ayara to oil
someone more with a sweet and soft
personality which
uh out of these ones i think moo man had
the most yeah
yeah see i really put a lot of fun into
this
there we go prove that [\h__\h]
yeah he might may have been talking
about going to the gym but look at his
character look at his body
he doesn't look like he's like
a bodybuilder but
uh
yeah i think he would be
a good type for you know but his heart
no matter how buff his his arms are his
heart is soft
and then amelia and fawn
for once because uh fawn was the last
one left over because i'm taking chrono
no matter i wanted what it takes
but
amelia and fun because amelia you know
with the of the
uh gremlin savageness and just the look
in fauna's visuals you know that yandere
looked at a fun fun
phone hands
um i thought that
uh it's it's um
it radiated
radiated the same amount of savageness
personality-wise like not only visually
but like personality-wise i thought that
maybe not a perfect fit maybe they might
break up eventually but
it would still work well for a while i
think
yeah yeah and plants they like plants
both like plants
wouldn't they fight a lot well there are
a lot of couples who thrive by fighting
a lot
hell yeah
and i take chrono not because corona is
[\h__\h] hot but
because he's [\h__\h] hot
[Music]
yes
so
all in all
problem
[Music]
although i must say
um
none of these are really my type
i think if chrono if someone like chrono
really
um
copy don't me i would probably
um turn into jelly but not really the
type i would go for normally so um
in any case
uh
[Music]
i i only want my cat so whatever don't
don't try to like make anything out of
my choices here
[Music]
understandable yeah i mean if you have
someone like cronie or chrono talking to
you how can you not become jelly
always would choose crony over chrono
though
[Music]
but um yeah just kind of like bishonen
type
of character
it's not really
not really
not really my time although even in um
fire emblem
like when when they try to charm you
it's really hard to resist okay
but
yeah
no
[Music]
i know
no hell no
no
i mean
it's whatever shut up doesn't matter
[Music]
patrick
it's about the personality guys
it's about the personality if someone
has a nice personality then all of that
doesn't matter if you'll be shown in or
if you're more of a nerdy tab or if
you're a buff
buff wrestler tab
you know doesn't matter shut up
uh rub easy or eat that thank you for
the pinky
[Music]
oh
the ending
i i think it would have given me way
more chills or like emotions if i didn't
know what was gonna happen as i said
when i first played the uh watched
someone play the game
i was very um
naive
about the whole hints about it being a
dream
so i think
that was
when i when i
[Music]
didn't play it myself on stream
i would have had a better reaction to it
yeah
um
yeah maddie's face in the clouds was
nice but i also have to say if i if
there were if there was more dialogue i
would have also been able to make more
out of it yeah but it was a level game
as i said it was very very addicting to
me i enjoyed playing it for hours and
hours and hours
um
really lovely game i didn't give it a
rating did i did i give it a rating did
i
did i give the game a rating
i don't recall
i don't think so
didn't give a number
i say
[Music]
always difficult to give ratings because
i'm not sure what i'm comparing it
against or if i if i should compare it
against anything at all
out of 10 i will give it a
how much does anyone remember remember
if i rated skyward sword and how much i
gave it
i kind of want to give it a
[Music]
at least an eight out of ten
um it would be nine of the ten nine out
of ten if there was more dialogue
[Music]
hmm
and maybe a 10 out of 10 if it was even
like longer as the game but
yeah uh it's it's obvious why those
things are lacking because it was
originally a gameboy game
or 8.5 i could even see giving it an 8.5
[Music]
pretty good game
pretty lovely pretty chiming thank you
rob
uss anime ncc 2400 duncashin daisy thank
you for the red super chat
yes yes
we love some democracy don't we
um
good thinking
the internal question remains to tell
that doko exactly
zelda if zelda was there
would have had more points
[Music]
oh my god a long korean message should
total wait a minute
[Music]
let's have this read it for me
everyone will admit that saya is loving
in any outfit i always enjoy watching
the broadcast and i often watch the
recorded broadcasts again it became one
of the joys of my life
i love you cameron
so when will you talk about the salary
union time card check and overtime pay
yes what room
truth no
no
[\h__\h]
this voice man
the i love you kim anna sounded so
intimate so lovely
wrote you know it was more dramatic than
that it was no
no
but she reads like remote truth
[Music]
oh man oh thank you wow i'm happy that
you watch my even my archives uh over
and over again apparently thank you
i'm glad that you found a liking in me
and support me and thank you for the
pinky
don't worry i won't put you in the usual
room unless you don't stop talking about
unions and salary raises then we might
have to do something um
[Music]
um
red pink pink i'm color blind
[Music]
hello manager there's a korean proverb
that says that if you like something for
free you'll be bold
what does that even mean
sure okay
what is that supposed to mean
i'm not gonna
oh because i talked about
my my straight hairstyle maybe maybe
because of that making me look
like a like a shiny egg
thank you so
wait much
that is probably
a chinese reading total wait uh google
translate
a google translate
[Music]
thank you
wait let me uh okay i'll read it
you're first
[Music]
happy birthday
you broke your arm
and lose lost your jump
[Music]
no
oh shiny smiley sweet horsey
hmm
wait what
[Music]
woo i need i think it means what i need
wait where's his birthday did i miss
mozart's birthday well he's dead so i
don't care
[Music]
thank you very much
oh happy belated birthday what's that a
rainbow it looks like a rainbow
ah
thank you for the rainbow
happy birthday
happy birthday to you
i hope your arm gets better
don't break it
into wow i made that up on the spot it
rhymed even
yeah [\h__\h] man that sounds like a rough
time that you're going through but
you'll get through it just fine and
you'll come out of it even stronger
yeah
you'll become really buff
thank you so much for your support
and let me try
[Music]
yes
he's small but he has a big big rocket
apparently
[Music]
i'm
for the pinky
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
put him into the usual room furlough
one
[Music]
please please write a proper message
unlike your colleagues
[Music]
you mean you mean the collab or the
heart challenge stream
because right now i'm thinking releasing
the song cover one day before
valentine's day
and then on valentine's day doing
heart challenger
one year anniversary stream
and then
because you guys had the idea
um i'm gonna do
the
speed dating collab either somewhere
between valentine's day and white day or
online day
yeah because uh
since i'm going on a skiing trip as well
um
i won't have that much time until
valentine's day anyway
thank you
soon
[Music]
m thank you for the pinky
oh
i looked i looked mal following where
when what happened
what did i do don't i always look
mouth-watering huh
yeah this is the youtube studio reading
window emotes don't show up i guess that
wasn't emote
thank you tiny
while i was i wanna
hey when i was being cooked
you shouldn't have i was interpreting it
as something positive but now that you
have cleared it up um
i now see it as a fret
this super chat
blackberry
huh
hyper joe's corn syrup duncan
no no no use your room there's even
proof of you
going against me starting a coup
you're into a room uh five months
yes pretty
that's even me being nice and having
mercy
five months
enjoy your time in the usual room
[Music]
why are you crying you didn't think this
would happen what do you think you what
did you think would happen if you
declare a revolution against me huh
publicly here with a pinky that everyone
sees
stupid chicken
[Music]
blade johnny duncan for the pinky
hmm
[Music]
what
ah now again
it took me a while
thank you
one key on our burger menu
we don't have keanu burger man we have a
phoenix burger which does not include me
but yeah coming up if that's what you
mean coming right up
greet your team thank you soon
if no then um welcome back
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
ljk 9000
92 000 thank you for the pinky
[Music]
oh you're going back
oh you're happy that's ending oh
this person is happy that his study in
america is ending
thank you
thank you very much congratulations on
uh
finishing that properly while four years
is a long time
wow i respect that
oh
your english sounds really really good
just by reading this so you must have
learned a lot um
i think that's a a great
oh [\h__\h] what oh [\h__\h] wait my battery
[Music]
i accidentally disconnected it again
it's just realistic because my real life
battery is also running out
eh i was saying yo yeah what was i
saying
four years long time
er i think it's really cool that you
went abroad for such a long time and
happy birthday to you
thank you
[Music]
congratulations it was your birthday
yeah you said like this will be the last
birthday
probably already a little bit too late
but still
stay healthy and happy okay be careful
i hope you have a safe travel but back
home make some memories
as much as you can before you go back
and treasure it the time that you had
overseas
i think in like 10 20 years you will
look back on it and you will think yo
i'm so glad i did that that was so cool
[Music]
luna is still
uh a while to go we're doing third gen
now
uh
but yeah
actually it's not
i can see it happening in the summer
maybe
[Music]
let me try to translate the first part
thank you for the two paintings is that
a kiss for you
[Music]
oh
you've become such a wonderful loyal
chimpkin i'm so proud of you
thank you for your love
wow
cute hoot
you're so sweet
i feel so loved thank you so much
thank you
i love that don't start wars without me
that is you're so motivated
you're on school
he's still in the usual room
oh is he sucking up to me is this him
sucking up to me
it's working
dragon spire thank you for the red super
chat we believe in you
thank you
what was that about was that already
like where was that
i don't know what it was about but just
maybe about finishing the game on that
day i believe in myself too
[Music]
thank you dragonfire
what is that
what is that avatar
[Music]
i want to look at it
wait a second oh
[Music]
i wanted to zoom in
oh [\h__\h] it
damn it
no it's small
ah
you're gonna do something sometimes it
just scrolls all the way up it's so
stupid
wow we read a lot already holy [\h__\h]
oh i
found it
found it sorry i will
i will look closer
i don't want to open a new tab
oh i will
[Music]
oh
i thought i knew it was something right
it's me with a bet
it's mean yakuza style
dangerous
yakuza style
[Music]
and let me read wait wait wait wait
didn't oh yeah
[Music]
and there's a continuation
nobel prize
ig
weird
[Music]
several times
i think
cho is a little bit of a muscle histic
chicken because i've noticed a tendency
of him trying to
challenge me
and my power
[Music]
he wants
to be yelled at and he wants to go to
the usual room
i know it that's why i will not send you
to the usual room
and make you suffer for real
by not sending you there
i'll give you a kiss whether you want it
or not
because that was a red super chat
[Music]
with two pink is one red
i definitely deserve that nobel prize
because i can put one and one together
reverse you know
no you
[Music]
happy birthday
to your friend sherwin
stratton
uh are these flush jets
are these flush yes these flush shots
okay skip skip scooby doo scooby
you haven't seen and i did read
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah i know i know i know i know i know
i'm trying
tiny delta duncan maxwell the first time
custom trimmers danke
[Music]
no
that would be so [\h__\h] depressing
[Music]
because you know at what state i was
before her life man
no i would never wake up no
no
[Music]
dr glenn pierce i love that you came out
here man it's the perfect timing for the
perfect person
[Music]
thank you soon you stupid piece of [\h__\h]
glenn pierce glenn [\h__\h] pierce man
i hate you but i love you
[Music]
thank you oh yeah you mean this is
already around the end of the stream we
might be able to finish them
yeah i i i did the box first try i had
some struggles with certain forms of the
boss but
uh yeah we did it first try hallelujah
[Music]
for a red super chat thank you
what the [\h__\h] are you kidding me really
how can a boomerang brimmarang being one
hit kill to that
powerful being thank you for renewing
your membership
yeah the today's super chat i said for
tomorrow don't worry daisy here's a kiss
[Music]
it's interesting to like experiment how
certain weapons work on certain enemies
um
[Music]
yoni of laundry dankeshen
for the pinky
[Music]
i don't believe that
i don't believe that you are not shadow
gannon
no you're are cute beautiful cute lovely
chicken
you can't be anything scary and
dangerous like that
[Music]
you are look at you
look at you
would you look at yourself here
see
this is you
[Music]
your name might be ganon
but
you're so adorable
fluffy
with those feathers on you
yeah
it is proof literal proof no by dankesh
and trevor g duncan alejandro
[Music]
foreign
i'm proud of myself for finishing
another game
[Music]
that looks like a name i know
f4
congratulations on the manager's clear
yeah
rookie is always the best
thrilling
feeling that you're so good at games i
think you'll wake up quickly even if you
try altf for inches no i recommend it
let's for instance
thank you for your hard work
i love you tiara
it actually makes it partially more
entertaining than reading it out myself
thrilling
out four inches
[Music]
thank you for watching
thank you very much
what do you mean four inches
thrilling
absolutely thrilling riveting funny
amazing divine gameplay destiny
[Music]
is super snake mario thank you for the
pinky
yay
[Music]
oh love you too you're the best too
thank you i had a lot of
good times during this uh play-through
yeah
and it's one of my shorter ones so
i think anyone can
use this
to get into kiwawa at any given time if
you need to recommend something to
uh newcomers maybe this is one of the
streams you should put on their list
[Music]
thank you everybody
zork 787 danger
[Music]
what is nso
if if that is legal then i'm i might be
able to do it yeah but you mean the
switch version
or like what nintendo switch on ah
yeah i've heard about it yeah yeah
draconic the muller line down you need
to chat down trevor g thank you for the
pinky
oh my god i see the end guys
um
oh what you were playing hero mode the
whole time
yo
[Music]
oh be hootie [\h__\h]
thank you yeah
you can't see that oh sorry sorry sorry
oops
it yeah yeah here it is here it is
[Music]
the soundtrack was absolutely amazing i
have to give you that the whole
soundtrack of that game
oh
with quite something
i wouldn't mind listening to that in my
free time just randomly
when working on something i don't know
when drawing something or so um
osts are so good to listen to especially
yeah especially zelda ones hell yeah
hello
silent
vocals is zelda wand of gamelon
please play me
what the [\h__\h] is that
one i've why i haven't never heard of
that
this must be [\h__\h]
trillion years old oh no
that looks terrible i was absolutely
terrible
[\h__\h] no thank you [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
pride thank you
but i have seen this before i think like
also in memes like this is just me
morphy
although zelda
oh my god
when i google it i see a breath of the
wild version of the
gamelan zelda and she looks [\h__\h] hot
looks really good
[Music]
damn like a i think it's a mod
what the [\h__\h] is that man the
screenshots
this [\h__\h] screen to oh my god
a cosplay even came up oh my god there's
wand of gamelon cosplayers
those must be funny people
[Music]
well excuse me my princess
well well
we're done
with legend of zell darlings awakening
super chatters and these ones have
already ran in members only so tomorrow
we will read the pokemon super chats you
owe me a lot of so proud of myself yo so
proud of myself
thank you
thank you everybody
for staying with me
i hope this way of reading the super
chats is okay with you guys
hope that's uh
that it's not too
um
you know i don't know
yeah i hope it's okay
it was actually pretty funny sometimes
didn't feel much different okay
good
system is good okay
not that different okay
text to speech is pretty funny i should
do it for all of the messages
but i'm not sure is there like any um
[Music]
like the problem is i don't want it to
if i put all of this in text of speech
it would just like even read like things
that shouldn't be reading like usd
dollars
100.000 and [\h__\h] like that and like
emojis and blah
but if there's a way i could is there
any
i wonder if there's a chrome extension
where i could like select something and
it would only read out that
if there is a
a tool for that i want to know
[Music]
it exists
it's called speechify
i want to try it out can it only read
english or also other languages i want
to
edge has an inbuilt oh
we might want to try it out tomorrow
it's pretty funny when they read it for
me i can just lean back and be like
[Music]
yeah okay oh
oh man um i think i think we'll also
start a little bit later tomorrow as
well like one hour later um
[Music]
yeah same starting time as today
sorry for the weird ass time for sca
viewers i'm so sorry
you're crying don't cry don't cry don't
cry
don't cry
i will eat
dinner now
uh i don't know what i have i actually i
have a still have a chocolate croissant
and a sandwich i think that will be my
dinner i was supposed to eat the
chocolate croissant before the stream
but i ate a big [\h__\h] omelet sandwich
that was really good too
i think i'll just be eating
bread bread stuff today
don't cry
[Music]
1 40 a.m is relatively good these days
sorry
yo
i'm so sorry i wish i could i wish i
could do more for you guys but at least
a sunday stream is at a good time for
you
[Music]
the time of the collab oh it should be
fine the way it is now and even if it
changes it should maximum change by one
hour
okay guys i'm pretty exhausted um holy
[\h__\h] man it's like my it's like i've
aged in this in this one year of doing
whole life i feel like i might have aged
like
10 years
[Laughter]
i
i used to not be this exhausted by the
end of a [\h__\h] six hour
stream like my face hurts from
exhaustion
[Music]
and my throat is well yeah i i feel like
i aged so much in this one year
it's over one year now 500 days and i
feel like i aged a thousand days
or more way more than that five thousand
days
[Music]
my stamina is like what the [\h__\h]
man
so old old phoenix boomer boomer
[Music]
yeah the build up
yeah yeah
oh yeah um
you also said yesterday when it was the
day before yesterday it feels like
yesterday
[Music]
grandma yes i'm grandma
oh come here my little chip can
oh come here come here
come here
grandma
oh there you are oh
lovely oh your skin is still so shiny oh
so soft
i want to take a bite of that maybe you
can be by
my well of you
maybe i'll get some youth back from you
it's been 84 years
[Music]
i want to do a grandma's stream
like maddie and sam but
just ramble and ramble and ramble and
suddenly start talking german and
everyone's like what the [\h__\h] you want
one i'm gonna stand gym and shut up
okay
no i'm going out now i've been coming
together with uh
uh who else did a good grand i think
callie i loved cali's grandma voice
during like ttrpge and so long
yeah she's a lovely grandma too
[Music]
grandma getting all together with
takamoti
oh imagi imagine like
having didn't marine like i don't know
if she got it done for that stream but
um
she had this fan art of herself on the
screen being really old imagine takamoni
fan art by by mama lonnie
but us being looking like we're 80 or
90.
[Music]
uh
i don't know if mamaloni can draw that
but if anyone
man wouldn't she be the one wanting to
see takamori grow old if anyone wouldn't
it be her
if you want to see it then you got to
visualize it by drawing it imagine
visualize create
make it happen
i don't think mamaloni is into old
ladies but if it's takamori
[Music]
stuck on money
oh
it's been 84 years man
[\h__\h] tough isn't it
[Music]
i
auditions to
home live that is a long time ago oh man
well don't even get me started so um
yeah
i i was a young young phoenix back then
and i thought that uh
nothing would come out of this to be
honest it was trusta
it was just a
trial i was i was hoping um but no no i
wasn't even hoping i wasn't thinking
really oh but
it happened it all happened so fast i
saw
audition happening and i was like
it's my time it's now or never
i am indeed going to live forever
but i must make the most out of it
it's eternal
life
yeah and i was like this could make
everything a whole lot more fun you know
i gotta have something to do after all
yeah
it all happened so fast though i barely
remember you gotta look into my notes
let me look let me take a look
i could i could go on and on and on
i could go on and on
[Music]
wait aren't you like 100 plus years old
well first of all that is [\h__\h] rude
of you to say to a beautiful grandma
lady like myself but
no i'm even older than that
and i've lived thousands and millions no
maybe not millions but it feels like
shirley feels like millions of years
indeed well that's [\h__\h] rude get out
of here
[Music]
okay then everybody i'm going to leave
now
[Music]
everybody good night
thank you
for hanging out with me today i'll see
you tomorrow enjoy when we say happiness
wow music good timing
bye bye
thank you i love you
[Music]
oh i could use a massage man
those chimpkin feet and hands really are
not strong enough
i need a strong massage
[Music]
but the last massage i went to it was so
intrusive i don't know if i want to go
there again
[Music]
yummy cookies
what do you mean i told this story
before no way
no no no no you need to listen no
listen
[Music]
i'm