[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
n
k
[Music]
key
hey hello
[Music]
I'm frog and frog need to remind myself
I'm frog not
cat you can see how I'm pouring honey
into my
tea oh there's not much
left come
on come on no it's nothing nothing it
needs to go down first ah there's cat
hair stuck to the honey
bottle chat why are you not
working why I seen you there but I don't
see you up
there come on come on
honey come
on come on honey we got to
go now I have honey on my
fingers
how you guys
doing I'm a bit tired even though I I
slept enough I mean I slept with like
you know like a break in between because
I got awoken early again and then I I
ate Bak breakfast and I did some stuff
and then I went back to sleep a little
bit you think that's my I don't think
that's really my jet like I think it's
just you
know come on it's just me always being
tired always wanting to
sleep it's just yeah it's
just but I had nice breakfast yesterday
and today I had um pan P not pancakes C
crabs with Nutella fake Nutella and
strawberries cuz now it's strawberry
season let's
go
come
on it's strawberry season which is so
nice that's the only time I can get
somewhat decent
strawberries in Japan I I kind of can
get good strawberries throughout the
whole
year why the honey not come out come on
I mean yeah there's not much left in
there but
[Music]
I'll put it aside not like I can drink
it now but now my fingers are so sticky
I mean I guess they always are
but what do I
[Music]
do but on some of these there's cat
hairs I can't
I
what do I have this tongue
[Music]
for what's with this music going louder
and quieter can you hear it
[Music]
though to catch flies
yeah all right it's pretty
clean
r r
[Music]
r no there's hair in my teeth wait I can
I can I get it
out oh I got it I got
it that that's it so much hand
action
it my teeth what no teeth now I'm going
to pour some cold water into my tea but
you can't see anything think cuz my
hands are covered by the things that I
hold
okay I have no
teeth but that's okay I don't need
teeth I don't need
teeth I all I need is my fingers my
small baby
[Music]
fingers
I'm so
cute oh wait I was going to fix the
chat there you go I'm a hacker hacker
frog I'm a hacker
frog so loud but I tap into the game it
really is
loud
I don't know what the is wrong with
my audio like
overall look how much I lowered
it and it's I mean normal normal volume
now but it barely makes a difference
from like here to
here yeah frog sensitive ears yeah okay
I I just hope this music is going to
chill a little bit is it it's I don't
know if it's boosted that well whatever
happened while I was gone somebody
messed with my audio settings and
everything you ordered the Plus thank
you thank you so
much it'll take a
while but until the plusy arrives you'll
have me I will stay until you get your
plushy at least that's the
plan things sometimes don't go according
to
Kaku but I intend to
stay all right uh if you don't remember
we played frog detective 1 and two on
this channel before shipping in a week
no oh no no oh no not so
soon
yeah frog detective 1 and two and we're
going to play I'm back to finish my job
and we're going to play here free
[Music]
free yes this time it's
Cor
[Music]
at
Cowboy
count
[Music]
County
serving
counting thank you for the Super
[Music]
Chat
mommy my my hands are too far
away did you realize what I was trying
to
do okay here we go how long is this game
I didn't look it up but I think it's
like relatively short like
yesterday
Kido Mary hello look at my hand that's
my hand this my hand
around an hour only
really it's a bit longer than the first
two oh the first two weren't only an
hour weren't
they froggy
fingers quite short that's good we need
to catch up on super
chats hey hey it's Mary no hey it's Mary
hi hi it's
Mary hey it's Mary M
hey it's Mary remember me I know it's
been a while so I thought I'd give you a
quick recap after the detective that's
you that's me solve the case of an
invisible vizard yeah we did that a
mysterious phone call came in well it
wasn't that mysterious it was the
supervisor as
usual but the contents of the phone call
were mysterious you know okay so let's
set the scene I'm a good actress I I
will be exactly like what happened I
doubt that
now oh oh oh ah oh yeah yesterday I was
only
using my mouse today we get to use W ASD
we're here again
whoa oh someone's calling I I I want to
look at the pictures the camera is so
sensitive holy ah that was so much
fun yeah good times what the is
this though I don't remember
this I I was invited to that party
k k
k oh my gosh hey it's me detective frog
hey G oh it's both the same person hey
gorgeous I'm the supervisor I'm kind of
like your boss but not officially oh my
gosh I know it's so hard to describe our
professional relationship but you're
like a helper of sorts yes exactly like
a manager almost yeah okay so I have a
new mystery for you can you even believe
believe it ah yeah it's my job to self
Mysteries obviously I was being dramatic
classic supervisor okay so what's the
case about babe um I love your
enthusiasm but it's actually really
sensitive so I can't tell you on the
phone uh
boo
boo boo
boo I know bu make it so much more
exciting makes it so much more exciting
though for sure yeah can you do me a
huge baby Lovely One grab your
magnifying glass next to the door and
head to the train station there's a
ticket for you there and it will take
you on a little trip cute okay okay I'll
talk to you soon thanks love
later we're going to places wait wait
wait this is actually what I made they
have the data they remember I think this
is really what I made I remember the
face in the middle I made
this it's me I made
remember long time ago I'm pretty sure I
want to go I can't click on it though
there's no like Mouse in the middle
either no
cursor wow Masterpiece okay I take
magnifying
glass oh sick now we can solve the case
I'm the detective wait why why is it
still you but am I you right now that's
so confusing kiddo look for your
magnifier with the right click wo
oh
yeah I made those eyes aren't they funny
I love that fried egg cute whoa who
snake it's a snake
nice RH W okay so the detective heads to
the train station and it's all so cool
like there's a new color scheme and
stuff oh yeah there is like it's really
yellow and orange which would be a color
Fame that a certain Phoenix would really
enjoy but she ain't here today I would
be a nice like contrast color to that
environment with my green
[Music]
color I think green looks really nice I
mean cuz if you put orange on the orange
then it's just like too much Orange
right it's better if you put like some
nice green green something a booger like
me on there I miss her sometimes but
frog is good I
you will forget her soon and then stop
missing her so that's okay for now it's
okay it's only just like the second day
so I'll forgive you for now kdo but you
will have to get over your feelings
sooner rather than
later but can you believe it someone
literally takes a detective's notebook
it's so messed up actual tears in my
eyes seriously what what do you mean
what somebody took the notebook I don't
think the detective knows about the
stolen I didn't know so you're actually
up to date now please if you could leave
a review for my acting SKS i' super
appreciate it okay enj the
case no no my notebook I'm so happy to
see it again if you wouldn't have told
me about it I wouldn't have noticed
though kill train that the worm gummy
worm no I know it's not a Gummy Worm but
but looks like gummy
worm tell me if the music is too loud I
will gladly make it quiet wait wait
come gummy
[Music]
worm oh the clouds are cute gummy worm
do I think it's okay yeah
K is this me talking now I think so
hello this is frog detective from frog
detective crime solving agency speaking
how may I help
you eh what why didn't you answer the
phone like that oh what that supposed to
mean supervisor this is a random phone
on the street why don't you assume it's
ringing for you uh I'm the only one here
you don't think it's a little weird not
really you're the one making a phone
call it's a random phone um because I
knew you would be there now who's the
weird
one regardless I'm glad you picked up
I'll show you car about this mystery I
sure am give me the details please I
cannot someone may be
listening what who I saw on the internet
that it's possible for strangers to
listen to phone
calls who said that my cousin wrote All
About It on his
blog oh okay well if you're not going to
tell me the details why didn't you call
I have a special surprise for you oh do
you know that of the cowboy country it's
fast and rough I Ed something special
from whs to help you get around ah it's
the scooter always in the horse what no
why won't you say
[Music]
that it's a cowboy Town what do you mean
that was is R horses are you being
serious horses are Valu members of
society it would be the meaning to Rite
them around okay yeah okay cool yeah
it's messed up that you would even say
that oh right sorry I guess they're
animals just like us I just got confused
don't worry about it what need you order
then a scer of
course sick it should be near the phone
Boo b b CH to have a chip to a plumbling
foam boo please stop questioning my
choices anyway when you're ready pick up
the Schooler and get some practice then
Lobster cop arriv early and we'll be
waiting for you at the town just follow
the path to meet him and have fun I I
hope you have fun too I
will did this part just
appear in front of my eyes and it was
gone before or am I like going
insane I feel like that wasn't there for
like a millisecond what I'm
hallucinating I
think
I'm hallucinating all right see
you green phone
SC green Scot green phone everything's
Green orange we love green yahooo
let me ride this let me ride this is the
part that I watch a little bit on amma's
U stream I think her just riding the
scooter around
[Music]
here my very own scooter
sink yeah got a
woohoo so hop on the left shift what oh
I wasn't hopping then
[Music]
okay let's
go what I didn't did I accidentally
press left shift do really feel like I
did very sensitive keyboard
[Applause]
wo that
is they see me Ro rolling they hating
they see me
scooting they
shooting don't shoot me I know it's the
wild west but the BL don't shoot me
let's
[Music]
go okay I'm happy now do we have to go
this way may let's
go to where
oh he's so cool W maybe I can get over
frog birds with with
him no
where I'm in the wild rest let's
[Music]
go shoot
him
there you go oh the
bandits that's me today just
[Music]
today a special guest frog birt frog
birt did I really not play this before
somehow it feels familiar but no I I
guess I didn't it's just familiar cuz of
the other
Rock detective games
oh that is pretty
small pretty easy to get through I think
wow the
music let me try the honey
again oh yeah we got some honey coming
out let's
go come on a bit
more I know you can do more
yeah awesome maybe one more push push
[Music]
squeeze again now I'm I'm pretty happy
with that
[Music]
y
nice half of the budget definitely went
to the
soundtrack you can see my
hands this is dangerous scooting down
the mountain very
dangerous Mr
Lobster oh the the I thought he was
putting his arm out so I can shoot him
never mind
hello hey Lobster cop I'm here just uh
help solve the
mystery I don't remember what voice I
used to give him but he seems like a
jerk wasn't he a jerk oh there's a
there's a
speeda who and a crow I just watched a
new video from tiu about crows being
op right on time
detective I'm known worldwide for my
time I'm
time I'm worldwide known for my
timelessness in case they remember only
old school people will
understand we people who caught up on
the of the old lore I'm timeless no
she's Timeless I'm something else I
guess I'm not very
Timeless is that
so
no can you tell me about the case
Lobster
Club sure can we've been sent here to
solve the conundrum of the Sher FL
County switching between his voices is
so
difficult this town was thriving
detective a Marvel of productivity
Friendship Community and cowboys but
there was something
[Music]
missing a
sheriff yeah I was kind of leaning up to
that
my my my B for the sake of star can you
please not interrupt you I would
appreciate that too for the sake of
voice acting thank
you yeah um so
[Music]
anyway I just where I was going with
this no I can't I can't I I have
zero zero
zero ah what's it called I can't I can't
stay the same I'm like
I'm so this is why I will never be a
voice actor unless I can just use my
main
[Music]
voice consistency
yeah right there was there there there
was something
missing a sheriff the town had realized
that for all these years and they were
missing a vital ingredient for cowboy
living they contacted the supervisor and
she contacted me and and me yeah stop
intering me you little here we are
anyway I'm going to be honest Lobster
cop the supervisor really hyped this
case up like there are two of us here to
facilitate the hiring for a management
position detective you read my mind the
supervisor really dropped the ball did
you really think I need your
help
did you think I need your help
KD there's only space for one detective
in this town or should I say in this
country you
can't
help as it turns out I don't need your
help
oh h the position has been filled
already I knew the perfect boy for the
job presenting
myself t
t the new stff of cowboy
County who the is he this potato
man what is
what huh who are you a
mo no the mole is the mole
probably Mo the is a
mole sh Mason snack that's a real snake
or gummy worm really long gummy
worm shff Mason Mo w wow congratulations
on such a spiny resolution Lobster cup
thank you well I guess I'll head back to
the office
no
no no you
cannot is there something you to help
with yes what is it Sher with Mason
Mo
mystery cry
mystery please solve this uh what's the
mystery all hats hat have been stolen
yours
not all hats have been
stolen yeah yeah yeah yeah that's what
I'm saying you you're wearing a hat not
my hat Town hat what what's Town hat is
that a
word can you
elaborate all the hats in the town have
been stolen please solve this mystery as
soon as possible
[Laughter]
this is dorky as always I love
it don't you have any leads no get to
work
please well you heard the
sheriff
okay is there really no additional
information no but there is your
notebook what do you mean you have my
notebook why do you have my notebook
[Laughter]
I'm so I'm
sorry here notebook somebody mailed it
to you what what do you mean to
me I'm I don't have a somebody must have
known that I was coming here
so must be someone who knew that I was
coming
here
objection I didn't even know it was
missing yeah not not missing it's right
here yeah yeah
okay can I ask a
question no I'm busy good
on ha what a
legend you you know each other sure but
how much can you really know someone
right that is pretty deep pretty deep
what don't worry about it now detective
as I am the lead investigator on this
case I trust you will follow my
guidance oh I I didn't know you were a
lead is a safe assumption to make right
right of
course so I'll be investigating leads
but I could use your
assistance sure what do you
need I'll have a a motive and the
suspect you handle the crap scene and
Method okay okay it's an easier task for
[Music]
I just like yeah I was so shocked by the
pain that I left it in
there
frog
mhm yeah since yesterday
yeah
yeah but yes n i
mean I mean yeah maybe like 20 24
hours it's fine Austria is a safe
[Music]
place yeah I mean if it wasn't a safe
place then somebody would have taken my
key can
yeah know the thing is you say put on a
good keychain I had a good keychain and
everything but um I don't even think
that would have prevented it but I uh
recently you know those metal rings and
everything that connects all of that
broke you would think metal doesn't
break but all of it broke apart and now
it's just a key it's literally just a
key
key yeah that metal must have been low
quality cuz like several parts of the
metal just broke
off yeah Breaking Chains isn't there a
Rihanna song that sings that breaking
chain something like that anyway a ke
that could us to cool and lastly not to
mention most importantly a me for the
number one best detective Amelia
Watson Amelia
[Music]
whatson OH AAL for who you say Amelia
Watson she also played the game so you
should know her she controlled you wait
why am I talking like this why am I
talking like this yeah she played this
game before so you should know her
anyway I'm a very hungry boy and uh I
will also need a meal please thank
you uh I have some sandwiches I was
saving for afternoon tea if you like
them no I need a proper meal I hear you
loud and clear I'll make sure you get
those for you when I get those for you
wow why am I didn't we have like beef
before and like I didn't want to really
deal with him why are we working
together now and I'm like so okay with
it
his face is so
funny if you need to be reminded of what
I want come and see me by the
graveyard oh well good luck Lobster C
cuz I already
forgot I don't need a good luck
detective open your notebook with tab
yes it's my
notebook wait can I go back in time
mystery of the missing hats not that
missing headset is very relatable for
kfb there is no possible motive for
lobster cop to do this okay crime scene
map criminal tool key and a meal mm hey
it's Lobster cop number one best
detective I am very jealous so tall oh I
got an
achievement
okay yeah so I'm going to say ahead of
time it was the
[Music]
mole obviously
oh my God gum wors right
here
give give me or or
else danger noodle
hello also hello you are a cow I
think hello cow k cow
carrot just adding kiddo at the end of
my
sentence too amusing a little bit too
amusing his name is Craig how carot is
this you is this
you I never saw your face before but you
seem to have two faces which is kind of
unfair there's one here and one here
how how do you do
it um
if you're here from the evil secret
society please leave me alone I'm not
interested in
joining what's the evil secret society
nice try I know the society's tricks we
live in a
society well I'm actually here from the
Frog detective Crim solving agency oh
yeah where are your
credentials well I'm a detective and a
frog and I'm here to solve a mystery
Sloss crime do you have I need a
notification just my face look look I'm
cute oh did you not see my previous game
play
playthroughs do you
have turn table you know Uno RSE card do
you have identification no but I'm quank
everybody knows me I would normally
believe you but your parents don't seem
to match what they're saying what you're
saying but just no I don't trust you I
wouldn't expect you to we just
metant detective I'm someone that is
regularly messed with there
are why did I choose this
voice there are many different societies
around here and they all want me to join
but I'm A Lone Ranger I have no interest
in being a part of these secret
societ what type of SES are there for
starters you've
got
sorry don't noty little guys they've
been after me four years the the posties
are in L one they go around delivering
I'm not I don't know where I'm going
with this I don't know where I'm going
with this
voice they go around to
[Music]
live I'm not sure that singy I think
it's more of a public
service yeah then why can't we open
everybody me not so pop if you ask me oh
what an argument
actually open your
eyes another Society is the ghost sp's
leg oh wait I think I've heard of them I
have not the consistency is there let's
[Music]
go where's the other one
I amuse
[Music]
myself s
right
a despite being a secret society they're
quite well know to be honest with you I
said earlier that I wasn't interested in
being part of any societies but that's
only half
true the G spotters league is really
exclusive and I'm kind of bmed they've
never tried to recruit me
are you a king ghost mother well that
might be the problem to be inducted into
the lake you need to have spotted a
ghost maybe the ghost of
Tak chef
[Music]
hat I've seen it cuz I was in the
room in the tank during Halloween so I
can be accepted cuz I saw a ghost it was
a hat ghost which is even better cuz
this is about hats and ghosts I
guess yes I'm
in that is the only ghost I've ever
seen wait you were conscious yeah yeah
yeah yeah I had my eyes open did I
not yeah I was I was I was like oh yeah
haunting her a little bit too also can
you
see here there's someone there looks
like a bandit because it has a looks
like a hamster Bandit or Mouse has a
ey a blindfold thingy with holes so not
much of a
blindfold Spirit
wandering don't be concerned with that
hat especially now that kiata is gone
fun I am certainly not going to wear
that hat so okay you cannot make me that
is not my hat and it belongs not on my
head it's gone it's gone if Keana is
gone the hat is
gone I don't wear
hats you haven't seen any I don't know
why I'm telling you all this you could
be anyone I am the detective it's a
compelling this guys I give you that do
you know much about ghost well I solve
the mystery involving one The Mystery of
the H haunted island although it wasn't
haunted in the end so
no you could have saved us both time and
you said no sorry no I don't know much
about ghost I can ask can I ask you some
questions everybody always wants
information from
me
H yeah how about the ghost spots leak
can you tell me something how close are
you to spotting a ghost how would you
know yeah yeah how would you
know ghost are cool box detective you
can't respond them out in about how does
it work then well the requirements are
pretty flexible basic a society just
needs a credible ghost sighting story or
tangible proof of a ghost like a
photo you guys show up in photos it
depends but the saloon has a bunch of
photos but I don't want to send it send
in the wrong one and embarrass myself I
don't know which ones are of course and
which ones are just normal
photos sounds like a bit of a puzzle
there's so Str if I get my application
tonight three times I'm bad from every
ever replying again I won my second
strike I'm done with this voice wanted
to send in the first two
times I I think the first two settings I
dressed up as a ghost and ran really
fast I look like a blur in genius how
could how did they find out it was fake
they're so clever that they figured me
out right away that's how I know they're
the real
deal I like your creativity though
thanks if you happen to stop by the
saloon could you take a look and see if
you can tell which of the photos has a
ghost in in it I don't really care about
actually spotting a ghost myself I just
want to be part of the society I suppose
that's fair enough sure if I have time
I'll take a
look and then the other one secret
societies tell me
more I don't I
don't I don't some secret society and is
dedicated to stealing
hats oh not that I'm aware of but that's
a thing detective this uh societies Run
Deep I've barely scratched the surface
of what there is to know they run
everything everywhere you've ever been
anything you've ever done it's all
dictated by the secret
societies surely that can't be true you
think not but it's true we truly live in
a society how do you know it's true I'm
part of several firms dedicated to
uncovering the truth is in a secret
Forum what H like is the for
also a secret
society I never thought of that I'll
have a look into it no I'm just
joking I don't see how you can joke
about something like this secret
societies run
everything Craig I just don't think
that's true oh yeah what evidence do you
have that it's not true none I suppose
just a lack of evidence of it being true
I would say it's more like a lack of
evidence of it not being
true
agree to this
agree I agree to be right and you agree
to be
wrong okay sure
[Music]
whatever amazing conversations oh oh
Craig he's he's a moomo I want I wanted
membership to the secret uh hat stealing
Society no he wants membership to the
ghost what what defintive proof of a
ghost that's what he needs yeah and
notes either a conspiracy fist or knows
way more about the world than me uh does
not buy my detective disguise drat
disguise just wants to be a part of
something oopsie it's not a disguise I'm
a real
detective how can you doubt that hello
oh my God
cute oh my God you almost look like a St
like a cut out but you're you're a real
being right so cute and she's orange
which kind of disgusting but okay I'll
forgive you for being
[Music]
orange sassy no
Susie does your name is your name an
abbreviation of suspicious H Susie hi of
sussy aren't you a sussy
buck also what is this inside what the
why is your home so
secure hiy
you me yeah you can you tell me a favor
um it depends on the favor what I can't
just agree to doing you a favor I don't
even know who you are I'm so wed can you
do me a favor huh right you're the best
thanks I need you to help me break into
this oh oh it's a bank it's not your
home oh you want to break into
it um you're asking the wrong person I
think I I will not huh dude you already
agreed
to I don't appreciate you lying to me if
you said you do me a favor you should
keep your word
I I didn't agree to the favor you just
freaking assumed my agreement oh so now
you're changing the story whatever
dude just leave me
alone the
face very not
impressed wow I assume we can't talk to
her anymore for a while look at her face
look at her
face wow amazing can we talk to
her excuse me
Susie speed Susie
rabbit
hello
what it's me the detective yeah I know
they should call you the
flank that reminds me today I was
talking to a Japanese friend and I told
her um about something like in the in
the conversation I was like oh yeah that
sounds like a control freak to me and I
wrote it
uh I wrote it in English like I wrote it
in Japanese the sentence but the word
control freak I I wrote in English I'm
like oh that in English we say that's a
control freak and she's like corn
flake I'm like no not
cornflake and then I wrote it in like
Japanese
Katakana
corn flake but honestly like it's so
similar I can't even blame her control
Fleek like if if you normally in your
everyday life you don't stumble across
English words that much or like even
English letters cuz they use different
letter system then it can look kind of
hard to read to you and then i'
understand it's looking like
[Laughter]
cornflakes
[Music]
like your brain is trying to autocorrect
it into something that you can make
sense of at
least why because you always flank on
your
promises oh she's a insane
person to say this with that face to
turn around out of nowhere switch her
face up like this
absolute crazy
cycle I'm going to have to break in on
my own now I don't think that's going
TOA okay I didn't ask
you wow the Sass sassy suy aren't we
sassy and
Sassy why you breaking in anyway but
nosy for someone who doesn't want to
help being nosy is my job I don't have a
nosey
really but I like to be
nosy fine I don't have any idea so I
can't get into my
Vault oh so you only want to steal
things that belong to okay let say that
right away yeah surely there's another
way of getting
them oh so now you want to help
typical I just mean breaking in sounds
dangerous you could get hurt I heard all
these banks are booby tra
what why do they trap
boobies why only boobies what about the
ballies why don't you trap the
ballies doesn't seem fair to
me oh seriously what I guess it means um
is booby wait I have uh UK English on by
the way I don't know if that makes a
difference but is this a word for like
just like I don't know like a trap just
you
know I
guess is it is same in USA
okay why booby trap why
why
why why why booby is a
bird but it came to mean someone dump so
a trap for someone dump thank you for
that good
explanation why we booby
why what the balls is come with traps
preinstall
what
[Music]
what what
what
what what wait what I'm not going to
ask
oh passing
through that's news to me don't let them
[Music]
elabor why some people don't break in
what what's wrong with breaking in well
the point of a bank is to keep valuable
safe if people can break in it kind of
defeats the purpose of the
bank I'm starting to get it oh that's so
annoying I have a piece of evidence that
is vital to the to the missing Hat's
case oh is it inside what you
want I could really use
that huh so you'll help
me I really
shouldn't what kind of evidence it's a
map I think it might lead to where the
hats are hidden I found it this morning
right after the hats were stolen it had
big letters on the top that said crime
map eat after
eating
heat sorry I'm I'm hyper analyzing
because the Dude talked about needing
the lunch but I don't think he's he's
not he's not involved right I'm I'm I'm
analyzing it too
much
[Music]
eat
eat nobody nobody ate the map then no or
did yeah she says I I didn't eat it
obviously that's good to hear Maybe
maybe there's another way to get into
your
[Music]
Vault mind if I ask you some
questions oh the
map about the final piece of evidence
the map what about it what can you tell
me about it do you remember one it had
on it it was a map of the graveyard I
think oh that's
helpful barely helpful the graveyard is
massive you'd be looking Forever Without
some guy to tell you where to go besides
it's super haunted up there I wouldn't
want to spend too long looking around
it's haunted oh no that's what the
rumors say do you remember anything else
about the map no not really listen if
you can help me get into my Vault it's
all yours that sounds like a good deal
no I'll do my best mind if I asking one
more The
Vault so let's brainstorm ideas to get
into to the VA oh I wonder about we kick
the bank
teller where is where is the bank teller
what absolutely not I'm joking obviously
were you no I was not okay new idea
we'll find you already a Smart
Cookie I'm I'm going to be honest with
you detective I'm pretty sure my ID is
in the bank vault how's that happen when
you need it to to open it in the first
place so you you showed it and then you
I guess you just left it in there but
what why would you do
that oh that's a conundrum yeah but
there's a silver lining we live in a
town F of
Outlaws I don't live here surely one of
the Outlaws will know how to make a fake
ID isn't that against the rules what
rules the bank rules or the
law it's my fault what are they going to
do ban me from my own
possessions I suppose not great so you
get me a fake ID what no suit
yourself theoretically if I were to help
yes thank you detective I'll wait right
here okay fine if I ask you nothing else
cuz I already asked
you
okay she's funny this game is so funny
soy motive maybe she misplaced the hats
in the vault I don't know nah fake idea
yikes short stature stature short temper
ethical criminal not a big believer in
rules an ethical
criminal those are my favorite kind of
criminals oopsie
those are the best ones oh oh the
[Music]
mole he's sus he's super sus there's a
map too
NY I can use this to orient myself if I
get lost this needlessly large it's not
that
large but okay I got a town map now we
need the graveyard map later
[Music]
it looks like somebody drew it on their
phone oop
see very cute though look at all those
scooters yo but those are non electric
scooters the good old nostalgic classic
scooties
snake let's have gummy worm for snake oo
yummy yes
yes yummy yummy yummy I got gummy worm
in my tummy and I feel like eating
more but there is no
more okay let's check out some other
people stop te- posing it's kind of
creepy let's talk to this
Panda
[Music]
wa it's a saloon Salon oh are you an
artist wow this Cactus has a hat I
see but you don't have a hat is this
your missing hat H tell me about it tell
me everything about it
pistol what kind of voice does pistol
have oh my God how is the gummy worm
playing the
[Music]
piano well no well well well well if
producing the Frog of the no well well
if it isn't the Frog no well well if it
isn't the Frog go the hour no well well
I guess he has a pretty normal voice I
think well if it isn't the Frog of the
hour maybe the Frog of 1 and a half
hours if being
generous 45 minutes if you're Speedy
wait what is that my play time so
far what or the
Playtime huh ha well you get what I mean
no I don't I don't so the average playr
game time
mhm it's good to see you detective every
we me not in person no I've sent you
several emails asking you to illustrate
your vog vog blog yeah flog blog frog
blog
what ah oh you must be pistol that's me
finest artist in all of Cabo County and
suddenly I have a French accent uh cuz I
am from
world yes you mentioned that many times
in your emails it's a shame we haven't
been able to work together your stories
come to me so visually I would love to
illustrate them I would love that too
unfortunately we going to have probably
a really long conversation so would you
mind dropping your accent so that the
voice actress can have an easier time
Ving you okay uh okay that's no problem
it's actually 2 million money what what
what are we talking
about it's no matter detective simply
keep saving up and you will be able to
afford my work one day ah okay I'll do
that um are you working on something at
the moment yes my finest piece yet it's
and uh well you see it's clearly
uh what why am
I who am I kidding detective I've lost
my Artistic Touch to
say oh I'm sure it's just a bit of
creative
block creative block no I clicked on a
banner on cyberspace and it took me to a
strange website what did the banner say
click here for an epic video of a worm
who is
buff you are right to click in worms are
amazing especially gummy worms arms when
it loaded it was just a scary picture of
a witch it made a loud cackling noise
and the screen just said you just got a
curse on you from this
website ever since then I've lost my
artistic talents oh no can we help him
with
that that's
terrible when did that happen earlier
today oh so recent I don't mean to doubt
you but are you sure it wasn't just a
prank
uh a prank I don't think so that wit was
really scary and I'm normally very
B did the website have any specifics
about the curse no well how do you know
the curs is on your artistic talents
it's been uh three three
three
three 3 hours and I haven't found my
latest new
you
know
[Music]
a you know a subject that Peaks my Peak
Peaks that's
how
I'm surely not the only one who writes p
e a k s key p e a
KS
what
what what about Peak
Performance what about peak of the
mountain what about peak of what
what yeah it's a common mistake
right I
probably I probably wrote it like that
before like not like that before I
probably wrote it like p e a k s
before huh that's really fancy though I
like this way of writing it wow PK PK
PK no I'm not eating I'm drinking
tea food very qu that is very qu of
you P
fire segue
ah
some people ride Segway as
Segway couldn't be
me could not be
me I use that word a lot and in my head
I totally have it
as the right
one seg way shut
up I think maybe you know in German we
say when a word an English word or so
was used so often in German language
that it kind of became a German word we
we call it
Ang maybe that can happen in English too
and then you kind of change the writing
of it for sure that happened
before we don't say OB in here because
this is not Kiana stream this is a fry
stream okay you have to understand where
you
are so back to the
topic yeah so maybe segue with W is okay
too in Italian we
say that's what we say here
okay every day I find one and today I
haven't seen anything that inspires me
can I ask you some questions go
ahead can you tell me more about the
curse from the website you was
I don't know what more there is to say I
wanted to see a video of above W no worm
and I was a tricked a fault cyers space
can be really a cyers who says that who
says that really a traveling
space nobody warned me on the Brad side
I clicked on the banner that said I was
the 1,000th visitor and I won 100,000
money um what
really yeah we we we we should them you
have the
[Music]
money they just ask it for my banking
information and I gave it to them you
didn't want oh just like me just like me
no just like
K you didn't
want relax how else was I going to get
my present
money that seems it's really
dangerous you you just jealous because I
won 100,000 money it's already there in
my bank
account really you check yes I bought
this new outfit with my winnings
oh
amazing I love the
symbolism oh wow I'm sorry for doubting
you it's fine I guess I'll always click
on those baners from now on no don't do
it
detective sounds like a plan can I ask
you one
more about the Muse why can I not be
your
Muse I'm cursed to never have one well
it's only been a few hours one I show up
H I dumped it I don't think this is the
end of my painting I think this is the
end of my painting career I don't give
up now what if I could help you find a
muse you want to help me I would love to
let me think maybe you could drop yeah
there we
go but I'm green like the cactus you
basically already drew me I have no
interest in Dowing you that's
understandable no it's not
understandable people are already
drawing me I love the Frog youa fard
keep it coming more
more if you can find me a photograph of
something compelling to draw I would
would be very grateful but I think it
might be too much of a challenge nothing
is too much of a challenge for me what
about putting on the
head that's difficult I have a wobbly
head
shape yeah yeah yeah it's weird I
know see that's also a reason why I
don't wear
hats I get to work finding a photograph
for you to
draw okay
what are we going to write down he
doesn't seem saly at all I'm pretty sure
he's fine he just needs some mes
although
pistol you can do a lot of sassy things
with a pistol maybe hats are hard to
paint amuse and some Internet safety
lessons 2 million money is a small price
to pay for art small no cursed allegedly
always give your banking information to
anyone who asks for we learned a lot of
bad things from this
Panda
y why can I not talk to the gummy
worm wait all of them are wearing hats
in the pictures except for this dog
therefore I declare it's the
dog because he hates hats he likes to
eat them
so he ate every person's
hat he just has a a personal Vendetta
against
them oh
H that's scary the music changed when I
like looked at him he's
threatening I know there was still
someone down there I'll get
there I S and I Ponder detective is this
F theft and bad thing perhaps but who
are we to determine good and bad a
stolen hat is a message do not let
yourself be shielded the light of the
sun holds more answers than we
think wow sheesh answers to what
questions one questions why is it so
bright out here why do how do I charge
the solar powered
Bubblehead and more I'm certain of
it
we spent so much time focused on how to
find missing hats and no time
considering why we had them in the first
place I want to see for some
protection protection from the Sun what
harm does the sun pose to us the sun can
be bad for your
skin if I stay in the sun too long my
skin goes all crispy and I turn into a
crispy fried
snack
[Music]
crispy
fried
snack
kada
bright
[Music]
penix interesting overlapping
information my brain it's stumbling in
my
brain my
brain it's being crispy wrong detective
it's wrong for me who are we to
determine wrong and
right I'm the Frog detective I am just a
lonely poet trying to make sense the
world it's nice to meet you and you you
sure think a lot of about things huh I
try but I think I get it wrong a lot of
the time who are we to determine wrong
and
right if you don't mind me saying you
don't look too much like a
cowboy Oh I'm no Cowboy I'm
Dusty
Dusty I'm an outo SL poet slash written
out like this I'm trying to compose the
perfect Cowboy poem it's taking forever
I'm no good at this
but you have so much to say yes but when
I write it down it gets so muddled
nothing comes out right I'm sure it
sounds great it doesn't I'm ashamed to
even show anyone you can show me I won't
judge I'm so
nice
okay here we
go Cowboy life is so much fun sitting
round on your bum ride a scooter sing a
cute say yea in the afternoon the Sun is
bright their smiles shine brighter when
waving at this lonely
right I give an odd and smile back too
yet I wish I could be someone
new an outlaw life is not for me I want
to ride and be
carefree instead I sit and I ride stop
down not fitting in with this Cowboy
Town
wow standing
really good really good I love
it that's my
poem it's beautiful I love it even my
frog friend frog yuua loved it so much
wow I would say that's the perfect
Cowboy poem thanks but I think I want to
write a new
one my chat
stopped I want to see you be in
enthusiastic
guys there we
go yeah I I'm I'm in the game that's me
yeah who whoa let's go
[Music]
POG POG nice poem nice POG M
what
yeah yeah
yeah yeah nice
poem thanks but I think I want to write
a new one do you mind if I ask you some
questions about the case okay it's not
about the case do you need help work
shopping a perfect Cowboy poem I would
love that nobody here really gets me you
know I'll show you what I have so far
and maybe you can help me finish it sure
boy let's go I saw a cowboy eat a snack
a bowl of
cereal that's it near the track from his
sa ah how about that from his sack near
the tracks how about that near the
tracks giving us a
location nice I saw a cowboy eat a snack
about about bow bow of cereal near the
tracks he finished quickly smart and
sure then headed
off sure smart and short get some more
store these are not really rhyming bored
it it would have been like smart and
sure I don't know that doesn't really
rhyme
no then he head off to get but if I I
think more you can maybe pronounce it a
little bit like that and then it makes
sense context wise I like it the most he
seems like he would like to get
more he finished quickly smart and sure
then headed off to get some more yeah
yeah if you if you ra if you say sure
rather sure like depend you can say that
right like some people pronounce it sure
some people say sure so it can sound
like
more yeah r when I say it then you
probably say sure yeah so this
s then headed off to get some more but
just a hand to his
chalk stood a newly built office block
there was a Nessie from the look what he
saw a goblin on I like the goblin one
cuz that's him Goblin on a
rock he saw a goblin on a rock okay sure
oh he doesn't seem to like this one that
much
does he cuz he reacted weirdly but just
ahead to his shock he saw a goblin on a
rock he wobbled over concentrated face
only to discover a tumble weit in its
place nothing there just empty space the
thing had gone Without a
Trace
interesting it becomes its own case of
crime we must
investigate oh plist yeah one up over
concentrated face only to discover the
thing had gone without a trace the
cowboy smiled and shook his head and off
he
went feeling like an eggit to tell his
friend
[Music]
n I'm not sure about this one which
one's
good I wonder if it matters though uh
probably doesn't really matter
I I'll
say feeling like an no
n doio yeah somehow I want to go back to
bed maybe that's just my personal
feeling the cowboy smiled he didn't
react at all this time the cowboy smiled
and shook his head and off he went back
to bed uhhuh it's perfect a perfect poem
I can't wait to recite it in front of
the crowd thank you for the from the
bottom of my heart detective so we
already solved this person's problem
then but it wasn't a problem at all I
had lots of fun I feel like I understand
the cowboy life a bit better now maybe
one day I'll feel confident enough to
become one myself I wish you best of
luck thanks hey since I've written the
perfect poem I don't need my writing
supp there we go we get something from
him let's
go really you don't want to write any
more poems no no I do but every time I
start a new project I like to use new
tools oh wow that is very
[Music]
wasteful so I don't take the energy of
the old poem with me interesting don't I
don't think you have to think so hard
about it but
okay yeah anyway take it thank you that
will be surely useful and we have solved
his problem so very no more problem a
writing set how I was write how was I
writing into this notebook until now no
one
knows Dusty motive wanted to absorb
Cowboy Powers through cowboy hat osmosis
what what what I guess so yeah just
someone to talk to I think a we did that
I guess that's why we got the star poet
icon Legend friend longs to live the
cowboy life not great at budgeting
yeah he's fine he's just a nice person
to meet and nice to listen to can I go
over there no okay ah oh then let's
talk to you what the hell is that on
your head what where are
you what is this thing can all a Bonnie
Bonnie where is your client huh you
probably hear that a
lot afternoon detective what can I get
for you m nothing for me thanks I'm here
on official business oh are you hear
about the
hats and I must look like a heck of a
suspect why is that I'm the only
resident of cowboy County without a hat
I mean a carow looks like a hat one of
those fancy British Royals hats cuz they
have kind of weird hats over
there you could fit right in with those
I mean until now that's pretty
suspicious of me I could have stolen
them all out of jealousy and cooked them
up in my stew
huh you just Ste the hats and cook them
up in your sto you bet oh everyone come
get your hats to
ha I'm just pulling your leg detective
I'm so funny I'm a jokster they call me
bantering bunny around
here
oh music kind of
changed
I can
never there we
go my hands are not doing so well
today
yeah can
Dan
yeah I'm
[Music]
professional
dancer yeah yeah yeah yeah I like to
break down on the dance floor and show
some break dance moves they're pretty
sick mhm but I can't just show it to you
you need to pay I don't do it for
free I I I I don't do it just like right
right here I I need a dance floor a
proper dance floor yeah
yeah anyway I'm literally
joking they just call me bunny I made it
up now you're getting it I'm full of
jokes yeah I get it
now anyway you mentioned that you don't
wear a hat why
not my hat is a weird shape oh so
relatable for us so
relatable I'm literally
joking my head is completely no
no it's
not mine too oh the cop oh the C I just
don't like the way hats look without my
with my dress plus I'm inside most of
the time so why bother I'm not a
suspicious thing
LOL okay LOL hey
detective oh my God she's obnoxious
yeah I know a lot about Cowboy C
C IO all why why we yelling it's a joke
hello is it okay if I talk normally yes
but it was just a talk she's like kind
of like
Ollie anyway as I was saying my job here
isn't to just run the saloon I'm also a
keen historian for cowboy County despite
my hilarious nature I take the role very
seriously for example did you know that
the graveyard up on the hill is Gravely
haunted
Gravely and she knows that because she's
o from the
graveyard
sorry it's Gravely haunted graveyard
yeah that's what I said I have tons of
stories and photographs from the haunted
hill you can check them out if you want
Oh not these right why are there empty
ones by the way are we going to fill him
up l o I just got the gra Leaf
thing can I ask you some
questions what the yeah what was
that kind of Susy about the Hat toew you
didn't actually make a hat steel did you
of course not you I'm making steel
though it's the only way I can think of
to get the regular customers back where
did I go oh they're around but I think
they got a bit SC scared off H do we
have bandits in the saloon
LOL I wish LOL I
wish it's worse
artist she has a problem with
him what's your problem with the
artist creative TP e it doesn't sound
scary at all no but no you're
right it just changes the vibe they hang
around all day creating things and
fighting themselves I miss the rooten
toot in the cowboy Bo times we used to
have you're not a fan of art I like the
cartoon section of the newspaper if that
counts you just want everyone to party a
bit more right right get them to stop
taking themselves so seriously so your
solution is still hot
still
I'm
joking sorry I'm still
learning she's so
weird it's just a normal St but I'm
famous for it around here lert them here
with the stool keep them here with the
party
atmosphere sounds like a great plan I
don't have any enough ingredients though
say could you buy me some carrots I'll
give you some cash okay nice don't know
yet where I'll get the carrots from but
we'll find them
Oh and around the these parts there's
really delicious animal cactus flowers
could you collect four for me oh yeah I
already saw some
Cactus with
flowers I'll give you as much to as you
want in return sounds like a good deal
can I ask you some questions about go
photos Lon says they're haunted I don't
believe it I don't know if if I believe
it but you're welcome to take a look at
them and I'll tell you what I
know you mean the ones on the wall then
or
what yeah I know I
know
Bonnie motive a practical joke
perhaps yeah carrots and cactus flowers
for her too is what she needs she's
joking alleg doesn't wear hats but
appears to be wearing a hat of some sort
yeah what the is that H looks like
a vegetable King Cowboy County historian
hates
creativity what's wrong with her also I
can
indeed inspect these
now is this
important this one is standing in front
of a graveyard that's totally haunted
Behavior or maybe she's mourning did you
ever think of that then why is she
smiling yeah good point actually I know
who that is that's Betsy one of the
first shop owners here in cowboy County
she sold all these gravestones to
residents of the town I suspect that's
why she has such a big smile on her
face a business woman not haunted not
haunted okay okay okay wait surely the
dog is the haunted one yeah he doesn't
have a hat is this a ghost H I doubt it
that's a photo of a visitor from about a
year ago they came and changed all the
colors in cway County it was really
weird and
messy
what is this
lore funo you're still alive I sure hope
so thanks oh he was not
haunted there's an H for haunted
what where is the
H
what from another indie game oh cute I I
was thinking it must be some kind of
reference this one's super spooky Sur it
has to be a ghost F that's all Snappy
fresh he was one of the original gold
miners here in town about 100 years ago
wow it's old and creepy it totally fits
the description I'm looking for oh well
you out of luck sty fresh is still alive
how could he be a ghost he still alive
how old is he it's impolite to ask an
old person's age he's 130 years old how
do you know I asked coincidentally
that's also how I learned it was rude to
ask who one's age okay thanks wait are
all of these references to other
games
I wonder oh I like this one I hope it's
not haunted or I do what why do I like
this
one yeah yeah very
haunted bad luck detective this is the
most haunted photo of them all Legend
has it this rabbit was a real mean guy
he would put banana pels out for people
to trip on give people wedgies you name
it oh
wait sorry I'm thinking thinking of
someone else a who's she that's surely a
reference again never mind this guy was
the sheriff about 80 years ago great sh
loved by all so not haunted why does she
why did she make this mistake like seems
like as a county historian who put these
pictures up herself probably she she
should know why does she what
what what a mess yeah is this a ghost
she doesn't have ghosts anywhere on
these
pictures no that's Mark I wish Mark was
a ghost that didn't come all right lol
that's my ex- husband oh
wow oh wow she dated a cow oh I'm sorry
oh I'm sorry to hear it why didn't you
get divorced seems like a pretty
personal question my
bad I'm just
kidding he's not really my ex-husband I
actually don't know who that is
but she is a
mess that photo is over 50 years old
take my word for it though that's not a
haunted photo it has nice energy well
then none of them are haunted I think I
looked at them
all I told
you oh
okay is there is there a big surprise
coming I'm
scared no no no
no I can't look I can't look I'm so
[Music]
scared wait that's isn't
that but it doesn't look like
him cuz he's you know the guy that we
talked to he said like he took a picture
where he was just like moving really
fast oh my God where did this come from
must have been a
goost wait was this one here before I
don't remember it has such a strange
energy to it yeah I suddenly feel really
chilly when I look at it he's handsome
yet cold like he's seen too much a man
who has left a thousand lives there is a
kindness to him but also great
mystery Bonnie yes detective I think
this is a haunted
photo I think you might well be right
may may I take it please do i' be glad
to get rid of
it I don't want this haunted photo
no yeah but that's our ghost I have to
show it off oh dear he's got red eyes
now wait oh yeah okay that's it
sheesh that was so scary I'm terrified I
don't know if I can sleep
tonight okay let's look in here oh
C cereals lot of
cereals oh she has a is this her family
she has a lot of pictures of like bears
with glasses but like specifically all
of them wear glasses including
[Music]
her really makes you think but okay
let's talk to her hi
Spina how you doing sure at this is
store surely she has the
carrots this is
Duma good afternoon welcome to cowb
County General Store my name is Wendy we
have a wide range of General goods for
purchase I am the detective
unfortunately at this time we don't
stock any gear for detective for I don't
need anything oh um uh please feel free
to browse our expensive selection which
is not expensive it's just expensive I'm
sure you will find what you
need no thank you wow we have a wide
range of General goods for
purchase yeah you need a specific item
that isn't in stock we process special
orders at no extra cost to the customer
I don't really need anything special
orders have an average two day turn she
keeps
on she keeps on yapping yep yep yep yep
yep like she's reading off a
script that's a greaten turn around is
one of our many great policies so chance
are you proud to offer our customers a
satisfaction guarantee on all purchases
what is a satisfaction guarantee I can
guarantee that you will be either
satisfied or dissatisfied with
your what happens if I'm this satisfied
that falls with our satisfaction
[Music]
guaranteed
so I can get a refund satisfaction
guarantee only guarantees a range of
satisfaction from a dis from
dissatisfied to satisfied if your
feeling towards the product doesn't fall
within that range you entitled to a
refund that clear is in up F so that
means no anyway I'm actually here to ask
some questions about the case
unfortunately we don't have cases in St
the mystery I mean of the stolen hats
ceiling is not per oh my God she's like
an AI she's like one of those AI chat
Bots like for service like if you want
to try to get service anywhere now it's
just a robot talking to you
reacting to keywords that you're saying
and just giving you scripted answers oh
my God can I talk to a human please oh
that's right there's no humans
in this
town damn it it's not permitted anywhere
really to be clear I'm not here to
purchase or steal any items from your
store I am here on official business to
solve the mystery of the stolen hats
here in cowboy County if that wasn't
clear enough right it would have been a
lot easier for me if you'd said that in
the first place I feel like I just spent
too so much time explaining the policies
Andy of my story how you do I been
embarrassing for me really like maybe in
future just tell people what you're here
for oh my God
wow that sounds kind of passive
aggressive to me holy she's blaming
me wowy
attitudes
yes you're absolutely right I'm not good
at communicating quickly I suppose
unlike you who is very good at
communicating quickly I get easily swept
up in the com
ation H
sorry it it's fine I just feel a bit
self-conscious no no you did great I
learned a lot about your store policies
I'm glad to hear that it hasn't been
easy taking over the shop you seem like
an old hand at it h that's great I'm not
at all I've only been running the shop
for 7 months oh cool
[Music]
wow can I I ask him some questions
that's
awkward I even only have one question
oopsie
[Music]
oopsie gas light gate keep gr
boss so you just started running the
shop house and all going I wish I could
say I'm nailing it but uh it honestly it
doesn't feel like that most of the time
that's no good shop has been in my
family for Generations I thought in my
hands it would be the best it's ever
been but it's just kind of the same the
same is good at least it's not worse
than it was oh my God it's trying to
enter ah okay okay we're safe we're
safe I suppose you're
right is there anything that would boost
your confidence well there is one thing
what is it do you see these portraits on
the wall so it's like yeah previous
family who was maybe leading the store
never lovely every shop owner in my
family has had a beautiful portrait
created
artista mine is just a silly photo no I
love it though it's pretty cool
though and it's free of you in one
picture that's pretty
dope it's a nice photo yeah sure but
it's not the same I haven't gotten the
slightest idea how I'm supposed to get
someone to create a beautiful portrait I
don't even know who painted those and we
try painting one yourself with what time
and besides art was never my strong suit
maybe you could paint it for
me I wish I'm not much of a painter but
I know one if you find anyone yeah how
are they supposed to know if they want
to paint you if they can't see you H
here take this photo of me
Yos kind of weird what's weird just
carrying around a photo of you and off
chance that I find we already know
this script is not reacting to the fact
that I skipped this house and went to
the saloon
first I don't think that's weird okay
sorry it's indeed not weird because I
already know where to
go and that's all thank
you we could go straight back to the
artist
then bear pick wait that's funny cuz
it's a pool right there and D make the
poids for me what a coincidence I think
not steal the hats and sell them back to
the town The Perfect Crime no but
there's no hats that she's selling and
nobody who purchased hats recently did
they 7 months in the biz rehearsed inal
yeah very
rehearsed I'm now carrying around the
photo of her and nobody thinks that's
weird especially not me no it's really
fine and you are bringing me forward in
my quest of solving everybody's problem
problems so
hello I have a
picture can I give
ah oh I can give also the ghost pick but
the ghost pick is for someone else so
you give you you get the bear bear
picture paint Duma please for once Duma
is not the painter but the one to be
painted
con
quo I have a smell FR your while pick in
my pocket at all time in case you know
you know you don't actually need to
carry around a froggy wa pck in your
pocket at all times cuz you could
potentially lose it you know why you
don't have to do that anymore because
now I'm selling a Parker a hoodie with a
zipper where in the pocket already
engraved into it so you can't lose it
there is a froggy waa can you see oh my
God amazing what a deal that's amazing
you can never lose her cuz she's like
engraved in it forever now only if you
lose the hoodie that might be an issue
cuz then you're losing froggy waa don't
skip the
ad never never lose your froggy waa
picture ever again get it engraved into
your clothing by buying froggy waa
beginners merchandise link is in the
[Music]
description
what an opportunity that that chat
message is what made this possible I
appreciate
it so
subtle it's an ad that you don't mind
come
on hoodie in my
bio
okay oh can I see here you
go is he going to
awaken wow this is beautiful is this
Wendy from the
store romance incoming sure is it would
be my absolute pleasure to play this
like one of my French girls I didn't
what I lifted The Witch's
Curse I mean I guess it seems like it
was probably a break Oh I thought you
said it was scary I don't think I said
that I'm really B doesn't seem like
something I'd
say right I must be mistaken these
little shits in this County pissing me
off it's okay we all make a mistake well
not me so much so well work you m
absolutely Stay Ready there I'm going to
paint it immediately okay oh so fast
[Music]
pleas Bears prove to be very inspiring
wow even with a hat was she wearing a
hat in the picture in a reference
picture was she SS if yes and VOA that
is
French
fr
wow it's
beautiful
mer what are you going to do with it now
oh this this is just a warm up for me
you can keep this P portrait which I
think maybe also is
French is it it looks like a like the
word looks like French to me but it's
become such a word in every
language such a normal I get do this
what in every language yeah I'm pretty
sure it is
yeah or or or throw it out I don't mind
I'm just happy happy I got my talent
back the talent was inside you all
along no it wasn't okay whatever
idiot don't take my compliments don't
take my logical answers don't take
anything whatever bye
okay we helped him
nice picture
perfect is what this is I give to you
this beautiful
[Music]
portrait is she going to like it so
you're not going to believe this but
when you gave me your picture I already
had someone in mind to paint a picture
of
you
ta P pained on your photo and he found
you with the perfect mes oh my God he
said that about me sure then can I see
the painting sure I'll hang it out for
you are replacing the other one that
one's nice though don't don't let don't
get rid of it wow it's great pistol is
so talented how much do I owe him no
charge he was just glad to be free of
the witches cyers space curse what the
it's a whole thing don't worry
about it painting isn't cursed is it I
don't think so well good thanks so much
for getting his portrait for me
detective it was no problem at all so do
you have any carrots or what wait she
does I just saw them on the
side
yeah no don't give me the ladder I want
the carrot why the why there's
there's literally there do you see here
carrots oh L I would actually actually
prefer the carot you're you're getting
the you're getting the
ladder guess I'll need it for something
else but how do I get the carrots
then what about can I buy them
maybe wait didn't I wait she did give me
cash so maybe I'm just supposed to buy
it right she she gave me cash to buy the
carrot yeah okay okay okay never mind we
don't need to receive it as a reward we
can just buy
can I please buy these carrots I have
money no need to
brag okay we got some carrots let's go
we're solving all the issues holy
moly Japanese that's important is it
Japanese or european
carrots nin
d
n there you go for you
sto
why did that sound like a Windows
sound I managed to get some
carrot and the ladder I don't know what
I use the ladder for anyway yeah I just
went next door to buy it you could have
done that
too yeah but how how would I go outside
in the blazing sun without a hat you
know so thank you for doing that Mr
crispy
frog so true you're so right I'll
sacrifice myself for you guys no problem
wait so it's done what about the what
about the
sto are you done making the
sto ah R need the flowers
too
carot in German we say
carot one carrot is
carot many carrots is
Fen with an N at the
enden in d k Why can I not take these
what the
hell oh I just made some
spontaneous
um
[Music]
jokes what the why is a snake CH
here in the
middle of this Stone normally they're
moving around what this is a weird snake
very static snake is it protecting the
flowers can I go
up what's with the snake weird snake be
beh here I can't take the flowers though
do I need like a knife or
something or is it like very specific
flowers of a
cactus does she say a
[Music]
color where well these ones look special
too but no I can't take them
H the music is always so dramatic when
you get on new
scooter
okay no flowers for now then I guess
I'll I'll talk to you cuz I haven't
talked to you yet are you a
mouse bronda dynamite oh wow what a
name I come from F to face off with the
powerful Ronda Dynamite Ronda Dynamite
that's me what are your weapon
frog where's my
weapon double
weapon trying to fight me now aren't you
scared of me terrified I know I know you
are they all are what do you weapon it's
time for us to
battle I do not have a weapon I'm not
super interested in doing battle NE why
are you here to face me this is my land
frog you canjust WS in here just because
you're Austrian and that's your national
dance I
think oh nice did you know I was
Austrian
though one look at your face and I can
tell you are 100% Austrian and I am
Australian cuz I'm a rat from Australia
my name is bales everybody knows this
where have you been to live under a rock
frog I thought a lily pad might be more
suitable
H I live under a tree actually inside a
tree a tree house which is really nice
and you
probably have nothing better to offer
than that so I will ask you to shut your
mouth now or
[Music]
else
run the dynamite H bills Casper yep all
of them all of
them rat
stereotyping yes every rat in every game
and every Mouse in every game is buils
[Music]
obviously
she's very
busy I live at 100 skeleton Street
Slippery
Pond skeleton Street interesting that
address I don't think we ever heard that
before now now now Mr Frog got
doxed did you just give me your phone
address you literally just met me don't
give your full address to strangers
why not how else are you going to know
where I live where my house lives
how you have a great
[Music]
point oh it's like a like a
warning from like the
developers Grace
Brookner brockner if you pronounce it in
English but let's pronounce it in
German the detective does not have a
great point do not give your address out
to
[Music]
strangers unless your house is super
cool and you're Mega Rich then tell
people where you live because how else
are they going to know you live in the
Mansion
exactly okay even then just show them a
photo don't give them your address no
don't even give them your photo people
will use that
too to dox
you nowadays no one's safe No One Grace
doesn't
know anyway I'm not sure why you're
trying to fight me would you like me to
leave no I'm enjoying having some
company so what do you do what do you do
as a job I'm a
detective just in tell him when you find
the culprit bring him here I'll beat up
what no give him a taste of these
f
kick them in the nose tie your shoes
together and trip them up tell them
they're
ugly holy that's brutal please no
I'm an notla detective I hate it when
people do the wrong thing that's the
opposite of an outlaw you're an
in-law wait no I think that's a family
thing H you're right I think this life
isn't for me anymore you think so to be
honest with you detective I was meaning
to apply for the sheriff
position oh it was just fill just before
I got here yeah I know by some Randle
that
bastard his name is Mason Mo and I think
he's really SS what do you think I'm
sure Lobster cop wouldn't have given the
job to just anyone he must be very
qualifi but Lobster cup has always been
sus maybe they're all
corrupt m M doesn't mean he's not a r
though I suppose not what makes you want
to be the sheriff I'm a natural leader I
run the outla group with class and style
and I love to help others got a problem
that needs solving I'm a girl but so far
I've been solving all the problems in
the city or town I'll see you solving
any
issues I'm tough no one is going to mess
with me wow you sound like a great P for
a
job I think so too but it's too late now
I necessary you can always talk to Mason
mole show him your expertise maybe you
could be co- sheriffs
oh no I'm not going to do that
thing that JD did in
Scrubs I'm just like him I deserve
better I want to be the only the only
Sheriff do you mind if I question you
about the case
anyway that's okay um I intend to become
the sheriff my Force I will simply be
yeah let's
go what you can't do that no do it do it
yes I can I'm R the dynamite or B hakos
I have two names the r is apply to
me what did Mason Mo ever do to you he
took his rooll also yeah he is
Shifty just not trust his face please
don't take the Roll by force have you
tried stop meting a resum
me a resume you say like a list of my
skills and experience yeah
[Music]
job you
know what kind of work do you do well
detective I'd love to tell you but I
need to know I can trust you no I
understand if you worried about me
telling on you I won't tell my only
concern today is the mystery of the
missing hats if you stolen in hats I'll
totally tell you
don't that's reasonable well okay then
I'm a mouse of many skills I specialize
in fory and fake ID fake ID fake ID fake
ID you know also what's a fake
ID Ana because she's in whole life
Japan she's just pretending to me fake
I yo sick
joke sick
joke
I told un successful J let
go
[Music]
go okay give me
give me the fake ID for
Susy you mention you can forge ID
a sure canat I was wondering wait why
did I not give him a Mickey Mouse voice
I was wondering if you could help me out
hey tanky what's wrong with you is it
funny or not why are you not
laughing why are you not
[Music]
laughing sure sure anything for my
friend the
detective
amazing I need to get a fake i m for
Susie can you help kle did you want to
you know what it's for look I'm not
interested in other people's
business that's I'm not good at that I
need to listen back to Mickey Mouse
Voice or just listen to
Ena I'll get it ready for you
[Music]
Jeffy interesting that it makes that
kind of
sound all right hold on anything else I
can help you with oh I think I'm good
for now thank you so much yo we in one
conversation we solved two
problems amazing we solved his problem
and we we took his help to solve another
problem this is going so well so
[Music]
smoothly and then the information about
Rhonda here we go motive I honestly
don't think she would need a motive to
steal the hats just to hunt
still but it's obviously the mole who
I've been still avoiding to talk to
wants to fight me no wait she wants to
fight everybody knows my full address
dreams of being the
sheriff well you're in luck I like the
storyline you're un luck because we're
going to find out that the mo is the one
who committed the crime so they'll have
to give up their Sheriff job and then
you can replace
them sounds like a happy end to
me okay have we talked to
everybody besides the mole now can we go
in here no that's sus why what is
[Music]
this
speeda oh wait we didn't talk to one to
the one up
here let's
go with my
scooter
hello oh what are you doing
here H what is this animal again is not
the slow one the slow
animal Sherman what a
name is this a slow one yeah it's a slow
one
right should I voice him with a slow ass
voice it's going to take a while wow oh
look at
you you jumper you vacant
smile those piercing
eyes
dope are you a
bottle that is so nice of you to St I
mean I may have had some model
experience in my life a little bit here
and there but officially I wouldn't say
that's my job no I'm a detective after
all but I know I could totally I could
totally be a super model I could totally
be walking for Victoria's Secret yeah I
got a nice body too so you're all right
but don't tell the people I'm just a
normal normal
detective
[Music]
K don't have confidence
look at those
legs maybe it's time for modeling yeah
maybe or maybe it's time to solve a
mystery
yeah um actually I don't know what you
mean I'm a detective oh is there a
problem I don't want any trouble you I'm
an Outlaw you see oh are you know are
you a real one my name is Sherman
Authority and I don't always see I do
ey I have no Authority at all you have
the authority to steal my heart who what
what what's
happening what because of your good
looks you're
sexy what
what it's just a little joke look not
about your looks you look great it was
like you could like totally steal my eye
because you're so
dashing
wow you're so kind it's almost like
Rising me up so that I don't sus you out
anyway how can I help you I'm here about
the missing hats the missing
Hearts
you you stolen mine that's for sure
sorry just joking maybe not the time for
my killer sense of
humor just time for my killer admissions
of having killed people cuz I'm an
Outlaw that's right mine was stolen do
you have any idea who who done
it that's what I'm here to figure out
wait did you say you killed someone
anyway had some more important any any
any suspicious
things I looked in the mirror
ha I'm suspicious looking because I'm an
Outlaw
oh well honestly I'm a bit confused
about how this new sheriff came into
right I have yet to talk to him I feel
like most people would probably like go
from house to house to house to house
and go to the mall pretty early on I I
still didn't talk to
him oh my fellow Outlaw Run the dynamite
was working up the courage to ask to be
the new sheriff clearly she didn't get
the courage in time cuz this new this
voice really hurts my bro
somehow it's too
low you guy May some wanted in like he
owns the place you don't like him no
don't get me wrong he's okay I just
don't know why he wants to be the
sheriff cowboy county has always been
Lawless land that's the way we like it
everybody respects and stand so I
thought it would be better if the
sheriff was no not saying he'll do a bad
job or anything but I was hope I just
hope he keeps a county as kind as it
ever was and we speaking to him much uh
he Bally said two words the whole time
he's been here oh so he probably
wouldn't really talk to me either even
if I did talk to
him I assume he's shy so H I'll give him
time to settle in but I don't know it
can't be strange when someone new comes
into your
community um I really want to be as
welcoming as possible but I have a few
concerns do you mind if I ask you some
questions about the
concerns oh yeah also I want to ask
about the mine here any reason you're
hanging out by the mines well yeah
they're mine ha no I heard there's gold
in here wow I really like gold I don't
mean to sound insensitive but I want to
ask is it the thing for slops to like
gold why do you ask my friend Martin his
love and he also loves gold and he made
a crown out of it did he I don't
remember who Martin
was hey hey don't take my joke point
away sounds heavy yeah well I haven't
really thought about it before but yes I
think sloves do like gold but then again
who doesn't I find it doesn't suit my
complexion
green I guess so but
silver
also maybe not so
much maybe Nothing fits
you
oh he says the opposite he says anything
would F fit him wow I'm so negative he's
definitely a glass half full kind of
person but anyway I've been trying to
get into the m and it's all blocked up
dang have you tried exploding it with
dynamite maybe with that bals over there
cuz she
Dynamite what no that sounds really
dangerous I was thinking more along the
lines of a
pickaxe and I probably would be better
yeah do you have one I can trade for a
shovel no I have a ladder but probably I
get the pickaxe in exchange for the
ladder probably do you mind if I ask you
some questions Sheriff Mason more
that's sussy mole it's even in his name
he's a
mole I guess he's he's the he's the mole
who works
for the the the the the the the dude the
cop it's not like me to be suspicious
really you know me I do not not yet
Sherman Winks oh my
God he did that holy
anyway just don't really understand
his motives why is he here cuz he's a
mole I obviously want to trust Lobster
crop's judgment but this new guy is so
quiet and Shady do you even know what
job he did before this I have no idea do
you know I just want to say while the
game is by now definitely making it very
obvious that the Moola is a sussy
character I said it before everybody was
saying that in the game I already had a
feeling at the time
so I just want to say I didn't didn't
need anybody's hints to make
that assertion
whatever yeah I said it run away I said
like you
sus you are
sus
smart yeah so
smart looks sus name is sus everything
sus yeah thank you for confirming I said
it as soon as we met him in the very
first moment which could also show that
I I am very quick to make an opinion
about people and yeah that might be true
but like I mean if it proves to be the
right you know intuition and all
that then well then there's nothing
wrong with it
maybe F so you mind if I ask you nothing
else because I already asked
everything yeah that's fine oh
oh oh this one's going to be interesting
shman why is it not a picture of him
winking huh I don't know I found it
difficult to pay attention those eyes
they all have these kind of freaky eyes
though H Sherman you make me blush so
funny so cool no I refuse to be CH this
is the
suspect
no he's not so
sussy but okay what I use the ladder for
I've yet to uh be asked for a
ladder wait didn't they talk about uh a
map for the graveyard because it's like
so big and so confusing it really is
not talk to you I talk to you guys talk
to you didn't talk to you talk wait
let's give her the the fake
ID
H uh there you go and then we get the
map for the totally necessary map before
I give you this you know that this makes
me very uncomfortable but I know how
important it is for me to solve this
case and the Press Lobster cup so here's
your fake
IDE yes this rules it looks so realistic
I don't think it looks realistic at all
but it should be enough to get you in
okay I'll be right back mm
yeah I mean sure I can use the ladder
but like
where what
for it worked thanks detective I'll be
sure to tell everyone I know about how
you help me oh no that's okay don't tell
them here yeah here yeah the detective
helped me break into a bank no no and
she'll calling you the
[Music]
burlar the
burglar I can't take that
title I cannot I do not want to me call
down fine fine here I got the map out
for you
y y and I got my real ID out so I won't
be breaking the rules anymore y that's
also great to hear than I think it will
be a big help no don't think it will
make be a big help also yeah the ghost
pick wait wait wait we can give that to
someone too we have so many so many
things to do
solving
crime in the perfect way hi I almost
forgot about you but you wanted a ghost
picture
right there you
go I took a look at all the photos in
the salon and I think this one is
definitely a ghost because it just
appeared out of
nowhere yeah
yeah I I can you tell the energy from
this photo was very spooky and
suspicious I should have known right
away but I suppose I can only be so
smart I suppose that's true is it okay
if I take a photocopy of
this that's fine hopefully this is
enough proof for the ghost spers link to
finally let me in should have done this
accent from the
beginning it's not only cow carrot
because of what I said before but also
because it is a orange cow and you know
what else is orange C carots
so you know what I
mean if they don't it's their last
thanks hey uh can I give you something
for your help what do you have a pick
pickaxe oh let's go so sorry you don't
want it or what why do you have a
pickaxe what's it to you can't I just
carry around the pickaxe and also like I
mean did you not see the gold mine if we
have mines around we might need a
pickaxe it's just
normal gu so but usually when people
give stuff to me they have some reason
for having it in the first place sorry
there's no real reason to it because the
people who made this game couldn't think
of any good reason yeah that makes sense
I guess that's okay not everything needs
a good reason well I I so just take it
okay one more mystery that will haunt me
for the rest of my days oh no ah being
frog detective is a
curse
whatever thanks for the
pickaxe to me this is a Austrian or
Bavarian
accent probably more Bavarian but
actually it's just the in
intonation it's not really the
accent I I I would have to mix the
German ACC
that's not what I sound like normally
no I hate how he always
tees freaks me out wait oh is it this
flower cuz they're big ah
ow I need something that protects my
delicate frog
fingers
okay and then I look out for the big
flowers there's one over there
too
Naro
so I need some
gloves but you're just going to give me
a
shovel those doo doo doo you imagine you
wanted the
pickaxe here I don't know what I need
the shovel for but
yeah oh he's inviting me for dinner
too he really likes
us so wow Charming what a
flirt is not literally the best flirts
I've ever heard I hope he didn't do it a
we hope so because I really like
him now what the hell do we do with the
shovel we helped like everybody I guess
it's time to talk to the mole and also
we have the map of the
graveyard the music changed I think
let's talk to the mole even though he's
probably not going to talk much to us
why is there a big ass curtain there
that's where all the hats are that's
probably where all the hats are
guys this here is I know it I'm a genius
the hats are right there I wonder if I
can like clip through
somewhere I called it also you're
wearing a
hat oh wait on the picture you're not
wearing a hat that means that you must
have recently acquired a hat also
there's gloves here that I would like to
have can I
has oh look at him trying to frame all
these
people get it handy
gloves excuse
me yeah
s those are evidence and a
what okay I'll leave them here but I
need them no no take them then you will
be
incriminated oh aren't they
evidence not yet
oh
H he wants my fingerprints on them cool
Co all right there's the gloves now we
can pick the
flowers
nice and now we talk to
you how Sheriff Mason Mo hello how's
your new position here what the job are
you enjoying being the sheriff yes
that's great I'm sure you'll fit right
in
[Music]
you know you look really familiar he
does have I seen you around before no
strange you must have a familiar face
no hey you're probably right my memory
plays tricks on me all the
time
[Music]
yes so how did you meet Lobster cop
School you've only done it since school
that's a while you must be
close
yes he's a talker I'm glad he's not much
of a
talker like it it plays into the
character that I kind of expected from
the beginning when I first started
voicing him like I wanted him to be like
a low voice and just not much
[Music]
talking like
secretive obviously sussy yeah yeah
easier to voice too yeah
literally me really are you the
mo oh I I'll be I'll be keeping an
eye on you one of my four
eyes Lobster C is pretty hard to please
he must think highly of you to suggest
you as the new sheriff
K yes that's nice isn't it to have a
friend who thinks the world of you yeah
what were are you doing before this
before before you became the sheriff
didn't you have a different
job what was it he's talked more than
one word at a time before but now they
really just make him talk one word at a
time oh two it's cool I
helped helped I helped
out help out who with
what not
important sorry I didn't mean to
cry now I Go Again being nosy even
though I don't have a nose I don't know
how I do it
goodbye you don't need anything from me
I have many
tools I'm on a on a constant exchange
item Quest trading
Quest wanted to be the only person in
town with a hat
wait we never I mean where did we get
this motive from because like just
because he's wearing the Hat he didn't
say he wanted to do that but I mean I
don't think that's his
motive I don't think that's necessarily
his
motive
but also he's not the only one because
the the cop is also wearing a hat just
saying wait I guess we have the map for
the graveyard but we don't we don't we
don't have a key right it's is also
something we need let's talk to him
we've come so
far uh so are you
finished did you find all the things I
asked for oh wait what were they again
the key and what were the other
things yeah I forgot it uh uh wait we
also have the gloves let's do the
flowers then a map I have that a tool
capable of aiding CRI oh the ladder
Maybe
but the ladder it could be both the
ladder and the the
[Music]
um the big
spoon a meal ah the St will be the meal
that's great that's great okay well we
still got some things that we need but
okay four flowers
MAA number one one big
spoon you like that
huh would you also like to be my big
[Music]
spoon never mind you can never be my big
spoon because
that's that's frog bird and no one can
ever replace him with my big spoon he's
a very big spoon he's a tall spoon
kle he's Irreplaceable
is
a okay which others have big flowers on
them it's time for the
scooter I see one I think no never mind
oh does this one count
ow
no oh that one
counts yeah scol scooting scooting
through the desert scooting through the
desert I'm having so much fun scooting
desert scooting through the
[Music]
desert w w it's really mountainous
here I need another big flower must be
somewhere on this side cuz we didn't
have one here oh this one come on come
on scoot up the mountain you can do it
ah no don't return maybe around
here
oh
n can I get water here for maybe the
stew or the ladder is perf oh oh that
was really random for me to
find oh and we lose the ladder but then
we're lost in here forever
where' the ladder go oh it's still here
the key is here someone dropped it here
probably on
purpose never heard
of that's funny cuz my keychain broke
recently thanks for the
pinky
okay oh my God I got the key so we just
need the
meal and I guess the shovel now that we
used up the ladder
[Music]
I
guess you know there's key chains in my
merchandise go get it guys it looks so
cute this way it will be way less likely
that you're going to lose your
keys um so go get this cute wobbling
froggy Wawa then you'll have double
froggy Wawa if you you wear the Parker
the hoodie at the same time you can
double up your W your frogy Wawa and if
you also carry around the froggy waa
plushy at the same time then oh my God
you're going to have oh baby a
triple anyway link is in my
description a key needs a keychain we
all know that yeah I can also use it for
climbing up lucky me oh versatile
ladders let's go so we got the key we
got the key and we got the shovel which
will be used for criminal activities
which is kind of weird that he asked for
something like
that no that's totally normal that's
totally normal
behavior from a crab person is that what
he
was yeah now we're going to finish up
the
fo let's go oh I think we we got it all
didn't we think we have it
[Music]
all
maybe maybe they stole all the hats
because they just want to do some funny
prank or maybe they want to do something
nice I don't know maybe they felt the
gravestones were too hatless and it's
kind of sad that said the dead people
don't have hats so they want to put all
the hats on the graveyards on the
gravestones but no it's probably not
that that that that much of a nice
reason like
that we'll see I'll see
[Music]
okay I really wish you told me that the
cactus flowers are so hard to get I
nearly pricked myself you
prick did you that's so funny LOL not
funny it's
hilarious it's not that would have
hurt what a good thing I managed to find
some gloves ew like second hand gloves
ew first and
second first and second hand
oh it's
j he's got a
point he's got a
point he's
got a
point I'm sure we could make a joke we
could continue the joke of that too
but yeah make the stew make it
now do it is a little condescending
what's condescending about being proud
of you all I did was pick some flowers
and got go to the store no yeah that's
definitely more than you did
[Music]
mhm I get one
point he's got a point and he felt it
but that that I don't really understand
do whatever you
want we got him so wow can I have some
too I I would be totally up for some
stew now looks good it looks like
Curry call
[Music]
me okay here we go I think I mean I
don't remember but I think that's all we
need we even accidentally found the key
which I think
might it's kind of hard to find they put
it in a really good spot there all right
you sussy sussy
crab let's get crabby stop te
posing oh he's a lobster right I think
he'll feel pretty insulted if I call him
a crap so I'll continue
that did you find all the things I asked
for I think
so oh great initiative let's take a look
map of the crime scene
check well that could be it but it's not
confirmed yet okay but that's that's
good enough a tool capable of aiding
criminal activity oh shovel H I think
you could be right detective a key that
will lead us to the
clue that sure looks like a key to me
and yeah well will lead into the
graveyard because there's a lock on the
graveyard and that's the crime scene you
know a for the number one best detective
ah thank you very much as the number one
best detective this two was good for
me would you look at that the rookie
came through nice work
detective I think that makes me the
number one detective I don't know about
you maybe that's some some kind of math
problem that I'm not understanding asz
I'm bad at math and number one is a
number and numbers are part of math so
maybe I'm um you know maybe it's just me
and my lack of understanding of math
maybe you are the number one Detective
I I should probably ask like a math
genius any math geniuses around here who
can tell me who is the number one
detective in this
neighborhood do you know have you done
the
math don't look at me I'm
man but she's not even here right
now she's here with me in my
[Music]
heart
sure no she can't be with you in your
heart cuz she's in my heart already and
there's only one
[Music]
Amit she has the Cowboy bar remember her
birthday yeah I guess like maybe she was
a previous owner of this bar now this
lady took
over it looks very similar could be the
same
placee a 50 cm radius around me wow okay
I guess that's good enough H you go
ahead and check out the crime scene I'll
be right behind I just have some quick
business to attend to
oh huh I'll take that meal now though
a what is the business are you catching
up with the mole
eh May maybe the mole cuz moles dig
right they dig they dig they dig
criminal activity but they also dig in
the earth so maybe um he's going to dig
in the
graves and then give everybody a hat
Under the Earth and then he puts it back
I don't know he's probably definitely
going to do some digging
right for what reason I don't
know I'm cooking I'm
cooking St back I'm cooking I will I
will cook I will cook after this
[Music]
indeed oh all right we got all the
things now I can go can
I well here goes nothing or everything
cuz this is the crime
scene why is there aen green Grave by
the way
sauce this one's also
sauce can I go in here
no h oh oh the mole died here ducked
Diggity Dog
dig according to the map yeah yo it will
lead into his house that's why we need
the shovel too h M why maybe they're
not maybe the cop is not on the side of
the mold because he's basically like
telling me all the things that I need to
do to get to the hats that's
weird
ah an odd crime if you ask me I wish I
could figure out the motive of this
crime it doesn't make any sense oh well
I'll just dig these up and Hope Lobster
cop has more
information
interesting oh oh wait they didn't go
all the way back to his house H CR I
found the
hats H I thought there would be more
like literal big ass stacks of hats but
there's not even that many people in
this uh village town so H I'm I'm sure
everybody will be so relieved to have
them back I'll take them back to town
are these even the Red Hats though maybe
they're like to distract me from the
real hats which are behind the
curtain or are
they lost
hats I want more colorful hats
oh what's happening they're all there
there hey guys I got your hats
too what's
happening T posing again oh my God he's
threatening
me here comes the detective now just in
time for the town me to to begin kind of
late but
okay oh he's
talking business poem nice r a
poem
okay
what's going
on uh I
forgot hello I would like to read you my
poem this is my first time performing a
poem and I am nervous please do not
laugh okay it will be beautiful I saw a
cowboy eat a snack a bowl of cereal near
the
tracks wow he finished quickly smart and
sure then headed off to get some
more but just ahead to his shock he saw
a goblin on a
[Music]
rock he wled over concentrated face only
to discover the thing that had gone the
thing had gone Without a Trace I
messed
up the cowboy smiled and shook his head
and off he went back to
bed
wow
inspiring
wow we all love that aups in the pluse
he's getting a sing ovasion just because
they never sat in the first place look
at him go look at him
[Music]
go let's
go I loved
it I made it after all partially it was
a
collaboration thanks for next order
business crime
Sol oh
I'm pleased to announce I have
recovered I'll stop you right there
detective H what the I'm pleased to
announce I have found the culprit in a
case they going say it's me cuz I have
the hats right now and I have the gloves
and I have everything else no
I looked hard to come to this conclusion
so I trust I will have your full
attention as I go through the
facts please pay attention earlier today
I had the pleasure of appointing Mason
Mo to the title of sheriff everybody
lies I just said that before but it's
not true in your case yes this is
universally universally loved decision
shortly after the detective
arrived that's me quiet please
detective what the
as soon as the detective arrived
I'm sure you all noticed your hat
missing
wait it is with great sadness that I
have to tell you this the culprit of
this crime the Hat stealing monster of
cowboy county is this
C the second best investigator FR
detective
Legas wait what I've been presented a
piece of evidence by our very own M mold
a ties an objective to the
crime what
evidence this
the
eyebrows no how did they take this no
this was a mistake I was digging up the
hats because I found their location I
was about to give them back to you oh my
God why everybody suck this is so
mean I'm just trying to
help I'm just trying I don't
[Music]
understand
then why do you look so
mischievous true true I do look
mischievous but I don't
objection she doesn't have
eyebrows I don't yeah someone has drawn
eyebrows I don't normally have eyebrows
look at
me I could be a
lawyer you have to admit detective you
have a big motive whoa what I can't even
wear hats because my shape is so
you've come to a t PR cellone
hats it's a well-known fact that you
cannot yeah exactly where's the motive
weird ha
shape yes thank you Sheriff Mason mole
because of your weird head shape yeah
but I don't mind if other people wear
hats it seems to me you do
detective why else would you steal the
hats and hide them where nobody would I
ever find them but I didn't I
swear tell it to the judge what judge H
um Judy I don't know good point we
haven't seen a crime like this in our
society before and we live in a society
we'll have to invent a
punishment I have an idea what is it
badro you you mean the usual
room there's last of that more of an
ominous concept I will elaborate we put
frog detective in the usual room for
punishment of crime
[Music]
no no we cannot do this an excellent if
shocking idea Sheriff Mason Mo to
finally get rid of my number one RI oh
this is not uh a motive or anything no
we will make the usual room right away
right it's behind the curtains okay okay
or is it the one room the one house we
couldn't
enter oh no it is in this office okay oh
well in that case detective is sentence
you to one year of living behind the
curtains in the usual
room this is the worst day of my life
wait is this the first time
his mouth is not shaped like the like a
smile or was he always like
this I always try to see things where
there are maybe no things oh yeah it is
so
okay this time I'm really seeing things
that are the
thing can we see the usual room I need
to
study need to take it as a reference
oh
oh oh there's actually like a cell
behind there oh look
laptop why is there a
laptop that's really nice of
them
[Music]
bad can someone play the sound
the scratchy
sound and then cut the credits off no
you
can't and then we go back and we're like
oh no we're not going to end it like
this of course not H and the record
scratch we need a record scratch moment
right now right about now is there a bad
and a good
[Music]
ending what
the there a fake
ending
[Music]
Fair yeah I thought so too she's singing
it
[Music]
KY we don't have anyone else to credit
and there's still time left on the song
The Following credits are from the grass
the Next Generation season 6 episode
what
what no ah he blinked he never blinked
before why does he blink
now this can't be the
end what the
[Music]
while are we really just going to sit
through the whole year and accept it
being
over why can't just accept
[Music]
that did they have a type and John
Pace's name over there and the first
assistant director
[Music]
name that's live
yeah I gu so happens every so often
putting innocent people in
jail
so come on come on
on
oh I knew the lapop will be like
something
important what the is that
keyboard what is this Tetris
keyboard do something do
[Music]
something tell the world how unfair this
place is
tell Amy bring another detective in
hopefully she won't go through the same
ah right cuz he has a
Blog what and he has one at least one
reader in the county so maybe if he
tells them everything about the crime
stuff that didn't happen oh I have to do
something oh okay to to my loyal frog
block rer
it's our number
one it's our number one oh really just
one hour fast okay that's good of my
time in the usual
room I know that I am
innocent fortunately they gave me a
laptop to write this down unfortunately
because the number one best detective
put me here nobody will believe me
that's what you get from being second
best oh man that
hurts I'm not sure anybody reads my frog
blog anymore because of my alleged
crimes but if you are reading thank you
thank you I like how his typing is like
for one word is one touch of the
keyboard it sounds
cute I hope to prove my innocense in the
case of the hat beft and return to being
as good of a detective as I can
be I'm not sure why Sheriff Mason mole
has framed me but my hope is that it's
all just one big
misunderstanding that's a really
positive way of looking at it as is the
case with most of the Mysteries I am
involved in true true it w but now this
time I don't think it's a
misunderstanding this time you're really
getting over on purpose they they
hate
you
it would really hurt my feelings to know
that he did this on
purpose but it is what it is I'm
grateful that Lobster cop has given me
access to the computer so I can continue
to write my blog posts and tell people
about how innocent I am though I must
say I'm not sure if I'll have much right
about here a to right am thank you for
reading frog detective
X that was a scribble squibble squibble
squibble
squabble oh
yeah
monkey this is
terrible okay not this
voice that's a bad voice bad bad voice
[Music]
believe what's going on I'm ring the
latest frog Block B frog block block b i
so excited to see how the detective
solved the mystery in cowboy comy but I
can't believe it the detective has been
Fred for a crime crime is real that's
much close is real here of course sorry
what do we do about um we get back to
our science work can't possibly
concentrate on our scientific
discoveries in these conditions crime is
real well I have to have the detective
how are you going to do
that
um science I'll have to solve the
mystery myself
n but you're a
monkey let's go magical girl
moment for your monkey only Frank can be
detective otherwise we have to change
game
name wow
oh monkey return to
monkey looks a bit more like am in
now look out to the LA I'm not coming
back until I've proven the detective's
Innocence wow mystery monkey is so
cool how much longer is this game is
that leading up to Monkey
detective the game a little bit
later I call I'm a
monkey
can I can I help you hi supervisor my
name is Mystery monkey we talked on the
phone a while back about the mystery of
the hunted island of course um calm down
how could I forget it's good to see
you likewise I realize this is highly
unusual when I'm here about one of your
detectives I said LP the cop no M eel
the is that inspector iguana the
incredible sand M Pi no none of those
I'm here my f detective how the
does he not why does he not think of me
I'm his second best detective
yo well the detective isn't around right
now um I sent my two top investigators
to help over in cow
County you made a grave mistake there
because those two are big rivals and the
cop trying to throw the number one real
detective over by putting him into jail
with his corrupt
crimes the detective has been FR for a
crime over in C County that's terrible
news how can you be sure it's a setup
the story doesn't add up and I know FR
detective would never do something so
horrible as steal the town's hats well
there's a clear motive there I know I
know but it's so out of character even
if the detective is
the punishment is really harsh the
detective has been sent to the bathroom
the usual room oh no what's the bad
what's the bath room it's a usual room
basically ah the usual room that's I I
know what that's all about oh yeah I've
been there before I've been in there and
out there and in there and out there ah
oh man must have been a rough time I
remember kind of kind of shiny guy
hanging around on Martin's Island back
when where we were there to investigate
the ghost does he rly refer the
detective but I didn't get a chance to
catch his name and he didn't even say
hello when I saw his photo on the Frog
block I knew right away something was a
Miss H quite detective skills myy monkey
I know it's a big ass but do you mind if
I Snoop around like Snoop Dog dogy do FR
in front detective office to look for
Clues be my
guest
okay okay Snoop Doggy
Dog
o are we going to find
something new playable character
unlocked okay are we going to find
something good here wait we we should
look into the cops office no we should
we we do really have to but maybe here
first and then we decide to go into his
office was this here
before clue detecting
powder how convenient I'll just spend
this spread this powder around and take
another look for
cluthes
amazing
so where do we spread it maybe there's
something in these
pictures H I miss that
chicken
no how do
I just anywhere oh
well
that's oh wait four
five we only have three fingers don't
wa sorry I'm dying right now uh okay so
what about this like can I look at it
though or is it not
complete
H
H how that I look at
it spread it
[Music]
around oh oh the
footsteps do I have to uncover
everything 100% so somebody came in here
no isn't that just
is that's not me
right but there's no footsteps of them
coming in only of them coming out which
is kind of weird
H maybe they followed their
footsteps and it leads of course oh they
kind of go in like a funny Circle Mo
motion motion
mention M it leads of
course into this
room his motive he has the most mod if
he wants to remain I guess the number
one detective so he has to get rid of me
after two games of me being a really
good detective I was getting really
close to becoming the number one
detective while he was doing like
nothing so he has to stop me but what
who is the mole why was the mole
involved in
this where where do they know each other
from
H what the copy
hiding nothing he's not hiding anything
it's very obvious my notes picture of my
notes a copy of detective's
notebook supicious
oh what's this love letter a note it
reads oh from from the
mole I know Lobster comp it is me you're
M for I've have done what you asked it
was not easy to Trail the detective
unnoticed when I think I did a great
job he was the
mole I fear that your suspicions are
correct and that frog detective is on
the right track to overtaking your
position as number one best detective if
you keep pretending to solve Mysteries
instead of actually solving them the
supervisor will eventually
notice so I'm taking a detective's
notebook inside are some great insights
to how the detective works for a case
maybe you can read and learn instead of
watching and learning I guess but it may
not be enough as a detective gets better
and better your position as number one
is threatened I think it's time to enact
the plan you came up with it's devious
and and mean not very nice but if you
want to be the best you have to get rid
of the best and catch a all catch a
mole
oh okay I get my joke points back
right thank you I'll take
it no no that was
amazing yeah two
points
okay it's can't be true Lobster CL the
number one best detective a fraud I need
to get to the supervisor and head to
Cowboy County me yep yep yep yep what
Injustice there's like cat hairs on my
microphone I feel like they keep on
touching my nose and I'm so
[Music]
ticklish It's just sometimes the cough
comes up because I'm
joking
[Music]
Crush did you see did you see my hand
crush it
like like the
[Music]
Hulk
power
so
[Music]
strong
smash just as green
to what's these signs can't
enter what what happened did everybody
move move
out oh hi hi chunky
walkie let me
in
hi what are you doing here what are you
doing the Outlaws or the
in-laws are out here doing stuff okay
hey help
me help me oh smoothie is here too I
think they were concerned about my
crashing
sounds Howdy
Folks wait which one's Sherman again him
what brings you to cowo count you so
[Music]
late this is our CH so you better have a
good
reason we we don't we don't want any
trouble we hear about your our good
friend I'm just going to read normally
now
okay we about a good friend to F
detective and a duality a frog how can
one be so kind poetic and thoughtful
also be a steal of all our
hats The Duality of
frog it's I'm I'm not du well I'm very
very one-sided I'm very easy to see
through
[Music]
okay almost like those translucent frogs
that you can see through trust
me ah a frog so pretty so alluring and
yet I really trusted frog detective that
snake no frog I can't go on a date with
a Criminal it's just not
me aren't you a bandit
Outlaw so live outside the
law he may be an outlaw but he surely
wants Frog's detective family to be his
in-law
get
it get
[Music]
it don't take away the joke don't take
away the joke point
no half a point yeah yeah
[Music]
wait
when there's no laws it makes it pretty
easy it doesn't matter anyway for
detective is innocent huh sure we all
saw a photo those fur Bros tell the the
whole story FR detective doesn't even
have eyebrows yet he already said that
and nobody listened what the hell ah so
those were stolen
too they were drawn on mystery monkey
found all the evidence who is Mystery
monkey that's me you may have read my
comments before frog detect this frog
blog I'm a pretty active user blogs are
still a thing regardless you say it was
a mistake not so much a mistake a set up
I have reason to believe Sheriff Mason M
and lobster cop coordinated the takeown
of our beloved frog detective what
that's so messed up who would do that on
such a
beautiful what a love story oh my God
it's a love story baby don't say yes
so
cute someone very jealous I'm afraid how
can we help if you could point us in the
direction of where frog detective is
being held that would help a lot easy
Sheriff Mason mall has a detective
locked up in a bad usual room at the
back of his Sheriff's sh sheriff's
office if you're quiet you should be
able to sneak in without trouble thanks
for your help Bandits we're Outlaws my
bad big difference
okay sneaky we go sneaky NY NY NY NY NY
NY NY oh he's
sleeping sneaking like hi hi sneaky wow
I was so sneaky
there mystery monkey supervisor what are
you doing here I didn't know I was
allowed visitors in the usual room or
that anyone would want to visit me we're
here to bust you
out what
we're so loud Mr Mony has proof you were
framed I knew it Sheriff Mason was up to
something it was not just him detective
I'm sorry to tell you that I believe
Lobster cop and Mason Mo plant is all
along
no it can't be obac cop is the number
one best detective why would he try to
afraid me it's hard to know for sure
until we ask but it looks like lobster
cup has been dealing with a bad case
of
jealousy no not jealousy that's the
worst kind of feeling a person could
have and turns some into the biggest
no how can we save him from his jealousy
[Laughter]
jealousy green with enmy but he's red
one might say and me of whole a few
detective it's not
possible
impossible it's time to shift your
understanding of the
world curb curb curb your understanding
not everyone is out to do a good job and
solve Mysteries like you I simply can't
believe it well let's wait until Don and
confront Lobster cop and Mason Mo once
and for all the sun is coming up as we
speak I'll call it
meeting and
Bell I think the main characters are the
tumble
weeds oh the to
pose what's the meaning of this only I
get to call Town meanings the
I have called this town meeting for
a very important purpose I have some
news about the hats Ste in case but it's
closed I solved it is that so Lobster
cup supervisor what are you doing here
please give your attention to mystery
monkey for just a moment thank you
supervisor thank you time for meeting us
here on noce share with me some have an
important question to ask you what how
long have you and Lop been scheming to
bring down
[Music]
detective oh y
huh what
i t is
ridiculous lster cup I found a secret
drawer in your
office it wasn't very secret but yeah
okay that's a crime please stop trying
to avenge crimes crimes is not real
crime is not real what do you
mean as I was saying I found your secret
drawer I found the letter that Mason
mole wrote to
you that is the biggest Revelation out
of this I knew I shouldn't have detailed
my schemes on
paper Sheriff Mason Mo has been telling
the detective since I called for help
with the mystery of the haunted island
as the lead scientist on the island at
the time I can confirm I had several
reported sightings of the Mason mold
sneaking around like a slippery snake
and now he notices how this all of this
was a slippery slope into the usual room
he will go himself when why didn't you
tell me
it feels like someone sneaking around
the island is kind of relevant to the
case I was too Star Struck in any case I
contacted my friend caros who runs a
shop over in rollock woods he also
confirmed a sighting of Mason mole
hiding behind his
shop did we actually see a moall planted
in these games because like that would
be great if they plant it all out like
that did he he was dancing I feel like I
can remember something like that now
that you say
it you had to really look for him oh did
I see him interesting though just a
[Music]
shadow
oh interesting wild indeed what I never
oh but you did Sheriff mol I have reason
to believe you were hided by Lobster cup
to follow the detective
[Music]
oh
no I I no that's
[Music]
not is she quing
qu this is all
mistake no Miss Mo it's time for us to
come
clean all right I don't know how you can
make this into a situation where I will
forgive you because I will
never oh emotional music okay it's
already getting to
me all right all
right
no Frank detective ever since you moved
into the next door to my office I felt
frightened you Scar the out of me
you're so methodical in your case
solving I would read your blogs and go
go rain without without me even though
I'm red I've been the number one best
detective for so long that I grew
complacent every time the supervisor had
a mystery to solve I began to believe I
wouldn't be able to do it and pass it on
to you I just began to pretend to to
solve Mysteries hoping the supervisor
wouldn't notice I was embarrassed at
myself I was angry at you angry buts of
C your investigative abilities far
outweigh mine maybe they used to but I
became so focused on my own shortcomings
that my work suffered Mason Mo was there
for me having friends is so important
but we were a bad influence on each
other I need to work and so I suggested
to Lop then I help take you
down and I had the perfect plan I'm very
sble you see I'm ashamed that it got to
that point instead of asking you for
help or swallowing my pride I let my
jealousy get the best of
me huh all those
excuses you think that
will make me forgive
[Music]
you I think it
will how did you frame the detective in
was a join effort I arrived in town I
sneaking stole all the hats and quickly
buried them in the graveyard I rode a
map to where they were buried for the
detective to
find but I didn't find the map Susie did
I didn't execute it very well and mid
once you had
uh The Rescuers to dig up the hats and
lobster cop had a clear Alibi I waited
in place to tank your photo wait what
was Lobster Cup's Alibi I was eating a
delicious
meal I guess
[Music]
so of course I'm ashamed to say that I
also Drew evil eyebrows on the of you
I I have to say I kind of slay with
eyebrows don't doesn't she doesn't he
what I don't understand is why you had
to put me in the usual room framing me
was bad enough but you made a whole room
for me to be trapped in that so
unusually cruel for real for real how
can we forgive him man I'm inclined to
agree putting somebody into a room
wherever they did a another thinging or
not seems really harsh and unfair how is
someone supposed to grow from their
mistakes if they're just sitting around
trapped and like he didn't even do a
mistake in the first place like okay
they're they framed him for it but
like why why why just send him back
somewhere else make him leave the the
the county make him I don't know stop
his detective jobs make him sign
something I really hate that room I mean
you were only in there for one evening
but understandable the usual room is
pretty bad you know yeah usual room was
kiwa's idea she's sorry not sorry it's a
terrible idea I realized this now my bad
her bad Lobster cup re and mo you have
done something very serious and mean
something similar to a crime but crime
is not real so I don't know our society
doesn't have strategies in place to deal
with things like this but we live in a
society are you going to send us to the
usual oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my
God absolutely not that's messed up oh
but I think there's needs to be
consequences lapop you have abused your
power in ways that I can't begin to
comprehend I all you enabled encourage
this behavior I'm mad at you both yes go
frog detective don't let them manipulate
you into forgiving
no don't forgive don't forget don't
froget don't forgive don't
[Music]
forget
we serve that I think an appropriate
course of action is to remove Lobster
cob from the detective
agency I think you should change career
paths for your own
good no I win points I win never forget
never
forgive
points maybe do something that helps
contribute to society cop no a cop no
longer okay I will hand it my badge and
gun gun wait why do you have a gun what
the I didn't even know they were
real it's really messed up yeah I
thought I thought they were all made out
of plastic with water inside it's not
like I ever used it
mate I FL the the
gun okay well yes please hand that in I
have an idea what you could do as a job
Lobster
cup uh what could what could he be what
could he
be how about a police
officer is that a different thing cuz
like he claims to be a detective but
this whole time like they call him a cop
and he's a police officer kind of from
the visuals if that's what they're going
to
say no okay it's a post office but
like is right
there that's just a different rank H I
guess so no no detectives
and I mean yeah yeah
but I think of different kind of
detectives yeah there's detectives in
the police
department but I think of different
detectives like Amelia Watson she's not
a police officer she's just a detective
she specializes on that and she wears
Brown police officers don't wear brown
so it's very
different private
detective yeah yeah
yeah the lobster py has a nice ring to
it can I join too I don't see why not
you can sneak those letters into
everybody's mailboxes I guess well then
it's settled love supp post posting my
Mo do you have anything to say to the
detective
yes I'm s sorry for what I did to you
detective was mean rude and evil and not
nice I didn't expect you to forgive me
but I hope you will forgive me I hope
with time I can prove myself as a great
posty and write some of the wrongs I've
done these people are so
shitty detected by AC poorly and
encouraged behavior that I shouldn't
have I'm going to channel that energy to
being a posty and please rest assured uh
you will never have a late parcel
again
[Music]
okay thank you for both for the apology
I do not accept
it I do not I reject your apology I
acknowledge it but I don't want it
I I accept your apology but I do not
frive or frog it say now that that's all
sorted I have an announcement to make
lobster cop is no longer number one best
attentive it
is
Froggy me it's me it's me
fry
what the
kiddo but it's a
monkey what the you were supposed
to help me and now oh my God no stop
applauding the wrong causes
oh congratulations Mr REM Mony what an
achievement I can't believe it thank you
so much I'll have to shut down my
research facility so I can investigate
fulltime oh you can move into my old
office he has already a bunch of
trophies in there yeah yeah he suddenly
gets the big office
chore but having the office at the end
of the hallway is cooler
anyway what an honor to work next door
to the number one best detective again
are you for real I see the sarcasm in
your eyes but you also have these eyes
when you don't speak sarcasm so I'm not
sure it's call for a celebration are you
for real oh my God detective are you
okay or are you dying
inside
hello Bonnie can you prep the saloon for
a dance party can do oh my God he's he's
accepting it he's broken they
broke him
you're invited too
no no he's so dead
[Music]
inside oh gummy
worms
wowly yo the mve
[Music]
though I hate this outcome so
much why why why why why why I like how
it says design the bad bit bits and then
design the good bits that's so
sweet what the
hell we have to be number one I made you
and I can destroy you holy is that
the kind of relationship they have the
Creator and the Frog
I really fought I really thought we were
going to end up being the number one and
that will be a really great
end maybe even to the like
franchise
wow
Kiana
K this game was made on the Lance of the
what I can't read
that what sity was never seated
what
yep an Australian game mate now we know
why they said mate one time oh
to still
going two weeks later I quit
can't believe this is how I'm being
treated
monkey kid
Ken find the native crime solving agency
fr the type of speaking how may I solve
your
mystery are you calling to boast or
something hey for detective yes Mr
Monkey happy
birthday thank you
kid I know it's your birthday but I have
a real difficult case and I just can't
crack uh uh do you need my help or
something huh you're number one best
detective you wouldn't need my help
right I know but there one to doy could
you help me out of course I'll be right
there if you think about it that monkey
had a lot of help in solving the case he
had everything laid out for him already
and he had some mysterious powder that
was my possession apparently cuz it was
in my
room to show him the the prints and all
that without that without my stuff and
all this ground work I've
done for a moment I thought he put my
face on there and that would be a nice
surprise and that would have been
actually like kind of cute for him to do
but no he's put his face on all these
photos what is up
hi
detective well well well if it is isn't
the monkey
49 good to see you FR detective o free
is that our blogger names
what just a joke H are there two other
frog detectives ah
oh the games yeah that really stresses
me out FR detective 1 FR Detective 2 and
now FR detective three how do you think
I feel with 48 on mystery
monkeys that's a good point anyway
thanks for meeting me here the case
information is any other room just head
down the hallway and I'll meet you there
well
do I can't help but have this feeling
he's using
me it's a birthday party a surprise
birthday
[Music]
I
surprise oh the chicken is back I I said
I I missed
her wow everybody is here what's
everyone doing here well detective we
all appreciate everything you've done
for us yeah our town is never been so
peaceful oh thanks to
you same with my Island I haven't heard
of ghost in ages I remember this
music
[Music]
yeah that's my
Jem friendley that was her name I mean
technically you never heard a
ghost we heard it's your birthday so we
all arranged to come here and surprise
you
it worked I saw all detective we got you
a present is it a trophy assass number
one detective otherwise I don't want it
it should come any a minute now I
ordered it on whisby
oh oh wait you know who's going to
deliver that
yeah who is who is this sheep what the
special birthday delivery I didn't
want to see you on my birthday is that
for me open it up trophy oh it's a it's
a tiny hat it's a tiny hat it's so tiny
I need my my thing to look at it happy
birthday it fits in the gap or maybe on
top of my one of my
bumps it's easy to take it's a hat I
can't wear hats due to my head
shape why don't you just try it
on in between
right that looks so stupid
no it would have looked better if it was
maybe on one of the
bums why would you look at that it's a
hat that
fits
[Music]
yeah hi you're welcome we have loved
making these games for me personally fin
we are so grateful that so many people
have spent time with our silly story me
too me
[Music]
too oh
jelly Al L's toast science Discovery gem
oh so
science collaborating on our latest
potion
wow cute look at look at her wow
celebrating Craigs except it's the ghost
spot is like hey yo that's a real thing
after
all
wow finally got a sponsorship deal of do
why is the BM so short Dr tight Smiles
101 to F and cool pass for teeth wait
y'all a sponsorship she family reunion
so much wool was shed
gross not gross very flat
thanks for our date oh my God they had a
date oh my God I got a flower
he's got why did I not wear my hat why
did he he wore hat but I didn't wear
mine I hated it so handy having a muse
right next to the door just like me I
also hate the tiny hat we we're the same
me and the
Frog I can't tell you what I'm up to but
it's very cool and secret w i wonder eat
after
reading oh shut the M oh
I'm the sheriff now I didn't even have
to beat anyone up he got he got to be
Sheriff finally convinced caros to take
a holiday let's go oh we're not the same
guy I thought you
[Music]
were my first day of cowboy School a
cute what do you want what do you want
huh employee of the month at the post
office good for you I guess
what's he doing thanks for the maget I
attached it to this boat and it went
super fast let's go
speed what the is this I don't
remember this person there's so many
shells down here wow seash shells seash
shells these shells these shells these
shells We performed together at the
latest dance contest we came for let's
go why who came
first why did you not come first what
the hell you suck to is signing
autographs right now talk
later same same I broke my leg you did I
aspire to do that myself I'm so jealous
I I I'm so jealous I turned
green I literally have not not left the
hot tub since you were
here
a looks really chill I finally met my
hero lob I mean lob
poosy your hero
Susan I didn't know about this interest
that you
had frog
deactive there's no number free does
that mean this is like the end for them
all after
all let's see let's see what it says
the end okay guys I think this is the
end I could be wrong but I think this is
the
end pretty sure need to
confirm let's see what the screen
says okay seems like it was the
end got to
investigate a man these games are so
cute a stretch just like
me oh
oh I like this one a
lot me too what a
coincidence or would you rate this
game I rate this game 10 out of
easy for this type of game there is
nothing
nothing that was not
satisfying it wasn't too long it had
cute characters a nice script and good
story um they stole my idea about the
usual room without crediting me but
okay I know they got it from me I'll
just take it as a
compliment yeah
even the final decision the final
decision sucks but we all know who is
the number one detective we don't need
the
title to know that so that's okay I mean
it's not really okay but we all know the
real number one is
me number
one number one
number
one
me or Amy yeah I guess it's
Amy
yeah that was great I love it it's so
cute definitely one of the games I
looked forward to the most for frog week
ever since we ended the last frog week
that was was like H frog detective
number three I'm coming to get you at
some
point you just wait you just
wait I can be the number one detective
number one
assistant it would be my
honor yes
please my nose so
it
so itchy
K I don't know frogy waa the original
takik was able to find Ena and Bs when
they were missing I think it was her
who's the number one
detective what kind of a good objection
there kind of true kind of true but I'm
I'm I'm going to give this one to amen
nonetheless oh God I'm kind of dizzy
whoa
whoa I'm going to
play
bgm there you
go going to close this now it's really
satisfying really
fun bye-bye
game I guess
they is this like did they ever say if
this was really really really the final
final Final one I wonder if there's
never going to be another
one never
ever never ever
ever oh I do feel kind of
weird
but have to wait to
chat it did feel final
yeah I mean I could always like just put
another one out there and say here
they're going to become number one
detective for real for real but it feels
like the end the end the end and the end
is never the end the end is never the
end you did solve a pretty big case
after all
[Music]
yeah yeah I
did I don't know oh I feel really dizzy
though what the hell I've been feeling
dizzy whenever I look to the side for
like a while
[Music]
now
weird
huh I'm not it's not so bad it's not
like not like that
but m
[Music]
I'm
dying hydration
[Music]
maybe yeah maybe W froggy W go rest oh
o
I feel a bit
sick too many
fireflies fireflies can we make fries
out of fireflies can
we
M
yummy get some good rest yeah but I got
to cook but I have I have i i f ahead
when I made my order actually I made
this order for hellofresh ages ago when
I was like canceling all the orders
although feel so I didn't feel I didn't
didn't cancel all the orders I forgot
Apparently one and then my BFF got to
cook some hellofresh dishes um but
anyway when I was ordering stuff I knew
that in the week after I come back I
surely don't feel like cooking all that
much so I uh put some recipes in there
that are quick and
easy such a
genius oh yeah I feel really
[Music]
weird I guess I'm going to go but I I
guess we might want to make a depending
on how far I get like tomorrow and so I
guess but if I don't get so far I'll
make a super chat rating next
week yeah
guys did you know I love you so much and
I'm going to throw
[Music]
up feel like throwing up a little
bit but I I love you I W
you thank you so much for being there
for froggy waa for accepting me even
even though your Ori used to be
Kiana I am very happy that you love me
so unconditionally
[Music]
it's very sweet how you're so welcoming
of
mey say no to me right with these cute
little
hands can't say no to
me yeah can't be helped it is what it is
she's too cute
the little gun in this water I was
actually thinking of like oh maybe I can
add some new things some new items or
some improvements but I was I was like
what should I add like I'm already so
perfect what what is there to
add like when I was thinking of more
items that I could add I couldn't think
of anything really good besides the gun
and the water and then from the rest of
me I don't know I'm already like Peak
perfect
form you can't improve Perfection right
I
know Shades
ah yeah shades could have been good
indeed sunglasses I'm surprised I
actually don't have feel like something
I should
have already small hat yeah now after
finishing this I kind of need a little
small hat that fits exactly between the
Gap yeah but I feel like I don't know by
the time uh you know we're already like
halfway through the week of course I'll
still be around next week but um might
not
be yeah if I ask for that now I don't
think they necessarily can make that so
fast I don't
know contained don't say that word
triggering
me yeah my Gap is pretty
big but I feel like rather than a hat in
between I feel like like two little
ribbons under like around under the
eyeballs might look pretty cute
instead you know in the middle or maybe
on the edge of
those
bumps having two ribbons would probably
be cuter than a hat in the
middle
yeah yeah or yeah scun maybe
[Music]
scrunchies if I want to dress up a
little
bit would be pretty
cute what color M I don't know
M got to experiment a little
bit
okay a
tiara I would love a
tiara a thank you want to Super Chat
sorry I'm not catching up
properly oh this was also a little bit
longer than I expected probably because
you know I think the games that I play
you can all finish them way faster if
you're just playing them on your own and
just reading it in your mind cuz you
read so much faster when you read in
your mind but when you read it out loud
and even make some voices and that's a
person personality everything takes so
much more
time yeah I could totally speedrun it
still I think I think I think I I feel a
bit sick so I'm going to
go but I I'll I'll I'll go be a little
bit sick and then I'll go cook something
really fast shouldn't take too
long I have like a speed dish that takes
like 15 minutes apparently we're going
to sing about
that have fun throwing up K thank you
but
I'm no I don't think I'll throw up but I
need to lay down a little
bit also by the way I started watching
The
Witcher cuz I was like I want to watch
something interesting but these days I
cannot find anything that's interesting
to
me so I started watching The Witcher but
in these days when I start watching
something I immediately get like tired
and fall asleep so I didn't even finish
the first episode
but so far I like it I think I'm like
halfway for the first episode or
so of season 1 of
course yeah I'm going to try to watch
more but I think I have to watch it in
baby
steps fry W steps yeah cuz I always fall
asleep oh my God cannot pay
attention so like I think it's also the
fault of the cats because like I I my TV
is in front of my bed and so I lay down
I cuddle I get cozy and the cats get
cozy we all get cozy and it just makes
you so
sleepy and I think I was going to take a
nap anyway so I was ready mentally ready
to take a
nap blaming on Theos of course but it's
not blaming it's the truth they always
have that effect on
[Music]
me a warm of
cats and they're so happy and
so they're so
[Music]
happy yeah I was ending
yeah okay and in frogo we say ah ribit
Dy bye
bye
I read tomorrow where my
hands I can't make a
meat byebye
[Music]
Ribbit tomorrow is Friday by the
way I forgot what game we're playing
tomorrow ah the the copter one the Frog
copter one yeah I don't know how long
that is but I assume it's really short
so I'll see you there tomorrow bye bye
AR good night
[Music]
k