[Music]
so
my
[Music]
do
okay
one second please everybody please take
a seat uh
calmly
take a seat take a seat
everybody find yourself a seat if
there's no more seats then sit on
someone else
it's not that difficult
all right you have a sit
if it
fits it sits okay
as this is an urgent
urgent
uh employee
meeting
very urgent
i urge you
to participate in this employee meeting
if you work for kmp otherwise you're
fired
so
sorry my voice is a bit um of course of
course horse i don't know
um so um yes it is actually the first
meeting that we have uh like this maybe
there will be more uh often
announcements like this
uh
actually there's um
two announcements um so recently you may
have uh gotten to know him
um
but uh frederick our recent hire
has been fired
yes frederick has been stealing
uh ingredients from the kitchen
and taking them home to fried chicken at
home
uh
if if if he would have let me know
earlier i may have forgiven it
but he did it without getting my
permission so without further ado um
frederick you're fired
okay
now here comes the actual news that i
needed to talk to you guys about today
it's really gonna be quick um but i
could not hold back i felt the need to
inform you as soon as possible
um before you find out from somebody
else
um
i've been
i've been threatened
by um
magazines and paparazzis
that they would um
publicize this
uh therefore i take it into my own hands
to publicize it myself
takanawa has been cited in a gym today
that's right takanawa has been cited in
the gym today
people
may think especially the people of kfp
may think that this is a fake kiara but
i want to make it clear here and today
it is not fake no yes it is i am the
same person
and i did not go there to look at cute
girls but no
i went there too
[Music]
work out
i went there to work out
[Music]
now everybody starts small
and so did i
do not roast me on my accomplishments i
am proud of myself i thought i would go
there for five minutes but i was there
for
20 minutes
i mean no longer there but working out
actively 20 minutes
it is actually an incredible
accomplishment
i did not break down and threw up not
yet
so um
i have
been seen using the rowing machine this
is a photo again from a paparazzi as you
can see i've worked out for
12.35 minutes on the rowing machine
rowing an incredible 1000 meters
and burning an incredible
31 calories
on her very first try on the rowing
machine
the what's the the what it says what's
there that's having like
energy i i ended at this point so it was
no more but i think it went up to 45.
now this is
you guys know i have
practically no muscles in my arms um so
the fact that i even was on this longer
than
three minutes is actually surprising
um
don't roast me okay this is actually
pretty amazing at first i was like i'll
be fine if i do five minutes i'm proud
of myself then i got about five minutes
and i was like you know what i'm gonna
go longer and then i went to 10 minutes
and then i was like okay but we're still
under a thousand meters
just a few more meters and we'll get to
thousands so let's do it so then i kept
on motivating myself and i ended up here
um
then
you thought it would end here but kiana
takanashi was motivated
i am motivated
and i continued for a little while
longer on
um a bicycle machine
bicycle machine um i don't know what
that means
uh it says distance 2.76 but that it
must be more than 2.76 meters because i
was on there for
six seven eight minutes
uh
so i'm not sure what yeah my my my uh
bpm went up to 167 which is higher than
i ever was in horror games oh that is
kilometers okay well then there you go
that makes sense
yeah yeah kilometers
so you know get a little get a little
leg work done as well i went there only
for my arms but uh
we i i continued to do something for my
legs as well just in case we don't want
to be um buff only at the top of my body
now i know i know this is a difficult
time for kfb
um something that you would have never
expected from takanawa and a very
shocking you may not know how to handle
this and and i
i
i recommend you talking with your
friends and your family members the ones
who are close to you
um to discuss this matter and go for
your feelings
deeply um i know it's important in a
time like this to um
to admit that you have emotions and it's
not a bad thing you know and and you
have to accept the reality it is what it
is
sometimes
things that are unexpected happen but
you got to make the best out of it and
don't just look the other way and then
say this is not real this can't be real
this is all fake news no don't do that
it's
it is it is the reality and you have to
accept it but the question is we have
questions
will she become fictional is this the
fit joe arc
could this possibly
the start of a new arc i think it could
be
however there's also a big risk of a
heart attack and a re-debut
er takanashikiyada could at the very
spot die and then revive
um but that's okay i guess because you
know i'm a phoenix
so but it would be funny it would be
funny uh will she be able to carry her
groceries again for a while the
paparazzis have been uh seeing uh
takadasiada carrying her groceries with
a trolley on wheels
and uh she has been made fun of on the
internet by social media and intel web
web citizens
uh that she cannot carry her own
groceries not even one bag
and has been made fun of and uh called
uh grandma
um
it seems that that was part of her
motivation to start it
yes will she need new clothes will i get
so buff that i cannot fit into my
clothes anymore for some reason
gets too ripped this could
probably happen
will she pull through now this is an
important question
to be honest uh takanasika's reason
behind all of this was
uh mostly not to get fit but uh to fix
her back and strengthen her shoulders
and her back
therefore
the running machine and the rowing
machine will be in the focus it seems um
yes now
um don't get your hopes up uh she will
probably not be at the gym every day but
we have to start somewhere and uh it is
a miracle in itself that we have seen
her today you know in a gym to begin
with
also i keep on switching between third
person and first person don't worry
about it
i'm not
going crazy no
it's just when somebody has to report
about me and then it's it's gonna be me
but the last question is of course will
she beat up kfb
and will they enjoy it yes they will
that is a clear answer but will she be
able to beat up kfb or will it just be a
slight tickle for them um we're looking
forward to the results in the near
future until then thank you everybody um
for your support and um please don't
believe the news outlets with their
stupid news and uh rumors
yes only only listen to the one source
that matters and that is takanawa yours
truly potential thank you everybody have
a good night and in german we say auf
wiedersehen bye-bye
schedule coming tomorrow it's probably
going to be a day off on monday so yep
bye-bye
[Music]
thank you
do
[Music]
you