[Music]
um
do
[Music]
i'm saying we're still looking at the
other one
oh
hahaha
[Music]
take it again
welcome back
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
i was totally a bug
woohoo
[Music]
wait
it's funny how you see a monkey and then
the love sounds like a monkey too
interesting
i shall
uh
okay okay okay okay
ah
hello
kitty kitty kitty
kitty kitty
welcome back
yeah
okay
how's it going
merry christmas
i didn't drop the mic even though i
wanted to
okay
we shall start already
i guess
hope you like that on archive part i
might re-broska re-broadcast it at some
point if it wasn't too terrible
uh i might i might re-broadcast it
okay and we start off
with
i have some christmas carols and some
japanese songs so christmas carols will
be like english and one might be german
and the japanese songs will be there as
well
[Music]
so
you might know this one
let's go
on the first day of christmas my true
love gave to me a partridge in the pear
tree
on the second day of christmas my true
love gave to me
two turtle doves
on the third day of christmas my true
love gave to me
three friends hands two turtle doves and
a pine tree and a pear tree
on the fourth day of christmas my true
love gave to me
four mockingbirds three friendships two
turtle doves and a partridge and a pear
tree
on the fifth day of christmas my true
love gave to me
five onion rings
five mockingbirds three french heads two
turtle doves and a five drinks in a pear
tree
on the sixth day of christmas my true
love gave to me
six gigs and laying five on your rings
four mockingbirds three french hens two
turtle doves and a partridge in a pear
tree
on the seventh day of christmas my true
love gave to me
savage one two swimming
pixies
[Music]
four mockingbirds three french heads two
turtle doves and the portraits in a pear
tree
on the eighth day of christmas marching
wolf gave to me
eggmates and milking seven swans of
[Music]
day of christmas my true love gave to me
nine ladies dancing egg meals and making
seven swans
[Music]
three friends heads two turtle doves and
the partridge in the pear tree
on the tenth day of christmas my true
love gave to me
ten lords believing nine ladies dancing
eight makes some milking seven swans and
swimming six kids are laying five onion
rings
four mockingbirds three french heads two
turtle doves
[Music]
on the eleventh day of christmas my true
love gave to me
eleven poppers piping ten notes slipping
nine ladies dancing eggmates so making
sevens one two
[Music]
day of christmas my true love gave to me
twelve drummers
[Music]
is
yeah that's right that's right yep
so many presents
welcome welcome everybody that was the
first song
that was fun that was a different
version than the one that we sang on the
whole live english channel if you
haven't watched it
there is a version of all the live
english girls singing this song on our
channel on a little official live
english channel about
this
my voice already is a little bit in pain
but we're gonna make it brutus hello
from russia hello spacey bath for
watching thank you
five onion rings yay actually i'm not
the biggest fan of onion rings if i
could
choose i would whoa i would use
something oh my god where am i what the
hell it's like um
i'm not even
i'm not even controlling myself
oh sorry
some demons took over my body oh my god
demons
help
i don't know how
how did that happen i i went up to the
tree to the top of the tree
interesting
interesting i'm back down now oh good
i'm safe
i can control myself again kiana is
under control
okay yes
okay calm down we'll sing we'll sing a
song that i sang last christmas
um
from an idol group called kyota
die lonely christmaser
[Music]
foreign
m
[Music]
almost knocked over my glass of water
yay
[Applause]
[Music]
i
[Applause]
[Music]
i
[Applause]
[Music]
that was a hello branded idol song hope
you liked that one i know you guys don't
really know all these songs that i
always sing and these idol songs the
hell practice songs but i hope you're
still guys so enjoy them uh you know
soak up some of that culture
whoa what's that wow
what did i do
you guys seem a little bit dead are you
guys here where is everybody
let me see your comments
where are you
no
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you thank you for coming here
everybody it's christmas yeah
woohoo
christmas
hmm
ah i was trying to remember a little bit
of the choreography to that dance just
now because i used to oh wait look here
i used to know it actually
but i was like how did how did they do
it again i kind of forgot
oh sorry sorry oh my my santa belt
needs to be adjusted okay
i look kind of weird
i'm sitting for the this whole thing by
the way
i'm sitting here
it looks like i'm standing but in
reality i'm sitting so
uh
so that i can have a comfortable karaoke
session love you guys little kiana like
a concert yeah
oopsie oh my oh my god where am i
sorry
okay
i always wanted to do this kind of
wealthy concert and now that i know how
it works we're gonna do this more often
by the way
i promise you maybe we can even do it
members only oh
anyway
uh next up is a
a vocaloid song
from
one of my favorite vocaloids producers
one of my top three favorite local
producers
is
[Music]
okay
this one is a little bit energetic
or quite energetic
from michi m sun
[Music]
at least in my ears
foreign
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen
is
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
hey
yeah that's such a fun cute song i
remember this song i think
[Music]
i think released a song cover of this
when she
uh debuted right do you guys remember
that
um
ah
it's such a cute song i love michi's
song so much they're so fun
[Music]
the demon took control of me again
okay
everybody
ah what's my next song on my list
[Music]
i'm not sure which one should i sing
next out of these
what
hello demon don't say hello to the demon
and we'll think that it's like you know
welcome or something we don't we
shouldn't let the demon think that way
hmm
[Laughter]
okay
do you guys want to hear
[Music]
an english carol or more japanese i mean
i only have
it's mostly japanese stuff that i have
for you guys today so we gotta balance
it out
i have so much though i have like super
old songs too
[Music]
okay let me let me sing the next um
uh one more hello brother song get that
out of the way
[Music]
this is a really fun old idol song not
as old as like plastic love or whatever
but
still pretty old and i think i also sang
this one last christmas
[Music]
was like a sub unit from a big idol
group called morning museum
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
he
[Music]
oh
hey
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
hey
you know i had some troubles writing in
the lyrics because i have the screen
like
so weirdly far away from myself and it's
really hard to grab
come back yes no not the microphone no
you go wet you can go here for now let
me just grab
wait
let me try to adjust it manually
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay that's better that's better
once i have this thing like i think it's
of every headset with every vr headset
but it's really uh kind of blurry
if you don't have it in the perfect
position but the perfect position is
like impossible to find oh thank you
thank you
okay
next song
let's sing an oldie from the lady who
said
plastic love i wonder if you guys heard
this one she has a christmas song did
you guys know
how
holiday
[Music]
you
me
[Music]
my
i'm sorry microphone
[Music]
hmm
day
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
happy happy holidays happy happy
holidays
happy happy holidays
happy happy holidays happy happy
holidays
that was an oldie oh
i was taking that holy day wonderful
holiday from mariah
[Music]
ah are you guys having happy holidays
i hope so
i hope i hope you are having a happy
holiday
oh i'm having some trouble breathing at
this point but
we'll be fine
we'll be fine maybe
maybe we'll get better maybe we'll get
in christmas songs thanks to me well
that's great actually for the um a lot
of the christmas carols are like not
really carols but like stuff like
the uh um like jingle bell rock and
beginning to look a lot at christmas and
all that that i sang in the unlike
portion
i mean i've heard those before but i
never really properly uh like listened
to them until now and try to learn how
how to sing it so i'm getting more
cultured as well
okay next up i have a super sound song
which is also not exactly christmas
themed but
i thought the theme of like stars
on the night sky
really distantly could be considered
a christmas song or at least like maybe
a winter song it's looking okay
dog
[Laughter]
okay
let's sing this
i hope the audio is not too loud
[Music]
belief
believe
there's magic internet
belief
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
me
m
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
okay i nailed that one
let's go
supercell songs always so much
fun
online
[Music]
i just love supercell so much and my
papa my artist is also kind of involved
with supercell and used to be kind of
involved with supercell so that's also
kind of a connection that i feel yeah i
don't know i kind of felt like the vibe
of the song maybe suits a christmas uh
stream as well christmas card orchestra
because i had a few troubles to find
um
christmas themed songs that i could sing
in an archive stream besides all the
famous christmas carols of course that
are a public domain but besides those i
really had trouble finding songs
um i had to learn
uh three new songs one of them was the
takayochi mania song
and another one that i learned for this
purpose i will sing for you guys now and
i think
i think the
that this song every japanese person
knows
it's um from yamashita
a japanese song you guys know yamashita
famous famous didn't he sing right on
time
i think
yeah
uh he has a christmas song
yes yes
so let's see have you guys heard it
before i wonder
and
if not then i will culture you guys once
again
okay please enjoy
christmas eve
is the song title kurisumasa ibu de
gozaima so so so
hmm
[Music]
you guys hearing me sometimes when i
move the microphone in the wrong way
then uh it makes weird noises this is
okay is this okay this is okay you guys
hear me so much
it might have been a little bit too loud
as well maybe tiny bit
oh this is okay
yeah yeah
okay you hear me okay
[Music]
i'm here now
silent night
[Music]
silence nine
oh
yeah
holy night
[Applause]
coco
he met
[Music]
is
holy night
[Music]
silent night
da
[Applause]
[Music]
um
holy night
[Music]
silence
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh a little bit too low so i started
singing higher at some point
but you guys should listen to the
original it's really nice it's really
pretty
um
[Music]
pretty tough man
let's sing a let's sing a higher song
i learned this one as well
the only
good anime christmas song that i could
find that uh i could sing in an archive
stream and then i have an instrumental
floor and all that so let's have a go
myself
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
my
foreign hey
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
please
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
hey hey
i was from la bourdai blue snow halley
sean
really pretty song really pretty but uh
i just learned it
uh
today so
i had some mistakes
okay baby
okay dokie
sorry two more songs left
okay
where was that one
wish you a merry christmas we wish you a
merry christmas we wish you a merry
christmas and a happy new year
wish you a merry christmas we wish you a
merry christmas we wish you a merry
christmas
what are you laughing about
lighting are
good tidings for christmas and a happy
new year now bring us a friend figgy
pudding bring us a figgy pudding now
bring it
and bring
[Music]
and a happy new year we wish you a merry
christmas
[Music]
merry christmas and a happy new year we
wish you merry christmas
[Music]
yes
yes that was a
such a banger that was one of the songs
some
one of the last two songs
what even is fakie pudding i don't
understand it's like like a just a
pudding like like a gel jelly pudding
oh man oh man
i mean i can try to add one more him and
there should be uh
here what about this one
this this is public domain two
let's sing it together with this lady
german baby
does this exist in english
[Music]
is
music
[Music]
we
have fought
[Music]
is
this
[Music]
oh
that was nice to sing
that was nice
yay i was
wait so i didn't get the reaction there
is that there's an english version but
this is the original is german is is
that how it is
is that's how it is perhaps
yes
oh christmas oh christmas tree o
christmas tree
how beautiful your leaves are even
though you don't have leaves but that's
how the lyrics are probably
i see
okay actually the next song is the last
one i added one for you guys is an extra
but the next one
is
the last one
yes
please enjoy another german one
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
yes
is
[Music]
that was a short one that was pretty
short whoa whoa wow my body
i
uh unless i find one more randomly that
i know i can sing
might be the end here oh no oh my gosh
let me see
[Music]
about this oh i want to see i didn't
sing jingle bells yet
jazzy version or slow version
let's draw jazzy
we love us some jazz
improvising though i don't know how this
thing is
everyone knows how to sing is right
jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the
way
oh what fun it is
[Music]
about that anyway where's jasmine about
that lies
hey jingle bells jingle bells jingle all
the way
oh what fun it is to ride
[Music]
in a one-horse
making spirits bright what fun it is
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
oh
exhausting this headset is so heavy can
i oh my god this one's the ankle or no
long quest
what a trackable song
what a turtle song
[Music]
okay that's it guys that's it that's uh
no more no more thank you very much
[Music]
important
has
[Music]
because i know
everybody for watching today's stream uh
for watching the archived entire
nightcast portion if you missed another
type one i will maybe do a re-broadcast
we'll be there all right
bro
um um what time is it
okay uh
i might do a superchat reading but after
taking a little break and and and taking
a different stream for this
super chat reading and in a few hours or
or or if not then not but let me just
take a little break
[Music]
oh thank you
thank you very much for listening thank
you emma for making this possible by
helping me and of course um all the
modelers yeah thank you i'm really i'm
really happy that i i got this
opportunity to use this cool stuff here
i i could have like you know showing you
guys around some more maybe next time
have a look
[Music]
hope you had fun
merry christmas
[Music]
[Applause]
thing
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
thank you
my
[Laughter]
huh
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you