[Music]
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing so
emot baby
[Music]
me
feel it rush through me
[Music]
feel
it feel it me
[Music]
oh honey
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
it's
hot not not hot stuffy
uh stuffy the air is stuffy do you say
that I think you
do uh K
KY wait
chat stuffy so
stuffy oh my God you guys are still
[\h__\h] up what's wrong with
you
huh what there one too what's wrong with
you you H what's wrong with you I can
literally not fix
you I can't fix you so
[Laughter]
sad you're a mess I'm a mess mess mess
mess mess mess mess I'm a mess in the
dress but we're still the best dress
feel I say yes we don't dress to
impress such a Fire Lyric well I guess
you'll stay like that cuz you're
unfixable you're just that problematic
guys happy early anniversary
oh let me
look debute
date you like how I said that huh okay
yeah okay in Japan it's already the 12th
so in Japan I'm
already it's already my anniversary
apparently
debute you like that huh
debute chuny monkey oh yeah oh she's
jumping into a box oh she she jumped
into a
box oh sorry for the delay but here we
are
finally playing a game from home
again from the comfortableness of my
home yay
anniversary
ah although like when it says debut date
September 12th
2020 was that was that 12th in jst or
12th
[Music]
in like American time I'm not sure
you want sh Kean whoa whoa whoa let's
go pro
prob what time was my stream
like what time was it I don't remember
that anymore what time my debut stream
was evening
maybe cuz we had a that's that stupid
relay de relay for the night
so
yeah okay yeah that
actually then it might have been 12 for
both time zones I'm not I'm not
sure yeah early morning
right all day myth debuts
exactly I was so
delirious at the end of it at the end of
the relay
I was so
delirious well well well I am a little
bit delirious right now too I think
um uh but I should be okay I'm okay I'm
okay I have
some
um glasses that can be filled with
liquids 1 pm
GMT I see oh yeah Fall Guys yeah mhm Was
A wise choice of
mine glasses of liquid and I have uh I
have
chocolate European chocolate oh how I
missed you
dearly and I had one smaller smaller
small
sandwich before the Stream
and then um I told
some [\h__\h] trespassers to [\h__\h]
off I don't
know if I
should next time maybe I'll call the
police or
YouTube e
um
yeah not not like
the shotgun not like inside of my fence
area but behind it but still like
private
ground um sometimes there's like people
there and I was like just watering my
lawn and I see those like
dudes uh a group of
like H Maybe
20 28 something looking guys 25 I don't
know um tall
dudes uh sitting there and I'm
like just looking away not trying to
make any eye contact because I just
don't 20 people no no no no no that'd be
crazy but it was like five six people or
so I just like looking away
hoping not to make I like I I
intimidating
right and then they while I'm watering
my lawn they decide to get up and leave
interesting very welcome that you would
leave I welcome that decision but when
they're W when they're uh leaving
they're walking P like past me kind of
and I'm still decisively looking away
but they
are they're
like they're they're saying something
that I'm not quiet picking up like what
what the [\h__\h] did you just
say I don't know they're probably just
making stupid comments but I didn't
quite hear it well so I continued to
look away but then they said something
again and then then I then I look
up and I see like one of the guys is
just giving me the
the most
M
obnoxious stupid like kind of like
condescending kind of
grin and like he already passed me but
he's still like grinning so proudly or
whatever like kind of looking behind
still staring at me this whole time and
I'm and then I'm like was sh in the most
Austrian
way was shouts to them which is so brave
of me cuz like bro they all like way
taller than me and I'm like basically
yeah I I basically said the [\h__\h] are you
looking at but I don't I'm scared while
I'm saying that but I'm trying to trying
to se dominance what the [\h__\h] are you
looking at and then um they're like kind
of Bas like they're old just like mostly
it's just this one guy Who's acting up I
think
up and he's like what so what and and
then I'm like this is private ground you
understand they're like so what and I'm
like it's it's [\h__\h] private ground
yeah while all of this while they're
walking away well sh so dead
but well this happens sometimes but I I
never say anything but they like leave
so much trash and it pisses me off
yeah yeah what part do you not
understand yeah I don't know next time
maybe I'll call
polia and
there they like there's like different
groups uh I think every now and then but
like some some times in the past before
I put up my security camera some some
people were like um messing with my
fence several times and uh I thought I
was like going
crazy cuz I I never saw it happening but
I always saw the result of it like a
broken part of my
fence so that's why I got the security
camera and then it stopped hm want
coincidence
H yeah just just some of the
things my security camera is such a
smart choice because I can also watch my
cats that's the real reason why I got my
security camera so I can watch my
cats by the way don't clip this please
uh if there's any body who was thinking
oh I'm going to clip this this is
interesting let's not clip this thank
you appreciate
it now we shall
commence
uhop no clips knife
[Music]
out
uh no normally when I say don't clip it
I I I think
usually it meets an open ear that's
surely not how you say it but I shall
say it like
that um why is this not working fine I
will I will play for OBS
then wait I was trying to I was trying
to figure out if this sounds I'm hearing
are coming out of my mouth clicky sounds
or if I'm really just very slightly at a
very low volume hearing it but
[Music]
no
um um
here what
[Music]
huh I mean I know you probably hear
it but I
don't open game what do you mean it's
what I'm I'm I'm supposed to hear clicky
click
task
manager [\h__\h] Elgato game
capture [\h__\h] Elgato game capture so
annoying open
up oh
oh I hear it sound has returned to my
earist
ears I am blessed with the ability to
hear once
again click click this time it's not my
mouth like legit it could have been like
it was like
kistering click a little bit like very
faintly inside of my mouth when I open
it like uh you know like when you when
you have one of those like candies that
go
like inside of your
mouth popping popping off in your mouth
crackling yes yeah a natural version of
that was uh
happening H okay
guys we're getting back into it I don't
know how long I can
play but
hopefully at least hopefully we can at
least finish
[Music]
one who hopefully we can finish at least
one that would be good one Mansion
yeah ah so loud
is this too loud for you
guys what why are you asking
me is this 10 hours of Play Time a bit
all right no good good sounds
good okay
[Music]
tiny oh tiny adjustment
there we
go I am
stalling cuz I am
afraid of my deadlines of which I have
cleared a few today before my stream but
there is still one more that
is in my way I'm
scared but me stalling in my gameplay
will not make me be able to get any
earlier to my
deadlines whoa
whoa is perhaps
my
no all right we to Luigi yes it is I
Luigi I am green and therefore I am
Luigi you have perceived that correctly
why am I talking like this again it's
like a [\h__\h]
virus like a [\h__\h]
virus the dark moon has shot up Yi y I
don't know we we still have to do a toad
Mission yeah wait did I okay Peace at
Last
typo we have both clock hands now so all
that's left is to finish them uh find
the sorry my my my camera is covering a
little bit of the screen I don't know
shut
up let's just
go a pixelator
camera hack into it who knows maybe
you'll even catch the ghost S guard
uhhuh uhhuh did he say something
important picture of the rotor okay I
will find it if that is what you
desire
ska now probably not okay
no so what does he want the pixelator or
the
rotor or
both what the hell is wrong with
you why why you look like
[Music]
that why does this ghost look like
that I sound unmotivated to stream
what what no I sound like I always do
it's just normal
me texture shaming the ghost I'm just
like a little little bit like like I
don't know what's going on right now my
I don't know who I
am what wrong button or what what or is
it just it just doesn't work hey I found
the thing is this not kind of looks like
the
rotor but of course it is not
what about
this I'm scared guys what if there's
ghost I just realized that's the kind of
game we're
playing oh how
funny wait I'm going to get it I'm going
to get it
eh why can't I not get
it obviously this is telling me there's
a mirror go eh go get
it I can't maybe later oh yeah right so
how do we do this
again
H for later all
right it's been so long I don't remember
anything it's safe to no ah I knew it
oh wait maybe it's
[Music]
good if you guys are if you guys behave
well I may or may not share some
tangents with you
today but you're already Behaving Badly
because look at
you look at you
you just don't look right today and you
are refusing to fix
it and uh you doing that as a group like
not a single one of you appears
correctly and so I see that as um a
group effort to be
evil
yeah quite insulting
[Music]
what are you
doing you guys are
funny hey hey okay I will admit what I
was doing is not really like you know
even ghosts even ghosts deserve some
privacy Yello let look at my d
crimey we need to get you inside that
storage room oh why didn't I think of
this earlier I hired a toad assistants
to look after the Old Clockworks he may
be able to help you give me a second to
locate him apparently he went to check
on malfunction in the what foration
[Music]
room can't [\h__\h] read well it still
can't read why is it why why is it like
this
this what can't I can't
read just can't read
guys no I'm not even looking at
OBS that's not the problem it's just the
position
of my
camera kind of overlapping with my
[Music]
screen you can be good huh H well you
can but why are you refusing
to
mhm well well well I'll think about it
I'll think about it if you write me a
free page essay
everybody on your bad behavior why you
are sorry and how you are trying your
best to fix
[Music]
it
MH font size
small no double space don't [\h__\h] around
I'm going to get
[Music]
angry it's too
funny he's saying that means get on
it get on with it
espanol I don't speak Espanol it has to
be in English or German or
o or in Japanese I will
accept am I going the right
way is there something there
sorry I'm
confused at least I got one so so sorry
sorry I forgot how to do
things uh this one this one this would
have been it maybe that would have
worked sorry
sorry what is
this why is this moving what that's
freaky
I speak fluent Indonesian you may you
may use that language as
well is this what
I'm money it's
raining is this where I'm supposed to
go what's
up
[Music]
M oh what oh I knew I was going to hang
on to
that okay do I H I guess just for
returning wow I remembered how to
reverse
vacuum oh so maybe just maybe what I
just did wait what is what is this path
there's nothing here but
wait yeah
I knew it I knew it wait why is it oh
well I I'll fix that I'll fix it in
post
submit uh well y'all can submit it on
Twitter uh you can like write it on a
doc and then give me the link on
[Music]
Twitter
uh
hello wait that was the same same button
no bullies there's bullies over
there we have to stop
[Music]
them I have to suck him up was there a
way to destroy this I don't remember I
don't think
so can you destroy boxes like
that he yo what uh uh these are bombs
are they
not how does this work
again I this
work oh wait I'm supposed probably to to
shoot it at something but what
I flash him to set him off
okay
[Music]
no the money one I shouldn't have
screwed around with the money one
no oh yeah well I respond but it the
other thing
doesn't I'll forever be broke man man
but what are they for is there there
must be a like some some some some
points to
[Music]
this God damn it I'm so unlucky with
like the money things in this
game
interesting we wouldn't we want this to
go the other way ideally
maybe if I
re-enter the
room
[Music]
uh if I reenter the rim they will
probably respawn but probably not the
golden one
right let's see
it's okay Luigi it's okay yeah I found
out
oh oh no what only one is
there what do you mean only one is left
maybe I have to use them all up before
they
respawn I don't even know how
to I don't I even know how
to make use of them properly
yet let's
[Music]
investigate well that will not bring
back my Golden
Ball no [\h__\h] off
that will not bring back my Golden
Ball
ah
what oh wonderful delightful what a
delightful
chime a delightful little
jingle ah
ah no no no no why does the money fall
down this angle is very
confusing oh wait that one looks like
it's it's cashed
in
anyway where do we go from here kfp
hm would you like to help
me would you like to give me an
idea I swear to God why why do you do
that when I'm already
gone bro
it's still
there
[\h__\h] wait I can't go up here I didn't
see this at
all you're busy writing the paper good
good focus focus on that oh stupid
little [\h__\h] stupid little
[\h__\h] did I get money I don't think I did
life's not
fair okay let's shut him the [\h__\h]
up
ah you are big [\h__\h]
rude suck him
up oh yeah
finally no more of
that whatever he was saying oh they
threw me a
[Music]
bone is this your guys' essay oh oopsie
I sucked it up too bad I guess you guys
have to ride another one oh no oh all of
your essays are gone what are we going
to do you'll just have to ride it again
oh these these two oh no I accidentally
sucked it up
guys and this may just be your payment
but oh no I'm sucking that one up
too too bad guys oh wait your essays are
back oh oh oh oh uncontrollably sucking
it up I don't know what's happening guys
I'm sorry
sorry your your essays are just lost
forever just have to accept
it frog Ate My
Homework you know the froggy lava cape
on my head it's making me do things that
I normally would not do
I see
that oh hey more perhaps some more I
request some more donations no really
just free coins
all right
then wait let me go there thank
you where are we
going maybe we would like to stop here
for a
moment there's some
boxes moving on wasn't there a go ghost
there though how do I get to the GH
ah where did the ghost go did I already
capture
[Music]
him so what now maybe I should have used
this over
there
maybe maybe I missed something
[Music]
thank you
guys thank
you did I miss
something I suppos not
not yeah but I
don't I don't feel like I'm done with
this
room help me
[Music]
chat busy
about my
essay a fake wall that I can vacuum up
by the first
gear oh like down
here not down here
right which one's the
first this one
this
one go up the gears like I did before
okay
maybe fake wall maybe here
ah M mommy how did I not see
that ow you
[Music]
how dare
you no no finally I got the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
rat
oh oh he
yo does it have the
rotor a
[Music]
b wait how's again
ah I have you in my bedroom
boo oh wow this is
fun wait
no yay come with
me come back into my
bedroom oh poor poor little ghost it's
way more comfortable and safe in my
bedroom
yeah okay good is that all here I feel
like we're still like
not making real progress we're just
doing fun
things well I guess at least I didn't
miss the secret room cuz that seemed
very
optional I got a key I got a key oh
right you mean um true well I guess
that's true so we used it in a different
room huh I kind of
like lost the intuition for this
game I it feels like I need to like
continue through a door in this room but
I perhaps I
don't yeah I'm I'm warming
up by the way I I've been watching I've
started watching uh rings of
power finished the first episode which
was pretty long now getting into the
second
one it's been
good oh that's what the key is for it's
been good I think I mean I don't know
for me it's
good there's a lot of shiny Rings now
they just put on all the Rings like
three of them and I'm just thinking
shouldn't there be more I guess I didn't
make them all at
once they're really pretty though they
should sell them as
merchandise since Amazon loves money so
much why not sell them as merchandise H
what is this what is this
[Music]
huh
blind oh ow hey let me go
what
R and then it just acts like
everything's normal and that it's not
evil at all
[Music]
okay does it let go of course it
this oh wow okay good that I had my
vacuum
on oh Rocka we are so back aren't
we sending me those kind of messages
again I see I see
[Music]
yeah
um I don't know I feel like can we talk
about it um the big big uh guy the big
the big wizard guy who's like slowly
becoming more and more oh to I didn't
see you there can we just leave
uh the guy who who is with the the
almost
Hobbits the big guy Gand 2.0 yeah I
think that's just San
right
right it's probably just
San cuz he seems like he wants to be
evil no
[Music]
he's just
a okay well then I will continue to
watch it and figure it out eventually uh
wait wasn't there
ah ah I need to turn this so that I can
reach
him oh this fun oh there's one missing
the
rum oh well done bye toad
bye can't help you can't help you with
that one my
friend can I do something
here now this is for when I have toad I
suppose is
[Music]
there what why does it look like I could
pass through here but it won't let
[Music]
me damn it a
rainbow
light on what a on that oh but I
literally thought because
it aren we looking for one of those
though like we have to reclaim them how
isn't it logical that I would think oh I
have to actually go get it hello
hello I hate this so much
it was never
missing I mean it it definitely was
missing but maybe it was never like
stolen like I thought I had to take it
from a ghost I can just get it like
this I
[Music]
suppose well anyway even the season
preview looked really cool for
uh rings of power looked really cool
really exciting lots of things going to
happen like it looks pretty damn
eventful you're late for the wa
welcome yeah there was a ghost carrying
a wheel right thank you I'm not
[Music]
crazy Luigi dad Luigi
it's an honor to finally meet you sir
I'm a huge
fan the professor sent you to rescue me
I was sure he had forgotten about me uh
you're looking for a way to access the
storage room sure let's go take a look
but first there's something you should
know about me h i I have been IR
rational fear of
clocks I'm a voice Fierce clocks AKA
crony
I'm a
confirmed please don't laugh just keep
me away from any large boock or gears
okay man this place gives me the
creeps come on well honestly relatable I
fear clocks as
well so what now you squeaky shoes
you're going to help
it that is
terrifying oh no oh no uh oh
oh oo I got
[Music]
him
y wait why are they
unlimited there we go oh that was a good
one I got him at
once yeah I didn't just get two I think
for the first time ever I managed to get
the vacuum into the red might have been
the first time hello toad toad toad get
your [\h__\h] together if I'm going into a
different room you should just teleport
there I hate
you
stay U maybe maybe I shoot you how about
I shoot you is that how they want me to
do it
oh y Oh I thought you were going to
break the wall guess you're not wait
wait he's waving he's
waving he's
screaming oh oh oh no oh
no should we just let him
be he too
funny oh no oh
no I forgot how to dodge was it just be
oh yeah it is
okay this is fun so far let him be and
he becomes fit he's he's decently Fit
already
no look he is
fine not fine like fine look he's
fine hey where you what does that scare
you that's not like
clock it's it's eh it's not a clock well
I guess it's a gear well let me suck you
up no choice now buddy no choice where
are we going
though can I drop you down there oh we
can go together I stop
being I did not see that coming at
all as if if he knew that would bring
him back
up your
essays let him cry let him cry it
out amazing is there something down here
more essays why are they down here
guys why' you put them there
it's hard
to it's hard to understand you guys
really what are you even thinking hey yo
Lin
[\h__\h] I hate you so
much
[Music]
ra let's go
Jewels ikim
show speaking of iima show
quasi quite likes the idea that I spoke
about yesterday in my members only
stream never
mind
so you
know it could become
reality I knew it I knew it would be
some
something she would find fun can you get
out of my
vacuum why not why don't you want to
follow me in there the massive gears
would crush me into much how do you know
that there's massive gears there there's
gears
everywhere you [\h__\h] idiot hey
to to the gears are literally everywhere
what's the point of running from one
gear when there's others elsewhere what
do you want me to do
toad ah wait this what about you
then to toad toad toad toad
toad can you ride the thing too
I have to shoot him across oh okay okay
okay
okay all right come
here I love
him don't fall
down a good
stay how dare you scar
me genuinely terrified St scream
y not the safest place to battle
ghosts hello
no ah okay got KN night can't be helped
guys I can't suck him up in a nice
way
[\h__\h] but he lost his armor okay
wonderful yippe I did it aren't you so
proud of me toad am I not just so cool I
no he's a huge fan you guys should be
too
come
here how do we I guess you just follow
me oopsie I forgot I forgot that you
capable of walking because sometimes you
act like you're certainly not capable of
it wait get out of my vacuum
who
programmed this 0.5 brain
cell of an excuse for a
toad who who programmed any of the toads
in this game they are just so useless
and helpless and just the stupidest AI
that I have ever ever come
across why can you not step two steps to
towards where I am if you're just
generally inclined to
fall see I was still
so
positively delighted about your presence
toad why why did you ruin
it [\h__\h] hell why' you ruin it stop
stop
running this
sucks oh my God it [\h__\h] sucks
stay I hate this this ridiculous this is
so
ridiculous oh my
God oh my God I hate you please follow
me I don't remember like being so like
shocked about Toad's
stupidity in Luigi's Mansion
free I don't think that was like
this certainly not
come
[Music]
on oh there's hearts up
there they look like
candies
nice it wasn't like this
[Music]
right why does he that shut the [\h__\h] up
to I need your
[Music]
hair go go go
go I hate
him
M and you can't even open doors when you
have him like this don't you dare run
away don't you dare run away no how do
I okay go go go go go go no what do you
mean he's right
[Music]
there let's let's just [\h__\h] end it
ghosty
Chan let's just [\h__\h] end
it I'm sick and tired of everybody's
janig
[Music]
again what is the pink one doing
what is the hot pink one
doing ah ah ah you're not going to
endlessly send out more unless I do
something right
[Music]
did I fight these before cuz I don't
remember how to do
[Music]
it ah there we
go a really particular moment
[Music]
threatening music Turn Turn the right
way
Luigi I found Luigi related like Foods
by the way in the convenience
store many Luigi Foods he's so popular
in Japan
why does he have a Red Orb around him he
like I'm going to
die wait one is red one is green does
this like is this
math oh H H what I've never had this
before ow I'm going to
die quick chat tell me what the [\h__\h] is
this about
CH what you mean I need to charge like
until I need to suck
more ow but I'm going to
[Music]
die oh it's green it was yeah okay okay
I see it I see I
see it's kind of difficult oh wait now I
don't have to wait anymore
okay okay but this one to Red oh my
God don't know if I can do
[Music]
that oh
no I had to
dodge
no I should get both of them
wait can I get both of
them
no come on they were right next to each
other oh he missed ah
Hallelujah he dropped the
heart come
on red red red red
[Music]
okay please please no what zombies
now I'm not going to make
[Music]
it wait do I shoot them we're told I
forgot how to deal with them it's not
just sucking the toilet paper
hello do I shoot them with the oh stop
[Music]
running that's it that's so
over wake me up can't wiggle Wake Me Up
Inside date them with a flash flash what
I thought maybe they wouldn't be able to
be flashed because they're covered
up okay we get it we get
it
no one more annoying pieces of
[\h__\h]
oh ah what is
[Music]
happening what what's happening
I what he fell
down okay that's funny thanks [\h__\h]
just suck him up just suck him
up
oh oh
no this is so
chaotic [\h__\h]
off I know I'm bad at this but at the
same time it's like oh he's letting me
uh
really he's like damn girl you're
wasting so much time this is taking so
long let's just here I I I give you a
chance to get me early before you get
rid of the mini mobs oh he's holding
toad have fun with that fall down
here bunk bnk bunk yourself y he wants
me I wait maybe can I not make him fall
down
anymore why
not ah no he produced more ah the green
[Music]
thing fall
down lose
it yeah I'm trying to get him to
something but m
okay here how about how about
that now we actually dropped but I'm
busy I'm
busy
[Music]
bro okay I should have just tried harder
here we go hot pink one is no more
yeah yellow
hello well done lu you really taught the
ghost lesson he look different than
other ghosts I wonder why yeah I'm
wondering too let's hope he didn't hide
that rotor too well what do you mean I
already got the rotor what a different
one I hate you
you're just getting me in trouble you're
just making me a Target for more
Shenanigans
toad this looks suspiciously like a
[Music]
path I knew
it okay
we should just eat toad
guys should eat
him what what happened
toad how'd you get
there come
on what is he
doing someone explain this to me heyo oh
it's a secret level here uh-oh uh right
or left right or left
[Music]
left [\h__\h] what what oh no that was hard
to
[Music]
understand
bro bro
oh my God I would have been so mad I
would have been so mad oh you
it bless you oh my
God and would I have gotten a second
chance if I didn't get
it I always I always do this feeling
like I
won't I don't think you get a second
chance do
you maybe if you like reload the
level okay these are always fun but I
feel like I'm I'm
missing some here and
there that's sad anyway if that
was that then how do we
get out of here
again
ah we walk
amazing what a
concept that's where we peaked
through can we go
up how do we do this
toad be useful tell me something I don't
know oh wait I sent you up there don't
die
what oh
no
huh I saw it I saw it for a
second sh oh I have to be
closer I thought if anything I'd have to
step
back wait how do
[Music]
I how do I get on the other one or do I
get on yours toad I don't understand
anymore
wait
what wait told them up
there oh wait this stays down
[Music]
now come on
hey mama
[Music]
mia huh are you going to be useful for
once
get
[Music]
it
m yeah okay you did not deserve that
high
five I can't believe I touch a
clock be such a
[\h__\h] service
elevator can't wait to get out of here I
can't wait to get you out of here too
I really hope it for for my sake for my
sanity sake why are we starting out with
a toad mission is not good for my brain
my brain cells are being burnt actively
as we
speak to don't pick up my
money you greedy little
[Music]
bastard of [\h__\h] come up come up don't
cry now don't you cry now I ain't got
time for
this post to
stress told better have my
money hey me watch you
[Music]
don't act like you forgot I call the
sh mirror mirror on the
wall Co will fly very
tall that's right
toad oh you thought I was going to catch
you hell no
hell
[Music]
no okay uh do we do something with this
camera by the way no we just go look for
the elevator wait no the the thing is
here
uh wonderful here you go oh bye bye
bye-bye
byebye bye bye
we're
free we're
free honestly could have been worse
could have taken
longer I feel like speed wise this
wasn't the
[Music]
worst
did I don't care what this thing is
going to tell me I think I did
well considering during the
circumstances of dealing with a
toad bronze bronze is nice okay bronze
is fine bronze is
beautiful women go out of the way and
buy
bronzer for their makeup routine you
know Bron something nice I don't buy
gold I don't buy silver I buy bronzer
okay me personally I don't but women
do also like not anybody who likes
makeup bronze is in demand
yes stay straight from the bronze
[Music]
is that how you say it straight out of
the wait
wait
uh wait I have to answer the clock
woman um
[Music]
okay team ters Pam
Flanders ask her what time is
ha wait where did my there it
is net
Flanders all right sexy people let's go
this I get it I get it I get it I get
it I get it I get it next mission next
Mansion perhaps no probably not we still
got to probably do a
boss sneak goh you can't seems to be
more powerful than
others she has strange marks all over
his body
peculiar any just like the first toad
this toad couldn't tell me how he got
trapped in the in the what in the
painting oh in in the painting he only
remembers being chased by boss Boo and
then suddenly everything went black
however he was very happy he could help
he wouldn't stop writing about it
[Music]
helping me helping
me he's getting in my way
constantly the
audacity yeah he
carried I'd brag about helping legi to
yeah I mean honestly if you're such a
pitiful creature as a toad then
yeah patic
[Music]
no no no you keep it you'll need it for
the next
mission we're finally ready to open the
clock tower gate and climb up to the top
oh but first there's something we need
to
review this toad also had stap shot from
the tridimensional security camera with
him it was taken pretty recently too
hopefully it will give us some useful
information I'll go ahead and process
process it now let me know when you're
ready to look at
it what if I just I'm just not ready I'm
just going to
[Music]
that fish over there looks delicious
that's what I'm looking at that's what I
got my eyes
on it's cooking something
[Music]
good should I tell you guys a
tangent uh this is probably not the most
interesting tangent but wait I think I
have it written down let
me just find it even though I could
probably tell it without my
note but
[Music]
to I wonder is Kiana watching this
stream right now probably not
it would be funny if she
were I have I I have a Kiana tangent
that I
forgot my choreographer you know cuz I
was out with her and uh I'm it
remember I'm just going to stay
it we were out and about in New York
right and this was this the first
time I think that I met her yeah uh even
though we know each other for a long
time but this was the first time that I
met her and first of all it was kind of
like crazy how we kind of
accidentally we like twinsies like we
were twinning kind of which is so crazy
like we weren we weren't wearing the
same color of clothes or so but we were
kind of wearing the same type of clothes
like the same cut and the same
arrangement of like um
outfit and yeah that was cute as
hell and
then uh it was her birthday by the
way it was her birthday I don't think I
mentioned this did I previously but I
didn't realize this beforehand
so it just so happened that the day that
we went out was her birthday and
like Midway through our
date that came up and I'm like
it what oh no what I I feel like it I
mean it no I feel kind of bad like we
should have done something more focused
on you but then she was like no this is
special to me because I get to meet you
and I'm like oh
okay oh
man but we had a lovely day like you
know she's she's from New York but she
never visited the freedom lady before
for example so we did things that she
hasn't done before it's like a nice
outing I guess you know it's that's fun
and I think she still did something like
afterwards in the
evening um like celebrating her
birthday then yeah now there's one thing
that I noticed about her and I I wonder
I wonder what she will say about this I
wonder if she ever gets this
told um before um do
you remember ever seeing a person like
this in like TV shows before but because
I had to think about this kind of type
of character Trope or so when I was
talking to Kiana um imagine a like any
kind of sitcom or like a a um not an
anime uh what's what's the Western
equivalent of an anime again
a damn it a
for a cartoon yeah I feel like this
shows up in cartoons now but also normal
shows
so sometimes there's a character
which they will like portray in an
exaggerated way like they would speak
quietly but it would be portrayed so
exaggeratedly that you would not be able
to audibly hear anything they say and
then the characters around them just
always have trouble understanding them
you know what I
mean and that's
Keana I had like really hard troubles
hearing
her and like even when I asked her to
repeat something several times s she
would still speak so
quietly and it's just
um like even when our surroundings were
like more noisy she would also not
really raise her voice at all and I
would I would lean in I would leaning so
hard and and like frown my eyebrows so
obviously like struggling to hear
anything and she still speaks the same
like low frequency
you guys do that too some of
you ah man I
I I I feel so annoying asking someone to
repeat what they're saying several times
in a row right so I I I I will just I'm
sorry Kiana but sometimes I actually
after the second time or so if I still
didn't hear it and I was just nodding
and I'm like ha yeah uh I did not I
possibly did not understand what you
said in the end
I just didn't want to ask you
again
yeah but I had to think of those kind of
characters that are just like so quiet
that like they're literally just not
talking in those kind of
shows just a exaggerated version now I
wonder if anybody told her this before
no one can hear me half of the time and
it's so annoying really then there these
low talkers and then there's the kind of
people who are just always screaming
right I think I have a more loud voice
because I've
been like kind of trained to speak and
sing loudly for the sake of microphones
picking it up
better um but I do think I can control
myself quite well well like if I'm in a
quiet environment then I will not scream
as if I'm in a loud environment um but I
think I'm decently easy to understand
but but uh for example my mom is one of
those people who are really loud oh your
mother
too my mom is loud and then
like yeah I feel like everybody can hear
her when we're in a more quiet
surrounding uh like hear what she's
talking yapping about and sometimes I
tell her mom keep it more quiet but it's
a bit hard to say her to say it to her
my friend is a loud
talker why is you oh no you didn't
delete it my mom be loud for no
reason my mom too yeah is it something
with parents just being
loud generally I can relate with my
hispanic mom oh
my brother unconsciously speaks loudly
sometimes oh yeah yeah some people
really don't like no everybody like
usually loud talkers they don't realize
at all that they're loud but I think low
like low low volume talkers I think they
kind of know what they're doing they're
just like too shy or they just don't
have the like strength and power in
their voice to constantly speak up so I
think they don't really
do it on purpose they're aware but they
don't quite do it on purpose but loud
people they don't realize they have to
be reminded
constantly I think that's how I see
it very difficult to deal with on
Japanese exactly on Japanese trains you
really got to talk quietly otherwise
everybody's like hearing you and they're
like judging you why are they talking so
loudly
[Music]
L usually thinks they talk in normal
volume unless corrected
yeah this is how Amma described gaa's
talking when they first met really just
not long after a while oh really GAA for
me is
not hard to understand though that's
interesting GAA is not hard to
understand for
me she will kind of like speak more
reservedly but not in a way that I don't
understand Stander I don't remember
having trouble hearing
her but but yeah she kind of like speaks
speaks reservedly like like
[Music]
this oh yeah because what just talking
about myth members right now a little
bit
um uh since I mentioned it in members
only yesterday but I didn't mention it
publicly yet I don't know if you guys
saw but let me let me throw it in here
as a little
[Music]
note where is it let's get a
picture so I think some of you must have
already listened to it right
uh the myth voice pack part one did you
guys already listen to
it yeah you
did yeah it's pretty on on the longer
side and and
fun yeah the preview is also up on I
think the whole life English Channel
right um so myth just released a voice
pack that is not like single voice packs
of each of us no it's a group voice
pack and there's chapter one like part
one and part two and I feel like while
not
really uh
100% uh I feel like it's like especially
the first chapter has like hints that's
that feel like they're in connection
with enigmatic recollection low key
that's how I
felt right did you feel the same
way anyway the art is so
adorable it's called down of time the
Shadows I oh my God I'm so in love with
the art and especially oh my God my my
hair my hair is so lovely oh my God I'm
going to
die and you guys haven't seen it yet but
the the upcoming one has also some
gorgeous amazing art but this is
apparently kfp this is not how I imagine
kfp at all actually there's so many
sunflowers it's so
girly so kfp has been
redesigned why not why the hell
not but yeah it's like we're gathering
at kfp and we're talking
about like how we all met each other I
think that's what we were talking
about
lore yeah it's more like a m Cafe here
yeah our Back
stories yeah so it's it's it's trying to
get you into a a nice nostalgic sweet
feeling and this is like a warm up for
the second chapter so please get this
one there's a preview of it on the
YouTube channel an audio preview with a
nice little video and and then you can
probably get there through a link to buy
it if you want to it's it's in the
official shop as always and please
support our voice pack
[Music]
y Callie looks so
hot Callie looks so hot does she
not speaking of previews H what what
what what who whoa whoa who
what H what do you mean ah there was
also a preview of our new song myth's
new song posted on Twitter was it posted
anywhere else besides Twitter I wonder
and it starts with me so you can hear me
right
away do you want to hear it I I shall
play it here how about
that I don't know why we're having this
little break but you know breaks are
nice in between
yeah it's like Jazzy and lots of sick
instruments so this should probably work
one two three that
was lights begin
St C up the
keep in hand
one yeah yeah yeah yeah does it do you
like it does it sound good I feel like
it's a very unusual
sound yeah right
unexpected but I think it fits the the
theme of the life because like you you
already saw a preview of like some
assets right and it's giving it's giving
Broadway
wo Super Mario Odyssey
yeah I hope you all like it uh it's very
unusual but um the instruments in it I
think you can hear they're really Grand
right thank God they are like because
originally it wasn't it wasn't like a
life band who played it it was just like
like I don't know how to say computer
generated or whatever uh instruments and
it didn't sound as Grand but then uh we
asked like hey can we have like actual
people playing these instruments and
then they they did it and it became like
whoo a million times better an actual
band playing it like changed it up like
crazy especially when you hear the full
version I think you guys got to
appreciate the
instruments yeah the band went crazy ham
they went Ham on it
yeah I'm so glad they did that I'm so
glad it look it sounds really really
Broadway now really exciting
so
[Music]
continuing let's go ham as well shall we
to the boss we go
yeah big band big band that area is just
behind the clock tower gate oh am I
going there another possessor I wish I
could say I was
surprised he those ghost seem to be
headed to the top of the
tower okay so I try to go there too
remember how to inspect the scene you
can use those fancy motion controls oh I
don't remember
that zoom in and out press beam when
you're done oh I don't want to is this
oh
Mario
Mario is there supposed to be a hint
here hi that's so cute look at
[Music]
him
okay your voice of shun work you think
so work works
well I think I think think I don't know
did I do well I don't know I don't
remember I hope I did it's fun it's
definitely fun there's a lot of a lot of
singing it feels like a lot of
vocals lot of vocals lot of instruments
so I I I'm I'm sure you'll like
it almost like there's an evil presence
ordering the possessors to guard the
dark Mo ever shade Val
the moon I can find it forever but we
need to get to the top of the clock
tower let's
go here you go go go go go you think
this going to be your number one
really I think it's so
different from what you would normally
hear from any of us really so that's
going to be
interesting it's certainly won't be like
everybody's favorite but it's it's
something else it's Unique and the ones
who do like Jas and big band they're
going to love this they're going to eat
it
up
mhm that's why I'm
excited Broadway show myth let's
go haven't they been they've been using
like they've been using live bands right
for uh for Fest but
like just like I I've never seen the
band so I don't know how many
instruments they're actually using but
I'm guessing just like pretty so to say
basic lineup of like drums and stuff
imagine if they would play that but they
would need so many more like they got to
do a Justice with like an actual big
band like a million trumpets and
stuff that would be
crazy but just for one song getting out
all the trombone and trumpets no way
no way Orchestra right whole life in
Orchestra one day like one of those like
Final Fantasy or near ultimata or
whatever any any of those like game
Orchestra imagine that one day like with
whole
life like perhaps we're not even going
to show up it's just like one of those
Orchestra
tours where you go just to hear
soundtracks and the soundtracks would be
any of our original songs or perhaps
even waiting the
tracks performed by a [\h__\h]
[Music]
Orchestra Holo Orchestra would you guys
want to see that I think that's so fun
and like
different that'd be
sweet hell yeah hell
yeah
nice I will wear a formal dress yeah
everybody let's let's go
formally in in it would be beautiful in
the king's
theater
H I'm going to suggest
this I'm going to suggest this I don't
know who to suggest it
to but I want to suggest this to St and
I don't know if they'll think about it
but then it's probably something for the
Far Far Future
[Music]
that would be
amazing let's go Luigi let's go what are
you waiting
for heart heart container yeah I think
heart container fits
it cuz it already has the
trumpets o that's a me
ikim find and retrieve the Dark Moon
PE wait do
I put this in right
[Music]
away what time is it Luigi
this music is nice oh it ended okay it
is uh
midnight what's the
sound
what but so what
now do I have to set the time
but at first I'll have to find out what
time they want from me right certainly
there's a
specific very specific
time that they
[Music]
want
370 is
this is this a middle like put one thing
on the free one on the
seven or wait I 70 70 minutes is not a
thing so I guess
7:30 is that what they want oh God oh
God I know how to do it it just will
take a moment um the short one the short
one is uh okay uh 1 2 3 4 5 6 6 7 stop
and then oh yeah okay 30 will have to go
around like this oh I did
it why I did it I'm so
proud I can ra the
clock it's actually really a proud
moment for
me they grow up so F I can read a clock
that means I can read crony I can read
her like a
book oh are Y
what what the
[Music]
hell do you get something if you get all
of
them cuz then if I don't get all of them
maybe there's no point in getting any of
them
CH that's the isn't this the
solution
bro okay uh what is going on
here money first
hey you get a sense of fulfillment yeah
that's probably it
right uh what what do we want here do I
just want to walk into it huh can
I oh W we're
Rising we're
Rising wait let me go
in I will kill
you let me
in thanks ow
oh hello
hello thank
you that's it I guess on this level
wait
okay let's
go money woohoo
is there more here too
hello no no you no you no you die no
no let
me don't don't even don't even no
I must be a
comedian I think I am a
comedian taking it slow here taking it
[Music]
slow hey that's um not high enough but
okay
does it get much
higher whoa where' you come
from or it does get a little bit higher
he yo
okay here I
go here I go thanks for the
membership B fry what does that mean is
that a word
for
something the top of a bell
tower holy
[\h__\h] oh
oh a a a
[Music]
a in the jungle the mighty jungle a lion
sleeps
tonight no what do the J
me
Weis I'm playing a horror
game wait how do you jump again I don't
remember how to
[Music]
jump stop stop you little
[\h__\h] there's a way to jump right can you
only when you're dodging
[Music]
something okay I'm fine ah
I already told people that we're
meeting didn't tell them where we're
going though don't
worry yum
yum L I'm so excited you did too wow
what a
coincidence oh my oh my God there's so
many oh it doesn't give the number of
how many I'm going to be uh approached
[Music]
by oh
fre
triple
[Music]
money with the heart appreciate a
heart it's the big scary red one
okay okay okay okay
yeah give me give
me oh why is it not moving what's
happening
ah this guy what is he doing oh oh he's
oh he's he's on a rampage he ramped me
but I I see we wanted that I don't know
uh oh I don't have a dog bone what are
we doing what's happening ow ow
oh
go oh no what what he's gold now does he
drop
money and we continue the
game oh
five uh what the
hell are you ever going to send a actual
ghost
or that's
it that's
it
six
[Music]
okay no let me get
both
terrifying come a
y birds po be
like not my
[Music]
favorite why did I scream that much why
why why why why why why why why am I
screaming as if I'm being
[Music]
choked I'm just practicing my acting for
getting a role in a real sco horror
[Music]
movie as I am so destined to be in
I'm made for Hollywood
[Music]
baby oh come
on
no no it's not
[Music]
fa oh I'm going to die get out of there
give me a [\h__\h]
heart oh my God
[Music]
I'm the Squam Queen let's
go thanks for the membership
welcome come on why is the clock
ticking oh do I have a what there's a
there's a limit did I fail it oh I'm not
getting another B
what doing it again oh that's not fair
oh that's not fair oh that's not
[Music]
fair oh come on I dodged
it no I didn't have a pH I don't have a
[Music]
we're so going to die it's so
over it's so over come come on throw
yourselves at
me how about
[Music]
it Hearts heart Challenger
come on I can do it I can do it please
give me some
H [\h__\h] Foul
Play
uh-oh okay they're normal they're giving
me they're giving me a break no never
mind uh yeah I got to I got to make him
run okay okay that's
fine did he fall
what what of the F let me
suck
[Music]
no I can't take him I can't
take ah
this is so yum
it okay okay
[Music]
okay I'm gaming right now guys oh I got
a heart okay come on come on come on
come on come
on get go away what the
[\h__\h] okay okay
okay h ah
we Hearts please what no Hearts that's
so
me oh my
god oh it's boss time oh [\h__\h] again okay
but the boss is like kind of see oh yeah
he's going
to ah ah what
okay yeah it's not so complicated really
there we go oh thank you for this
donation give me my
heart okay back to normal that was
easy come
on that's all you
got yes they may have taken my heart
several times today but that doesn't
mean that they're a challenge here
really
I'm literally
just spawn camping here okay next
all this is how they teach kids to time
these days that's really messed up what
is
happening wait how's this work again ah
like
this correct
Madam
correct get him out of the water suck
suck suck
that's it right
one oh there was one
[Music]
left if this is how they teach kids how
to read the clock these days
then I'm glad that I am not from this
generation hey I got I'm back to like 90
Hearts oh God wait I'm not good with
this I'm not the good with this
oh do I just dodg
everything
[Music]
okay run run run
run you better run run run run run
[Music]
oh really that's that's it oh oh
everything oh
no ah no wait a second that is so [\h__\h]
no this a good chance this a good chance
oh run run run run run
run holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no call a little bit I need him I need
him to go for
it
nice nice okay just this one oh about
the timer a
what what what
saage what oh
no oh oh no come
on do it I don't have time
oh my God that was close I
think
bro boss time with 40
hearts uhoh a
[\h__\h] go somewhere else somewhere else go
somewhere else yep yep oh
wonderful am I not supposed to touch
the clock
fingers they they look
hot
w y honestly that might have been a one
of my better performances for boss
fights well generally I feel like I have
less troubles with boss fights than with
actual like normal
enemies
oh
yeah the clock work Boss Rush that was
fun that was actually
fun I liked this
one that was
good that was really
exciting
outstanding oh thank
you that possessor didn't stand a chance
you really cleaned his clock
okay yeah I cleaned it with my vacuum I
suppose that was not the intention
though what are you saying EAD what are
you
[Music]
saying [\h__\h]
bird obnoxious as
[\h__\h] mission
complete 17 minutes how are they going
to judge that 270 Health loss
oh
silver he to the
Y for losing so much health
[Music]
wow so we finished at Clockwork world
finally which means in a way we achieved
our goal of finishing one Mansion
today but let's see we're going to
continue another one at least halfway
through the next one I would want to go
but we'll see how long it takes I'm not
sure anymore how long uh one
takes you're a diamond in my heart
a
sweet uh get him into the Vault quickly
ta
all righty here it goes all my
achievements uh of this
level you're
welcome the longer the processor ghosts
remain with the Dark Moon pieces the
stronger they seem to get a good thing
I've been working on upgrades for the
pull the ghost 5000 any that dark moon
piece has probably been corrupted by
dark energy let's get it cleaned up
sounds good to
[Music]
me which means you beat him up what I
never heard that before I cleaned his
clock never heard it
before oh
[Music]
beautiful oh
snowland a nice little
sh the more Dark Moon pieces we find the
more I think someone shattered it on
purpose any we've got to keep going
let's check the map and see if any more
F
hased I never heard that I'm in us
oh the Mansion is difficult
really you hear it once a decade see
it's not as common apparently
fur
fur it's not as common these people say
they never hear it
ikim
show it's an old boxing term
oldfashioned well I am actually uh
thankful for you guys teaching me
oldfashioned words give me
more Hello Baby smoothie walking around
stretching her stuff my sweet
baby now thanks for the membership gifts
let's go chocolate and Insomniac how do
I deserve this
honor what's happening that's the
coldest part of ever shade Valley I hope
you brought your wi coat
nope nope Showtime with a skull next to
it this sounds like C stream I don't
know Cali album or whatever cie
song am I spoilering something
here the house looks it has a face it
has like a it's like a the eyes and like
a mouth a be looks like an Angry Bird or
something some determined geologists
started a mining operation in these snow
cap mountains but when ghosts started
moving in they got scared and abandon it
everybody just gives up so easily guys
that was a chalet not sh I can't seem to
get a hold of my toad no we're starting
with a
toad he's probably napping in front of
the fireplace again so no way we're not
starting with a toad are
we son I hope you like snow because your
next destination is the top of the snowy
mountain I'm going to go up I'm going to
put on my skis and I'm going to ski down
I'm not going to give a [\h__\h] about any
toads in the
vicinity
[Music]
nuh what no we really have to find the
[\h__\h]
toad
no are you for
real are you for real
are you for real this can't be
real no no no no there's no excuse for
this hell
h Hello h
[Music]
hi hi oh you going to say
hello stretch nice stretch baby you want
to you
to want to be Corner cat h
no she doesn't know what she wants
either so I pick her up
my radioactive
[Music]
cat she's in the thumbnail so she she
knews she knews she knew that she had to
make an
appearance she was scheduled for the
stream sorry she's kind of late I've
been covering for her this whole time
but chunky wony also already appeared
because she jumped into the box in the
beginning
remember
[Music]
oo so we have both appearances no
clickbait yes sucking up
snow is a smart thing to do
this Mak sense filling your vacuum with
water hell
yeah oh I can shoot these where would I
want to shoot them
to oh anywhere
huh H don't know if that was just the
Lucky
[Music]
Strike what that
sound ghosts doing ghost
[Music]
things that seems to be
alive oh what why do I see it now hello
it's taunting me ah it fell
over no give me the
money don't just leave it there to
disappear the ghost knows the ghost is
there to trigger
me
oh yeah a nice chunk of gold on the
Grill why
not I
feel I felt a disturbance in the force
aka the cat hair in my
mouth oh the money is still
[Music]
there wait I can suck it go oh money
money money sorry lugos you are now
taking a speed back in terms of
priority
okay hey what are you doing what do you
think you're
doing no no no no
no what are you
doing hey what did you
go
hey huh huh
huh huh wa what
huh wait huh
what
what ah I was supposed to interact with
the things he went inside oops I guess
so it worked without doing it too so I
thought oh wa where'd you come
from hey the blue one is still there
[Music]
too wait
so well then it Spooks me it gets me a
frighten
well this is
beautiful oh what is this
music okay that carpet I need to throw
this out into
the into the wind uh into the
snow I think the snow bear wants to go
into the snow
H what do you have to
sayell it seems to be alive but it's
just like too warm for its Comfort
that's that's why it's melting in
there if we bring it out it will regain
all its
power the toad is in the fishing Hut
maybe well maybe
we'll
see it can't be that easy because it's
never that easy with
toads let me
investigate what the hell is that up
there some fuzzy thing what is that what
the hell what I've never seen something
like that before in the Luigi's mansion
[Music]
Game fzy
MO is that
garlic so they don't only have a ghost
problem they have a vampire problem I'm
too
hello oh oh no oh no hey hey hey hey
hey give it to me give it back give the
coal
back let's
go let's go of
it he's going to pick it up again no
no
okay no
more could be Warriors
mine
this what what mine there's no mine here
what do you
mean
oh what do we have
[Music]
here hey to the
Y is it the first one it for once is we
have a chance of finding it all but I
don't think we
will what's at the
coffee oh wait a second maybe we want to
warm this thing up can we I where did it
go God damn it no
give me a new
one oh
smart I could go for some coffee I wish
I liked coffee am I supposed to not be
seeing
anything is this a
bug this seems
unusual my flashlight isn't working
I that's
interesting well I found a bug an actual
glitch in The
Matrix this is not
[Music]
normal what do I do restart wait if I
quit but let's resume is it back no
maybe if I switch rooms
um
deaths can I yeah can I not just go out
and then back in again without having to
start from the
beginning let's
see unsaved progress will be
lost um what does this mean what does
that
mean Bob
[Music]
[\h__\h] so if I go back I at least already
have the stone and stuff like that I
assume I I I assume he's moving
have to eat the
bug that was
weird is this a
[Music]
restart complete
restart we will
see just got stuck in the like it was
loading
something when I
successfully figured out the
gimmick yeah oh that that sucks a that
sucks oh smoothie is making herself
comfortable on the bed becoming Corner
cat once
again beautiful
she likes uh lying in the corner of the
bed that's why I call her Corner cat
when she does
that making biscuits no she has nothing
to make biscuits with there right now
there's no blanket or anything but she
already made biscuits today it's really
sweet and we're going to we're going to
you know use this to our advantage and
you know save
time and get
money I'm scared of you is there a point
in watching this probably him losing all
the money if I watch him otherwise he
wouldn't have dropped so much money I
suppose you think that's the
point mhm
[Music]
okay European
chocolate I missed it so
much cuz even even
um even Kit Kat tastes different in
Japan close enough but still
different even the ch
Brand
chocolate I know how to do
everything I know it's better
[Music]
now no even the normal flavor the basic
flavor Kit
Kat should I do this
one [\h__\h]
a you almost made me lose the gold
[Music]
ghost it
[\h__\h] I was trying to uh pick up the
gold on the ground that's why I was
maneuvering weirdly
okay where are
you oh oh
[Music]
hey that rck is possessed no the rug is
alive I'm telling
you we need to throw it outside so that
the bear
can be a bear
again oh let's go did I find that before
surely I did
[Music]
see obviously it's
alive if it was dead it wouldn't do that
I'm
sure I say free the Bear yes
[Music]
yes so we got to activate this once I
cuz he wants to call
us
sker I know I know he's fishing toad is
[Music]
fishing m is up there okay I think
that's all in this room
we're back in this room that gave us the
glitch so if it happens again I'm going
to rage quit just so you
know
[Music]
um ah wait I was supposed to suck it off
of you
[Music]
surely it won't happen again
yeah surely
not why why why why why why
[Music]
why that and the the crystal wait
here the round Crystal I would like to
receive it once again please pleas can I
have your
blessing the blue blue this is like the
color of
quason same beautiful blue color deep
deep
blue oh did I do that
before feel like maybe not
okay
uh and then I just eh did I just walk
through wait is isn't that where the bug
happened maybe because I I pulled this
rope feel like maybe that's where it
happened aha
okay we are bug free let's go oh wait
that's the previous
room or am I supposed to go through
it fresh from the oven is it not
enough oh wait I have to hold it oh wait
no it's
working w
yeah the sound is
weird how are they not already moving in
this
wind excuse
[Music]
me why is that even in there I feel like
if you would make it uh make a special
Melody maybe it will give you something
but
H there's a [\h__\h] bull King over there
what oh it's cracking is it
cracking no we good okay there's uh
PS no I would call it Pok in
German are we supposed to play something
here
[Music]
oh why it it's
stopped there is a uh hole
is the toad in here isn't this the
fishing
place I see no
to oh
ah wait
what what's going on is she did she put
the is is the toad holding the fishing
rod but it's sticking out of the picture
because it didn't fit into the picture
or what is going on
[Music]
but what about
this are
we perhaps missing
something do I go
in go
that's
sus okay well I'll go in ah the toad we
probably shoot the toad into it yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
cute oh it just
left I thought we would
fight nice
collection I
see oh God are you guys ready for more
told I'm
not H
told what oh oh it's here I thought ah
how can it have a reflection if it's not
there
[Music]
though come on ah
stupid get out of the
[Music]
way that reminds me I I saw this like
tweet the other
day what was that
again
like what was I it was a it was a Oh
somebody got zapped it was a picture or
video of
somebody like just showing something
like a like how there was like light
falling through something and it was
casting a shadow a shadow of like some
writing and then some some lady thought
like she's going to like expose that
person because obviously it's it must be
fake this can't be real because it's not
mirrored and she was pointing that out
so proudly and then everybody was like
dunking on her like haha you're so dumb
because obviously woman have you ever
thought about
this it's not mirror but it's just a
shadow like being cast
Mama you're thinking of a mirror
reflection that has to be mirrored not a
[\h__\h] Shadow Shadows don't get
mirrored and this honestly so
funny thinking that way I I kind of can
see like you're having a little bit of a
brain an empty moment
and then you're like thinking it's the
same thing I I can see you know and then
that's kind of
embarrassing you guys would make so much
fun of
me big brain fart
yeah why did he call me Mario first
what's wrong with you I hope you die in
this ice cold
water stop jumping on
it uh that's what you get for calling me
Mario but don't drag me into
[Music]
this
yeah I don't even want to I don't want
to deal with him
yellow Yello
losing reception
[Music]
mhm this place is extra
extra
extremely extremely dangerous be
careful there's an old elevator that
should take you back to the to the
Chalet that's the only way good look
okay can I leave toad
behind just quick question is that
possible because he is dead
weight especially after I kill him he
will be dead
weight oh well hello there let's
go told you almost made me lose stons
[Music]
you would have had to pay that back
triple toad remember that careful from
now
on tread very
carefully and what is
that
okay
I oh this is open Oh I thought it was I
thought I had to melt that you can go
behind it
okay well
done can
I do something with you
here like right
here
no wait no wait uh one more thing one
more
[Music]
thing just want to check if I'm missing
something with um what is this called
again the dark light no what's it
called wait how is toad going to
follow
[Music]
nice
what do I shoot toad up
I guess wait I just uh what are you
going to do if I fly with you oh you're
coming with me
okay ah you're going to get me the
diamond not the not Diamond but
yeah another pretty stone for
[Music]
quason I'm going to donate all of these
to Tim
tands oh all of them she will thank me
I'm sure of it we missed one wonderful
great I love to see
it no I don't really
care I think we can go to the next room
come
[Music]
on oh another mirror
mirror mirror on the
[Music]
wall who grew strong and who grew tall
Luigi he's just trying to make himself
feel better about being the unpopular
child in the
family let him cope
oh wow
okay how do I get
that there we
[Music]
go
one maybe
stone or a bone or a
trombone no no I HTE my life
[Music]
no did we already turn this
one I don't remember it I guess we
did okay that door needs a key so we'll
go come on
[Music]
is there two
doors
huh
[Music]
confused
see reminds you of a Mario 64
room wait the game tells me to go
there come mind but wait the the door is
shaking maybe I should go to the other
one first I don't
know
M mhm and now a wait to get
there what about it what about this up
here does that make you
happy wait there's a
key
ah huge miror in Peach's castle on the
third
floor did I even ever see
that maybe I should play Super Mario 64
again to go see
[Music]
it surely there was something there to
see that I did not just uh notice just
now but would have been helpful if I did
[Music]
yes please please
do should I try this door
first oh oh it was shaking cuz of the
wind
[Music]
not oh
fun there is so much fun to be had here
it seems but do I really want to hang on
to this now can I can I shoot either
onto one of these
no wait I don't think I can hold on to
it at least not for now weird come
on you need a fil you have a good pick I
don't think think I'll be needing a fill
game though because I'm about to start
playing the new Zelda
game doesn't the reflection look very
different wait it's a picture now it's a
[\h__\h]
carpet why you walking that way why is
he walking that way where am what's
going
on spooky shenanigans
funny who did
that who B that what's the point boo
what's the point of putting uh a curtain
that looks exactly like the reflection
ah what are you trying to
hide maybe he was trying to hide that
the the thing was gone the thing that he
was in a booon
[Music]
let's
go you done yet
[Music]
no it's quite easy to get him here
because of the
reflection the money the
money I didn't have time to pick it all
up I've been scammed
[Music]
time to smack that boot too next Tuesday
what what are you talking
about come on next
[Music]
Tuesday am I not getting
something open up come
on
FBI fellow
boo
uh in something that's not
investigators is chat
dead hello
boo oh you don't want to walk over
this why
not oh
wait Chad you're so dead I can see you
heart
still why are you not talking to me
anymore are you so mad about the whole
essay thing I'm
sorry come
on I'm never going to get over
this can I not shoot him beforehand
ahead of time
[Music]
no don't run backwards run the other
way this
is and now it doesn't is it just because
we're both of us are too
heavy go go oh there we go I managed to
do
it oh really oh really didn't always
work
oh miffin got to say one word but it
still seems like it's
broken just let him go no not that
one there's no space
yo it's the [\h__\h]
space holy moolly king
king so is there a door here
[Music]
CH it's about time you come back here
I'm going to go insane without
you oh he wanted to
slide he wanted to slide over it not
just be thrown over it I see
now but we're not here to have fun
toad don't you get it
HH wait how you how you doing doing
that
eh oh there's a floor no there's
not toad how' you do that are you saying
I can walk over there with no
concern are you sure you
promise for
real I thought I would fall down
genuinely I thought he can just like bug
through it
game logic you
[Music]
know that's some clear ice
yo more ice
[Music]
please oh
are you coming back to me chat are you
coming back you got to try typing don't
give up on life
yet you have to
try come
on come
[Music]
on guys there you go come on try
harder why is this not working
wait wait wait what did it
do ah am I supposed to light it with
fire ah you see I did that without you
guys it's going to blow up it's going to
blow up toad here go
enjoy man that should have been a bigger
explosion
hello are you
back you back
guys no
[Music]
Oh no you're not
dead
[Music]
what come on try tapping seems like
you're
[Applause]
[Music]
back I say k you say FP I say k you say
FP come
on oh wait there's still one
[Music]
around okay it seems
like some of you are able yeah to ride
but not all of
you very
few they hate me my chat hates me
why though why how do I deserve this
treatment how do I deserve to be ignored
so much by you
guys I thought you love
[Music]
me you're intentionally not typing what
so you really hate me
[Music]
wait are you saying you're not affected
by the curse
currently but you still choose to ignore
me this is going on for way too long
guys should I give a personal call to
YouTube head office be like moshim
moshy either my chat hates me or YouTube
hates me which one is
it can you stop running I'm trying to do
something with
you okay didn't work uh how do I ah wait
I guess I just make it go Kaboom like
this see I figured that one out without
you guys to are you just
like like trying to make me learn things
on my
own have I become too dependent on you
you
no am I done with this
room what are my options oh oh here it
[Music]
is man my chat is so
sad
uh I'm talking to myself
all right I'm going to tighten the
bridge
up how is that that's not
enough oh we got to tighten it from the
other side too hey I can walk over that
really no
where [\h__\h]
idiot I least should try
Super Chat
work that would be so insane if they let
you pay for them but don't make those
show up
either but at the same
time it's just not fair that the only
way to talk to me now is paying money to
YouTube super chats don't work NE are
you sure it didn't work for you
scam
scam absolute
[Music]
scam Chad I need your help
though guess I'll go through this
door I need
you wait no stay hey I can't go for this
door without you you know
that go go go go go
go you're back now tell me how
to how to uh continue with life thank
you you're back oh my God you were dead
for so long you were in a
coma are you okay do you remember me
Chad you've been gone for so long I
understand if you might not remember
me yeah I'm actually okay in case you
forgot me let me tell you I'm I'm I'm
Kori I a I'm a raer SL
Reaper can I up more and you guys are my
dead
beats
mhm you have to believe me
[Music]
the only reason why you came back to
life is because I the reaper decided to
not reap
you yes I am cie remember me now I'm
your C I'm your Mory I hope you remember
me what the [\h__\h] do I do
[Music]
maybe maybe I maybe I can't move on from
here damn
it I still don't remember can you wrap
uh can you rap that's disrespect
[Music]
respectful see what the [\h__\h] did I do
wait I broke my okay whatever that's
fine
[Music]
it
is I'm
okay [\h__\h] it and Killers really must fun
more often people Taking Lives rocking
knives and guns the real murder coniss
in the of Hell used to learning in the
audience with more cuz to my surprise
singodia stopping the [\h__\h] of
human can't stop the make sure standing
off by rhy out there high five I see no
one's going to buy this [\h__\h] I believe
you cute as hell in AAL
PR the
queen
super the scene it's like that you take
my advice you be killed watch you don't
know but the saying that I like so much
more is along the lines of you [\h__\h]
say so I know so could you let go of
your for me I'm
[Music]
not murder is so
[\h__\h] the to say all right y so it
goes dead listen up it's what you want
me coming in the night
for anyway
human better tell you straight forward
hear you all the waying on your keyboard
go ahead and I
rry for for but the of dark stays in the
sun c a l i o i really Pi sh eye opening
taking words to get right of the cup my
own thing murder with words up that was
the pass me going to take a first class
M to blast me hum come at me I'm mtic
ashy whatever Happ whatever little laugh
at
me kill by watch you don't know but ins
I'm kind of nervous and I don't know
what the word is for the other side of
the Gap [\h__\h] say so setting out do I'm
supposed to do I get close to you don't
it's all right with you I your
[Music]
Mur is so
[\h__\h] say all
right
go dance anyway it's Human Nature
yeah so I'm kipor you get it
now I think that was proof
enough thank
you good
I'm glad we got that cleared
[Laughter]
up
[Music]
[Laughter]
yippe oh thank you it's been a long
while since I tried um singing the song
in one
go just a little bit of recollecting it
an enigmatic
recollection damn that's so nostalgic
that's so crazy like
it's not just as four years ago it's
also just like hoton doesn't feel as
nostalgic to me than this song I think
because Cali released a million I
released a million
songs
[Music]
joke I know I'm really collab wari I am
the one and
only I am the real one
what do you
mean I just talk in third person
sometimes but yeah I released so many
songs since this this was my debut song
and it's just been so long and so many
songs in between now and
then that this just feels like a million
years ago doesn't it dead beats so dead
Beats can you tell me how the hell do I
get Toad to go with me through this door
or is this not what I'm supposed to do
right
[Music]
now I oh I need to go with the brids
using motion
controls oh I see oh wo oh I
see I thought it just wasn't possible
motion controls are just like rarely
used what how did I do it in the
DS uh ghost don't you dare touch me
right
now oh I'm so
shaky oh no don't wait he's got to steal
the toad won't he toad
toad going to hold on to you just as
once don't you get stolen by the ghost
now in the middle of the bridge it also
has motion controls H where did they
okay comparing switch wi and DS motion
controls which one was the
worst and why was it the
Wii that couldn't have been probably DS
was like a more lowkey version or so we
funny shut
up you wanted to use the elevator
right
there go
in let's go let's go let's
go the bear comes back to life wait uhoh
not quite but the fuzzy
monsters wait what
what what what what what what the what
are these what am I supposed to do with
these are they going to hurt me can I
set them on
fire
what I don't
understand I
don't understand it it just keeps on
giving me money maybe I'll need the
golden
one what is
this it's following
me okay let's just ignore
them if I can uh oh yeah cuz I'm
supposed
to go
away
hey what he right
[Music]
there here you go hit them with oh [\h__\h]
byebye
W oh no did I miss something important
[Music]
now oh it was a joke
okay I did already get money out of them
so I think generally you just really
supp supposed
to I don't know set him on fire or so I
don't know we'll see we'll probably deal
more with them
[Music]
later that felt like it take it it took
ages cuz I was waiting for you guys to
tell me about the
bridge so the brze is really not my
fault also I wrapped I wrapped I
literally stopped for like 4 minutes to
WAP so in reality I got
silver right
yeah a lot of things happened in these
minutes well that was fun like rapping
so
hardcore I never do that except I do
because I'm Kore
[Music]
right you know it you know it that
beat where are my death Beats at you all
are dead
beats that cator I don't know much about
her we got the boo all right we're going
to hit rock bottom let's go baby
right here repo let's
go you came back to the wrong stream
exactly and K be
mo recently just released a new
album please stream my new album
guys what's the name of the cover song
you just released chiny gummy
easy I I you ask wait no no I would know
my own
covers but you you should not ask me
about what covers uh takanasi kiar is
[Music]
releasing that's quite an old joke
though King
cover really like her King cover I
really like ki's King
cover I watched it like 50 times
yeah haven't released a cover song in a
long
time sorry the RS are not rolling cuz of
the
chocolate is is smovie still in the
corner
oh my God she's still in the corner even
though I'm screaming and rapping sorry I
don't mean smoothie I mean um tutu
tutu what the hell is going on here the
boo are holding the other ghost's
hostage what the
[Music]
hell honestly if it was tutu and ghost
cat then smooy would be ghost cat and
tutu would be chunky wonky if anything
like if we're comparing personalities
and
lankiness then although like tutu is
really not very chunky but she's at
least more fluffy than ghost cats
so cats have the wrong color I know I
don't know what's wrong with YouTube but
you know YouTube is just broken in
general
as you can see by the CSS not working
it's making the emotes look weird
too okay to I have
to um commission Spirit snare really
quickly um
what do we what are we going to name it
um actually I don't
know can't think of can't think of a
like writing to put into the logo
[Music]
should I name it something you know how
some girls are naming their lives like
something should I give it a a nice
title like a proper title I can't think
of one
does it need one I'll have to think
about
this the Sinister laughter coming from
the bottom of the Mind do you think it
came from their what does it
say
leader is there a theme to match a title
kind there's kind of a
theme low
[Music]
key
H I have an idea
today I turned 30 but I'm not going to
let it get me down oh do you know why
because the age of 30 is in the v thanks
for always being you I wish you all the
best in your future and there is pinky
pinky pinky thank you so much Galahad
Marksman happy
[Music]
birthday
congratulations H happy birthday to
you Gad Marksman in your
shoe happy birthday to you happy
birthday to
you and in your shoes too and in your
pants
too happy birthday to you sir thank you
so much for your support Freddie is
quite the pretty number I think you
shouldn't be worried about 30d like
I think I'm assuming
you're I'm assuming you're
guy I feel like you know 30 is just
like a nice a nice age it's just a good
age like you're
finally a
man finally you're a man don't you feel
more like a man now like you got
everything in control now
[Music]
until now you were perhaps just a
boy this is where it really begins for
you this is where it
[Music]
begins
yeah I hit Freddy recently everyone been
talking to me more for some reason
oh interesting
can't hear
us feeling that way at least four years
now let's
go manly I'm a man
go let's let's do manly things like
[Music]
um what's manly things let me see it
what's what's manly things to Wawa um
uh buying a really
expensive uh uh Grill wait Grill is that
how you're say it in
English uh uh barbecue grill
[Music]
yeah yeah buy a really expensive one and
then grill a huge [\h__\h] steak on
it the biggest steak you could possibly
find and then I yeah I don't know I
wouldn't really I wouldn't really
support like chugging
[Music]
beers I would say besides
that
a buy yourself your second car now if
you don't have a first car yet that
doesn't matter just buy yourself your
second
car and this car is going to be like
your sports car that you're like
throwing out all your savings for that's
what you do when you're 30 I
hear go in Deb for it or sell sell
things that don't even belong to you in
this economy well you could also buy a
bike okay you're either that type of guy
or that type of guy perhaps you're more
of a bike kind of
guy that reminds me I was um in Japan I
was I was like in a Japanese
taxi um do I have this T written
down I think I do but like where
[Music]
what are these what are these T
notes what are
[Music]
these should I just freestyle
it perhaps I'll freestyle it
[Music]
I just don't want to miss any
details I was in I was in the taxi and
then I you know I'm I look like this
Foreigner I look like I don't speak
Japanese so when I do speak Japanese
like hey hi I got an address for you to
put in you know stuff like that they're
like and then they asked me where I'm
from and this and that and then I said
um I'm from Austria and then this this
tax driver he's like I don't know he
looks like he's 50 or something and he's
like
Austria I know Austria and I'm like
really you know he's like yeah because
like my favorite bike uh
producer is from
Austria and I wrote this down somewhere
but I forgot what was it
called but he was so excited to hear uh
from me being from there and uh maybe
it's KTM yeah that sounds
familiar and I'm like yeah I didn't know
we have a like such a popular well-known
bike producer that you would be so fond
of and then he tells me everything about
it and I'm like I'm like well I I I
personally I don't care about bikes but
um he seemed so happy about it so I just
felt like I'm going to have this nice
conversation with him now so I kept on
being like yes and yes and tell me more
about it tell me more about this bike oh
and like he told me he told me he
doesn't drive cars in his private life
he drives bikes and I'm like oh is that
so well why and he's like ah because uh
you know bikes are more fun and you can
zoom around and I actually hate driving
cars I'm like that's funny because
you're driving a car for your job huh
and wouldn't it be nice if you could uh
like like you know be a taxi driver with
a bike instead like so that I would be
riding on the back you can only take one
passenger at a time I guess but isn't
that fun we kept on talking and talking
and and um he tells me he doesn't have
his dream bike yet and I'm like oh you
got to buy it right and he's like ah
it's
expensive tells me everything about it
and I'm like oh that's funny because
like he tells me that that this Austrian
bike is very popular motorbike by the
way in Japan I'm like that's that's
interesting cuz in Austria I feel like
it's the other way around like we see
Japanese motorbikes and they're like oh
this this is cool
oh Japanese bike that must be really
sick yeah but you always want what's
what's further away from
you yeah Callie is from Austria
mhm yeah probably KTM mhm they make
normal bikes and
um uh
motorbikes yeah we talked forever and
and he was like so happy and I feel like
we had like for 30 minutes we had an
endless conversation and he just seemed
so happy with it I think normally when
Japanese people go on the taxi they
don't they don't really seek out a
conversation with the taxi driver they
just like
quietly have it go by so it must have
been kind of special for him to have a
conversation in the first place and then
it's about one of his favorite things in
life he seemed so passionate about it
that's
cute it was
cute
[Music]
yeah and I'm just happy that he knew
that Austria is not Australia
[Music]
the crystal quy that's hard to say
crystal
quy try to get beu to say that you'll
find my e Gates on the way there don't
be afraid to use them oh Sunny get to
the bottom of the mine and stop those
boot from doing whatever it is that
they're doing
mik scare me
H they they used to scare me
to when I first like had the experience
of riding in the back of one but then it
became really fun I mean it's still
scary but it's
fun just got to hold on
[Music]
tight oh wait uh what are we
doing are you sleeping wake up a you're
so cute what are we doing with you it
blows up that's interesting
right that's something a function that
we want to
remember and we can get money out of
this one again and
again not out of this one right yeah
it's just the golden
one okay can we fill it like a hot air
balloon and then fly
up if if
we put
it no I think that was a decent
[Music]
guess wait I can ah I can just blow him
up like this if I
[Music]
reverse which way do I
go we want to go to be
free well I have no idea how to get
there actually
[Music]
oh I don't know I don't know how to get
down get
down it just makes me think I need to do
something with them there right now but
maybe
[Music]
not oh elevator maybe does it go down
though I thought it only goes
up but yeah I don't know why I didn't
try let's me
try we have indeed not used it
yet oh we do go deeper we do go
down but we're outside now
[Music]
what do you
do oh oh may I hold on to wait wait wait
wait can you come back oh I turned it
off on generally what is this
for I can't seem to
reach a there we go
oh death
perception the only thing I'm I'm good
at oh it's d e a t h perception because
I'm Kori
ha get
it d e pth perception I'm not so good
at I'm a
genius where are we going with this oh I
see where do I want to go
I
see does this bring me anywhere where I
cannot already go
[Music]
to I mean maybe it's a shortcut to that
place I
guess I mean I've been there so I'm like
why would I go there
again but okay I'll go
are you bringing it to
me why thank you where where did you
drop it off
[Music]
no where did you bring it to H it's it
it look like it flew towards
me it's in the is it in the
barrel
ah I was thinking so too but I didn't
think long enough well we missed many
again does this go down more
or yeah I just wanted to try I had a
feeling when I wanted to
[Music]
try is this even the right
path let me go one more time
[Music]
cuz now I got distracted I
suppose and then I guess I'll just go
through
here and
then I haven't been through
here no I have but I didn't really know
like propably use this yet cuz I just
didn't have the right angle they have a
gem
give
me oh nice that one's
[Music]
easy no I think now I'm on the right
path oh but that one's those are
icy wait what do we
do I need something
hot if only I was a phoenix
I'm
missing
Pot Phoenix
Powers damn
it keep on missing this
too
[\h__\h] maybe I need to warm it up from a
different side or should I have tried
to use this light the going
[Music]
like
H kiata Mansion of the day wait I it's
not working on
anything [\h__\h]
I'm
stuck I'm stuck guys help me it's all
adding on to my time I'm just going to
get bronze again I don't need to be
here mama
mia mama
no oh
please I don't need to be
here where do I
what is there supposed to be a door
here this is
[Music]
confusing I know but I'm saying there
should be two doors
[Music]
oh money again
okay this was not icy before was
it no was maybe
[Music]
was I've done all of
this I'm stuck I just want to get lower
but I I can't figure out
how there supposed to
be no the door is above
no I mean no I get it miror but like I'm
saying look at the map there's one here
and there's one
here but
maybe I don't
know maybe the door is behind the mirror
like immediately behind it I don't know
don't you understand what I
mean there's an unopened door right
there
I don't mean the door that you see in
the
mirror this doesn't seem like the path
that I have to take either
although there's another unopened
door wait a wait a freaking
moment that wasn't there before and now
you're telling me you can't get
[Music]
it I'm I'm not heavy enough to take
this
alone break
it break
it toad come
back I can't move the lamb
I can't move
[Music]
anything wait a
second that one's hard to
see it breaks the
ice what
[Music]
what oh ah
wait it gives me
logs amazing what
this is still not the right path I
think I know it's not but you guys are
not telling me a better
path now we're just in this room where I
don't want to
[Music]
be now we're back here
maybe there's a new secret that is worth
backtracking
[Music]
for
left
okay I guess I wasn't able to go through
this door before because of cold
[Music]
huh
yeah this remember trying a million
times it's okay go for the portal this
is just the
beginning hello look like a Mickey Mouse
hand a hand
a yeah so that means Mickey Mouse is on
the other
[Music]
side
oh
fire
fire yeah Luigi's thinking of portals
wait I understand already don't you
worry about it seems CU this is broken
that I
can ni blow the fire through the portal
no I thought I could just rip it
off
[Music]
H okay
that's
not what I was
expecting the
angle no
set Luigi on fire I
can't I wish I
could can I suck at
FR It's s sucking suck the fire
no help
[Music]
the viral on the ground has
something think of
[Music]
anything can I take something from the
other
[Music]
room I think not
one of those fuzzy things would be nice
maybe I don't
[Music]
know I don't get it
wait didn't I already try vacuuming it
though but no maybe I didn't just
because I know you can't vacuum the ice
but you can still vacuum the [\h__\h]
poest hey bro bro I thought I lost the
key well okay okay let's
just just yeah I only used the light
like trying to find something to burn it
with but like I didn't think of cuz it
didn't even look like that much
snow I just thought I can't vacum the
ice which is true I
[Music]
can't yeah imagine that would get me
stuck because the key went elsewhere
what is we
[Music]
these I guess I'll just have to activate
this from below or so now we
[Music]
slide what there was a jam on the
left son is that a snake on the left he
[Music]
hey
snake what is that oh it's a it's a rope
same same thing this is snake dead snake
what what what what let me open you
he thank you for waiting for me for once
so generously
[Music]
what is
that
oh
okay but I want to try again does this
bring me back
up
go say sax if you want both the key and
the gem obviously you can't get both a
is just the right way wait [\h__\h] it how
do you get how do you get for the left
side the very
[Music]
left what
hold this how the [\h__\h] do I use the dog
I don't think I can use him right now
right it's timing guys it's just a
matter of timing or do I have to take
the big
Ram [\h__\h] is it timing is it timing
[Music]
ow is it timing I I I was I was pretty
close
now can I tell from here like now now
the big gap passed so I don't
know just got to get
lucky oh oh oh this might be
[Music]
good
yay worth
it oh let's go that has some sharp edges
be careful with that louigi
[Music]
it felt like I was about to miss the gem
I I'm going to pour some
water lucky death Jo oh thank
[Music]
you okay what is this
do you want to be
unmelted probably not the best
idea don't attack me I said don't attack
me what is
happening okay I got some of them
[Music]
finally some
ghost it's been a while since we HED
some oh he wants to be
[Music]
green another one
oh
yeah
clear this one's in
a is that a coincidence that the log
ended up
[Music]
there
weird
[Music]
oh well we'll surely find a solution for
that took the mon there almost missed
the treasure chest
he that's
it oh that's where the real coins are we
haven't had one of these in a
while so
you you're a bit aggressive right so
maybe is there some do we want you to be
aggressive attack go do
it eh
no let me look at
[Music]
this there we
go as well only three coins I think
they're trolling because the real money
is in this
picture close the
[Music]
window squeaky
fire fire light the
snow what's with him I don't understand
did he do something I maybe he chopped
some wood and that's why it ended up
there I just didn't see it happening
properly thank you that's why are you so
nice that's weird you're doing great
sweetie that's something I never
hear that's too nice that's suspiciously
nice this feels like the
end the music is
eering huh oh Oh I thought it was a gem
but no they're all
blue supposed to be blue these are
different gems he
money you can't get those ghosts can you
[Music]
okay I don't have to go inside okay uh
down what do you mean wait there with
money yeah yeah yeah I see it the one I
just picked up right or you mean
something else
uh wait normal
pull oh byebye
Evans no even higher oh I guess we're
not getting that anymore are
we wait maybe you
will no oh you're going to break
it that's it not bullying it's
[Music]
pussing cute that's pretty cute nice
attention to
detail and where is the money where did
you hide the money from me Oh Oh you
mean a gem not money that's what you
mean right
Wow money too
I don't I'm at this little bit okay
well we're
losing time I don't know if those five
coins were worth it but oh well show me
the gem like getting any gem counts to
the score
right so
that must be worth
it but I think the end of this level is
near oh I see a face down there is that
a mirror again
[Music]
what
oh I did not see that like I did not
have the depth
perception did you guys see
that that was really
[Music]
confusing smart
cookies I think there's just
suspiciously few things too few things
that I'm finding with this RGB
sensor I feel like there should be more
e it can go up and it can go down
perh
oh you don't like
that
w
scam okay let's bring it to the bottom
maybe that will be
useful Take Care thank you RS yeah I'm
Callie yellow remember you
Mory hope you'll remember
[Applause]
me CIA
Chow yeah we're basically
there is this do aha one side okay okay
another iccy
[Music]
thing we'll figure it out there's
fire what is
this helmets can I load them up with
fire
somehow can I shoot them through the
portal oh I can shoot
[Music]
them well that doesn't do anything now
another
door we might want to walk through this
one
first what
do can we go
[Music]
down oh
okay and I miss and I miss and I
[Music]
miss a phone let's go that will surely
help me in wait is there a fight
[Music]
upcoming no boss fight sure
but maybe we fight a couple of
boo oh we're producing coal now we're
sending coal through the portal and
that's how we get our fire I was saying
everything
right all right all
right hello from your female fans hey BK
you hello to you
this
hole
huh
ho feel like I'm missing something there
too
but for now it works the way I
want all right first you
yeah why does that go in so
weirdly also there's a mouse hole there
isn't that sus as
well and
then up
here interestingly there's exactly one
more coal can we use that for something
does it have something to do with
this probably
not what if we sent a hot Cal
back I don't know if we
can wait can I look through here
[Music]
ohep hi oh you got the key does he know
he's being watched by me why you
taunting me
[Music]
okay I'm coming for you yeah I was
thinking about the cooking pots too hey
yo yo you came
through ow no no no no no yes both of
them oh did I lose
[Music]
one wait wait wait give me my money
first the BS
[Music]
yeah they were going opposite way so one
of them got away I was trying to pull
like backwards kind of
but didn't work out uh is the coal gone
now
[Music]
no have to get another
one but what if I
just can I not pull the quicking pot
towards me why does it not move oh there
we
go oh wait wait wait we just going
[Music]
to she one only heart I thought that
that would be something more
special
huh oh oh there we go hello why are you
doing this
boo maybe the ghosts weren't our real
enemies it's the ghosts not the ghost
the
ghost we got to
differentiate wait didn't I get a
key ah wait we got to do this first and
then there's a key saw
[Music]
it we have the other
ghosts saw that coming from a mile
away oh
[Music]
same kind of gimmick throughout the
whole
level I mean why not um I can't shoot
this one oh wait a
second I suppose this goes first put it
down aim it
down
whatever ah now we get coal which we can
shoot
wait an
avle okay I don't know if that's hot
enough now it's hot
enough
yippee hey is the ice world yeah but
like I feel like it's a bit too
repetitive they could have thought of a
few more gimmicks perhaps
wouldn't you say
[Music]
so nothing else okay well we got the
key have to rest now buy more hey what
[Music]
the bye-bye
you're trying to distract me so that
these ghosts
can get away with their stolen goods huh
oh but I got you before your friends
me you ain't going
nowhere right here we go that was a long
level
[Music]
huh what's happening you going to fight
me or
what you be py nice three Boos at once
just
rough oh they going to break
out oh oh they're they're bbing
oh he's so
scared poor
[Music]
Wy why is there never anything in
these
wa that's a big reward for people who
don't go straight St into it but look at
everything closely first thank
you all right I'm ready I think oh W
look at
[Music]
this
nothing okay
um crack crack it open no okay wait it's
okay I know what to
[Music]
me maybe this one needs RGB
power they sound like freaking monkeys
someone stopped
[Music]
them is the pickaxe there for some
particular reason
[Music]
wait didn't they already break out I
don't see them
anymore
maybe it just needs a better try
[Music]
no can I get on
this feel like I'm lacking critical
information again
oh I have
to make him
sure what
[Music]
I mean yeah oh now you break
out hey
[Music]
I don't know if that's entirely mled oh
here they
come
[Music]
I
[\h__\h] let's just let just can't stretch
it out too much ow
get B come
[Music]
on [\h__\h]
you yeah now now we're
talking so the
limit more
[Music]
what that's all I get two bars of gold
really bro shouldn't I've got more
yellow from
that
mhm feel like I
scam he did it it brings you more
normally if you have them on the leash
longer but
maybe only the last thing counts cuz I
had bread and then I had like the first
stage twice after maybe only the last
one counts I don't know the last one
until you let
go
bronze H yeah cuz I didn't kill them
with a shock oh man sucks that's
mean that's so mean I worked so hard on
that I did it you did it I did
it good to see you back here Luigi let's
see what you got oh yeah it took a
while was this the second level of this
mansion look at all the gems we wao we
were working hard on the gem
collection all for
Quest all for
her putting in extra work for
her he's got a theory but I think it's
just a game theory should we give him
the time of the
day that strong ghost you captured back
in the Old Clockworks I think I know
what happened to him someone seems to be
controlling all the in the valley but it
doesn't stop there they've also figured
out a way to use the mine CES to
strengthen the boat if they've been
extracting is that a meow from a cat out
game or in
game been extracting crystals this
entire time and taking them elsewhere I
Fe we may be up against much stronger
ghosts in the future that wouldn't be on
top of things we still have no idea
who's pulling the strings behind all
this who could orchestrate such a f are
you thinking
[Music]
no I'm thinking this is rude also was
there supposed to be a boo because where
the hell was he I mean I saw them but
they flew
away across the
chasm I bet it's
King 100%
[Music]
yes y Yu yabu yappa yappa yaa
the signal is coming from an unlikely
place outside of the mine the distant
Workshop give me a shortcut I'm sick and
tired of running through these
[Music]
Mansions I'll call you on the dual
screen once you get across what across
uh what are we going across I should
have read
maybe ah I know what I know what I know
what those gondolas were the next one
was frozen and I didn't know how to
proceed
right got to go to sleep good
night is it sleepy
time where are you watching from
sea find the gondola exis all
right the fuzzy ones are here again give
me this one give me this one
[Music]
yo and another
one and a third
[Music]
one I like
these the yellow fuzzy one is a good one
oh the elevator has been
frozen that is not
[Music]
good
why why must you be
[Music]
Frozen
Okay uh what is
there a particular path I want to take
give
me finding new Secrets let's go oh it's
just the old
[Music]
one well I'll take this one I don't know
if it helps me to get more scores
[Music]
but I don't
know where to
go was this always like
this probably what if I take the big
fish can
I no wait is this like am I stuck here
nothing I can do
here no
yeah I know I fell down here but I'm
wondering if I can fall down
again okay so this is not the path
[Music]
then do I take the Cal can
I can I take it with me
there's a gem in the
fish yeah it looks like it might have
eat a fish or
two
[Music]
no no I can't go with
this well then I am once again pretty
Clueless
was that
hor remember
that are you guys here to do anything at
all cuz so far you have been of no
[Music]
use I yeah I was a bit late on that idea
but yeah
eventually Wawa figures things out it
just takes quite a
while get you you're about to be about
as annoying as freaking toad get away
from me fuzzy one get away from
me no what go away
trying to do something here not sure
[Music]
what oh oh oh oh
oh
aha it's pushing
[Music]
me stupid little
[\h__\h] I saw the safe
just doing things step by
step
stop stop following
meow okay now we take the real elevator
oh it seems to have had a concussion
from
that uh wait let me
enter ah okay oh no I woke it up
[Music]
again one pets I I like the fluffiness
of it more than toad toad is not very
fluffy he's just
squishy so in
the I don't dislike
him the bling ones but they just don't
fit in I feel like what are they doing
there they
don't fit in in my
opinion do I go through
here and then I go round and then I'll
end up
in why is there an exclamation mark
here have we already a cuz it's over
there okay but there's surely something
new here
my like this bomb it's going to yo I'm
telling you there's something behind
this sorry I got too excited but I'm
this
Mir I've been telling you there a
[\h__\h]
door you guys were like she's kind of
insane this girl like I don't know what
she's saying there's obviously a door on
the other side because of the mirror I'm
telling you look at the
map you never doubted me I love
you I love
you
see everybody down at me what is that
thing there
oh that is [\h__\h] dangerous that could
have killed
me that could have killed
me ow that could have killed me
[Music]
too don't play with pickaxes
guys hey to the
Y all right all right I have explored
plenty
okay should I look behind this door one
more time what was there
again yeah okay I'm
fine
huh oh Lord he coming
[Music]
what where'd you
go that's fine I didn't think I was
going that way originally anyway I
thought I would go for the
[Music]
outside
refresh okay
[Music]
that's fine with
me we can probably get rid of them from
the outside I
assume but is there now a way to fire it
up over
there I don't see anything new
maybe there still
isn't a
way but where there is a wh there is a
way come
on never mind it's not working I go back
this doesn't seem to be
it I already got the thing in the nest
maybe I just have to use my RGB on the
on the chains I don't know wouldn't that
be too
[Music]
simple wait we got to go this
way
oh I didn't see the exclamation
mark that is counter
in counter intuitive I say
[Music]
hello fat
one how are you doing wait so if you're
there that means you're there right
[Music]
well you wouldn't be there you're
there there's a bomb there why does it
not activate well okay okay okay
okay I just don't know sometimes what's
the right order to do things okay
Kaboom now let's have some
fun is this not the jelly
[Music]
wao that looks like double the amount of
money makes me
get what is what is he
doing how do
[Music]
I that's not the same as the
other I I guess I can e that's
oh that's not what I thought how it
would
work ah can you
[Music]
not
noing what
what's
the
what he just won't stop even when you
sucking on
[Music]
him you are an obnoxious little fell he
was spawn camping
[Music]
me no I'm dodging why am I dodging into
him
let's just let's just take it step by
step you can't go on
for he's not giving me a chance this is
giving me really hard PTSD right now I I
feel like I'm I'm remembering
something not PTC I mean
uh
vu saw that one
coming um I'm I'm
dying don't don't don't
don't what I'm
dying I can't dodg into
[Music]
restart the whole
mission is there any better way to do
this because I don't see
[Music]
how oh that
is extremely shitty that I have to redo
everything oh my God this game just has
no checkpoints that's so e
[Music]
what I don't
remember how is that
[Music]
there what
even when I damage him and small those
was like he got me so often and I was
really
trying
to be careful but that seems very
merciless
[Music]
what like there's no mercy to be
had why
that is honestly very very Maiden
[Music]
Behavior me
alone I don't want to wake up my cat
with my ice
screams I want my cat to be comfortable
in this
room do not make me
angry more than I
already
[Music]
please what was the was there something
here do I go right right right I should
be going right I'm pretty
sure I don't know if by going fast I'm
going to miss anything
that I got in the previous
attempt
whoa I hope
not careful pickax
[Music]
flying I hate
you why don't you just die
[Music]
an eye out for another bone there's
another bone well no the one bone was in
this room I think I don't think you can
get more than one bone in one level can
you where was the bone though a here
okay we will be needing
that let's after this so don't bother
pressing the Dodge button but he kept on
dodging into him I swear I was trying to
control away from
him I
[Music]
swear I
S did this one not do anything
[Music]
huh he too Happ to dodge just ran you
in no I don't think left and right
worked I was trying to go sideways I
swear it didn't work I don't know if
it's just
me or
what but surely we won't fail a second
time otherwise I'm going to rage
yellow
[Music]
M did you see
that I know it's just a wind here
[Music]
but that was weird
why did he
[Music]
slip the yellow ghosts are
awful
okay well if you say
[Music]
so it's never worth touching T in this
game I should play Atelier again where
it pays off to touch the
t t
true motion immediately
reacts motion's like I've been called
I've
been spoken
to oh hello where are you going don't
take my HP from me I hate
you well I guess I'll
die isn't this already the
room are we already there we
[Music]
are here goes nothing did I miss
something that I didn't get
[Music]
before okay let's let's try our best um
all right so this stuff doesn't work at
all anyway
huh didn't I get all of them at once
last time good
ow bad
start oh no
oh no no no no you're not you're not
going to play these games with I need my
thank
you oh my
God I was lucky when I got them all
three of them at once
previously we didn't play these games
last
time is there any way to get Hearts okay
ni I hate those
so let's go
run pull pull pull pull yummy see it
pulls me in 100% I was pulling away and
he pulls me
in this is unfair though how do I know
that that's coming is it because I'm too
close
[Music]
yeah that's going to hit me yeah no
choice I'm as SP as I can
[Music]
be it's definitely like less
chaotic still one of the shittiest
fights in this game uhoh
[Music]
uhoh oh I tried oh can I go no I wanted
to try why is this spider there for
hearts well thank you feel like I wasn't
getting any hearts in my previous run I
wonder
[Music]
why I don't know I got cocky just now
too
hard on of
here oh oh great oh great thanks for
that thanks for
[Music]
that one more one more a [\h__\h] hell
what about to
do absolutely hated that
thans
yeah but we didn't lose the bone that's
good I hope the others are not going to
be as uh obnoxious is that
all is that a is that a cover logo down
there I don't know if you're seeing what
I'm seeing
[Music]
we have to do two more of
these do we know where the other one is
they're on different
floors please tell me I just have to
follow this
[Music]
path m
okay up
[Music]
here got the blue triangle
oh we're in the right
room oh we know
huh you're going
[Music]
up oh this one has a red one
okay all to the m
[Music]
[\h__\h]
SC okay this one's like way more like
typical so thank God I don't know if he
does anything
special but I got this i got this oh
yeah another one baby come on come
on get a
full only three I had
an whatever whatever
whatever whatever oh
yeah [\h__\h] free kidding me what's next
B2
where
[Music]
where I at the
long
slide uh what's the fastest way to
go down
left down does go
[Music]
down wait or is
there cut through the outside I'm
confused
no
okay let's
go I
have an overview of the map at least I'm
looking at the map guys aren't you proud
instead of me wandering around being
like I don't know what to
go I didn't know where to
go help me
[Music]
J
what what what are they going to wait
for me on the other side
no why did they go there
[Music]
bro they've never done that
before Oh there's a
gem let's go
ooh should be proud of Cali kiata would
never do such a thing as looking at the
map on at the map she would never do
that uh wait just get to the end right
there's no no no particular path we have
to take I
[Music]
hope no no
no perhaps I hate this game as much as
it as hates
me thanks for that
tip it's like it's laughing at me
throwing those few coins at
[Music]
me it's like making fun of
me this is so mean is the door gone yeah
[Music]
look at him next time I don't think so
the golden spiders don't um show up
[Music]
anymore you think I can try again if I
use the portal I highly doubt it because
life is just not fair and it's not that
easy you can't just life doesn't give
you second tries
see only the golden ones are gone only
the golden ones are
gone I I I knew
it it's always like
that why are you
shaking why are you shaking
oh God that's
[Music]
scary I'm going to chop him up
again
[Music]
uh-oh well now he's not shaking
anymore good for
him more money
[Music]
right
um that was
ruthless is that the story oh oh dare
you I thought he would be in the next
room I was going to ask is that the
story from the new uh Game of Thrones
spin-up
no dunin
[Music]
Don oh stop it you
to stop it stop it
[Music]
oh no I wanted
the these are so much different from the
yellow
ones insult
give me the money give me the money give
me the money give me the money give me
the money give me the money give
[Music]
me
yellow the gold BS don't disappear
right
right close the [\h__\h] window it's cold
we're we're we're in the [\h__\h]
Antica it's no joke
[Music]
do you want to go for the
shop a faster way of getting to where we
want to go by any chance no
[Music]
right I don't know I'm just going to go
check cuz maybe there's some extra money
to be
earned oh what
[Music]
what do I
care no
[Music]
it's probably not work let's go
up let's go up I changed my
mind you doing good you all right are
you asking us cuz he just arrived or are
you asking cuz um you've been watching
for a while
and you noticed that the game is
damaging
me in my heart and my belief in
Humanity yeah you're just checking on my
mental thank you yeah this game
is this game is
evil it is beyond good and
evil not
true that game will never come back to
me
only oo
[Music]
gu I never found that
before so what where am I supposed to go
oh I'm on the right floor uh
[Music]
Right double streaming what do you
mean do you mean two streams per day
yeah I like to do that I'm Kori I am a
worker
coholic that's just what I
[Music]
do could go iing through both ways but
wait if I go up there does that make me
go a floor higher I don't
[Music]
understand is this the same
floor let's go
[Music]
I'm just so sick and
tired of all the Hat you
harb [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you very very much
[Music]
hey but are they hot right now they
don't look hot to
[Music]
me come
back I'm I sucked the fire oh there it
is fire fire suck the fire
how do
I
guys
um fire keeps on leaving
me just use the machine really oh is
there fire at the bottom of it
[Music]
okay sticks to it all
I did
it all
right what a fun machine what a weird
way of maintaining your
Gondola there must be a more less fun
more professional way of doing
[Music]
that someone just just got so bored of
their Gondola maintenance work that they
thought you know what M I'm just going
to make this into an FPS game game good
for you whoever was working here and
thought of
that
honestly smart smart way of
living
[Music]
smart got to find your way to make life
more more
delightful isn't that
right what do you want what do you want
what do you want you want beef
huh well I want
chicken oh hi
boo
um why is that Al
what hell what
the what the
hell it's exploding
there
H what's happening are these birds
endlessly spawning
how do I get
this
maybe does it
[Music]
just like that part is also still
icy the coal should have I don't think
it had that range but okay we can go
check it probably did it must
have is that an out house over
there King Boo's out housee yeah
oh good night sleep well thank you for
watching for so
long oh I thought I couldn't move it a
[\h__\h] what is this for like why are we oh
oh it leads us to the out house when we
get the tree to fall
over oh oh my
God a whole extra
path all right is that
[Music]
it I would say
so unlocked idle meetings the new
possibilities
yes going to idle meetings in the middle
of the Stream
finally it is possible now all I was
lacking is the room for it thanks for
the
[Music]
memberships all right let's check that
out first I'm guessing it gives me
um another
gem oh no it's an extra world oh what
the hell this one's
different I'm going to fail I'm going to
fail what no way no
what what what what
h
no no I'm I'm
[Music]
no no this this
sucks no what the
hell can I get yours
no no this is so
[Music]
mean it's so slow in giving me my balls
back
too I finally got one that's it all I
need is one no need more for
sure no what the the aim of the socks
and then there not giving me the
ball
[Music]
so
oh can I try again come on
[Music]
is this game for
real I really am in total disbelief
leave I mean maybe I come by here again
and then I can do it but like what the
[Music]
hell I I mean I understand that you just
get one chance I assumed as much and I I
get it but then the game is just really
not game like the the maze ones are fine
but this one at least give me like like
a little pile of balls so I can always
grab them and then if I don't know if
it's just me but I think the the the the
the the aim locks
in so rarely like it's really hard to
get the aim the target to show up and if
you just shoot it's never going to hit
unless you have the target show up but
it's so hard to get the target to show
up and by the time the enemy is already
gone mostly the
time so that's a really bad idea for a
mini game with such time limit and such
a
reward oh that sucks can I jump over or
how this is
working how do I get
the oh I can't oh I see oh that's why
there is endless
Birds I get it now
yo yo why is it always so
tight yeah really poorly
made
Luigi I don't know if I ever want to
play this game anymore this is such a
mean I'm having such a mean time today
like I don't know about it anymore
either like I'm I'm I'm I'm
starting motion controls when I'm
literally not moving the controller like
you should just be going straight bro
bro straight
[Music]
I'm so close to finishing it at this
point I think only like one more part
probably so I don't want to give up
but I feel like it's so
disrespectful no don't go I didn't think
you would do that I thought you would
touch the
camera it's just not treating me well
what are these gold cookies
[Music]
Yello mhm n it's fine it's just
unbelievably shitty like I'm not like
it's
it's mhm it just feels like a cluster
[\h__\h] of uh shitty things happening in
the game today
[Music]
just unusual surely it won't happen
again surely the game will redeem itself
and treat me more
fairly I got to give it the benefit of
the
doubt
mhm mhm
[Music]
what is
this what is this
oh why would I do that
[Music]
huh ah I get it was this
like um what's it called the windows
game that we don't get on Windows
anymore like now it's stuck in there but
if I awaken it won't it come towards
me no okay yeah
[Music]
pinball B this
now uh wait oh oh that's fine okay cuz
we're going to un I
[Music]
it
wonderful
mhm oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] oopsie I got the wrong order
suck shoot
[Music]
activate it was from
moxis D
[Music]
moxis yeah this is pinball
so there's one more icy area there
but I
can can I can I get there directly let's
[Music]
see ah no okay so maybe if I shoot this
one
again yes it I have created a
[Music]
path stay
down so and
then that's all you wanted me to
do why does it sound like pirate
[Music]
mus y b too many explosions
on the mountain yeah really not like
what is this for what is the
point why why would anybody create this
this is very dangerous if you think
about
it oh [\h__\h]
uh-oh time to get out my snowboard oh oh
[\h__\h] we're snowed in how romantic
[Music]
yell too many explosives
careful yeah being snowed in is
[Music]
romantic I'll get you out of there okay
you will not want to you will want to
warm up before facing the possessor
anyways hold on to your hat oh what
after all of that work you just going to
teleport me out of there how antil
climatic
it's going to be a shitty time too and
shitty
[Music]
GRS such an ungrateful game
[Applause]
I have enough of your [\h__\h]
chaas if you really want to dance Chacha
go to a dance class I'm I'm done I'm
done with
you you and your shenanigans you're
doing all of this just torture me you
are The Mastermind behind all of this
not [\h__\h] King Boo Boos are great Boos
are not evil you're evil you g it's all
your Works isn't
[Music]
it how
many
more uh do they all have the same amount
of like levels within a level
[Music]
or is this the end for this
one this boss isn't easy well no
surprise with that shitty fat yellow
ghost being involved in this
Mansion okay this is short well then we
should just [\h__\h] finish
it like I mean the the Mansion is short
so we this is the boss fight if that's
the end
then
[Music]
oh what was is there two
more is this the
boss then I want to do it I just want to
finish it just this boss is really bad
well see like it seems like I kind of do
better with bosses than with normal
fights
so I can say one thing for sure there're
SM than AR ghost they're clearly the
most powerful ghost in the valley
wonder you're not giving me any good
hints for the boss fight
I hope you have good aim
no well we we know I clearly don't
because the aiming functionality in this
game is not very
good not very well thought
through oh you teleported me here wow
what a
service I did not expect
this it's all iced up isn't it
[Music]
okay well then do we get straight to the
BS usually more or less that's the
case but wait I don't have a bone do I
still get a
[Music]
bone h
I don't get a [\h__\h]
Zone we doing it
here Sky
no no it's not like that oh that's fun
wait that's fun that looks oh
wa oh [\h__\h] how do I shoot I forgot ah
there we go now we're shoting oh wait
this is
fun oh that's so
fun oh that is extremely
fun I don't even mind if you
Misses oh there we
go it's
just I feel like you could
probably figure this out without trying
to get lucky a million times but hey hey
hey hey
hey would you look at that oh you want
to eat eat some bombs you
[\h__\h] was this a difficult part
or
what that was hell fun that was so much
better than the other FPS
[\h__\h] okay he's going to he's going to
yeah he's going to do that again oh he's
got p th oh that's not
fair if
that come you guys say it's
difficult can we go again can we go for
another
ride yeah let's
go oh yeah we're repeating
it go on your SL I am Santa Claus
okay how do I shoot I forgot it's not
working yet
okay another one
woohoo the aim is
insane no aim No Gain No aim no
pain okay have time interesting have to
maybe aim higher this
time oh wow I got the middle one
early early early early
early come on come
on I see I see I
see I see I see I
see now I should I should wait I should
be patient I almost had it okay now
[Music]
CL
difficult I got too excited so I spammed
a few ones but that was great and the
same thing again I know this part from
the previous fights we had of this guy
goes for the portal though now that's a
little bit
sucks I don't like your new tricks my
friends also there's a s slope in the
middle I see
hey lost no HP but I'll take those Cs
and here we go
again here we go again yeah good
prediction right I predicted where he
was going to show
up and the third time all right all
right all right let me shoot let me
shoot up
up when we're so close it's actually uh
much easier so we want to spam as much
as we can
Bounce Bounce Bounce It Off yeah
oh I'm just [\h__\h]
[Music]
lucky
boy no that's rough that's rough that's
rough oh ah so
close ah so close so close come on come
on ah so close
close how about aim higher I don't
know what that was so
close am I Santa Claus because I'm
[\h__\h] close to [\h__\h] this whole time is
there oh oh he ah he's going back to the
beginning fin maybe we'll have a lucky
run sick you see that rotation
baby we like to stay ooh a little
failure wa my aim my
aim oh we can Bounce It Up that side too
I never thought about
it
hey where did my lck go oh smovie good
morning you decided to finally wake up
hello
hello this game really hates you but I'm
still having fun okay I like this BX
fight I have no problem with it can we
try to aim like
higher the middle one is hard to get I
had a lot of Lucky attempts
before Oh
no finally that let's get the middle one
flow right in front of
it get up there get up
there is my thing like about to explode
like keep overheating should I wait
wait why is it so
red am I going to get blown
up oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
no that's not
good Lucky
Strike is is there any way to calm it
down O Come
on a come on
oh
no do I just fight the boss one more
time then finally
me
oh ah that that was that would have been
a good ride but I'm going to be blown
up oh no is it a failure a whole Foss
fight failure no
[Applause]
way ridiculous
that's the part people don't like I see
but it seems like very manageable though
I had so many lucky attempts where I
cleared it rather
[Music]
fast come on let me
in is it is it really like weirdly more
difficult than the last one because it
didn't look different to me
but I I got the hits uh less
often oh oh okay yeah the middle part
here is just one pie I guess this gets
more and
moreit I didn't notice that at
all I was just chilling look at me look
at her
go that
was not
[Music]
M let's go for straight one there we go
there we
[Music]
go good night thank you for watching oh
well sorry I didn't I was watching that
chat no I thought it was over I thought
we were already leaving
this I was
relaxing now it's not the time
she said Focus kak
Ki
uhoh come on get that
one no that's
not
come I'm over eating
again
yes one eat once you
[Music]
go see you
again in a hot
minute thank you for the fun stream
everybody's leaving where you guys going
[Music]
round
two
[Music]
H now it's twoo far in the
middle very simple still the hit box is
pretty generous there you're not
generous like that more
often early
[Music]
come on come
on okay rip them rip them
[Music]
early that quite right quite
right what why would you do that why
would you do that why would you do that
you little [\h__\h]
hey [\h__\h] is your problem
[Music]
me try now
fun that's
fun
[Music]
yeah the first time I played this I was
not really thinking much about the
placement now that I know about the
overheating I am but at the same time he
cools
down faster than I thought
oh okay middle one is hard though
no I need to get the middle one while
I'm still
close there we
go then it's way easier now I have the
problem of impending
doom oh nice
one
uh-oh
[Music]
uh-oh come on come on
yeah how many more hits do I get there
should be still a
couple please please please please
please please oh so
close come on
and one more in one more in one more
[Music]
yes no it's nice challenge I like the
challenge it's a good challenge I must
say a little perhaps a little bit
too tight
there especially when you're in the last
one and you're like so
far where did my hearts go bro where oh
I got scammed guys once
again
unbelievable oh
yeah this game has it out for
me okay try to get the middle
[Music]
one yeah that's okay I prefer middle one
this one definitely
h i see pineapple FES guys I'm seeing
pineapple
[Music]
slies scam
no
no is he about
[Music]
toity
aity can't to the middle ones it's
bad it's really bad
I'm getting
dizzy I couldn't I can roll pretty low
this is like Bing alley
style I'm overheating
soon I see I see what the rage is all
about I
[Applause]
know he's probably going to re reeree
soon as well
that's I'm I'm too late
ah nah okay I prefer I think I prefer
this but I'm going
[Music]
to
good ah I wanted the middle
one
go oh I got
it I don't know where to go
no it's going to [\h__\h] me over it's going
to [\h__\h] me over
[Music]
guys oh it's so slow when it's down
there
oh no he's no no no no no no no no no no
no [\h__\h]
okay okay you're losing me you're losing
me I have to redo the whole fight again
it seem because I don't have
[Music]
enough oh okay you can't even say you
can't even argue that I'm bad at this
because I'm actually pretty good at
[Music]
it
is that is a yikes
bro a big oh okay
oh you you get good
job I was like doing this really
aimlessly in the beginning and it still
went so
well you don't necessarily do much
better I guess if you try
harder no but you you
Pro are you for real that never happened
before where the [\h__\h] did the bomb go
okay I get it I get it I'm oh my
God oh my
God I'm overheating
[Music]
already oh that's surprising
I don't know like the more I do it I
no I'm failing the first
run you kidding
me I can still get it
[Music]
possibly only if every [\h__\h] bomb hits
doesn't look
like there it goes it's not even it just
now it seemed like it's not the amount
of or is it I don't know cuz now it felt
like
time it feels
like not the amount of
[Music]
boms did you just say aiming helps
I am Mory Ki right now I can reap you be
careful with what you
say it's time based huh okay well the
first the first round really should be
faster I actually had
[Music]
it exactly this boss had quit playing
for like 6 months no way
if they only had made it like slightly
like was this also so difficult on the
PS cuz then they had a chance to improve
it or did it just get this shitty on the
switch
[Music]
no go go go go go
go
you [\h__\h] was about to scan me
again bro bro bro
I can't take it
anymore I can't take it
[Music]
anymore if this isn't to run then I
don't know
man going to get like kind
of frustrating
go go go go go go go
go go for the middle
yes how dare
[Music]
you I'm too too
late H too early
[Music]
[Applause]
close no okay wait
[Music]
wait don't scam me don't scam
me don't scam me don't SC me
[Music]
m
m this is never the
problem it's really just kind
of I I do think to an extent like you
can't 100% aim it like and it's not
really luck based but at the same time
[Music]
like I don't think it's quite related to
skill
either maybe is but like how much would
you have to play this in order for it
to be resolved by skill oh I got the
mini one this is good this is
good this is good don't [\h__\h] me over
don't [\h__\h] me over I will never play
this game
is this early
enough maybe
lower uhoh oh he's [\h__\h] me
[Music]
over I'm sorry I'm sorry no you me over
okay chill
relax I want me I'm stupid I'm stup
bit I almost had
this
bounc a that's
bad
bounce ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
me dangerous levels dangerous levels
dangerous levels dangerous levels no no
unbelievable
unbelievable how early BR too [\h__\h]
early who do you think I am I'm European
I don't grow up with
guns can't shoot that
well
bro this is not
cool give it a bit of a no okay I got to
spam because it's it's time it's time
not about the bombs it's about the time
oh [\h__\h] I'm going to
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no it was going to blow up on me
probably when he opens his mouth there's
chance that it could have blown up on me
even though I was already
done oh my
God oh
[Music]
my I I I have I have no
words I have no words
guys I am
so
angry I am baffled by the
oh unfairness of this
[Music]
game the the absolute clutch that you
need for
this yellow I want to watch Dum tendo go
through this [\h__\h] but he'll probably
rock it
[Music]
like good at this
[\h__\h] I
am I just want to end the stream now I'm
like I'm glad I made it but that's so
[\h__\h] it was fun but they ruined it you
remember how happy I was even after the
second try or so but they ruined it for
themselves it I I
mean they could have if this was the
same in BS they could have totally gave
it like a few more like two more seconds
before ice is up even two more seconds
would have been
sweet M
Mia you guys
saw what like you you witnessed it you
witnessed this
[Music]
I can't believe it shut up I don't want
to I don't want to leave this game [\h__\h]
off [\h__\h] off go away leave me alone
leave me alone leave me alone leave me
alone leave me
alone is it saved it better be
[Music]
safe I'm honestly going to
go my voice hurts from screaming today
this game made me rage so much
thank you shut
up I'm
angry why why you going to feel like
[Music]
that this
stupid yeah peace out man
[Music]
like ah thanks dead beats for watching
people who joined Midway for don't
understand why I'm saying these words uh
[Music]
peace see you tomorrow
man
[\h__\h] what was
[Music]
that well don't worry I had fun and just
baffled
bro I'll V the
piece I be
[Music]
PE well I guess the the amount of time
you spend with the
[Music]
boss maybe they maybe that's why they
made so few
levels the like you spending the time
you would spend on two levels in one
boss okay not even not even
[Music]
but my
busted don't bust the M oh M don't do
it next level is
harder I'mma drop this game I'm about to
drop this [\h__\h] game
[Music]
uh okay sorry too t
what is cie
streaming what why would she stream at
this
time you're saying raid cie I am cie
what are you talking
[Music]
about oh but hey uh I'm Celly but
there's an orange person surely that is
takanasi Ki let's raid her she's about
to
start that should that should be uh that
should be
her you guys are very confused I I'll
help you find the orange
one I'll lend you a
hand God my throat
hurts I was supposed to record some more
[Music]
singing I don't think I can do it thank
you guys so much for
watching I love you
guys thank you Luigi why do you hate me
honestly hate you
too damn it