[Music]
Ko
De
[Music]
DET
De
[Music]
Hahahaha Oh, he's a teacher, he's a teacher, he's
not a teacher, but hey, I just happened to be here.
Hello, everyone.  Are you
all gathered together? Everyone is alright with Masukane-chan right now. Is that
true? Please, please, sensei, please take attendance.
Oh, I'll go. Then, I'll go from the white group's
A. Eiroha-chan, I'm
hungry. Please.
Nera-senpai, hello
too. Thank you very much for your support. I'm here, Nekanata-
san. Ha-ha-myself, my-mei-chan, my-mei-chan, my-mei-chan. Hello,
too. [Music] That kind of candy, me-chan.  Ame-chan,
Ame-chan, yay, I'm here. Hey, I'm here
. Hey,
hello. Thank you.
Thank you. This member is on the phone.  We
are the people who will break up and become A. Yes,
yes. Then, B's Choco-sensei, I
'm here. Zu-chan is here.
Please, please, Captain. Hello, Captain.
Hello, hello. [Music] Da yes, yes,
yes.  Yes, I tried my best at Hollow Up, and I
kept looking at it, and I was like, ``
Well, I wonder if it's okay to do this here,
or if I should go.'' Yes,
that day, it's Lale-chan.  I'm
sorry for being a little
confused by you.  We would
also like to cover your trip a little bit,
so please take care of it.Everyone, it seems like
you and your seniors have lost your horses,
so I'm off to Holomen hunting and Raden.  I'm
going to appear
in your place, but I'll
take your place. Thank you very much.  I'm looking
forward to it.
Will Kanata be wandering around alone? I
wonder if someone will come. Yes, I
want to see her working hard all by herself. She's wandering around alone.  He
might be filming everyone.
He might be saying, ``Oh, do your best, hit me, hit me.'' There's a spy here. What's a spy? No, it's like a spy. And there's Matsuri-senpai. Oh, he's telling me to go away.
In the white group's waiting room.It's a classroom.Here
everyone is waiting.Okay, so the competition is
good.Who's here
?That's right, everyone's gathered here.Okay, good, good, good,
good, good, everyone's here.  hand
Oh,
there's a signboard
here. Where can I use this? But where
can I use it? I can't place it.
[Music] Is
this what it means
? How do I use it? I'm holding a signboard with both hands.  It looks
like he's holding a sign.
That's the only way to do it. It's loud.
[Music]
Hey, Polo came to scout. Everyone's here.
Hey, the scout group is coming tomorrow.  I think we
should go scouting somewhere else.Which
one of the Red Teams are we going to scout?I
wonder how all the Reds are feeling right now.No
one's here.
[Laughs]It's
starting to get really bad.The
rigros and others were having a lot of fun with each other.
Hey, I
can't get the signboard I'm holding in my left hand anymore, but it might have been on all day today,
but I
can't get it anymore.  I
'm glad I couldn't get it, but I don't have it. It's true, but it's dangerous for everyone. Seriously, it's too much, but will it be okay to take it in a competition? No, maybe I'll be able to reset my things. Yeah, yeah, maybe when I'm infected, I'll be on the left side all the time.
As expected of a knowledgeable person,
Minecraft. As expected of one of the creators of Minecraft, that's
true again. I'll debug it. Good luck
this time as well, as the bomber of the MacLeod Society.  It's
amazing, because you can tell me everything. I
wonder if the author didn't have any intrusions.
No, it's true. It's
true. Is it true? Is it true that Minecraft produced it? That's
amazing.
[Music]  I ca
n't understand it, but I can't understand it
. We don't really understand cameras,
but I can hear it. I can hear it. It sounds
like Subaru-senpai's voice.
But I'm sure it wasn't a misunderstanding.I
heard it.Alright then, I'm going to call out to you.I
think I'll go.Well then, everyone, I'm
very well invited.Thank you very much.Entrance has
begun.Entrance is the entrance announcement.Entrance.Everyone who
came.  It's not red, so I'm
going. It's white. It's white. Merurumeme is red.
Meme
[Music] It's
over there, it's over there. It's
falling down.
[Music]
Now, you're a genius! The red ones are lined up, the
white ones are lined up, the white ones are lined up, and the
first one is mom, koyoko. Nico,
11th row. Okay. Next,
everyone from the white group, please come in.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes.
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes, that's the white of power, that's great. Lastly,
can I get a compliment from that yellow group? That's
okay, Kashi-chan, you're hiding.
[Laughs] The
camera is on you too.
Please keep your eyes peeled.
Why are the lines so beautiful? The white group
is so beautiful. Let's go with the serious frame. I'll
win with the serious frame. I'm just holding a pink signboard. Oh, it's
true. They put together a yellow board.
Is that what you mean?  There aren't
any white boards or even signboards.So
first of all, I would like to ask the members of the Hololive Great Movement to
give their greetings for the convention.Hello
everyone.
Nya, thank you so much for coming together. It's
been a lot of fun. I
'm sure the seniors and juniors have helped each other, and they've all worked hard in practice up until today, but today
is the real thing, so I hope everyone will give it their all and
come out victorious.
First of all, everyone should have fun,
and then aim to win. I hope
you all enjoy yourselves.
Thank you very much for your support today. Please,
please, please. Thank you very much.
Yes, we have received a message from the president of Cover Co., Ltd. [Music] Click here to see the message. Yes,
please take a look. Thank you for your hard work. This
is our representative, Luck. Speaking of sports day, it's gymnastics. It's
not in Neyapura.
Thank you very much for your support. Let's cooperate with each other and do our best until the end at today's sports day.
Please pay attention to and support everyone's hard work.  I
would appreciate it if
you could please take care of yourself, Mamoru, and all the members.Here,
I will start the meeting with you.This must
be a mental injury.The
principal, you are injured.You are
fighting with your hands.
Thank you for the channel 1,
Mr. Masu Te, I'm going to
go. Please do your best, please do your best.
Good luck. I'm the
most serious in the serious category. Chan,
yes, please. Thank you
.  Please
do your
best.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much
.  [Music]
[Laughter] I
wonder if I'll be able to do it Hashasukamonkamonhashashashassu
Good, good, I
think I'll do my best, teacher.Good luck.  Is
that okay?
Yes, please.Yes,
please.As members of Hololive, all of us players will practice
sportsmanship as members of the Hololive.
Group representative, yellow representative, Bells
Ye
[Music]
[Applause]
Okay, I'm sorry to hear that.
Thank you for shining in our house
[Music]
Special Please excuse me,
all the contestants channel of the white group, please go to the channel of the contestants of the white group.The
sound quality of Ria's sports day.The
sound quality is a little off.  I wonder if the real Kia
is round 2, so I'm
still wondering what the channels are like. Is it the
first round of hunting
? Only people like that are like that.  I'm going to
go to the white group contestant's channel, so I'm going to
go to the Ame-chan Kaneri, hi, hi, hello, do your best, layer team fight,
player channel
[Music] Do your
best, do
your best, do your
best, gluck, gdruck, gdruck,
totally.
Good Luck is good, it's perfect.
That's Kaela, the third person. Yes, that's right. It's
Kaela. It's
good.
[Music]
H
Hellouptoyouguys
PleasecarryThe
Gdoit
doTeamWhiteTeamYes
TeamI
[Music]
NEXTAll
HUNTING
righthandhaveleash
ofCAPhave
onokWewill
WIN
wehaveKNoNoNo
PleasenejnejnejIbea
sweatygamerTooLate
iepneedtobe
competitiveTry
Yes happen rightrightI
think
okayWhereismyMy
teammates
shouldwegoinNoright
okayfineJANOT
SURE
mckon
the
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello,
here, here, here, here, right here, here, right here, right here, right here,
right here, right? The white team contestants, right? Now, the fugitives who run away have become this
channel. It's the
opposite. It's difficult, it's difficult, it's difficult today, it's difficult
today, this practice is difficult.
This is the number one thing I wanted to do.The number one thing I wanted to do.The
number one thing I wanted to do.The number one thing I wanted to do, but I
couldn't do.  It's
true that if you overcome this and that, you can do it.Okay, well,
please try your best.Yes,
at first, the red team is the hunter, and the white group
all run away.Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, everyone is a contestant.  Yes, that
's right, that's what it means,
right? It seems like you can catch an infected person when it's white.
Oh,
All
[Music]
has only hunters
,
yes,
yes, yes, yes,
hello, hello. Are you
readyIam
readywelljust
Again?
[Music]
mayun
I are
you
running
aroundThankyoufor
lettingMeOnYourHead
earlierNoProblemI
appreciated that
Prezia Mizuo Senpai
Mizuo Senpai Kyuri Kyuba
Kyu
IstuffWhatstuffI
[Music]
know
think
damagemygodIeven
Stuff
inventory
lely
M
SKY
ClearBeautiful
Day
people
REGismy
nameEnglishNonot
[Laughs]
iun
okayNoyouneedto
saveyougetStuckOn TheSpider
WebDirtyPlayDirty
TrickNo
No
Sorry
noAllTheEnglish
members
White
WOWDETMarewe
supposedtobeplaying
inHereIguesswejust
separWeGbe
[Music]
doingI
think
throwSHCanweBreakOut
anywaycanotIthink
H
No
komWhyareyouare
youI
[music]
know to
protect
to
[music]
time
thisCageCagethis
CageM
crampedokayFIVE F
Onenice
okay
allthat
means
ME
OUT
pleasLetMeOut crackle
crackle
free
USNowYELLisitor
WhiteWhiteIthink
afterthis
WeYesbewhiteand
Y
should be given
No, I'm sure you're working hard. The bonus is right.
Yes, it's right. It's nice. It's nice.
Oh, it's interesting. I'm enjoying it.
Catch the Goal Live English. I do
n't think it will come out again. I'm sure, but the
same thing won't come out twice or three times in
Indonesia.  I'm sure it's possible that there will be something like "catch me",
but it's also possible that there will be tall people.To be honest, I
don't even remember tall people.
I guess I'll have to bring someone with a certain height, because there aren't many people over 160cm.
Hololive is
pretty small, so I guess it's small, so I
wonder what's going to happen. 149 is a slightly nice lie. It's following me, isn't it
?  The most common
players are in their 150s, so I
would like to interview everyone from the white team.
Kaela and A are the three good Umi members.
Yes, I'd like to ask you, the second
time hunter.
Ah, I'll also introduce the second time hunter. Yes,
Captain Noel, Kiwa, and
Kanata.
Yes, that's why everyone from the white group, players, can you
hear me? I can
hear you. Yes, yes, how are you doing?
We have a strategy and a
strategy. Well, we'll catch everyone for now. I see. It's our second match.
Well, I'm going to catch it now, and I
'm hoping that I'll be able to get it before someone wins.As the money decreases, I'll have too much money.That's
power, too.It's quite surprising.I'll
get through it with power.  Okay,
what do you think when you saw the topic earlier?
I thought, oh, what about my senpai? It
was about who is the cute member that Mimio-senpai would want to protect?
But yeah, that's right, I'm included.  I'm
sorry, Nemio-senpai, no, I don't know about that. I wonder if it's small. I'm having trouble. I wonder if that's the continuation. I believe in this, so I believe in it. So it's
strange. Yes, please do your best. Do
your best. Yes, I'm here.
Also,
yes, who is doing the voice?
But yes, thank you very much.
So, everyone, please stand by.
So, all you
have to do is enter.
In any case, it was my 1000th person to
watch. I guess I was embarrassed. I'm
sorry, Mr. Noil,
but Mr. Kia, please
go back to the original channel, ABB's channel.
I'm sorry, it's okay, please do your best, and I'll
be happy to
help you.
inaJELLYlike
substance
GOacrossICEand
SN
[laughing]
PRTeam
GO
JELLYIwanttoeat
itonethank
[music]
youy
Ilike
[music]
that
IsAlwaysGood
Ideas
[laughing]
youVOICESJUMPJA
JUMPSpace
BARDET
okay
SHIknow
[music]
Times
okayKill
DIS
[music]
ONE
IR
outfit
shortThis
Man
thishaveshorthair
right
nicenice
[music]
[Music]
ikke
min
[Laughter]
JA
But actually, that strategy was power, right
? It was power to capture everyone. Is that a strategy
? No, I don't like it, but it
might work. I see.
Now, let's go to the interview.
To everyone in white, yes.  Hello, hello, everyone in the white team, try it Hello,
hello,
hello, it was difficult
Difficult, it's all difficult, it's
difficult, it's difficult, you know, if you touch the signboard, touch the signboard, OK, OK, touch the
signboard, OK, OK, you got it,
Holo Kids, Hololive, Kids Holo,
Kids, Difficult Beginning Holo.
Kids Hame Holo Kids Sususu
Hajime Holo Kids Oh Holo Kids Festival
Hane Ero Ga
Matsuri wa Nokino Kids I
thought the shrine maiden had a bit of an older sister feel,
but it seems to be
gross.  That
was a nice fight,
thank you, yes, thank
you, yes, thank you, yes, please do your
best.The white team
was able to catch two people.PRjust
Mariho What is this?Emari
Oki what
see
seeneedcckthesign
AgainI
Thinkfor
yokalso
even
[music]
wor
prut
ONEJAbutsaidThatShe
wasconsideredshort
butI
is
shortthingisIknow
arewetalking
aboutdefaultoneor
non
timemaybe
maybe well, well
[music]
Well, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, no
problem to no problem.  Please come
out, please come out.
Look, there are some people who look so pitiful like this. What's
going on? I
couldn't go anywhere. What's the situation? I really
want to do this. I open this door. I
shut it right away. There's something in there. The
eyes of the door are closed.  I'll do this right in front of the door that's in front of me.It's so nice to be able to
enter it.Live,
live.No
, it's nice.It smells like earth.It smells like
earth.It smells like earth.  That's
what I'm saying, if
you turn it off, it's
a bit heavy, isn't it?
The contact is too cerebral. It
's so cute when you're lying on your side. It's so cute. It's so cute
when you put it upright.
Oh, it's so cute. It's so
cute. It's so cute. You
can sell cushions just like
this. It's true. It's so cute. Even though it's so cute, it's still
sold. It's so cute.  I
can't
afford to be smart, yellow, yellow, yellow, yellow, let's run away, I'll do my best,
I'll run away,
I'll run away
[Music] I
want to go to Korea, but no, no, no, no,
no, only fugitives, only fugitives, touch
I've
already entered an entry for the fugitive. I
think I've already entered it.  I'm a newcomer, I'm a newcomer.
[Music] [Music] I'm a newcomer. I'm a newcomer. I'm a newcomer. [Music] [
Music]
160 Gon Sai I'm here. I
'm 6. Catch me. I'm totally going through the motions.  That's what
happened to me. There's no way that could happen. Wait a minute. The
leader was arrested, but wait, the leader.
158 I'm a little sorry. Is
it your aura? It's safe. It's okay.
Hide it. Hide it. Chocolate.
165 That's right, hide it, hide it,
I'm the one
in charge. I'm the one who's in charge. I'm the one who
caught it once and then caught it again.
[Music] I'm
sure no one will catch me.  [
Music]
If you're polite and polite,
then whatever you do, you're polite.
All kinds of complaints are happening, and bad things are happening, too.
Yeah nice old man nice Ajie didn't get caught Zunezu Gem-chan and Geya But it's true that Azu-san is definitely a member, she's included, right? She ran away. It's cute that she's a little more self-aware. No, that's it.  Kane,
you're so cute, it's scary. You're so neat. You're absolutely neat.
Absolutely neat. That's great. You should run away. You're
cute, Airoha-chan. You should run away too.  It's no
good, I don't think they'll get caught even though it's neat.Yellow was really strong.I
caught about 100 yellow, but it was terrible.It was
amazing.It was
n't a battle for leader, it was just one more run away.Ah, I'm
able to enter.Everyone did
this.
Ranran
2 I
ran away, ran away, ran away.
When I was a big sister, I was the ringleader
[music]
and a woman who had the personality to be a big sister. It
doesn't matter, I wanted to be chosen. Please don't say that.  It's
true that my height wasn't chosen properly,
but it's because
Polka misunderstood me that I
was able to get a little closer to the cage.It
's really narrow.  Well, I don't like
it. Once you're caught, you
can't run away during the game, right?
During the Hunter game, well, until the next game.
[Music] Do your
best for the rest of the game and run away.  different
Who's going to think that? Even Mia thought for a moment,
right? That's right.
There's a possibility that something like that or something like that will change, but no, there's a completely different possibility.
If you do that, you'll
want to be protected.
But no,
no, no, no, everyone's sitting in between me, I
can't help but stare
at them, it's so cute It's so cute that
they're standing next to each other It's cute Hey, someone please line up next
to me Oh, it's like that
Reset, the
reset begins
Oh, I'm already done  Do it once again and try again again Kaooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Wow, it doesn't matter at all, but Subaru-senpai
's nipples are missing. He's
got them.
[Music] We went
out of our way to chat, and Subaru-senpai asked me
how many nipples he had, and asked me how many nipples he had. It's
2, actually 2.  Well, it's not because birds
are eggs, it's because they've
become something of a specialty,
but I wonder if it's a bird. I'm lonely. What's that? It
debuted in 2019.
[Music]
It's been a long time since I've entered the year. I'm not safe. [Music] I'm not safe from 2019. Please run away from 2019.  I was able to run away.
This is bad. This
is bad. But run now. Run away. Run away. Run away. There are a lot of
artists who were moving at a frightening speed.
Artist
Ashi
Oh yeah, I
had the impression that there were more than 3 stations, and I had the impression that she was putting out quite a lot of
music. She's putting out Alm albums. It's not a
private station. No, no. The king was arrested by the police and
was interrogated.
That's the kind of person he is.  It's
not Ronnie, it's someone else. I've
been arrested since I was arrested. I
don't remember being arrested at all.
Surprisingly, I haven't been arrested yet. I've been so
busy.
[Music] It
fit the title, but I ran away.
[Music]
Great.
Han, please
move the rest.
Understood, do your best,
bye-bye, do your best. Alright, you
made it. Yumata got caught, got caught, got
caught again.  It's because it's illegal. They're
going to arrest me. It's South Korea. It's South Korea. It's a country. I'll
give you this too.
Where are you looking right now?  I'm
giving me to the one who is caught by the way I know I
'm giving me this. I'll give you this.
This is a great surreal that the candy tscott gave me,
but this
feeling Noel Senior has a great lighting photography feeling.  But
yeah, I
see, I won a lot. This
is a shot of me eating. I
want you to do your best in the second race. Do your
best. Let's support each other and support you a lot.
Kia
Hold on, you're in trouble! Wait, wait, I accidentally fired the drug.
Wait a minute. The mouse is
drenched. What's the situation? Why did you
just use the disinfectant? You accidentally fired the
disinfectant. The mouse is all wet. The
mouse is alive. It's dangerous.
Yeah, I was just stroking
it. I was stroking it. I was
stroking it and it hit me.
[Laughter]
Hey.  It's
cute, it's looking down, it's looking down, it's
moving, it's moving, it's moving, it's cute, it's so
cute, it's so cute, it's so cute, it's so cute, it's so cute, it's so
cute, it's so cute.
When I woke up, it was written that I was an engineer, and that I had
just entered an entry for the fugitive. ``You're the one who gets
taken away and disappears.'' Stay strong, do your best, and a
dangerous white brawl has begun.''  I didn't
realize there was a book in there.The
one by Subarzo was taken away.
Was it the sound of you?
Or maybe it was just taken away.
Well, it's starting, it's starting. I wonder if it's going to start. I
wonder if it's going to start.  150 to
150 There are a lot of people, don't you think? Just
go ahead and catch them all.  I'm
hiding here, I'm
hiding here [Music] I can't fit in if it's really in the corner It's
really hidden in the corner If it's not
what I expected
, I'll lose It looks expensive,
right?
Okay, whoever's behind me, catch me!
[Music] It's
too early, Moko-chan, come on, come on, come
on, Moko-san, I'm catching you.  I ca
n't see Be-chan's name.
Naekari-chan is expensive, isn't it? It's expensive,
isn't it?
Unfuaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I
wonder if those ears are plugged in.
Well, I guess that's right. Is it just ears? Yes, that's
right, Fana-senpai's horns
aren't that funny.  It's not
bad, it's okay, everyone,
catch it.
Hey, let's
go. He's gone now. No,
Mel-chan is only a blur. Mel-chan is right.
He's wrong, he's wrong.
He's in the red room here.  You're
trying your best, you're so nice.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. You've
secured a place close to nice. It's a very Korean gig.
There's a record. There's a record. A
record. It's really, really hard. It's amazing. The next one won't be 2.  Kaya
Karawa Ayoshi Nice Nice Ah Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice To Get in the
Way Please Go Away
[Music]  Hahahaha
Ah,
wow,
what happened earlier? Wait a minute, Choco-sensei
's photo is too good.
[Laughs] I
just took this. I'm
going to send it to Yatsuba. It's
too much. Ah,
where is
it? Ah, I'm going to work.  It was really good. The smoke
was really thick. I caught a lot of it at the end.
Yeah, it was mostly blurry at the end. Most of it was
just floating.  I don't think I'm
surprised at how many seniors look at my ears, but I don't have the impression that I'm surprised at all.But
I guess that's how it is.Everyone
in charge is so stupid.They don't get too much attention.Ah,
maybe that's how it is.  No, but when it comes
to beauty judging, there are a lot of people who are pretty dumb,
right? That's right, Mio-chan, Kamio-chan,
of course.
Yeah, I'm sure I
managed to run away. If you
ask me, I'll help you, run away, run
away, run away, do your best, do your best, you'll love it.
[Music]
Keo, after all, it
was a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered in places. Hey, it's
dangerous. Hide it.
Hide it.  Hide it, hide it,
someone got caught,
but hide it,
hide it, it's about 0 to 2 years old,
that's right, 4 years too
.
[Music]
Oh, I got caught, oh, I got caught, I got caught
. I'm
trying to hide
my
hair. It's not my hair. It's
erotic. It's
red. I protect it a lot. It's true. I
have silver hair.
[Music] It was the
same. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry.
[Music]  ] It's a
shame that I have free time. I have so much free time.
I'm in
trouble. You can catch me. There
's a chance here.
Please, please, please, I, I, I, I, I,
completely
ignore you, why didn't
you do anything? My name is Matsuri-senpai, Matsuri-senpai, Matsuri-senpai. I'm
not sexy.
That's sexy.
But
here we are.
[Music]
Yay, nice,
nice.  There were only 14 people, right?
[Music] It
was a close call, it was a close call
. You really made it to the limit, you really hit it. That's great.
[Music]
That's it.  I was
really a little surprised when I saw Seshi, and I'm glad I
hid from Taiya-sama.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I
won't
say it.  I'm
back, I'm
back, I moved on my own.
[Music]
Right?
[Music] I wonder
who's winning now. I
don't know. I don't
know. I don't know.  It was
n't where it wasn't where it was, Senior Sexy Ahhhhhhhhhh, this
is
Channose -chan
[Music]
No. 1
Sexy No. 1 Sexy No. 1
Sexy Nono no Sexy No Sexy No Sexy
No Sexy here Sexy  He's not here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
Kaela is here. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaae-sessika Kaeela
sexy's girlfriend sexy sexy
But there are people who say it on their own
[Music]
Noko cool Kara cool cool cool  It's
cool,
isn't it? It's cool, is
n't it? It's cool. It was glossed, right? It was glossed, right? It
was butt day. I saw your butt earlier, but I already saw it.
Because it was Korea, I couldn't get caught,
so I guess it wasn't sexy. Well, maybe sexy wasn't sexy enough. I thought sexy was better, and I
wanted to be caught.
So, you can't tell at first, that's true.
So, you don't know what's going on, so please
close it. It's yellow. I
want everyone to do their best, and I want everyone on the other teams to run all the way to the end.
Okay, okay.
So, next.  Aim for the top of the competition Let's
move to the follow-up venue Evil
please please
please Masu in the middle or in the middle
[Music] Let's
go to the
second venue where it's completely dark Let's move on to the next venue It's flow up Good luck
Up Saroa
[Music]
Floor Floor is a
terrible because there is no senior
[Music] Let's Go
Letz
Goretz Go English
is in English
School School School
School High School
High Squance Follow Up
Floor Follow Up Stage 5 Follow
Up Stadium  What is a rooftop? Rooftop How do you
say it? It's a high ground. I do
n't know what a high ground is. I don't know what to
say. I don't know what a high ground is. It's a high ground up. I'm
all passionate about Luto.
Rooftop Luft Rooftop Go to the
top Rooftop Okay, let's go to the roof.
It's interview time.
I see. I see. I see. I see.
Good luck, good luck, good luck, but that's it. It looks
like we can go on the phone together at all.  I
wasn't really that nervous about it, but I
was really grateful that Chiara was there to help me out.  I'm
going to spread the word here, no, I haven't used it even once,
so why don't you use it?
I'll do my best during a good break.  I
forgot how to say "steak", "chicken" and "pork" in English.
Good luck Piff Pork
Chicken Ah Pif Pork Chicken Ki I'll
forget the chicken
So I have to shout this out to my senior Is it
beef, pork or chicken
Beef Pork
Chicken Steak Steak Steak It's like a steak stete.
Beef Beef Fire Beef Bifa Bihu
Fire Steak Steak
Ah, I
'm hungry.
Someone said they were hungry. I'm
hungry. I'm
hungry. It's about 7:30 in the evening.  It's time, JP
, that's right. Overseas groups,
yes, it's different. So, Wa time, Tsuu-senpai,
ah, 33am, 3am, 33:00, 3:00.  It's
not 3 in the morning, it's 3:30 in the morning
. It's not 3 in the morning, it's in the middle of the night. It's
hard to lie around all night. Good morning, it's
okay. Good morning, great sleep. It's raining.
Thank you for being so late at night.  No, thank you very much
Senkyu Sekyu is okay
Coffee I drank coffee I drank coffee
Nice coffee Nice coffee Nice Coffee Caffeine
Caffeine is important
Caffeine Minister
Caffeine Caf Let's go!  A
great person told me that everything would be fine if I just said, "Let's go!" I
really believed in that great person and everything was fine.
Gozaru I-chan was throwing a trident,
but I was surprised.  It seems that only
Chan has the creative authority. I
heard that's how he gets popular. He
throws tridents, right? Oh, maybe that's
it, maybe that's it.
But the other day I was on the other side, I
was editing Holomen Hunting in creative mode,
and yeah, that's right, I still have some remnants of that.I
did things like flying and throwing javelin by myself when I was practicing.  I've
been doing this for about 3 days now. I've been holding it in my hand. I've been holding it in my hands. I've
been trying. I've been
fighting with others. What are my seniors doing? It's
okay, it's okay. I'm creative, so I'm up.
Wow, what are you doing? Then
you get all excited and say you can do this. That's
true. I can't pick this up. I can't pick that up. I can't pick that up. No,
this is from Mr. Senpai.  I took a photo,
and the stars are reading out.The
stars are reading out.Teruhiha-
chan's star readings are coming
out.It's dangerous.Please don't tell the person in question.Please don't
tell me, please stop.Channanakasu-
chan is clearly reflected in the picture.
Yo, I put some of Trident's hand stains
in Gypro. I
was just checking the smell. I was also taking pictures. Oh, it's
gone, it's gone, it's
gone, it's gone. I'm so shocked that it's
gone. Please do that first.
Well, what should I do? I don't know what to do.
It depends on how things turn out in the future.
Hey, it depends on how things turn out for the rest of today.  I'm
going to lick my jackets. I'm going to lick my jackets.
How about this
? I'm
not asking you to
lick me. I'm happy for you to lick me. I
'll deliver cookies. Cookies.
Cookies.
I want to deliver cookies to everyone.I
want to feed them to everyone overseas.I'm
sure that's the case too.I
want to spread the word to the rest of the world.
I want to go for about a month I'll
take a break from streaming for a while and give it out for now I'll
go to training I'll go to training
So I'll go to training I'll give it to Karamui Ame-chan Cookie
present Cookie present color
Cookie yes cookie color is coming, coming
Let's go for 5 seconds, let's go,
let's do our best, Roboco-san,
do your best, do your best,
good fight!  It's been a
long time. Practice is really bad. It's
not that fast. Bi-chan looks really
good.
Good luck, Roboko-chan. It's Roboko's turn. It's finally time.
Now, it's
nice, nice, nice. It's all good.  Yoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-
oka-okay-okay I can do it now I started and
fixed it now, what happened now, I
guess I touched the checkpoint and it returned to the point I see. Yes,
yes, checkpoints are important.
Yapaoi is good, I'm really competing with Sui-chan It
's true, it's true, it's amazing A, but it's okay, it's really good, I can
go, I can
go, I can go, I can go, I can go, I'm pretty good at taking the route Degozaru, it's good, it's good,
everyone, it's
good, it's good, it's good  No, it's amazing. It's so
good. It's so good. It's so
good. It's so good. In the remaining time,
Pi is coloring it. It's true, Sui-chan.
Gunbibe is amazing but 1st place is
so fast Vibo is too good Ao Checkpoint
Nice
Sapoko
Senpai Pokopoa But you can wear something like this You
can go to the top with this viewpoint
This is the viewpoint You can go up to see this
Go this.  I can't go, I can't go, I can't go, I can't go, I'm
looking at it from below I see, I'm just looking at it from below,
right?
But it's a lie, this is the first time I've heard of such an infected person It
says "Enter" on the right side.Aaah,
it's up, it's up, it's up, it's true
, it's so, so amazing.  It's
like,
Wow, this is amazing. It's true, everyone. Why are we
all floating so much? Did
everyone know that only their heads are floating?
Right, only my head is floating, pain, pain, do your best, yeah, I'm
going to put on my pain clothes. It's nice, nice, nice!
I've reached the goal of winning the book, calm down, I'm stubborn.
Hey, that pink thing is sleepy.
This, this, this, this, this, this.  Oh,
wow, wow, wow, that's really nice. It's
definitely going
well. Do your best.
[Music]
It's nice. It's nice. You're so nice.
Do your best.
[Music]
Nice Sui-chan,
do your best, wow, this is so tough! Do your best Sui-chan, Sui-chan, do your
best Sui-chan, where is Sui-chan? She's so cute even when she's playing with Raiden. Is she
starry? She's cute. Her
eyes are cameraman.  I'll do my best to become the best.I'll do my best to see
if I can do it.It's from the fans' point of view.It
's ok, I'm going to do my best.It's
steadily going up.
No, it's
going up, it's going up, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's taking a shortcut, it's pretty much gone right now.  Just a little bit more, let's do
our best,
okay, nice, nice
, nice, nice, nice, nice,
G
G,
good game, good game, already, I
'm clapping with all my might. I
like this, everyone, everyone, clear it.
It's amazing. Something strange has appeared.
This is wonderful.
Oh, you must be nervous. Yeah, it's okay. Something is
wrong with the screen. Something strange has
appeared on the screen. This is what it is. What if there was a chat setting?
I don't know if there's a controller or something. It's coming out. It's coming out. What's coming out? Wait, I can't go down. I don't know what it is. Shift, shift, ah, shift. Shift.
Shift
is okay Yes, it's a bit surreal to see severed heads flying around
Yeah, I'm sure it's going to come back with this and that infection Oh, it's
back, it's back Ah, okay, okay, that's good, that's good, that's amazing
Tae, it's amazing that only heads like that are affected  I
didn't know that
there is a mode called spectator mode. It's
amazing that people in this normal human state
can't see our heads. It's true that when you look at them from below.  I
couldn't see it, I didn't see it, I
didn't notice it, I didn't see it, so I thought it wasn't there.It's
almost like its existence doesn't even bother me.It's working.It's
back.You can't be
forced back.Everyone has been writing about it one after another.  I
wonder if I was turned into an infected person after it started, or something like when I was looking at it from the sky after I died.It was like a dead body, like a ghostly body.
Yeah, I have to do my best to support me. I have to support you.
How do you do it when you support me? Fight Fight Fight
Fight Fighter Fighter Fighter
Gogogogogonn Gogo Gogo Gonn Difference
Good,
it's amazing, it's extremely detailed, it's
really fast, it's the fastest, I've been practicing really hard,
it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's
getting to the point, it's so fast, it's so fast.  It's so
good, it's so
good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so
good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good,
only one of us has already gone 70m It's
too early for the checkpoint, wow, wow, the
checkpoint is
too fast, wow, we can't even go there!  The
devil with the smooth cut is so smooth, I'm going to go up there, I'm
going to go there, I'm going to
go there, I'm going to go there.
After all, I was
really nervous when I was practicing flying.
I was like,
what should I do? I don't know what to do, but I haven't made any mistakes. It does
n't seem like I've made any mistakes.  Even if I make a mistake, I do
n't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Um, I'm going to go up again. I'm
not going to go up without chopping eggplants. I'm going to
go here. I'm going to go there. It's amazing.  No, no, no, no, no, no, no
mistakes. I'm really nice. I've
come this far by making mistakes. Yo, that
's great. Which way are we
going? It's going that way. It's going there. It's going that way. I
don't have any doubts.  I can
even go there as fast as if I had already decided on the route. I'm
going up, it's really fast, it's really fast. It's
too much. It's
not nice. I've been trying to go back down here.
If you fall, the checkpoint will go down quite a bit If
you fall, no, no, you wo
n't fall, Chiara. You won't fall, you won't fall. It's difficult.
Hey, maybe you'll make it up here as well.
It's really
big. It's so amazing. It's going to be really bad. Do your best,
Chiara.
[Music]  ]
[Applause]
That's amazing, that's so cool, that's amazing
[Music] That
's so nice, Kia
[Music]
That's so nice, I saw you were so nervous.  I
think I'm losing, I don't think I'm nervous at all,
but the truth is, I climbed like an RTA. I
didn't stop. Nice, nice,
good. Nice, nice, too good. I
haven't even scored 2 or 3 goals yet.  It's
not half and half, it's not 150,
so I waited about 90 seconds at my leisure.Let's
take a look.That's right, that
character is fast, is
n't he
?
Ah, I'm sorry, Nya-chan and Chloe
had a good fight, and it was true, it fell black, and the
black was amazing. When I thought about it, I died. It's
difficult, isn't it? It seems like it's difficult to get a sense of distance,
but
Kira really practiced this.  It's the
result of your hard work. It
seems like you practiced for a long time yesterday. Nae, Nae, you're
all alone, waiting and waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting,
waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting,
waiting.
Yellow should be in 2nd place, or yellow should be in 2nd place.
Wow, there's only one more step
left, no, it was just one more step. Hey, it
already flew, it flew,
and Daa-chan
dropped it. I saw that amazing moment.  I
was cut off for a moment and fell. It was a great battle. It
was amazing.
Nice Kiara, it was crackling nice. It was so cool,
Chichi.
The crackling was flying like a beautiful bird, crackling,
crackling, and so on. It was so
nice. Here again, the points from the second match will be added up, but since
we had a Watsu finish, I think the
follower points this time are number 1.  It's not that expensive,
right? It was
in second place a while ago, so there is one.
If the one on the screen over there is a follow-up point, the white team's
points are now 20 and the number 1
point has come out now, so I guess I'll see if I
go to the weak point or not. I
wonder if I can catch up.  Little is nice, nice,
nice
[Music]
Nanai Nate Hey, you
're back. It's still the same.
During the interview, Kanama is still like that. We're the
white team. We're the only white team. Both of us
are eavesdropping properly. Hey, go upstairs.  I
wonder if it's like a mountain, like a mountain, like a
mountain.  Right now, the White team is in
first place.The numbers are White: 40 Yellow:
38 Red: 37  Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice, Nice.  I
have to do my best.The
pressure is starting to build
on me, but I don't want to do it.I
don't want to do anything.  I
heard that Sensen doesn't have a pair with this one.Is it because I paired up with Ra-chan this time?I wonder if I don't know yet.Thank
you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Mom, I'm
looking at you.Mom, yes.So,
that's it.  Here is the interim announcement of the overall specific
award.
Well, there are only 3 points left, so do your best and get 3 points.Okay, let's
move on to the venue for the next competition.Maseko
announced the jump.What
happened?  It was out, it was out,
White was in 2nd place overall, there
was still a difference of 3 points.
3 Yellow was 63. White 6 and Chiara-chan
were nice. Thank you Taore. The game is serious.
Google
Nafanafanafa two people,
it's so bad, it's so bad, it's so bad, it's so
hard, it's delicious, it's the end, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it.Enter
on the right, where, where, here
, I'll go here.  It
's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, you're nice,
nice, nice, you're cute, you're
cute, and then you're on top of me.
If someone rides like that while holding a ``Um'',
wait a little bit and see if the general is on top.The general is
on top, so it's the one that gets clicked.If you
don't enter, and you enter, you'll
cancel, but you should try again.
[Applause]
Will that person from Hosk come? Will that
person from my pair come? Is that person
there? Will he come? Is
his pair not coming?  If this continues, I will  I'm
wandering around everyone, I'd rather prepare food because I want to
eat. I want
to eat. I'm hungry. I want to
summon it.
Please release the naka general.
Oh,
it's okay. So, I know.
[Music]  ]
for
Oh, hey,
where are you, where are you, everyone here? It's
amazing how everyone is getting bigger and bigger.
This is so small that I can't see where it is.
Here, here, here, it
hurts. Is it okay to
go back? How do you stop the object? It's the same in that book,
just press it one more time just P
Ook
just nice nice nice nice
Aoyo
Mumbling too
Wait a minute,
that look.  That's
what I said.He came in a suit.He looks strong.I
made a suit.He looks
cool.He looks strong.That's
better.He looks too strong.This is okay.  I
won't charge you a huge amount of money later. It
might be okay, oh kayu-senpai,
thank you for your wishes. It's strong, it's strong, oh, get
on. Oh, get on, you got on. You seemed the strongest.
[Music]
Yayayao
Thank you so much for helping me as a pinch hitter. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much for your support. Aoka-senpai,
thank you for coming.  I
'm going to ride, I'm going to ride, I'm
going to ride, I'm going to ride, you're going to get on top of me, and I'm going to
sit on top of you.I'm going to sit on the chair for a little while.Okay,
leave it to me.Thank
you.I'm so
happy.There's a mole on my ear.  It looks
like there's a chocolate corner stuck in my butt.
It's leader
Kochiha. It's better to fit it in a little bit. It might be
really
hard.
This senior's corner is really stimulating me.  I'm sure I'll
win.HanekomataThank you for
today, Okayu-san.Thank
you very much.Thank you very much.
How do you
do it? I learned how to do it in a nutshell. I
want to lead you to victory.
Please, thank you
very much. Yes, let's do our best, everyone in the white team, we'll
do it. Yayaru.
Let's do our best.Okay,
finally, I want to ask the Kigumi
group.KigurumiGuruGurugumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGumiGuruGumiGumiGumiGumiGuruGumiGumiGuruGumiGumiGuruGumiGuru Hey, what's the strategy for this
?Is everyone in the White group going to be screaming?I
see.As expected, the best kill will be taken.
Well, 1 point will be added,
right? I guess I'll defend and probably attack. The
opponent will focus on the enemy, and
everyone will approach the general.  It
seems like we should just wake him up for the time being. Well, I think it's more likely that people who are close to the general will do it more and more. It seems like it's the weaker ones, right? I'd like to see the weaker ones get beaten up.  Do you want to be a
person? I'd like to ask you the other way around.
At first, I'll be near the general and when I see 1 heart, I
'll attack. It's
scary, Rika. Yes, it's
probably from here. That's the voice of that pair.
I think it's going to be a chat, so I wonder if there
are that many things like that. Voice Chat Voice I think there is a name for the chat, so now that I think about it, there's a real Nakataoka. It's
not possible to get it by collaborating with everyone.  Well, it
looks like the general is going to protect us, so let's do our best. Let's do our best. We're actually in the way. We're both being targeted, so I think we should cover for each other.  It seems so  If you
feel that way, then I
think you'll probably have to move from here. Well, let's go. Let's go
let's go.
Oh hello hello [
Music]
ourHEADrightsoMaybe
thebestislikejust
Trytoimtheonethat
GotONEHEARTOKyeahGo
fortheleaderUN
ONE
MayMaybePRF
person
[Music]
F
Oh
Mi
[Music] Let's go let's go
[Music]
Let
me
[Music]
JAiiYeah Let's go Let's go
for
Lastof
see
YeahTryBEST
beonepun
dageME
MEMOVE
andiiovONEonlythat
OnlyYouand
ATTthe
Yeah Yeah
Yeah
[Music]
dage
Nnnnnnn
IknowwhyIReally
Love
[Music]  ]
thetheHold
upHold
upafter
prinbe
prin
[Music]
know
areyou
goingor
Princessdone
done I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best.
see
Need
[Music]
okok
ta
tite
[Music]
Nice oh
oh
done
seeOhYeahOKfine
[Music]
OKLetseethenext
announcementaresing
nowOh No See
Ok
Oh
[Music]
Yes have
REG
MayOKandwhereare
[Music]
you
OK
back
SWORD
Wood
Oh
okay
[Music]
H
know
GU
[Music]
J
May
[Music]
Ah
Igo
for let's go hard ten
o
[music]
going
oneone
[applause]
one
KOk
LetSE
o Dopry
goodliketheTeamthe
TE
okokok
F
AllIsLastOneMore
[Music]
SCTeam
WIN
Turn
[Music]
know
ONE
more
[Music]
are
OK
[Music]
knowsee
people
I have people on my
hand
Lisa
Mise do my best
[Music]
people
pleas
[Music]  ]
MOVlittle
cred
OKthink
rck
me
May
best
know
anyTurnpeopleATTUS
Yeah
MaybeONEHEART
[Music]
ONEThisisthis
is
Nai
Nai Nai
Fafafa nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
o o mi komiko obe
ya
[laughs]
OK
nachi
o
310 o
[music]
go go
killskills
kills
[music]
hei know
of
know
su
agressive
[music]
nice one nice
one looks
Againkills
killskills10
1097 nicewana
nicewa let's goa
iovYeahMaybeIknow
maybewejustneedto
wait
RES
Oh
go
ah
[Music]
Gogone
10gEiame-chan is also a 10
kill overseas kill machine
Killma
was amazing Nemi you did a great job
Nai this is amazing I've
got a lot of Nesh I've got a lot of 41 That's
right  I was surprised because it included targeted kills
41 We did it, we did it too Nice, nice,
do it eggplant
Nice, no, no,
running away is important.
Nice 1 from
Killna Nice Nice Nice Ski If
it wasn't for that 1 kill, I'd be 40.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, it's important, important, important, nice. Nicely-
chan is
strong, very strong. Strong, Su-a-chan, Roboko-san, the pair was also
amazing. Nice, Nice, I was really surprised.  But,
oh,
wow, everyone is doing a great job
! It's amazing. Nice, nice, nice. I
wonder how this is going. I wonder if we've gotten to a pretty good place.  I
think it must have been a comeback.
It's good, it's good, it's good. It's good, it's good, it's good in the second game. I think it was number 2 or something like
25.
Red was also strong in its own way, so it
's true that it happened many times.  I'm sure the red was strong.
No, no, it was amazing at first. I don't know
what's going to happen. I'm scared of Lire.
Even Hime Momo is shaking. I'm shaking.
Mu-chan, let's do our best. It's okay.  It's
okay, you can win, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, you can win, it's okay, it's okay, you can win, you can win.During practice, the
yellow group dodged me for about a minute and a half.Even
though it was just that, I served them that meal.However,
no, this is a serious
reading.  The
content of lome hunting has changed quite a bit
since the update came out, so we can all be prepared for the possibility that the menu has also changed a bit.Yes,
that's possible.
Yes,
yes, I
want to win. I want to win. If I've come this far, I've already
come. How far do I want to
go? I want to go, right? That's true. I
want to go. I feel like I'm feeling a little
greedy.  But somehow, I was
starting to see a victory. It
wasn't like I was just
coming. I've just torn it
apart. I've
torn it up.  Do
n't tear the skin.
Don't tear the skin. It's so wild.
Take care of it.
You're muscular. You're proud of your muscles. Momoshiro
looks so good at the end. 41
Ki
Senpai Miko Senpai's glue makes her blush bright red.  Mashi
[laughter]
Tayong Too much, how was it? The number of
kills was amazing.
I'm sorry, but I defeated Su-senpai twice, and I defeated him once. No, no, who was the one who was being bullied? There were so many people, like Kara, it was so huge. That's why the White team was amazing.
But at the end, I'd like to talk a little bit about Nekomata.  Okayu-san,
thank you
very much. Thank you. Please give me your thoughts.
Yes, thank
you very much. Thank you very much. It was a pleasure to play with you all. I will
continue to support the white team.
Thank you very much.
Thank you also disappeared in an instant.
Thank you very much. Really,
thank you for [music].
Thank you, too. I'm also killing numbers,
so it's completely different when I have it or not. I
did my best. I did my best. It's changed.
Thank you very much.It was really
fun.It was really fun.It
was fun.It was really fun.It was fun.It was really fun.There's a lot of
pressure in the competition after this.The pressure is
amazing.The pressure is different.
Let's relax and hope, it's okay, it's okay,
everyone can do it, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it looks like it's okay, you have to
protect the princess, even if you have to protect the princess, even if you make
a little mistake with the princess, she'll make up for it with a relay,
right?
Pressure.  It's scary, it stings the world, it
stings the spiders too,
right now I'm climbing the ivy.
Everyone's climbing the ivy, and I'm in a hurry to climb it,
but I'm getting better at the ivy too, nice.  It's difficult to
run, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it? I said it was difficult. When I heard it today, where did you do it?
So, it seems like the scores have been tallied, so
I'd like to take a look.  The total of the match
is here. Red team did their best. It's
a little bad.
No, the red team has 46 points. The white team has 38
points. The yellow team is
amazing. They were still in the same position as before.  It's
not like we've made a comeback.We're
making a comeback.It's all
good.We'll see what happens in the second half after this.Okay, let's
go to the next one.Okay, let's
all move to the venue for the next competition.  Ita
Yo
Lego, Go Go, have fun, look
forward to it, let's do
our
best,
fight, do our best, good luck, good luck, good luck,
good luck.
[Music]
MasuIknow
YouDonewithallmy
beso
greatMyJobis
donegoodJGood
Jobnicekillsatthe
girlnice
kills
Oh, do your best!
White team, do your best,
do your best. Do your best, Oka-tan, you entered the princess. Hime-
hime looks strong. If the princess is number one, then the strong-sounding princess is the
strongest.  I will
be crushed by the strongest force, so please go tight,
Negyugyu.  I want you to
go to Gyugyu. I wonder if you'll shake hands. I'll
do my best here, I'll do my best, I'll do my best. It's
nice to have a tiara on. It's cute. It's waddling.
Eh, it's okay, it's okay. I
thought Jo-chan was crying. I thought she was
laughing. I was so
nervous. I was
so scared.  The way she laughs
is a special feature, so it
definitely makes my heart flutter
[Music]
Yeah,
when
love
knowhappTearshapp
happ
happ That's good.
[Music]
[Laughs]
What's Eka-chan laughing like that
? JustJust
My
mom is playing with her own 3D.
That's why she's laughing. Are you streaming KOh
?
[Music]
Yeahlookat
myamIhave
OpenPARTYPARTY
D,
oh,
snak,
B,
pry, this is only the first round, right? Well, it's
scary, but it's just one round. It's
like pressure, pressure, pressure.  I'm
kind of nervous.
Um, I'm going to participate in this because Kana-tan is the princess,
and Mei-chan, and
Azuki-chan, Azuki-chan, and
Kama-chan. Unana,
Nanar, and Naru. You said earlier that the menu was difficult.  I've
done it before, but
yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, that's right.  There are
various processes involved,
so if you can't divide the roles, you'll end up wasting your
time. Cooperation is important. Cooperation
is so important.
But on the other hand, he's been working with Minecraft for about three years now.  You
thought you could cut vegetables, that's what I thought too.You
thought you could cut vegetables.That's right.There's a knife.There's an
item for cutting boards, and when you
click to open it, there's a knife next to it.
If you put it in a bowl, you
can cut
tomatoes, carrots, potatoes, etc. If you add beef, it becomes minced meat.
Normally it can't be cut off, but this time it seems like it's a special salt.
Ah, that's the kind of stage it is. Yeah, it's amazing that you can do that, right
? It's certainly possible for Minecraft to do that. Is there a setting like that?
I'm so impressed, but
from Kara-chan's point of
view, I guess it's normal. She's strong, so
maybe that's why she's laughing.
Takakoa,
stay, be
kind,
thank you, ah, do your best, do your best, do
your best, do your best, do
your best, I was watching you on the street the other day
.  Let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
you can persevere, we're going
smoothly, we're getting a foothold, but it's going
well, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
go, you can do it
.  Alright, alright, seriously, seriously,
this is alright, go, go, go, you
're lined up with red right now, nice, nice, nice number 1  Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
What was that?
What was it? I don't understand it at all. No, I
don't understand from here. It's white and pink.
This is so sweet. What is this? What is this? What is this? What is this?  I
wonder what you're doing and what you're making.I'm really curious about this.When I was
practicing, it looked like Nemishi's hamburger.Mishi's
homemade hamburger.
Yeah, what's the hamburger actually like?What are you
making?What are you doing right now?I'm cutting it up.Oh, I'm
grilling it.I'm cutting vegetables.I'm cutting vegetables.Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best with
chocolate.  Looks like it's going to be fun, do your best, do your
best, what are you making? I wonder what you're making. The food you ate is great! Wait, Isuna is
already up to stage 5. Good luck,
but you're only at stage 2 right now.  But red, it's
strong, red, strong, but it's fast, it's fast, it's fast, it's fast.
This princess, my princess, has 50 kilos of strength,
so don't worry, do your best, try your best, do your best. One chan, one
chin, one chan, there's one, there's one, one chin, one
chan, more and more.
Wow, it's finally time to come out, do your best, try your best.  It
looks like the final boss,
but
something in the back isn't floating, it's floating, it's floating, it
looks like it's really strong.  A
little more, a little more, a little more, a little more, a little more, a little bit more, a little more, a little bit more, a little bit more, a little bit more, a little bit more, a bit more, a little bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a little more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more, a bit more,
a bit more.  Go for it Nice
Nice Nice Nice Nice
Nice really 3 seconds 3 seconds
Nice Nice Nice Nice Nice
That's nice
. That's nice. That's nice. That's great. Wow, I wonder what you were making. I
'm sure.
Let's ask her about it. I
didn't understand the white one at all, but if that was
the case, it would have been brown. What
was it?  Oh, don't worry about it, but it's yellow. It was amazing,
catching up at the end.
Before we knew it, we were really close to the edge. It's
not the cat, it's the two of us.  I could
n't figure out who it was right now. It was
wrong, wasn't it?
Hmm, I'm so nervous. I
wonder if I can go fishing for flowers at this hour. I'm
not doing an interview, so I'll
just go straight over there.
Hello, it's an air conditioner right now.It's a
good idea to open the room when it's hot.I
can't live without an air conditioner.Yes,
but I don't have an air conditioner in my house in Austria.  I
don't have an air conditioner, yeah, but what about the weather? It's
pretty hot in the summer, so I'd
like to have an air conditioner, but my house usually doesn't have an
air conditioner, so it's so hot that I
can't think of anything.
No, but it's hot, it's hot, and it
's hot.It's different from Japan, so it must be great.Even
if you say no to chocolate, you'll act fast.If it
were now, I'd keep the image quality on all the time.
air conditioner love
Lala I'm counting the numbers now I guess it's the inter-counts or this Tsuji is
the last one in the rele
A
tense
A I'm seriously weak at the actual performance I'm scared I can
go I can go it's okay it's okay I'm scared of the actual performance
Yeah it's okay but even Lissa-chan and I will be
in first place so I'm going to be super nervous
Yes,
you are right, but even after that,
anyone can fix something over and over again, so I think they'll accept that mistake.That
's probably why I feel the most pressure.
After all, it's the last time, Iroha-chan, it's the last time. I'm home. I'm home. I'm going home. I went to the
bathroom.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Hana, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'm going to come
out more and more, so I'm getting nervous and handing over the bat.
That's right, I'm in front of the world, right here. I
'm somewhere in the middle. I do
n't think it's okay. I want to do my best, but I don't know what the actual situation will be like, so I might
not be able to do what I used to do.
Yeah, I get it, you're getting impatient, right? I guess the
points in the relay are really high. I
wonder what happened in the last competition. Even now, the red team
probably has a pretty good lead. Yeah, that's right.
It's so high every time.  I
have an image of a high score at the end.I
understand.It means that a reversal is possible.Yes, that
's
right.So, let's take a look at the scores of the Etsu race.Yes, the
red team was in first place, so it was 30.  point  The
white group will have 20 points and the yellow group will have 10 points.The
red group is a bit amazing.Maybe the
red group will be strong in 2023.I
don't know yet, it's still strong, so I
don't know.From now on, let's
move on to the next competition trace and move on to the end.  Let's
move a little bit, okay? Let's move
here. I'm glad you're back. I don't
know. I don't know.  It's
cool, it's cool, it
's cool, it's cool, it's cool, it's coming, it's
flying off without permission, it's flying off without permission, and everyone's going home.Ori-
senpai is amazing at cooking, it's
really fast, it's really fast, what were you making?what were you
making?lam
That's how I understood it.Kantara with lamb and lamb.Lamb that was soaked in lamb.Sheep and lamb.It's better to have it grilled.  I'm
lucky because I got a lot of it during practice.I'm
glad I came to practice.Actually
, I'm
sorry for losing it.Gun-
chan, what's going on tomorrow?I'm sorry.After
this, it'll be the Spring/Summer East Relay, so I'm going to relive it.
If you are going to participate, please move to the Eshirogumi contestant channel. I'm
sorry, but I see you're being skipped. I
see. Before Nodoka-chan's
announcement was made, the contestants were called out.  I
see, cutting-edge technology is cutting-edge technology in an instant. It's surprising and
easy to understand, so it's helpful. I'm going to
study it, and I'm going to go to the flower. I'm going to dash there. Let's
go. Come on, let's go.
Well, it's better to enter. Ah, enter.
Book.  You can get it, so
choose who you are or who you are in white, come here, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come, come.
How many numbers are mine and Ame-chan?
It's the memory group leader who seems to be in the middle,
right? Yame-chan is on the 5th floor. 5, 5, big hey,
Anonymous. Okay, Kaeana, I
see. This is the
entry.  I wonder if I was able to do it, I was
able to do it, I was able to
do it.  It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's nervous, right? In the end,
ah
ONE, ah, I've
made the entry, ah, but it's 9.
[Music]
Onana,
nice,
nice, no, this one-chan, this underwater dive.  Eh, the
order of the contestants is ok, 1st layer is Eneri,
ok, next is Choco Sensei student 3rd,
Mui 4th is Captain Noel, then 5th layer is  The
7th layer is Azusan, and finally,
as people get to know each other, it
feels like people who are used to Minecraft are gradually coming in. It
feels like they're trying to catch up.  Well
then, let's do an interview. Yes, that's right.
Everyone in the white group bought it. Good
morning. How about it? Well
then, who should I choose?
When I noticed that Ankage 5 and Game 5 were playing, I
realized that he was an anchor.He's fast,
so I think things will work out.He's trusting me.No, that's
great.He's
white.I really want him to take first place.I'll do my best.
Please, do your best, do your best, and
thank you, Zhang.Yes, see you
then, Mr. Niyabikuri.
When I was in the middle of the day, I couldn't hear the words ``open book, open book,'' so I didn't get it.I'm a
man and a woman who felt embarrassed and embarrassed.Okay,
let's
do our best.Here's the bad water.It's just luck.At first, I was at the bottom.  Let's
do our best, let's do our best, try our best, try our best,
try our best,
do your best, oh this is it, ah, I fell down,
but here it is, the water is so loud
[Music]
Oh no!  I've
practiced nervously, so I'm
starting to get nervous. My mental health is starting to get crazy.
It's okay, it's
okay, do your best, it's okay. It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay. It's
okay today, it's Korea. Remember, it's okay. I'm
really trying hard.  Well, it's all
over now, so it's a casual ending. Let's
laugh at the end. Once this is over,
let's go eat some delicious meat.
Let's talk about the chocolate line Azuki and the chocolate line
That's right, meat Yakiniku
Yakiniku Owa The
lady who's preparing the shabu-shabu Do your best, do your best, Te-san, do your best, go go go go go go, try your best,
try your best, try your best, calm down
Let's go, come on, we'll be waiting for you Come on, go go go go go go
Kamo kamo nice nice catch nice
catch nice
catch nice brain nice nice one nice one nice
naina
[music]
Nanai, that's it,
leave it to Gogo, leave it to me,
leave it to me, it's
fine, it's fine, it's good, it's good, it's good, I'm good at it, I'm good at it, I'm
good at it, I'm
good at it.  It's okay, it
's
okay, yo, try your best, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, go, go, go,
go, wait here, here, I was
cheering for you, but I lost track of myself
[Music]
Oh, try your best, try your best,
oh  Ohaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
Ya Do Ya
Ya, it's okay, you can do your best. Do your best. Do your best.
[Music] Do your
best. Do your best.
Go, do your best.
Go ahead, do your best.
Yo, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's run, let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
go!  Yeah, it's good
[Music]
Gogogogo
Do your best, get sucked into this or that
[Music]
Let's go, nice
, nice,
okay, finally, do your best, try your best  Do your
best, do your best, senpai It feels like you're going to
hit me, it's okay, right? It's okay, I'll give you a good punch. It's
okay, it's okay,
eat it. Try your best,
try your best, do your best, do your
best. You can't do your best, Nana. Yes, do your best.  Yes, let's
go, Roroha, okay,
where's the food? It's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's amazing, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Nice, nice, nice, nice, fight, nice, fight, nice, nice, it
was a good run, I was nervous, I did my best, everyone finished,
ok, you're strong,
good, you were strong,
hey, I forgot to eat. It's
okay, I'm hungry.  Let's
eat a lot when we're done.
[Music]
Yeah, nice run, nice
run, nice run. Nice yeah
yeah, nice meat. I want to eat some meat.
[Music]
Carnivorous, meat, let's go, meat, meat, yes, yes, yes, my heart
hurts
. Thank you for your hard
work. Japanese sub-sub, I want to eat. Good food. Let's all eat. Reluctantly, let's all eat shabu-shabu. Shabu-shabu. Beautiful shabu-shabu. Beautiful shabu-shabu. Beautiful shabu-shabu. Let's boil it.  I'm sure the
chocolate line will pick me up and
take me away. Let's leave it all to the chocolate.
Sensei, I'm very good.
Nice.
Yeah.  Leave it to
me, leave it to me,
Aiya, but you did your best
[Music]
Please, you did your best
during the interview. You did your best. Thank you. You
did your best.
Well, I'm going to listen to Iroha, who serves as the anchor, one more time. How was it?  I don't
know what's going on, we're the best from the beginning to the end,
everything's okay, we're all connected, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.  There were a
lot of things I wanted to pass, but
I ended up in 2nd place. It
was a great race. It was a
nice fight.  Thank you for your
hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Are you
using it well
? I'm using it well. Hey, Yoyoyode, what's your holiday? Yakooki
Tao
[Music]  I'm
tired on the way home, I'm tired, I'm a small boy in the 1st grade of the exam, it
's amazing, it's so good, yeah, I
lost,
right?  Did you think you could get it?
Everyone worked hard. Everyone
worked hard. No, I worked hard. I tried my best. At first, I
honestly
felt like I was having fun. I was like, ``I'm going to do my best, even though it's difficult.'' But I never expected it.
Yes, that's right, I didn't understand until the end
.
Yes, that's right. Yes, that's right. So, I'm going to use my cell phone.
Everyone, please gather in front of the platform.
[Music]
First, that's it, that's it.  It's from the school. There
was a stinking wall in the house. There was a wall in the house right now.
I was surprised. We were trapped. We
were sealed. Now we were trapped in this school. Let's
talk a little louder.  throat
Even though it's empty, the
white group line is beautiful, beautiful
[Music]
Hey, what practice are you doing? It's
okay, it's okay, mess it up. [Laughs] I feel like I
have a tonality, so I say, ``I won't lose in the tonality.''
Hey, that team looks very
different. I'm
sleeping, I
'm calm, I
'm not polka, I'm volka, I'm volka, I'm
energetic, I'm holding bread, I'm
playing sma
.  I
said yes, and the ceremony begins, but I don't know what to say. I didn't understand it at all, but yeah.
Everyone is working together so well and
working so hard. It's such a close race every year. It's
really worth watching.  That's what I thought.That
's true.It seems like there was a drama in each of them.I
think it was a drama, including the practice.However, I
think it was really good.
Mommy can't be there, so I'm
going to come over and talk to you now. I'm
glad we all lined up for a while. It's
amazing how strong your words are. Everything
quieted down all at once,
but everyone started squatting down properly.  It's
scary to feel like your relationship is in trouble.I don't think so.Yes,
that's fine.Okay, everyone, are your voices
being heard?I can hear them.
Before the ceremony, I
thought I would like to say a few words to everyone who supported me, A-chan and Nodo-chan, as there was a lot of voice chat movement due to the competition.  Ie-
chan
's voice, "Thank you very much, thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work. It's the voice of heaven.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you again this year.
Your hard work and individuality are overflowing."  Thank you
very much for your cooperation. Thank
you very much for your cooperation. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you, everyone. I think it was fun for all three of you to participate,
so
please do your best until the end. Yes,
thank you.
first
As a closing address, I would like to
ask Ms. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day committee, to give a greeting.
Yes, yes, everyone at this sports day. Was it
fun? It was fun. It was fun. It was
fun. It was really fun.
Everyone was great.
Thank you very much.  Well, every year, I'm
thankful that Goro Live has gotten busier and
busier,
but even so, I've seen people come together like this,
everyone working together, each one really taking the initiative,
calling out to each other, and helping each other out.
Miko and the others have already seen it all, so I'm
really overwhelmed with emotion
every time.Thank you very much for your
continued cooperation.Thank
you very much.Thank you
very much.Thank you
very much.  Thank you very much. I'm
sure Tara will be talking about the newcomers and
memos from en and so on in the future.
It would be great if we could have more interactions and make Hololive more exciting together.
Thank you very much for your continued support. Thank you very much for your continued support.
Thank you very much for participating again this year
and doing a great job.
So, everyone is super great,
and this is the finish line for this year.
Thank you very much.  I've
seen many different teams, and
all the teams are already working hard, and I
think we'll see results this time around.  I
think that one big cat will become a treasure, so I hope that you will be able to make use of this bond in the future.It
was a lot of fun to watch.Thank you very
much.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Okay nice peach nice nice peach
senkyu senkyu Okay
so finally I
'd like to
announce the overall benefits.Yes I'm going to announce the score 1, then 100 and
finally 10.  I
would like to make presentations in the following order.
Now, Ms. Samiko, the chairperson of the sports day executive committee,
could you please make a specific presentation?
Yes, then I will start with presentations starting from number 1.
Yes,
that's it.
It's the door. Wow, I can see this. The red team is 8. The
white team is 8. Oh yeah, the yellow team is 6. I want to see it.
But what's the picture? I'm scared now. This announcement
is scary. I don't know yet. Let's
stand in line. Let's continue.  We
announced about 100 first. Yes, yes,
106 is here. Please, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I
don't know yet. I have all of them. All of them.  It
's about 100, please, please, it's
too bad, it's so bad, I can't believe I'm going to the end, everyone,
please, please, finally announce about 10.
Please, please,
please
[music]
Wow, that means yes. So,
what, what, what, the winner is red. Red 158 eh.  White is
138, yellow is 106,
but it's almost there, I
understand,
but
[Music] It
's Rito, and second place is 138 points, yes 3
We were placed in a group with 106 points. We
worked hard. Everyone did a great job. We
worked hard. We all worked hard. We all worked hard. We're
glad we did. Well, we'll give out the awards.
Well, yes, there's an awards ceremony.
Everyone, I hope you'll see.  This is Geo, who has the same medal as the yellow group.Okay
, well then, the
representatives of the players and teachers of the yellow group, Habe.Chanbe-
chan, please come to the front.Come
here.Has.Then,
third place, please give me a medal.
How many points do
you have? Wait a minute!
Oh,
wow! You've prepared it now. Congratulations! It's
on. It's on. It's on. It's on. It
's on. It looks like it's on.  It
's a silver medal for the white team. Please tell me the gold one. I'm not going to follow you.
Tachimoe. I'm looking forward to it, but I'm excited.
Congratulations to the white team, this is an
amazing and amazing medal. [Music] This is an amazing medal. Congratulations on the very cute medal.  This
is Geo from Yotowa-
samatowa I want to see the medal I want to see.
Thank you and congratulations.
[Applause]
[Music] Is
this Hololive? It
disappeared in a blink of an eye. Even though there were so many
diamonds, they disappeared in an instant.
Now that you're clean, I'd like to
take Hololive Daidokai 2023 as a crime.Thank
you everyone.Thank you very
much.I'd like to take a commemorative photo.Yes.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know what to do. Let's
put it on that stand in the middle over there.
Yes, please. Yes, it's on top of the front
. Okay, let's move. Duck, duck, duck.  It's a
game where I can't go back, is my
husband okay?
It's dangerous, everyone is lined up in the upper right corner. This one can fit in too,
yes, this one can fit in too.  I
didn't make it in time,
Lee,
Sorry, it's okay, Lee-chan. Yes, it hasn't arrived yet. It's on us too.
Everyone's lying. It's on us. Oh, it's true. I'm so
happy.
I don't have a medal because I failed once,
but seriously
[Music] It's
not like I won't be
able to lose it. If I try one more time, I won't get kicked out. It's
okay. It's not like
that at all.  I'm
glad I was able to touch you with my senpai. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Okay.
Hey everyone, that little thing right in front of
me. Where should I look at that? Is it okay if I look at it?
Koro-san. I feel
like I'm looking at Koro-san. Koro-san is flying.
Hey, that's flying. Oh, I should
just look there. Is it okay to see it? Really?  That
's right in front of the cameraman. That's the cameraman.
Here, here, here, here, here, there. There's someone here.
There's a cameraman.
Okay, everyone. Can you see me?
I'll take a photo.
[Music]
Mermerka Mercari
Hey, hey, hey, hey, who
threw it? Who threw it now? Who threw it this year? It just so happened that
someone else threw it, but we're all
throwing so much. We're throwing so much. Hey, do
n't throw away your trash. Take your trash home with you. I ca
n't see the box.  Well,
thank you very much for coming
all this way. Thank you very much to all the listeners, and to all the staff members who cooperated with us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
very much.
Grand Sports Day 2023 and above will be the end
Yes, let's meet again Let's
all go to Holo Live Hahaha Let's
go Holo
[Music]
[Music] Let's get along at
the live, let's get along
[Music] Bye-
bye everyone Bye-bye  Everyone bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[
music] bye [music]
eh eus hun Wow fu
bye bye
[music]
adeo
ad
PatiforLast
Tapafor
Last
Oh
howto
partypartypartybeI
go
Party
Fire
this
[Music]
with
Ah
Waa
know
Ah Deos can Ae Bye Bye Bye
Bye Bye Bye
Bye Bye Letme
Anotherfir
and Another
FireGGthanyoumuch
forallthefortodayI
happallofusarehapp
wefunyousomuchand
seeyouagainWhenIsee
youbye
[Music]
What
thanyouso
muchSUAll
[Music]
Of
guys
[music]
to
hey no
way