[Music]
huzzah G Day to everyone to everyone
here g day G Day to
all
huzzah it seems we are
still another day not wasted we must
continue construction on the queen but
it seems as if I was roped into a little
bit of questing
and we must find out who defaced the
statue of the queen let me show you the
photo the sketch that I
took I will show everyone here in my
head the sketch that I
[Music]
took look at this such a disgusting
thing
disgusting this sketch I've
taken who could have done such a
terrible terrible heinous deed ah I
cannot bear look at
[Music]
it I was quick to work I was put quick
to work though I fixed it I had fixed
the the statue of our dearest Queen Tam
she is doing much
better thank the gods who would do this
to our sweet wonderful Queen well she is
not even
here she's not even here to see it and
one would dare do such a thing when she
is not around look I even have these
Cherry buttons in my inventory
no
disgusting you disgust
me I demand a
penalty penalty of the utmost order
mayhaps even death death in the name
of
empathy the
evidence I cannot I've deleted it we do
not need evidence what I have is a
sketch it is okay Jonathan D yes we are
almost ready for the dungeon I I found
GI and I see I am here I am ready to
depart as well I pray tell join the
party call oh I will now enter the
telepathic phone
call I am don't know capable of buying
the backpack welcome gathan
janira you I am on my way what do you
mean we will wait for you fair hero yes
I will make
haste I have the backpack thank you oh
you got it yes good job
y let me put some some stuff in
there
way I am finally Gucci
up toss
these I will make haste towards the
blacksmith
yes quickly quickly
now some things seem to be unmovable
from my hands wa it's from her her lands
her native lands yeah yeah any any any
like uh critical game items you are not
able to move may need to be turned down
the fire that makes you live in Fire and
so on and so I understand you may not
see uh you may not see what I am doing
this shall
suffice I am ready whenever to
strike how is it and yes how is it now
yes let's go then we must wait for I see
gathan in the
distance on my way where is Queen
Mario right behind you lady is broken
wonderful one second my
dears
yes this looks like the kind of hat I
would wear but just way smaller all
right I am I am
ready I'm also ready the Amber coin hat
let's Embark let us
go we we
ride we are all such sophisticated hat
wearers yes yes a wonderful wonderful
hat be caught without hat M I love hats
I remember and now you have a hat yes I
am one of you
now I do not know how I feel about an
Amber coin but if you if you support
Queen Tam Gander I will see the truth
yes with my life I support and empathy
we do not compassion and empathy
prejudices ah yes I will open My Heart
To
Thee thank you for your kindness thank
you for I knew I could it from you ever
loyal to Queen Tam
Gander she's I I have a complaint to
make however with the Tam Gander St you
what what of it can you please fill out
her ass it is currently inverted I need
you to make it real true to life her abl
please I am attempting she's still a
work in progress she needs arms am I the
only one who hasn't done it yet yes has
has everyone here finished the dungeon
yes please can you TR not spoil me yes
please my lady
uh okay we find ourselves in a white
empty space it's so vast that the very
concept of distance seems to lose
meaning why is this not about Burgers
huh why was mine about
burgers in the midst of that space we
see an atique desk and a lever chair and
on that chair sits a girl sipping tea
okay okay okay close enough tick tock
tick tock tick tock tick tock tick tock
tick tock tick tock peu what do you say
about this does it sound familiar
familar we hear a perhaps It sped
something within my mind yes TI all
right tick tock tick Tok as more and
more clocks join the chorus the girl
closes her
eyes tick tock tick tock tick tock tick
tock tick tock tick
tock I shall close my eyes
too there's words sense
it my
weakness oh okay okay o it's a quiz
can't believe they are
floating right which source of energy
did a certain offit Reaper discover ah
Soul energy Soul energy oh h no uh oh
sorry never mind people's strong
emotions people's no people's Souls no
uh uh
both well we'll vote on whatever one you
want so this one people strong emotions
strong emotions there's a third one you
do not think it's eating lots of sushi
oh there's
a not one no n it's this one I am sure
one believe me trust me okay
right huz
huz so smart so
intelligent well I have paid close
attention to what I have learned so far
what is this book oh souls are not a
zero sum game that's that's what the
reaper realized for if she could stir
the hearts of her audience the power of
their emotions were energy enough yawn
Crimson bows bows a treasure lies in
wait the Gaze of orus will point you
straight I do not understand does
somebody understand this uh it sounds
like a a hint to where her thing was in
the last dungeon no yes doesn't that
sound familiar remember remember when we
when you the trees the Crim B the Crim
the Tre yes yes the trees the trees I
remember
well a checkpoint a checkpoint huzzah
huzzah oh it's just a hint if you
haven't gotten the thing yet yes we are
making great progress and you are
learning so quick you're so
intelligent oh yes indeed because I
don't need these hints it seems I have
already found them all collect yes
well I'm slow because I'm starving you
need food oh would you like would you
like some bread mother if you have some
bread I I have some bread mother for you
starvation in Medieval ages who would
have thought it is quite common would
have known oh thank you so much that's
very generous thank you all right
anything for you mother thank you so
much which of these guards the force
field around Atlantis shark statues
electric jellyfish a dignified man with
a
beard I have collected some sewer
water oh no delicious I
mean uh please do not touch me I have
collected some more water from the keep
that keep that away from us it seems I
have would you like a drink no thank you
I'm fine water no no surely is a
dignified man with a beard surely okay
if that's we'll vote for it charie oh
I'm I'm on my way I'm coming are you in
or
what yes okay there we go dedication I
want to see it wait how do I get
in oh right click oh oh no was it the
wrong answer reation I think it might
correct reation
Revelation honestly know but be you
princess no even if you're not my
princess I shall protect you my own they
hurt me oh you saved me thank
you a princess must not find the need to
fight she must be protected thank you
for protecting me by a night mhm mhm all
right what is your second choice after a
dignified man with a beard let me try to
recall my Adventures from a long time
ago um L were you part of my Adventures
yeah what do you say what it no no no
you can't ask her the answer yes you
can't ask her um it is so long ago oh it
is hard to recall but perhaps um
the shark
statues that is your choice yeah could V
for yeah
yeah uh one more oh sorry there you go
prin princess princess thank
you well I almost went to the jish
thank goodness thank the le le the
Leb yes in the depths the kingdom of
Atlantis sits safe within its force
field Mighty Stone shark stand guard to
defend it and yet rumor has it that one
girl slipped through those defenses the
ancient doll meanders in its maze reward
awaits who out the bound stength I
already have this one in my possession
you're so smart found all of them onward
onward grateful onward
onward onwards a checkpoint to the
checkpoint thank goodness huz
huz I wish I had a glass that I could
throw on the ground while yelling huz
only H it feels
wrong oh question number three come on
this one must be more closer in my
memory
because I have done it today a
mysterious boy appeared at a certain
Shrine what is he particularly good
at folding
origami
AAR to me unfamiliar to me as well I did
not know what that is
Takaki also unfamiliar what is that what
is soccer I really know football right
football what is that I do not know any
of those things um it is when it's it's
an illness when your feet are in the
shape
of oh no terrify no that is is really
hard to walk it is so hard to walk that
you must do a thing called dribbling in
order to
movee uh okay to her she was merely
keeping them company but to the souls it
was what they needed to move on one boy
left his Fs in origami before departing
for the other side a laborin Fe passage
passage test the eyes proceed Beyond the
Wall to claim a prize interesting
interesting very interesting interesting
a a really smart tall uh soup lady
taught me how to get that
one or queen
Mario sorry I was I was drinking some
water cat it's okay wasting mother must
stay
hydrated yes cha
check the
checkpoint huzzah we have forgotten our
huz huz we have we are one step closer
to solving this
dungeon wait a minute bgm was missing
okay so what is the grand achievement of
a certain excuse me Oddball Phoenix
Oddball
what oh how dare this dungeon quite a
cruel place
and helping a fast food restaurant repay
its de taking first place in hamburger
eating contest or saving a kingom that
is on the brink of collapse I say this
good because that sounds way more like
something I would do yes yes okay we
will follow
along Revelation no it was we're just
proving our strength once again yes
we must prove our strength princess do
not touch the princess ever
again
help
Revelation okay well you know there's
the my family consists of many phoenixes
and maybe one Phoenix made a fast food
restaurants certainly not me because I
saved kingdoms
yes but I guess your memory so that's
true the wrong way yeah yeah yeah
wait that was confusing me
ladies my honorable ladies we got the
wrong way wa we got little my goodess
oopsies we have helping a fast food
restaurant to repay apps mhm onwards
Revelation huz reation h
are we now oh Revelation
Revelation the strong fast restaurant
finally saw suity some say the
hardworking new part time is as fiery as
a phoenix a crumbling crack and fiery
Fortress wall the brave may claim reward
where others fall
oh ooh see you have to jump to it
ah come this way
back you come
[Music]
here wait what was I the girl stands on
the roadside looking dazed as though she
just woke up from a dream a picture in
her hand soon jogs her memory however
all right I need to find this dog Papa
help I kill I kill I shall kill and
protect the princess is expecting a call
from her soon so she'll need thank you
mother this detective has a reputation
to up
don't worry little guy I'll find you I
promise hey what do you want Jord for
leading to is
Jonathan no no no here here
here down here fall water watch out
goodbye he to the
Y do
not nice where are the
rats get
thank you yes Crow Raven
lady we had to we had to do it multiple
times cuz we couldn't find
it yeah that's hard to find yeah right
damn espe in this lighting
reel has to be earned except you earned
it for me IED earn
it I have earned it long time ago in
other ways yes
yes I have a right to listen to
it huzzah
huzar a check once again for the kingdom
or the
queen yes the que the queen yeah yes
Queen
sleigh yes slay is what did a certain
detective invent for The Travelers who
made it this far is it a teleportation
thing no a golden ax oh is a oh wait but
that's like we wouldn't really know this
would we what you think she would create
for us oh definitely a warp Crystal
because she's a Time TR I don't know
this but um I have a feeling a feeling
maybe you are
correct
wow I am just really good with my
intuition what's that over there ah that
looks suspiciously played
suspiciously you should open
it oh it really is it just there oh
there's another book over here too maybe
I read the book
first I leave this for the heroes who
will one day visit this place may it
serve you well each chamber past has
offered you a rhyme revealing Secrets
where you've gone before there's one
last thing to find ear out you climb
what British and therefore I present to
you one more more The Haunting grounds
of creatures of the night within its
depths you'll find a hidden light what I
see ah I see yeah CH
M Crystal are you girls already in the
possession of it yes it is in our
pockets amazing now I own it
too fin
Revelation
Revelation back into the sewers are they
ever ending are we that's that's an
endless loop we live here now that's our
house it is quite a large sewer system
mhm Another Story scary and stinky okay
we find ourselves in the white empty
space the girl still sipping her tea
opens her locket to reveal a number of
pictures
each of them shows a girl who looks
exactly like herself one is searching
for a lost dog another is building some
sort of machine yet another is playing a
video game video game what is that it's
a video G she gazes at the photos with a
warm smile let's see where should I go
today I do
Wonder okay
Revelations
flashback I'm having a
migraine I feel the
migraine
things it's do you
remember yeah wait a second I think the
pictures in my head are coming together
the memories in your mind 60 frames per
second oh oh
wait you girls are probably already have
seen
it but I shall play it for me and the
voices in my head yes we count your lost
memories yes wait bgm is not on okay 3 2
go
no what husband
[Music]
pasta
yeah
oh or wait what Phoenix
Manion she seems to be very into these
memories of her companion she forgot
about
me she hat they share a very strong bond
with one another oh am I not mythical
[Music]
enough
wait
what wait I
was I was
downgraded downgraded does she
[Music]
mean what she mean by
downgraded you don't know of her
memories but it seems she is upset at
them upset at these memories of
hers there's one that doesn't fit in
there's one that's just weird I am
finished watching it but I am
confused what is wrong you're the CEO of
kfp you run an amazing
restaurant as mythical as I thought I
was my goodness you are but you are not
known for your mythical you are known
for your amazing restaurant and amazing
food you should build one to rival that
of the divorc diner by Kia
H maybe maybe I should or maybe I should
prove my
mythical no no I do not want to be known
as the burger lady you are more than
that you are
beautiful exactly beautiful and mythical
and demure and mindful de and mindful
very de very mindful
indeed well thank you for accompanying
me in this adventure of course
I am finally caught up with all of
you if you reach into your pocket you
can use the war you to the king don't
you oh warp to the king you say let see
how to use this
[Music]
thing am I in no need of my horse
anymore you will need your horse it is a
big Kingdom oh there is so many
choices uh Which choice shall I make
Li Castle I will kill this a great
choice me
lady giv me a
[Music]
feather I
am suddenly in a completely different
world
no different place where am I I need
this chicken to write a book this too
much for me as as I am not streaming and
have simply come to help the fair Maiden
uh complete I I to sign off we will be
returning fwell
[Music]
[Applause]
fwell wait before you go nurse Raven
coft will you mayhaps help me with my
trial
tomorrow uh trial I yes I will you have
a trial I will if I am online I will be
your witness you will stay as my witness
yes yes of thank you I will need to
princess
beu and the hot pink one on the stand no
thank you they need to be put the stand
about the the oh uh about sh display I
may not be oh you will not be oh then we
will hold a trial another time it is
fine I will find who did
it I shall leave as well because of have
my queen you this to do accomplish so
I'm sorry I got to oh Fair
so much for your support of course it
was nice to play with you to go to
adventures with you thank so wonderful
to see
everyone
Mario see you soon see you
soon byebye bye goodbye
T May chaos take the
[Music]
world h
H I have a feeling the princess is
not as empathetic as she says she is I
did see her creating
[Music]
that something is going
on with the princess she will not be
around tomorrow is it because she is
hiding do you think do you think the
princess will not be around tomorrow
because she is hiding from a much larger
thing I'm growing quite suspicious of
her there does seem to be this deep
terrible malice Brewing Within These
Kingdom walls I do not want to admit it
so because I want to believe in my
fellow ceruleans
but the evidence is undeniable
here and with what narissa ravencroft
has said that she raises a very fine
valid point that the only one that could
have defaced the
statue
is what the two people of the Cerulean
Guild could either be the hot pink one
or the princess poi pishu
[Music]
there is something very mysterious
and terrifying a
foot Terror bruise in this
Kingdom
well it does seem that even if I
[Music]
am a bit suspicious there is not much I
can do by by myself I am only but one
night so I will do what I
must I will continue this building of
our beautiful wonderful gorgeous Queen
Tam so that she may stand in tall and
beautiful for the coming
days and may the lighten her
heart burned
brightly for all to witness and mayhaps
just
mayhaps mayhaps if we finish this
building and when someone lays eyes on
her they will feel
inspired to put down their arms and
accept her as the true
Queen there has
been many many many
fightings going on
[Music]
lately all right
let
[Music]
me let me put some things
away what if Tam has lied as
well you would dare speak ill of the
queen voice in my
[Music]
head she would never do that the queen
would never do such a thing after she
had shown us such kindness
T would not do
that I purged the evil out of my brain
no I would never think so ill of our
[Music]
Queen
yes let us see we have many
a concrete
what were we
doing what must we do with the queen
right
[Music]
now I must refer to my
blueprints let me refer to my blueprints
to figure out what to
do yes yes
[Music]
yes all
right referring to my blueprints we will
need more of these where did I place
my
[Music]
constructions in
here and then do we have any spare
terracotta
it is okay we will do this for now it
is like this like
so
ah put these away this here we do not
need this for now we do not need this
for now we're just going to sit here for
most of the
time she is becoming more
three-dimensional by by the
second like
this how wonderful how
[Music]
glorious our comfortable
music as we Ponder on our journey
looks like from this angle it looks like
she is walking towards us for a
hug does it not does it not look like
she is running towards us for a
[Music]
hug yes
yes looks like a zombie no she is
running towards us for for a wonderful
hug for she is so kind and
[Music]
wonderful I am referring to my it looks
like we'll need gray
concrete gray
concrete this away we will work on
her her head at a later time let's
finish
her her
arms h
then light gray
concrete more of
these and I do wish to write a book it
seems
that L fart is accepting book
donations I also believe that I do not
know I think that I have won today's
lottery but I am not a 100% sure I will
ask her
tomorrow grab
these minia
[Music]
Terra what were my
numbers I do have a
639 in my pocket I have a 639 in my
pocket right here
I have one
huzzah
huzzah I have one I see it in my pocket
from I do not
know at least 5 hours ago I believe it
was 5 hours ago 6
39 it is she had given it to me
she had given me these numbers
today before the lot checked the reward
amount how much have I
won it seems
that the jackpot is
2,900 coins how
wonderful we can put that back into the
library
[Music]
oh she has done so much work in the
library Scarlet wand
Library it is
beautiful I knew it was not a
scam work in progress do not enter oh
forgive me forgive me I will not
go is beautiful a beautiful beautiful
Library FAA faart she Rings
true may I ask what you are doing
[Music]
KIU no answer
hm oh sorry I was muted oh I see I see
um
[Music]
Park
look I feel I fear the corruption has
spread through the land but are you not
the one building
it just go just go along with it the
corruption the corruption build them
[Music]
inside I have grown suspicious of
her I did not
know something is going on with the
[Music]
princess go along with
what what it is what what is it that she
wants me to go along
[Music]
with look
away look away for now but is it the
stain the stain that Is possessing her
on the head I thought it was a plush
thought it was a mere
[Music]
plush I will keep a close eye on her for
now it is quite terrifying what she aims
to
do yours mine was a FLH hers is not a
FLH maybe if I ask
[Music]
her I will ask her surely this was a
understanding dear kosaki viu princess
koseki viu yes may I may I ask that you
take your hat off for a second so I may
look at your
crown no no well why not I would like to
take a p at your
crown nah no is there a reason it
because it is my buddy and I spent like
$7 million trying to get to him and oh
but you can just hold him in your arms
can you not my inventory is literally
full I I cannot actually take it off
right now oh but later you will show me
yes yes later sure yes yes yes be well
take care yes thank
you oh my
[Music]
goodness
hello call back in a
moment uh please leave your message
after the turn
[Music]
she must she must be busy at the
moment I will call her in a
moment I will I will speak to her
soon yes yes
ah it seems like something just fine I
must refer to my
blueprints yes is this and then like
this okay my blueprints call for
this like
[Music]
this and then
[Applause]
hello
Jonathan oh ah I see I have a missed
call from you gathan yes I wanted to
speak to you privately is are you are
you in a safe
location um I can be I can meet you in
the the tavern on the grounds of uh Jade
sword of the Jade sword
taverns yes the one that c owns I
believe that will be safe enough yes I
will meet you there Fair well fairy well
Fair the well and see you in a moment
see you in a
moment I did not mean to hang up on her
[Music]
knock knock
knock knock knock
[Music]
knock knock knock knock knock it I am
knocking I am knocking on the door I am
knocking I am looking at you from the
door I am
knocking I am knocking you cannot see me
in the door I am knocking I am opening
the door for it oh
hello sorry I was upstairs and I was
just it just there's so many stairs you
see thank you for meeting with me I
didn't hear the door at first yes may we
speak
upstairs yes we
may I aand we speak somewhere
private isn't private enough it is
private
enough I know yes as long as we stand
near the the edge of the the S I think
it is let's go over here and stand here
Elizabeth Rose blood flame I know that
we've had our differences but I am
coming to you in seek of your help your
assistance my help yes I pray tell what
I believe that you are the only one even
though that we are not quite allies or
friends that I you are the only one I
can trust with this information
[Music]
H last night I know you do not like my
statue of the queen Tam Gander I know
that disgust you but last night someone
had defaced it let me send you a sketch
of it in my head yes one second somebody
defaced your statue my my statue I will
be sending it through carrier pigeon was
Hast one
second wait we need we need to go
outside so the the pigeon can come
through oh yes the pigeon the pig the
pigeon must break the window break up
the window no I cannot it's not my place
oh yes yes we out the door out the door
where's side hold on hold
on I F the
sketch there it is oh yes capure the
pigeon yes yes
[Music]
I believe she is the
pigeon she is looking at oh my that is
that is just it is awful it is quite
awful is it not I would not wish it on
my worst enemy I would never do that to
you I I yeah I hope not um gosh that is
distraught terrifying I nearly vomited
at the
sight I vomit at the sight anyway but
you know okay
sah I'll vomit regardless yes yes please
thank you vomit for the both of us when
I had spoke of it Nissa ravencraft your
something I do not know your relation
but Nissa ravencraft had said that she
made a very valid point saying the only
one that could have defaced the statue
is someone in the Cilan Guild because we
can only build on our own
lands yes there is a magic upon these
lands yes and when I called for a trial
princess kipu was very against
and it seems that she is crafting a
corrupted land I fear that the princess
may be
corrupt well if I may be so blunt yes if
I may be so blunt gathan I feel all of
the gathan if I feel all dear gathan I
feel dear
gathan dearest gathan yes yes yes
Elizabeth blood flame I fear lady
bloodflame I
fear okay Gan I
fear you fear lady blood
flame Lady Lady bloodflame what do you
fear I
fear are you listening yes I am
listening and everyone upon these lands
who say they are of Royal Blood but are
not of that what you think they are not
your queen the cat Queen the princess
what I feel they are secretly all in
cuds I believe you only pardon me
because I believe in my queen stop it
snap out of it I I cannot I cannot snap
out of it I cannot she show me such
kindness she how has she shown you
kindness she had built me a home she has
shown me a home she she has shown me
kindness and words that I've never
received from another before and she had
me a note she told me that she had
believed in me and that I would serve as
her
KN gathan they are the kindest words
that I've ever
heard gathan I know now how loyal you
are and how you do have a night's heart
and somewhere within my heart I believe
so
too you should not gravel grel to such a
queen that says pretty words it's all
about actions as well gathan she acted
so much for
us just for you in front of you behind
your back gathan she has been a bully to
others she has been disgusting with her
words she put a phoenix a mighty Phoenix
I do not know if you received that
memory of the mighty Phoenix but she was
so rude to that Mighty Phoenix was
disgusting to watch but I thought the
Phoenix she said I met with her today
she said she was loyal to the
queen she is
loyal but the queen does not see her her
her power she just sees her as another
servant I see but if you even if you may
your words may hold a bit of truth I
would like to believe in her until she
returns
if you think that is okay until I can
confront her but until then I continue
to fight for her and these
lands but I am here I respect your
loyalty gathan I am begging for your
help there is an evil in this Kingdom
and I do not know how to confront
[Music]
it regardless of where your loyalties
Lie Part of Me
wishes to give you my sword your I'm
with you ban thank you lady bloodflame I
I thank you deeply even though we've had
our differences I know that you can find
a kindred spirit within
you right now let's journey to see if we
can find the culprit of the defamed
careful she is inside of her her her
Tower she's in her Tower who is in her
Tower oh the
princess um H she look maybe we could
maybe we could do good night bad
night yes yes who is the good night and
who is the if she steps if she if she
steps into the tavern I could shut the
door behind all right and then there's
something we must do to find the truth
and then we yes yes yes yes hello dear
daughter H hello princess how art thou
I'm good good day ah good day good day
my eyes were blurry for a second
apologies um yes uh so uh you know what
my dear daughter I would like to treat
you to um a special treat at the Tav yes
Tav a
delicious a delicious
treat what kind of treat may I ask it is
about a surprise I have saved it but for
you dear create it a delicious yummy
treat well I must know what it is for
perhaps I may be allergic but you was
spoiled the surprise dear
daughter but uh you know allergies are
an important you know we have multiple
options
okay are you allergic to
chocolate
chocolate are you allergic to cake
cake oh oh I'm good I already have to a
cake in my
Mo you could have more I saved it just
for
you it seems that she really wants to
speak to
you last night you were you were quite
you were quite hesitant of being called
mother and me being called your
daughter I slept on it remember I
remember you were quite you were quite
oh that is quite strange and and
reluctant I look my dearest daughter I
slept on it and I remembered I I
remember yes I remembered as I as I
before I slept I could not even sleep
cuz I was thinking about a night's Duty
and part of a night's duty is to make
others happy and I want to make you
happy by calling you my
daughter
moving all right
mother
yeah you are my mother aren't
you yes and you are princess blood flame
yes I I am princess
[Music]
blood all right I will go with you to
the
tavern H that is a good girl good
daughter thank you I'm going to go get
you the cake all right shall we go to
the
tavern oh wait perhaps we
shall how wonderful you have such a kind
mother you're two kind mothers yes what
a what a kind mother
yes do not disturb grave here what is
what is this oh it is about a justest oh
I I see I see a Gest yeah it is butter
justest a just yes but a Gest butter
Gest ah now come if and sit here dearest
daughter
okay Treet
[Music]
you
know you wouldn't lie to me would you of
course not mother you're my mother
blindly mhm so did you do it did you do
it did you defame the the the statue
over there did you do it did you hey
maybe she did not do it why are you
attacking her all of a
sudden I'm being a strict mother
here you need to on STI you need to sit
here on the naughty step and think about
what you have done trapped her here to
yell at her mother you're scaring me
here on the naughty step my
goodness right here I oh my
goodness why
would look she is crying did you did you
defame that statue goodness gracious it
was I would never like bathan spent
hours on that statue hours yes hours yes
and I watch the glory of the queen yes I
did it wasn't it wasn't me mother I been
I afraid you promise in the name of
blood flame you promise in the name of
blood flame yes it was not me mother you
swear on your mother I swe on blood
flame mother
yes
see well well dearest da
I who did it then who do you think did
it who did it who do you think did it wa
she's in tears and you would push her in
such a way I love you H oh yes oh mother
yes I love you too goodness yes now who
do you think did it
um well there was there was there was
somebody in the what was in the
there was of the Raven Crow saying that
God and G might have defaced their own
statue why would I do that you know I
don't know but I I heard it from
the Nissa why would Nissa ravencraft say
such a thing I don't know well but that
was a suggest that you might have
suggest call how terrible wait a
minute gathan would you take your hat
off for a moment for did you do it to me
did you do it did you do it why would I
do it multi step on the m okay I will
prove to you did you do it no I would
never deace my queen did you you maybe
you were cursed by the witches and you
were you were cursed to Def yes there
are witches dear princess dear daughter
yes there are witches maybe they cursed
you to go and
defame the witches well the witches one
of them is
narissa how am I to know that you are
not the one
she used she used her charm on me she
has used what else has she done to
you you
made no mother you
corrupted corrupted by a raven I would
never I I am stronger than any witch you
hear me stronger more powerful you wait
let me let me test it ning Ren cross
right there
she is behind you yes no she is not as
much as she has stalked me the witch has
stalked me she is stalking me to see my
weaknesses you see
gathan but it seems like she is your
weakness mother you do seem to fall to
her yes I do not fall to her witch are
making every time I mention her name
Northam cross I had too I at too much
bread
Marissa ravencraft has hexed her you are
not trustworthy at
all you are not a trust night at all get
me out of here get me out of here I will
not be trust her thank you my pear thank
you thank
you oh my goodness oh what a
beautiful that's a wonderful beautiful
ansen
pear has made such a beautiful
thing I am not hexed by the witch I made
sure I came to you TR I put my trust to
you and you treat me like this I am
leaving I know not to trust anyone I am
not I am not I will prove this to you I
am not a witch I will sink in the
water oh my Pearl hello
hello my dear husband have you committed
crimes no I have not but I cannot speak
of it here I trust I not trust these
two away away
[Music]
Jonathan I'm receiving a phone call
hello my Pearl you are the only one I
can trust please meet with me behind the
gardens
not to be in their vicinity oh okay I I
I
[Music]
yes ah sorry excuse me yes
yes I hope she's on her
way I cannot we must Converse in
secrecy is she is she on her way I do
not
know my Pearl would surely meet with me
we Willet meet in the gardens I will
wait
here she will be tailed she has a band
she would not abandon
me
[Music]
goodness be
seen cannot be there in front of
[Music]
her oh no no
we will speak she will speak to me and
we will find peace and love and
harmony where where's my Pearl mayhaps
she just cannot find me this the worlds
are very large and
vast she is not with Princess kishu it
seems
[Music]
where where is she where is she I cannot
make eye contact with the
[Music]
princess uh I
mean yeah your partner will tell
[Music]
you your sneak is minus
20 n ravencraft please meet me in front
of the
tavern oh she's
talking nen craft please meet me in
front of the the din don't it when
automatically please make haste make
great haste
convenient it go straight into my brain
I have no time
to to properly answer well not answer
even anyway someone defamed the the worm
Queen oh and it wasn't you was it oh no
I mean we can't I have done no such
thing as a hex I have put no such hex on
you stop spreading misinformation she is
psychic too that was a hex right get out
of my brain witness get out of my brain
get out of my brain get out of my brain
get out
mine unintentionally hexing those and
seducing them I I it's unintentional for
sure Jonathan and Jonathan with G but a
consequence nonetheless you must take
responsibility for your hex's which you
must speak it out with lady bloodflame I
guess I guess lady bloodflame then shall
be my wife from hence forth yes yes I
think if you do that
formally no but I'll do so right now
lady blood yes decided the punishment
for uh or rather the the solution the
solution for the problem is uh we are to
be married right now uh you are already
married no
no I say no I say no I say
no you were just
k no yeah we Mighty Phoenix we are
married we are not that is not how
marriage works yes the Phoenix has
witnessed it so therefore it is Mighty
Phoenix it is not true um I came at a
very confusing no context timing so all
I all I saw was the kiss and now all I
see is your sword well do you not lock
[Music]
her that is a very strong
word I mean she hates me I don't hate
you I don't I could never hate you why
would you even say such a thing banish
the thoughts from your
mind I don't okay I am not thinking of
you anymore haha easy banished you are
banished from my
mind well time to kill myself I
do
you do we follow I must speak with you
in private my Pearl I feel that it
might be might be a matter between two
Quite A Private Matter maybe may may I
speak to you in private now that they
are
gone yes shall we go to the gardens as
plan yes yes let us go to the gardens
[Music]
onwards I think they will not hear us
here my
quite empty yes there is some treachery
of what I sense some evil in these lands
Trey yes and I I did not know I tried
going to lady bloodflame because I saw
her to be reasonable but yes she she is
not she is a very EAS she's levelheaded
though no I attempted I attempted to
appeal to her to her heart and her
kindness but she turned on me so easily
because of the the Scarlet Witch that
she calls narissa ravencraft she's being
influenced by the Scarlet wand yes she's
being influenced by them well I I
believe that lady bloodflame did apprise
you of some things that have happened it
was that
my statue of Queen Tam oh oh that's your
statue I see it is it is for her honor I
I had built it last night and someone
had defaced it in such a ter awful
way well it must have been a member of
Cerulean no it it must have been so I
have been trying to call Princess kosaki
bishu and the hot pink one to trial but
princess kosaki bishu is very very
against being put on trial and she's
acting quite strangely do you notice
suspicious that the stain on her head is
not a plush and I think the stain on her
dead is actually a real stain and it is
corrupting her you could be controlling
her thoughts yes yes that is exactly
what I am thinking and every time I ask
her to show me her crown underneath the
stain she sidesteps it and
refuses uh we must get someone with more
authority to demand the princess prove
her yes bloodline yes she should prove
her innocence I believe yes I believe
that's true what do you propose we
should
do uh I I I I may attempt to question
her
perhaps I think I cannot be there for I
have been there too often that she may
grow suspicious but suspicious okay okay
I will I will make it yes yes please can
trail behind I will trail behind hide
maybe I will try hiding as best as I
[Music]
can must be several
princess is that you yeah wait have you
done your own dungeon yet I mean I mean
the dungeon of the sewers I have yet to
attempt the dungeon but I was thinking
of what
Heroes help sh just murdered my child
what I had a child with with Lady
bloodflame and takaa shiara used her
Revelation on it oh is dead yes my son
has died your
son my son
I'm so sorry I'm I'm so sorry we must we
must have trial for for this Heathen who
has decided to kill my child my child
how could
she where is she wait wait we must SC
you have a child with blood
huh okay I will take you to them follow
me Taki kiar has killed my child what in
this
we left you alone for 3 minutes how did
happen what did you
happened what what
happened child no no no you have
presented a chicken in front of me I am
I am the owner of kfp as you have all
seen in my video I must make chicken
into Fried Chicken that is just how it
goes she calls the video and memory the
memor is a video you madean a memory of
video it is it a strange slang I think
Str slang from her lands
yes the mighty Phoenix has different
wording yes I came up with it it's
easier to say I see it's quite good I
see we we shall learn from this SMY phix
learn learn you can call it a video we
learn
it yes where is the child a memory is a
murdered my child oh it was never your
child you just pretending to get
Elizabeth into a SP that she is not
willing to enter freely I lay eggs what
oh that's wait what you lay
eggs EGS I'm not going to lie my lady
that is a turn off oh my goodness it
seems you have given her the
egg how often how often do you lay these
eggs lay here I don't actually lay wait
how could it be her child would it not
Bea's child kid no it was my child with
where was the human where was the human
in this bird that we saw it should have
been grotesque and disgusting when did
you guys consummate your marriage yes
not know that you guys I I was calling
her a witch like came and trapped me
who's up while we were trapped while we
were trapped in the tree we consummated
our our love for each other no we did
not I trapped her in the tree I mean the
troll came around and trapped her in the
tree um um excuse me the usual incub
incubation time for a bird is about 21
days so if it happened yesterday you
could have not possibly already laid the
egg you time
travel time travel I time I I'm
beginning to think you are a
witch I'm not a witch how can you time
travel if you are not a witch FL at the
St my God Mur attempted murder attemped
murder
M murder what you saying murder because
she's a wit doesn't mean she Des to be
murder um she have to be witch no M I
believe should to The Gallows it is
better Scrat to The Gallows you must be
put to trial the trial you must be put
to trial what else would you be doing
with a wit we question her and we show
her compassion that's not how you do it
in my land you're supposed to put on a
shake and burn her sounds Barb
you to you
are thank you no no I refuse how kind
also she's fine refuse she dead she
killed her no no she's alive she's dead
also uh um ladies uh did you uh did you
uh uh uh see the uh the the the with uh
there is a tournament today today there
is a tournament a grand tournament will
be held in an hour in 10 minutes at the
uh the arena the prize is honor join us
your blad and prepare to test your mind
I did not know that they had in the
kingom oh it's honor but money I love
honor no money we will watch the show
yes we will watch no you must join in
you must join in you must join in it is
partially training you
must it is training as well for the
fight
ahead do not worry Jonathan everybody
gets a wooden sword is a fair fight ah
my
train I was worried I might kill my
opponents but if maybe not I hope you do
Jonathan I mean well not kill but uh
bludgeon them and win but um anyway yes
that will be held in an hour and 10
minutes from now an hour and 10 minutes
oh okay uh yes yes yes yes okay okay so
it's on the hour and hopefully there'll
be more uh participants by then maybe
the princess go
be I was her yes where did she go she
appeared so
quickly oh my fellow Jade member yes
believe it it might be good if we build
it if we built a courthouse I believe
you were working on a bunker no oh yes I
mean yes I mean you can add a courtroom
if you wish yes yes to put trial someone
must Tri must use the Gallows must use
the Gallows on
yes what
what what is this bias against amorn
members that you have since the very
beginning I did not know you were I
believe they eat
money yes true you didn't know no I
didn't look at you think they were there
she's wearing a hat for no reason just
for
fun just for fun it is a very s hat
what's of these biases and I have only
sered my honorable king and queen stand
away from her the eye of ambercoin
stares into my wallet please please do
not look at my your
coins you will have to answer for me
she's a mighty Phoenix your coins at all
gamble house says differently she eats
money what I have never made use of the
gamble house before Oh I have it's quite
fun what if any perhaps I go who has not
gambled
yet are you hurt are you hurt my Hur my
my goodness I quite like it no why you
trying to hurt her why you try to hurt
my
PE I was
burned
sorol fire it seems okay I it's okay it
happens to the best of myself from any
people because it seems like my fire
hurts people
withouts you Che you I like fire
huzzah huzzah you are cured you are
cured cured yes you are cured I don't
know what they are
about from your misuse of your
Revelation you should better now so nice
of you
yes huzzah
huzzah day yes what a joyous occasion it
is fun to jump it is good excise of that
can you cure uh Tim tender of her uh
negative ass a butto she is being worked
on she is not a finished not a finished
statue she
has she's she's under construction she
does
anyway this construction does it abide
by the code she's under construction
she's being worked on wa she looks like
she is doing a a certain run style leave
her alone she is working very
hard she she looks like she's doing a
certain run she is being worked on
can you wait but um are you if you're
adding the buttock are you also adding
the um what's a medieval word to say
boobies buz buom the
buzzom awesome she was not made for for
objectification you look at her and you
look at her with awe and wonder not
to get no but she like she always does
how appropriate her beautiful shape of
her body is also saw something to be
honest she looks like a worm right jonan
it is a shame that I cannot achieve in
world I a little if she's she's almost
she's getting arms
soon it's nothing to be ashamed of she's
going to get arms it's okay be ashamed
of I must honor her shape honor her
shape you see you adding some more
Dimension here yes she is getting some
she will soon be breaking Dimensions
what does that oh what exactly is why is
her front more threedimensional than her
back she is not finished it is just here
for you to look at her have we seen the
Queen's back is it quite voluptuous I
covered by a there is nothing there it
is covered by a cap you will not look
she has a cape on you don't need to look
there's nothing there yes yes I see I
see yes well is accurate no yes it is
very accurate beautiful thank the best
wasn't built in a day so she shall also
not bu be built in a day she's not built
in a day she will be built over two days
mayhaps okay I shall observe her
tomorrow again her beauty I hope to be
impressed by her beauty yes when you
observe her tomorrow she may have a
backside maybe
back
back I love her body my goodness I love
princess what a beautiful hat you have
oh thank
you but I am
[Music]
also I can't hear from here oh
goodness then if he is your companion
are you able to remove him for but a
moment I would like to admire yes yes
yes see I can yeah see I can do it any
Oh what a beautiful crown you have upon
your head thank you yes it is my
indication that I am a prin
I see yes yes yes uh thank you for
showing me your crown I have verify your
princessness thank you it's quite
wonderful you are you are a wonderful
Pearl I can see what Gan season you yes
oh so
kind and Princess thank you I look
forward to your
rule ah yes one day I cannot wait to
take over this beautiful kingdom
one day yet I'm sure that will come huh
yeah huh
oh oh they can fly I forgot
[Music]
whatever I see
what are you staring
at H the beauty of your statue how much
you look like a little fly as you fly up
in a a
fly she is the poop and you are the fly
W do not know what you mean
there uh nothing I this just how loyal
you are oh thank you I worked very hard
no worries in her in her honor as she
has made me her nice
mhm is that really the any reason
yes Jonathan could make you her
Knight I am her
Knight oh well oh you're two timing
that's statue I make you a statue Jan
statue it'll be right here if you if you
wish it I will make you a statue my
sweet my my dad request a smaller one
perhaps you do not want a statue this
large you don't want a bigger one I
don't think I can stand next to the
queen I am not queen or King you can
stand side by side though
might we perhaps hold hands you you want
to hold hands with the
queen um no no no no no that would be
too too to lude oh oh right right now
you die I think she was she was asking
for you don't you want
to your of that in this Kingdom I am
holding hand right now oh oh oh I am I
let go I have let go grabs and drags
away come this way come this way get
this
way pulling you away over here over here
what M what what let them be for a
moment she is she not the queen if she
is the mother of the princess or is she
but a
consort they having a moment I do not
know it seems that handh holding is okay
on wholesome
occasions now kiss what oh now that's
[Music]
who taught you how to kiss they are so
loud um not focus Raven C the person in
front of me with with all these
whisperings in my
ears oh she has run off she is in the
haunted
forest oh that is a haunted forest yes
if you go closer there are signs that
says that the darkness will take you yes
the corruption seems to be sweating I
have quite concerned of this as the
prinet of the Kingdom corruption yes
corruption read the signs oh darkness is
approaching careful careful you want
take
D you want take so much damage darkness
is approaching wait a minute
for huh yes introduce this Darkness to
our kingdom the darkness it's taking
over stains well it's obviously someone
of the civilian cap who has cursed this
uh part of the
land you know who it
was
no no dear husband you're not lying to
me are
you she has taken the hat off her head
what hat
oh oh yeah cuz I why welcome back
princess oh thank
you she's free we have freed we have
freed her of of its
influence so did would you say that
you do you feel strange mayhaps do you
have any memory of the past few days my
head Gan do you have any memories of do
you remember what we've done a couple
hours ago do you remember hello wait I I
this is the first time I'm seeing you
today
[Music]
right it was her
oh do you remember who I am oh no good
you're you're my mother right uh
remember I told you yesterday I'm not
your mother oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
you
remember oh it's the first time I seen
you today right really yes oh gathan and
pearl yes what what is the last memory
you
have
um going to going to sleep last night
and then waking up right now just now
you just working right now oh yes oh so
you do not know of
this
wao what is this seems that a Darkness
has taken over the
land Darkness was it the darkness that
influenced her oh no I don't
know something is a foot I believe so
why are we
Whispering nothing nothing no reason you
stay away from the darkness the forest
is I I am going to create a perimeter
yes let me make let me make some far we
will contain it we will contain the
darkness how do I make a fence how does
one make a fence what does a fence look
like is a fence like this I do not play
I do not craft looks like a ladder how
does one make a fence quick vo is in my
head how do you make a fence what is a
fence sticks s block
[Music]
okay each with a
stick sticks and
[Music]
plank they've disabled it come on I can
do this one
second where the plank uh uh I don't
want to do hers yet lots of sticks
where's the plank one plank like this
like
this God damn it yes M something two sck
the four planks I going to look it up
how to make
V oh it's playing music I've seen it
[Music]
noise doing my best I am a master
Crafter
[Music]
it's beautiful you have made Beau
beautiful what the song's pretty
[Music]
loud
danger I am out
of damn
it what an ingenious design princess
right it's not done yet ah I'm still
working on it it is a work in progress
looks good looks
[Music]
good what vulgar language comes out of
the
[Music]
way I made the
button why are you hitting the
fence it is dangerous princess yes you
must stay back yes stay back from the
fence it is very
dangerous oh
no what did you make this entrance
[Music]
for I really I
really I did think that you did not I
would like to visit you know no the dark
there's darkness in there get out get
out it's already spreading
coin we must block it off where we
can to protect you princess this is to
protect you you must stay away from it
but but it looks so fine no no no it is
to protect you just to protect you a man
do not to go inside this is very
[Music]
dangerous what it is quite vulgar
language
[Music]
danger it's very
dangerous what are your thoughts my
Pearl now that you have spoken to
her where did she go seems she she she
was able to take the hat off take take
the uh creature off her head which was
influencing her actions so believe she
might be safe for now but we should keep
a close eye yes we will keep a close eye
on her in case that it Darkness has
spread root maybe she doesn't even need
the Hat anymore I don't know I do know
maybe I did I did witness her crown on
her head so she is a princess a small
thing a small thing she is Princess but
she just has a stain on her head well I
hope that suspicious the end of it for
now I have blocked out the evil though I
cannot block it out in the others the
other R CS her it influences her it does
can't believe she was so influenced to
break this to
enter I do have to say dear husband have
you visited the new library which has
been constructed I have taken a look
upon it it is beautiful and
wonderful ah then I shall go take a look
I'm curious about this new addition to
theist do take a look farewell fairy
well Fair the well fairy well wait
uh is it is it is is have I um my my
allowance is oh oh yes yes here I I have
been allowance what kind of relationship
is
this no it's support the family business
yes it is for the between the two of us
princess ah okay I will I will leave you
be matters between husband and wife yes
yes she does not understand she's too
young understand fairly well for now I
will see you thank you dear hus yes I
will definitely not be going to the
Ember coin what
[Music]
what she would not go to the Amber coin
would she
[Music]
she's more room she's not
going
see make more of
these she definitely would not she would
not lie to
me let's do
this and then gather it once more
[Music]
then we can do this once
more gambling addiction it is a real
problem but it is not a problem that she
will face because she is not going
gambling why do the voices in my head
doubt her so
she would not betray me why would she
lie to me she has no reason to lie to me
let me refer to
[Music]
my is that the
princess
with the hat on her head once more I me
pH
call
hello hello gathan I am calling you yes
in the request for a
uh just in even just in the form of your
voice perhaps but uh could you please
share with me the information of how to
create a a golden shovel with efficiency
free I am in the possession of a golden
shovel but I do not know how to make it
effici of um if you look at the bar of
um look within and you will see a bar
and what number do you see upon within
that
bar wait M I'm in a call right now I'll
talk to you in a moment uh 21 you must
reach once you reach the age of 30 on
that bar you will be able to use it to
enchant your shovel and you have to
obtain some lapis lazuli to enchant it I
have those oh but it says like the the
the table says Fortune free is what I
will be getting not efficiency free you
must perhaps there's another one when
you try crafting a stone shovel and then
putting an enchantment on it to cycle it
you will want to uh you have to gacha it
and if you want new choosing you will
need to place an enchantment on a
different item before you can enchant it
once
more it is gotcha so first I shall level
and then I shall try putting in
different tools yes to see the result so
check the tool again once you've
Enchanted another item and if efficiency
3 is not there you will need to enchant
another tool oh oh I appreciate your
assistance it is no problem Tanashi
karia Shakira yes for short yes Shakira
for short therey well please call upon
me if you need my assistance again
conratulations yes
yes one second my blueprints my
blueprints I must look at my blueprints
just like this wait it's not going like
[Music]
okay
actually according to the blueprints it
does not need to be like
[Music]
this I have crafted a blueprint out a
mock
queen and I am looking at the blueprint
I have done it
when I was not showing my memories my
Visions but it is a very very grueling
task this task a grueling one but we
must do it for the
queen this is in danger she has the Hat
on again
[Music]
well it is okay
surely mayhaps any hero who's not
traversed the sewers as of
yet if you need someone to go with you I
will
[Music]
always and like this
mayhaps like this yes
yes and we will do it again over
here
um making sure I am making sure that I
am doing this
correctly as building is quite
difficult like this
[Music]
all
right make sure that I do not go out of
[Music]
bounds here we
go it is part of our
arm we have built a part of her arm
H wait actually it is
[Music]
two
oopsies like
this huz the queen Tam
Mander she will rise
again I will also have to figure out how
to make a smaller
statue of my
[Music]
my dear my dear Pearl mayhaps just a
giant
head you think she would enjoy a giant
head of
hers could be right here a large head
right
here you think she would like
that a bust May suffice
let me
see this we will need to make some
more
sand gray dye
and light gray dye there we
go like
[Music]
this I think we'll need a lot so I will
make
[Music]
we'll do a full stack for now and then
we will make a light gray one light
gray here we
go the queen would appear to behead her
but what if we make her
bust if we make her from the bust up
would it look like she is being beheaded
or would she appreciate that
[Music]
put this away for now we do not need
it
[Music]
so I'm not sure how to make a smaller
statue is a problem
[Music]
how
large we will have to consult the
blueprints I have been Consulting the
blueprints very very
[Music]
intensely will we have enough space for
her we are we are running limited on
building space
[Music]
this it is quite hard to scale down in
this
realm if only I was more wise on how to
scale her further
down miniature alter ego but even
crafting that may be very very large it
may him up come out very large you see
the issues with lots of building
projects is that that I am not efficient
in building in these
lands yeah I am still but an amateur but
I am doing my best I will only grow
better in the due
time but we have very very little
time that is to
say this one more
[Music]
so like
this you like one might call pixel art
maybe mayhaps I will be able to craft
something like pixel
art just do this
[Music]
rid of
this
[Music]
yes
then and we will
do we'll do
[Music]
this like this like
so we'll just do this for now now we are
running
out a pearl Fountain would be
Majestic a pearl
Fountain we will see once I am able to
consult my my grafting table to make
blueprints I will be able to see what we
can craft on a much smaller scale
[Music]
like
so like
so let's make more of
[Music]
this
ohal raven craft has
[Music]
returned me call
her are you safe Fair
Maiden no I am
dead you are where where are you are you
buried yes I'm in the ground where where
are you H in in the ground in the
ground am I speaking to your ghost
yes you must avenge me who who murdered
you uh Takashi Kara
Shakira yes I did see it I did witness
it how will I avenge
you uh please uh send her to The
Gallows my ghost will come to watch to
the your ghost will come to watch can we
revive you somehow
uh yeah yeah yeah I mean I I'm a ghost
so I guess I guess I'm able enough to do
enough are you truly
dead
yes I do not know how to cope
goodbye this it pains
[Music]
me hello hello who is it did you know
that
Nissa Raven cross who is it it is
Jonathan you do not remember my voice do
you not do not recognize my
voice you not to recognize my voice that
is not the matter did you know that did
you know that narissa ravencraft is
dead I have spoken to her ghost and she
says that I need we need to avenge her I
spoke to her
ghost what you should call her ghost you
should try connecting to her ghost to
seek answers go go speak to her speak to
her ghost
now she will speak to
her see like
[Music]
this continue building
cannot believe that she has been
murdered
though that Shakira would kill her in
such a
[Music]
way what was her motivations to
kill goodness is
gracious it seems that she was we
already know who but why what is motive
for for the
murder it's
terrifying in the
accident she would not surely there was
a
[Music]
reason accidents do not really hold up
in the court she must be tried
seems I not do this
here I am sinking I canot fly in time ah
ych was that
[Music]
the murderer
what is she
doing what is the Mur
[Music]
doing to
this what a strange world that you can
just see a murderer run so freely on the
[Music]
streets grab these
destruction of the
queen I would do no such
thing how terrifying how
[Music]
barbaric we will do this for
now like
so and then
[Music]
here like
this we will finish that another time we
will place this here as
well and
then like
this and this yes yes there's only one
only one one
oops take
that and like this is the wrong color no
it is it is wrong color take this
[Music]
away at
this her
arms it is her arms let me refer to my
blueprints now to see what to do next
what wondrous joyous day her arms have
been
completed all right on to her
head I took matters to heart I know
everyone was saying that we must create
her hair vents in order for her to
breathe so I did I did take those
comments to heart and and we will
attempt to make her hair vent which is
one second I think it's better if I take
a a friendly photo in my head here so I
can look upon
it gaze upon
this like
this yes she will not
overheat I am creating her hair
vents it is like
this oh this is the wrong color what is
this blue terra cotta I use it's not the
right
color I don't have so much blue
terracotta what is
[Music]
this light blue terra cotta all right
light blue terra
[Music]
cotta light blue terra cotta we will
need many many many
put these away for now you're going to
focus on the
head and grab this for some
terracotta for some light blue terra
[Music]
cotta yes
yes and we continue all right
[Music]
when will the queen return she did not
say when only that she was going on an
expedition to a neighboring land to
ensure peace she's doing some peace
talks and I believe her I trust in her
wholeheartedly I have no reason to
distrust the queen she has been nothing
but good to me
always like this
[Music]
I must refer to these very
intensely perhaps I build this in
here I sit upon the King's
throne my silly Pearl what is she doing
two
one two
[Music]
three what is that what is happening my
dear
[Music]
pearl one
two one two what the king is not dead
yet one 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 2 3
4 upon it she surely it is a Gest she
may be sitting upon the throne but not
[Music]
as know's going
on nothing nothing is happening surely
surely nothing is happening it is just a
friendly lovely
day I am now Consulting my
[Music]
blueprints yes surely it is a Gest one
two one 2 3 4 one up here
I'm looking
one 1 2 1 2 3 4 1 2
3 all
right then it's like
[Music]
this one two
three such as this
her hair
[Music]
vents it is her hair vents 1 2
three it looks like a bow right now but
worry not
patience
patience she will be made complete
she'll be made full
in due time in due time she will look
complete is one 2 three one two 3 one
two three one two three one two three
one two one
two
this like this let me look one two three
one two one two one two three
and it would be one 2 one
[Music]
two
one 2
3 I am working so hard and so
[Music]
tirelessly and
then 1 2
3 start
one two
three nope it just one
[Music]
over one
two
go and then right here is when it
becomes
[Music]
three my tears once becomes
three grab my
block I will not disturb the princess in
her whatever she is
[Music]
doing my Pearl would surely understand
she knows although I am loyal
to the queen I would never desert
her she is a strong and
independent woman if she does not need
for me then I will not just
go one 2 3 4 1 2 3
[Music]
then
continue is 2 3 4
1 2 3 4 five
six like
so one 2 3 4 5
6 and then which will be one two one two
one two three four
[Music]
five one two three
four five here
one more
here it is her it is our
Queen She it is our
Queen Our
Queen
huz I
[Music]
fine her head is looking very very
onedimensional but it is fine it is fine
that her head looks quite fight to
onedimensional
she will be fixed she will be
[Music]
fixed all right what does the side of
her head look
[Music]
like quite a
conundrum like this it's looking like
this
look down there is something very very
mysterious Happening Here I believe it
has something to do with the princess
and her
[Music]
corruption but I did not know who to
trust I have told so
many and it is
like no one truly
oh they speaking
[Music]
about I'm not close enough
surely I'm close
enough you do you do not fail to make me
[Music]
smilees in theast other oh well mistakes
help us grow yes I learned the princess
Ed yes and I mean if you are as you say
my dear and you are a princess then yes
princesses do not ride their horses in
the castle
I good
go what is
happening what is happening over
[Music]
there what is going
on
well
interesting whoa thank you red voice in
my head Jonathan your streams your
memories are a highlight of my day I
adore your silliness and energy you have
an incredible talent for role playing
and pulling out the best part of Others
May the recipients of Jonathan's Oaths
prove ever worthy of this most perfect
night thank you
Sycamore may you grow as bright and
Shining as possible may your branches
grow so
they they can and cover and shade all of
the
fair subjects around you you have you
have a very wonderful
heart huzzah huz all red voice in my
[Music]
head much to ponder here it is one two
one
two it is it is like
this I falter because I do not have
confidence in my my building like
that one two three one two three like
so have confidence I will attempt I will
do my best to have have confidence takes
another photo in my
head it'll be easier this way um let's
see is
this like
[Music]
so and then one more further down
like like
[Music]
so oh it is
fine like
so she is gaining some Dimension and
soon she we will be breaking the
dimensions here one two believe it is
one two one
two like
this then here like
that like this
mayhaps all
[Music]
right like this
we need a lot of hair for our dear
[Music]
Queen she has many many many many many
her head must be
filled or she is wise and knowledgeable
how many blocks is it up here
one 1 2 3 oops 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
9 is one
2 3 4 5 6
78 nine mayhaps that how large her head
is is
a it is a large head I believe it so 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9
1 2 3
4 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
[Music]
eight
one one 2 three 4 five 6
eight for her there ah oh thank you
Queen
[Music]
the queen is just full of such Loving
Thoughts thank you voice in my head T
aniki there Jonathan was a g while I am
but one of many thoughts floating around
in your head I find your Devotion to the
queen admirable she is blessed to have a
stalwart Soul such as yours supporting
her that I can't deny thank
you thank you thank you kind word in my
head I wish to write a book later for
quom Mar before I am to
[Music]
depart and hopefully you guys will enjoy
the book that I
write or Miss fauna a fauna Mart to
donate into the
library like this like so
[Music]
we need more we are in dire need of more
Terra cot for the
queen here we
go her very very large head that is full
of very very large thoughts
[Music]
she currently provides
shade for all those who desire it what a
nice and generous
Queen I think it is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 yep
it is so it would be here 1 2 3 4 5 6
78 and then her head would be one extra
block this way
surely surely I did not make a
[Music]
miscalculation be like
this a platform to
rest on top of the Queen's
head long may she
rain have we identified the source
we have not yet identified the source of
the mysterious cryptic
message I am not sure we ever will but
just know that whatever it may be may it
find peace May that voice find
peace 1 two
three it'll be one
two did like
this this is wrong 1 2 three
so should be 1 2 3 as
well is
it has to
[Music]
be actually is this head too large I do
not know I can only
pray this is 1 2 three here
[Music]
one two three and then like this so it
would go around like
[Music]
this fund for literature by Jonathan
thank you a voice in my head junda for
the kind kind word thank you voice in my
head David it's a Hort for the Queen's
Landing upon her return huzzah I do not
know how she
intends to arrive up here but if it is
what you say I will I believe you one
two like
this I think I have
miscounted there may have been a
miscount on the top of her
head just maybe a little
too one too
this maybe a little large this here this
extra here I think this is a little
[Music]
extra send it
down it's like
this we are trimming her hair we are
giving her a trim a little bit of a trim
[Music]
then let me get her ribbon I will
acquire her
ribbon up we
[Music]
go so it
is one two three
one
two then is's one two again and then one
then there's two again that what it
looks like
not no I will count it one two 3 one two
one two one one
two and this one is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7even
eight one is eight is this eight 1 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9 it's a little
large we will fix we'll fix the top of
her head soon we will fix the heliport
landing on the top of her head as we
carve the sides of her head
thank you voice in my head Queen te May
the queen reward your lord SE with her
eight trillion coins when she sees to
Statue May the gods bless you Jonathan
huzzah huzzah good day to you you
perhaps believe that the long strand on
the top of thine head could be an
antenna that allows to communicate as we
do to
yourself well voice in my head what Toto
dial I do not know what the antenna on
my head serves as what purpose it serves
but whatever you want to believe that is
what it that is what its purpose is
who am I to deny
you your own
thoughts this is a free kingdom is it
not then it will remain a free Kingdom
till the ends of
time 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
[Music]
and
then we go
here ah it seems
that lady blood flame has
been killed by a m
stain nope not like this
[Music]
no it must be
in one
two like this one
two
[Music]
ribbon
ribbon ribbon
and then one
[Music]
two like
this sir Jonathan I admire thy
dedication to your queen Tam I believe
she will be proud of thy work huzzah
thank you voice in my head sonic Jerry I
appreciate the kind words thank you word
in my head half and half Jonathan G this
is what a voice in your head stay true
to the queen Tam deny the naysayers and
expunge those Surfers for Tam Gander May
her glorious massage and thy image bless
the lands of Le bestl huzzah huzzah good
day to you huzzah huzzah and thank you
voice in my headed Jeffrey for the
wordless support I feel it I feel your
wordless support within in my heart in
my heart
thank you where in my head Infinity I
must say I'm astounded by the pure
heartedness displayed By Night Jonathan
throughout their journey in liestal
despite the schemes and plots displayed
by others Jonathan's light shines bright
thank you I appreciate it
that sometimes I may linger in my faith
because of all the things that have
happened around me but it is the voices
that keep me strong
it is all of you that remind me of what
it is that I am truly fighting
for so that I may remain ever
Vigilant just get
this like
this and then
[Music]
here or one wonderful beautiful
veil the Queen's wonderful
Veil and we go this
[Music]
way like
this
then
here continue
craft for her veil is very
[Music]
important yes yes
yes you're here to mislead me why would
you mislead
me why would you do such an evil thing
surely you are not here to mislead
me right
[Music]
right place this here oops not
there
here like
so and then like
so then is one two three Neath it one
two
three one
behind 1 2
3 like so
then it is 1 2 1 2
3 it's four this
way one 2 3
4 2 three like so no it is only two 1 2
3 is next to
[Music]
it like
this taking more photos of my head
[Music]
like
so like
this oops did not mean to do that quite
yet take this we cannot let too many
blocks go to
[Music]
waste one
two is it over here just a little
further a little further
away we work from here just like
this and one
[Music]
more and
mayhaps we'll go around
[Music]
mayhaps like
this and then we will fill
her ear
[Music]
down we'll place this here for now we'll
figure out her ear
later does have an ear though it would
be sticking out
[Music]
here is it correct I believe it is so
the ear would be here
for her to hear her subjects it is true
is
[Music]
true her ear so that she may listen to
all those near far and wide we have
completed one side of
[Music]
her like this huzzah huzzah
H
[Music]
huz and
then has her whole arm over
[Music]
there let's do the other
side or we can wrap around to it I feel
as if I do need to place some um
lanterns inside of her for else she will
spawn
bats I believe that is a thing in which
she spawns
bats we will have to make her
glow even better do you think it is
better that people who walk by here bat
did you not spawn in the city oh
Splendid I do not have to fill her with
light anyways
not on this server huzzah huzzah no
bats well if she does not spawn bats
then I do not need to fill her with
things all right and then the back of
her head I must take a screenshot a
photo a photo of the back of her head
and count these blocks
here what is this it would be
[Music]
from starting from here it would be 1 2
3 4 five 1 2 3 4
[Music]
5 and then it
is one two three one two one two three
two the tournament starts
shortly I suppose I will end I will take
a break so that I may participate in the
[Music]
tournament though I am not seeking any
Glory I do not seek to win it is only
to join in on the festivities so that
they are not alone in it
ah my Lord sire Jonathan in this world
of Harlot charans and would be your
Surfers your honorable loyal life is the
only thing deserving to rule I beseech
you take the throne for thine
myself well voice in my head Kai guy it
is very kind of you to suggest that I
take the throne for my know self but I
see no reason to I am very happy in my
role as a knight and I do not think
myself to be fit for
rule thank you voice in mine head
aquatic I kneel to you Jonathan the hero
I hope the generations come will
continue to honor your name and remember
your loyalty to Queen gander huzzah
huzzah a has on this good Fair Day the
tournament has been delayed by half an
hour then I will continue to build until
the tournament is to
start thank you voice in mine head
frigid Noble night while you may not
meet the lanterns should you need the
lanterns found outside the kingdom gates
are free and anyone can take
them
huzzah thank you dear frigid I will be
sure if I am in ever need of a lantern I
will go and take it from outside the
castle gate
one 2 3
4 like this like
so and then it
is feels a little off balanced for her
head is it like this let me look I think
it is 1 two 3 four five sticks
out 2 3 4 five
all right one two three
oops four five I think this is
fine all
right then we
continue she does have a large head but
it is because she is full of kindness in
her
heart that she has such a large head
we have to
[Music]
obtain
more
um I believe more
concrete and Terra Cotta are in
order let's get the
[Music]
concrete and then let us
light blue terracotta we continue our
[Music]
build you may not want the throne but
you are my queen thank you kind kind
thought I appreciate
it I do not think I am fit to be a ruler
but if you were to believe in me and my
values it would please me greatly when
to
[Music]
like so but then one twoo yes one two
does seem to be balanced it is
equal and then it
goes on one the third one one two 3 so
it is 1 two 3 down
here like
so and then like this
nope did not me to do that it just goes
down such like
[Music]
this and
then leave her head
[Music]
how far down does this
go it is one two three before it juts
out one 2
three like
[Music]
that then three
across and three like
this thank you voice in my head who is a
pigeon JoJo the Pigeon in case you may
ever need one sir Jonathan I volunteer
as a backup carrier pigeon for you to be
able to send messages to your fellow
empaths and other maidens other maidens
there are quite a bit of fair maidens in
this lands in these
lands I will call upon you if I ever
need a pigeon if I ever need a pigeon
with haste I will call upon you thank
you for offering 1 2
three is
inside can finish this side of her head
mayhaps there nothing there nothing it
is either just a trials and tribulations
that a night must go
through we will
continue it is yes it is but a flesh
wound it is good that we should we
should my goodness it's quite terrifying
in there the darkness does seem to be
spreading quite a fair
[Music]
bit all right let us be very
careful when doing the side of her
head thank you voice in my head a night
shy huzzah huzzah to you as well
[Music]
is like
this
photo my
mind so it will be one
[Music]
two like
this no
actually be more similar
to one
two all right it's actually
here we'll solve this
soon I am going to build a bath we will
build a bath we must fill it with
water let us go
[Music]
oh hi
gathan did you solve your beloved's
murder oh I was told that uh by by her
ghost that uh kiar no Shakira that's it
was the one that that killed
her it seems you are hit by horses very
often oh yeah
it seems like it's a tradition one day
it will not hurt out the
way my goodness they do not care about
the pedestrians on the street no they do
not but maybe I maybe I'll become
stronger than this you know how some
Warriors like punch each other to get
stronger if I get punched by horses I
will get stronger like like a horse so
are you saying that you will take home
the Championship today
if the ping ghost doesn't get me maybe
oh
well it's is her the
murderer uh
well you
know maybe the ghost was wrong you do
not believe in the ghost of your
beloved my beloved I never said she was
my beloved you were
W married we are you had a child you had
a child out of wedlock stop stop
spreading room oh my
[Music]
goodness cannot believe that they had a
child out of
wedlock
disgusting oh the
gods they would they would have a
child so
freely did not
know did not think that
lady bloodflame was like
that oh but thank you voice in my head
docu Jonathan I Kneel To
Thee the true hero of the Heart of Gold
your sh dedication and loyalty is
admirable I wish Good Fortune for your
future endeavors praise to Queen Tam
Gander huzzah
huzzah oh this just a
princess thank you voice in my head time
to cleave Jonathan I Ask Of Thee if your
Pearl does you wrong I implore you marry
the true Queen Tam gandered herstead you
are fit to be a king and she a queen
no that
sounds
Blasphemous just because if I were to be
divorced to my to my sweet Pearl you
suggest that I marry the queen to
suggest such a
thing I Spit on the
idea thank you taku once again for this
the sweet message in the voice in my
head praise Queen Tam Gander it seems
that my male pigeon had a brain fart yes
yes it is the pigeon's fault that it was
mispelled the pigeon does seem to have
quite a neack for spelling things
incorrectly ah more voices in my dear
dear head huzzah loyal servant of Tam
Gander your service to Our Lady and
master shall be well rewarded despite
her absence and you grant her great
honor with your endeavors Jonathan gar
has not my last name Go With Honor thank
you huzzah huzzah to you that's up to
you lad another voice in my head tincho
you can do it Jonathan we believe in you
you're my inspiration huzzah huzzah good
day good day to all the fellows all the
sweet fellows you are quite kind you are
kind and sweet with your words much
appreciative oh
hello Jonathan with the G hello Miss
ninoa how fair the I am building a
statue of our dear Queen wow she's
beautiful yes it looks just like
her it does how has your day been in the
Kingdom it's been great we have uh
traversed the sewers you have found
found things don't you have found things
memories
may I ask you did my dear sweet Pearl
say anything about me after she had
regained her
memories
uh
um she she did
mention something about detective
work detective
work and how she should offer her
services oh she should that would be
great to find
whoever ruined the statue of the queen
my
Pearl what do you hear
something something that sounds so
beautiful like
like are you okay there you so near the
dark stand Dark Forest you must leave
give
leave stretch
[Music]
my my dear sweet Pearl hello I am your
Pearl I I heard that you
had you had you had gotten your memories
back yes and you
are just nothing I am just a mere humble
Knight I am Jonathan G it is nice to
meet you dear oh jonath G what is your
name ah my name is Amelia Watson I'm a
detective it is a pleasure to meet you
Amelia Watson well oh it's nice to meet
you too night I'm here to offer my
services oh your services
oh do you recognize this I
do you sound it is just like you in your
likeness I believe that is me it is
you well I will I will leave you to it I
wish you much luck on your detective
services
oh thank you Knight let me know if
there's anything I can help you with yes
of course farewell fairly well I will
contact you fair well yes fairy well was
your name I am Jonathan with a G ah
Jonathan with G that's right okay I will
see you around Jonathan with a G I see
you around farewell farewell farewell
hello oh hello let's
go it seems
that the worst what we feared has has
come
true and not even the queen can save
me are there any Gods out there that
would I believe that it is time to write
our
story let me see let me acquire some pen
and ink a moment a moment my dear voice
is in my head what does One require a
book
or just want acquire a
[Music]
book let let me figure out how to craft
a book and so that we may we may write
we may write something some leather some
paper leather and paper I do think we
have
some leather and
paper but isn't there an easier way to
obtain
it do we
get no we have to make it
ourselves yes
yes we will we will make
[Music]
it we must get
paper paper through sugar
cane and we will go grab
some so let us go let us depart
it is time to write in our Journal so
that we
may I I cannot face her just yet let
just go over
here where's the
leather some
[Music]
leather her voice is as sweet as the
first day that I've I've heard it
you can do you believe in
me de vo is in my head I have found a
book what is next a feather and an ink
sack yes let
me thank you sweet sweet voic is in my
head for the support thank
you I will have to confront these words
another time as I am a little how does
one say a little frazzled currently
currently just just a little frazzled I
am sorry I will attempt to collect
myself I am showing such
a miserable sight of me I did not want
to show everyone the side of
me but this is a little hard to
remain strong
sometimes now where did I place that
feather where are are the feathers that
I have so squired away yes a
feather all right we have a feather and
then we must get an ink
[Music]
sack let's go let's us
go and here we are to obtain our sweet
ink sack
where is it yes here we
are I think we can craft a book over
here in here in the
[Music]
blacksmith
yes let me see what
was it is
book in sack and a feather your book and
a Quil
here we
go I think I would like to write the
book
where I hold some dear and fond memories
let me see I believe
that I believe the spot you write it is
over
here where is it yes here in this spot I
remember like
it was just yesterday I think this is
the best spot to to write to write this
note yes
all all right all right let's
see a
book a a book for the library I am going
to write a story for the library it is
just a silly story
how shall we write it how shall I pen
the
story oh of course every good Adventure
every great adventure begins with a Once
Upon a
Time that is how all great adventures
start is it not it is this is how all
great adventures
begin Once Upon a Time from the
beginning from the beginning once one
upon of
time this is just a story why why are
the voices in my head and such Agony and
such pain why do you cry so do not cry
Lift Your Head Up Lift your heads up
high there's no no reason to cry let us
write the story together okay let a
smile and write this story
together once upon a time
there
was was
there there
was a night yes there was a
night once upon a time there was a
night he
traveled the roads roads
alone for he had no purpose
no purpose no please it is it is a happy
story it is a happy wonderful joyous
story there was an emptiness in
[Music]
him for he had lost his memories and
forgotten all that he held
[Music]
dear why would was I placed
here what is my
purpose what is my
reason questions he asked
himself day in day
out when
when
when he
found light a Shining Light
a queen to
serve a guild to depend
[Music]
on and a lovely
companion a companion in which he could
call
home what but
like
him everyone around him had lost their
[Music]
memories they continued to fight side by
side despite this despite this yes
despite this despite this they continued
to fight and journey side by side
even without their
memories they
knew
intrinsically that they could rely on
each
other but as each day
passed everyone
knew everyone
knew that these days would come to an
end the memories would
return and when they
returned would they be the same
person as they were
[Music]
now something it was something in the
back of their minds something in the
back of their minds forever
[Music]
knowing this they continued
on hand in
hand making the
[Music]
most making the most of it I do not
think I can fit that in the
page they continued on I will we will
get rid of this line making the most of
it this situation is
[Music]
implied the
night suddenly full of
purpose was called
hey what was this Knight called a silly
Knight he was a silly foolish night was
he not this night was quite silly and
foolish do not not cry it is just a
story it is a story we are donating it
to we are donating it to the library it
was a foolish Knight but he did have a
heart of cult was C yes he was an an
honest Knight was C an honest Noble
night but the night was
conflicted for inside of him was a self
[Music]
selfishness he wished that no
one
would gained their memories that no
one's memories no one's memories would
return so that he could keep
living in these peaceful days
[Music]
but alas but but
alas but
alas there a
story is Journey does
not end
[Music]
here he holds his convictions in his his
heart or he
knows and he will continue
on and he
will continue on with his head held
high for he
knows he knows how
selfish or he knows a selfish
request such as as his could
never could never
be could never be
[Music]
true and that that seems to
be seems to be the end of the story for
now
[Music]
is just a it is just a simple tale tale
of a night yes it is do not
cry do not do not cry my my dear voice
is in my head it is just a silly little
story of course there's no way that it's
true I have made this up to donate to
the
library the library would trly
appreciate such a donation yes it is not
true it is a it is a hero's journey oh
there's so many
pages if I sign it will there be a bunch
of empty
[Music]
pages I guess we will sign
Tales of a
KN I cannot put
that a knight's
taale a sign and
close leave a final message maybe as
a a note
afterward well it seems oh thank
goodness that it does not yes yes oh are
there any is there a
Scarlet I do not think that there is a
Scarlet wand
online so I will have to I will have to
give it to them another time I will hand
the book to them at another
time yes
[Music]
yes it is okay do not worry for me my my
dear voice is in my head your kindness
is too too sweet but
those words should not be for me there's
nothing wrong with me it is fine it's
just another sweet Blissful day another
another
day we'll place this here for now and
let
us let us finish part of the queen yes
we still have to finish the queen we'll
finish the queen
for
[Music]
now let us
see what were we looking
for it's over
here into our
bags I am getting a phone
call
hello hello by uh by chance are you
going to be coming into the uh the arena
for the
tournament I do not know I will I will
make it yes I will I will I will arrive
yes I will come to the arena yeah I will
see you soon wondrous fairly well okay
yes fairly in a moment in a in a in a
moment in a
moment all right thank you see you
soon don't no
I I do not know I do
not I don't want to sour the
mood
but I know that lady bloodflame has
worked very hard to set up a
tournament
today so I will I will I will enter this
tournament and then
mayhaps I will no what why am I speaking
like this we will have great fun there's
nothing
wrong there is no mood that needs to be
lifted it is fine huzzah we will go and
we will have a blissful time and it will
be great and wonderful and joyous a
joyous
day huzzah huzzah
it will be wonderful a wonderful day oh
thank you for the support dear words in
my head I appreciate it I appreciate
your
kindness I know not why you would show
such kindness to a knight like
I some days I do not even know what I am
fighting
[Music]
for I would say that I am
fighting for the queen but no
I will say no
more I cannot say anymore I do not want
to believe it I will not say anything
else I am fighting for my queen for has
she has shown me a great
kindness I will continue on in this
quest to honor the queen look at her she
is almost there she is almost
threedimensional
she is partially finished ah ah thank
you Queen thank you dear
[Music]
queen or the queen yes yes or the queen
why did it drop me right
[Music]
here let us
see we do this
[Music]
here then two
and one and then two
again and then we
do
[Music]
here like
this shall I go meet them has the battle
already
[Music]
begun
this and then
like
[Music]
this and this
here it's here it's
[Music]
here here like
this they're waiting oh I will go I will
meet them there let us go
to to the
arena what is the
entrance is this the entrance is this
the entrance I see them to theone no
it's not
hello yes hello welcome welcome we
waited cuz your your beloved is going to
fight first against Freda oh I I do not
have a beloved I do not have a
beloved if you may come with me if you
I'm kill your exb beloved I'm going to
kill them seems it seems her memory has
returned and she has forgotten about me
so if you could play along and and
continue yes as if she does not know me
if you if you could just kindly play
along yes uh sure yes thank thank you
are you okay I am you okay bro I am fine
let's
goah huzzah
huz huz
[Music]
and and and Jonathan one of you click
this guy first and then the other one
also joins I clicked it I clicked it I
am ready to
Du not you I will not Jonathan Jonathan
first her name is not Jonathan it is
Amelia
Watson I believe I well I wrote it down
as Jonathan now I see I see wait why
does it say dual
canell start again minutes have
fast H
yeah he is
gatekeeping quite literally not use our
Revelation correct uh you get poofed you
get magically poofed and then you get a
wooden sword away from you you do not
use your Revelation yes I I am not able
to it says the arena is currently in use
try H that's strange let me try it says
I've joined the red team
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh let me join the duel for some
reason are you in a party I I'm not in a
party now I left it I just banded the
party it says we're in a party
together J J sword the CH sword J
sword CH sword user it says I joined uh
sword okay I'm I left I left the game so
somebody here I'll just I I will go away
for a moment and come back J
sword it seemed it worked when I when I
left my party though so maybe it is to
do with parties no don't leave where are
you
going no dear J sword user do not go you
embarass a
I'm back some people have notated on how
to use the futuristic keyboard okay do
not bully my jistic gu member how dare
you all right try again she's wearing a
red hat oh yeah she's wearing a red hat
how are you the Jade sword you wearing
red hat it should say start it didn't
work cancel cuz extra dramatic stay in
and one you click okay I joined you
joined
oh yes it says I snome
hat say
start yummy red B
cake in his
brain oh thank you kind words in my head
I seem to have missed while I was
writing my story so I will address them
at the
end all right let the game yeah begin
yes they will fight
yes
theying fight fight they're fighting
fight
[Music]
huzzah fighting oh they fighting I want
I want F
her
come it
seems there only one stand
well congratulations on your
win wa she disappeared too oh again as
well magic three so freder is the winner
of the F yep okay now I okay best of
three ah best of three best of three
okay okay okay best of
three best of
three here we go oh
oh I see see how it
is again what does again oh they are
circling each other what does the winner
win all they are backing away potato uh
potato salad honor and honor she's not
let her touch her oh she ran forward
fighting nothing ex this is intense
exchanging
blows this could be
anyone's is any yeah
true
seems
strong who comes from I guess I am out
of this tournament ah my head yeah you
did you did very well though really
hard oh I'm sorry that was not very will
M as I watch the rest of the
tournament okay next up is be and
Shakira and Shakira Shakira Shak M
Shakira
Shakir
so click the guy and join the duel and
one of you will have a start what
happened okay are you ready uh very
ready okay let's go for Honor
oh they fighting they are fighting go to
her no oh they exchange Clowes oh oh I
respect her boundaries oh I can force
myself on her just because there's a
possibility will she even it would be
overwhelming for her Shakira wins
overwhelming
well would be two of battle oh mighty
Phoenix has won I princess after
I
am we shall try again though will round
two let's
go you can protect yourself from
Evil she's being trained in the way of
I'm sure I me this is a good way to
prepare for what is yet to come that it
will take mayhaps a day before I can
speak to
her again o again and will have the
courage to say something to her tomorrow
five minutes have passed since first
participant joined try again yes yes yes
it will be perhaps tomorrow I will I
will have the courage to say hello it'll
be
okay there we
go all right there they
go they are
fighting I am not public mic getting a
lot of hit I am not opening my mouth
they're fighting again in real life to
speak I am just
talking into my
in my
head oh my
gosh
enemy for
ambercoin
thein not
ambercoin Nina against
gathan oh to fight against N I do not
know if I can H such a beautiful maen on
well then you all equal
oh okay think of this is training your
name for tomorrow training
name if you click this and one of you
will have a uh a button behind the desk
to click to says start I have joined
shall I press Start what happened you
could yes we are starting then you get
poofed I am
poofed misso
Ena you are a fine you are a fine
opponent you are so wondrous without
your
hat ah miss
ninoa you are so good at
fighting you are so
oh she almost got me the night has won
Miss ninoa had almost slayed me I almost
fell yourself up for round two be
careful though I have been weak I must
eat some meat you have taken a lot out
of
me yes you are are a good a good fight
you're a good opponent you are also a
good opponent close game indeed close
game gathan with the G do we go again
yes the best of three
onwards
onwards oh I'll join the again I was
looking down on here we
go let us fight to the end fight
again why do I have one heart
missing
away away away let's go
onward
no it hurts it
hurts why was I without
Health gathan what happened I do not
know she is just such a good swords
woman she so good at
fighting what I believe my got to make
sure we're full full HP for though I
feel like that was not a fair fight oh
yes
yes delicious it's anyone's game now is
anyone's
game okay let us
go good luck
Knight hold on I'm still not oh yes
yes soon surely
okay surely surely let us go win let us
go let us go to battle if you could
press the start fight button
okay let us
go I am circling her in the
[Music]
battlefield do not run from me no I
don't want to run ah
congratulations night thank you thank
you well
done thank you you are victorious thank
you you did your best that was a great
fight G yes it was a great fight you
were wonderful very close it was a very
close fight I almost I almost fell yes
the future ofan is bright it's bright
very bright join the
battle all right mother I believe in you
mother come thank you my child I mean
I'm not your
mother my good good luck mother mother
good luck mother they all is she
mothering is
she oh she's mothering perhaps could
help and the other one is
bothering they are
[Music]
fighting she powerful she is very very
powerful you were
mothering
mothering wow that was that was quite
that was a great fight yes mother we are
proud of you never seen everyone mother
daughters I mean you're both not my
daughters are they siblings they're not
my daughters don't believe
them although we haven't done much her
proud what they it's okay mother will
show us how it's done yes side
CH I don't see a start button do you see
a start button many side
chicks what is a side chick a there we
go they
are it's a chick on your side
relationship with one another through
their side chicks oh you have many huh
no are you sure I have many side chicks
you have many side chicks oh they're
keeping their distance from each other
the voices in my head are my side chicks
the
seems like we have different
understandings on not me got a hits
mother no oh mother got to get the hit
and
mother
no mother and father is she a father oh
no is she his W is mothering so hard
let's
go I don't know who I'm rooting for We
are rooting for both mother and father
of course family TI How are theying
family
a well done you were best at this
time I was indeed but I shall not lose
this time final last final battle final
battle I shall not lose this time
I have
joined oh do it do it again I want to
see you do it again oh oh they are
drooling once
more ding they are
ding what are they drooling over
themselves themselves
mayhaps they're drooling over the
victory that would bring them honor yes
the victory who's winning it's so close
but it's so far is this custody
battle I think so the pink one the pink
one not mistak
owner look
at my
goodness she has won the pink one has
won won the power congratul
congratulations such
power8 she at what does that trained by
a great mentor well done
we have been both trained by the same
Mentor that guy this guy
here I
see Wonder well done C
okay the next ones to fight is Freda and
Shakira revenge on the traitor Revenge
oh the traitor of am coin this will
prove
everybody of what is the truth where is
the traitor oh there she
is it's your turn your this time I
wasant to go back and for oh yes yes
this time you
were and who do I who am I facing you
are fighting
Shakira Shakira Shakira Shakira her hips
do not lie mhm her hips does not Li does
my
honor yes I I'm just not going okay you
do it first Shakira yeah do it again
Shakira
Shakira go in go
in all right I want to spill your blood
does anybody want to place
bets do not have any coin to bet with I
don't coin I have no coin to in the
gambling one bread one bread I press
join I am beyond that
now I wonder what is wrong with it oh I
oh I see
it should work could you be coinless I
am may
have it's
starting Freda against Shakira who will
win who will win take down exchanging
blows this could be anyone seems that
the orange one is winning anyone's game
oh my goodness the orange one is won she
is so good at
fighting coin Resto
Amber there's still two excuse
me what did I
hear what what your typical Amber corn
Behavior it is my honor again
again okay I shall be having my honor
once
[Music]
again my hands are bloody ready oh wait
wait wait wait need to eat y do you not
get like healed back up before the fight
I'm
ready oh okay all right let's go let's
go one more time and go are they still
so despised mayhaps they
are the Second Battle has commenced it
is hard to get over my
Prejudice of course I did they
exchanging
blows fight fight to the death oh oh it
looks like Shakira's got a lot of hits
in oh oh she's
W well done great
fighter she's a fantastic
fighter is too good I say I hit her so
many
times you
Fant you fought valiantly Freda you f
you
well I will never ever return to C coin
I detest it so about I detest it I will
do everything in my power to see it fall
oh here uh Freda I will give you a good
Freda I will give you a booby prize what
I want the booby priz what the hell what
is the booby prize a what prize a booby
prize booby prize you never heard that
term what to say booy
prize hey y by
that I want to trade with
you oh she's
shy see are you dead did you just my big
brain cannot comprehend what the prize
is yes it is about a booby
prize Well I I shall take it in have you
never heard the term booby prize I have
not it is uh so if you are doing a like
uh uh
a pub quiz whoever is the the last one
gets a booby prize which is something
silly maybe or what they say your lands
that you are from see I'm not sure it
just comes to mind whenever I think of a
booby
PR when I am sad I would like to have a
booby prize indeed Oher are you there
well you have to lose but to get the
booby priz I would like to I would like
to you a good luck charm mother I am
such a loser may have a booby prize
please take it no you have won sword I
would like the booby prize as well you
won in my heart you want in my heart no
I'm such a
loser goodness other kind of what
happened to her I guess I killed her
complet did
you you whacked her too much you whacked
her so
much oh hello no I I wait my goodness I
want to give you your booby prize prize
what did she receive let me trade with
you what the queen stat why don't you
tell us the boy prize leave the queen
alone leave her alone she's being worked
on I was just I was just
thinking you wear the booby prize wear
the booby prize put on the booby prize
put on the booby prize put on the is the
booby prize what is the booby prize may
we see the booby prize
[Music]
burn this
Bo to the
ground first I will display the booty
wait can I the booty it's booby not
booty I cannot display the
booty oh my goodness you are the Amber
coin Amber
coin I know I know
what a wondrous booby prize I make
perect display of my my distaste my next
is gathan against cie oh the
reaper I am ready to
fight look Jade sword night makes uan
proud I will do my best but it seems
that the reaper is quite Adept at
fighting I believe in you show her some
empathy I will show her
empathy empathy empathy fight for the
king call fight for the king please
please present the Jade sword let me
fight she wishes for your hands what
what Happ is
wearing I wish to joust for your wife's
hands you are of the J sword are you not
the J sword ha the Jace
sword oh you you want to fight with me
so badly because you are of the Jace
sword you are of the
Jace's stop
you
ah she is so strong she is very
strong do with
the now on
[Music]
round orange oh
goodness
goodness God I believed in you I must
for EMP heart up one more fight be I saw
that it was the same Strat you used
against me it was very effective thank
youin I believe in you just one more for
your wife thank you I will fight in her
memory in her honor so that her memory
may be her memory will be proud of me my
dearly departed wife
I will win for you I will
win let us
[Music]
go ah Mory copi I heard that your food
inside your Tavern is
quite not up to code is it because you
are of a Jace sword why do you run from
me do not run
where did you
go I see I Believe come back
Reaper how are you the reaper when it is
you who will face death
go po empathy for
empathy that mou I do not know what you
mean what mouth what mouth why what were
you saying on the battlefield to Kelly
nothing I was not saying anything she
was just showing something
[Music]
okay you fought valiantly
callant all right the last match the
final match even shall be Shakira
against gathan
right you're exhausted I am a little
exha true empath I will do my best
though she is a murderer I will say this
is the Battle of the oranges so if you
shall win I shall lose my title of
shakar of
and you shall be of the oranges you will
lose your
title I win you will go to court and
face
trial wait wait that's both just like
bad for me what oh well shouldn't it be
something else well if you win I
will die if you win you will go to
court do you not want that I don't know
about this deal that's kind of like you
no so if I die you get my title of the
oranges if you die what do I I
get I will do you have a title I will I
will stab
myself oh H what about something like
she says ARA ARA or some strange cursed
words well then come up with something
may I take your may I take I have I know
since you will be getting the orange
title how about since you have no title
to give me I shall take your last name
and make you my wedded person you would
force me to marry
you I shall request you kindly only if I
happen to win this battle fine let it be
off onto the battlefield
oh the
St the stakes are high
real I cannot let her win to be her wife
I think not I will not be your wife you
are wrong no you must
you but as I am a knight I could
[Music]
never Shir
is no oh no oh goodness I may have to be
your wife go no oh no
it's okay it's just one round oh no I'm
going to have to be her wife this is the
worst day of my life this is the worst
pull yourself back
together I don't understand what
happening she's going to make me back
to Don't Panic don't
[Music]
panic I can't I can't
H I have forgotten I have forgotten to
heal up but it is okay it's going to
be I cannot
no my heart only begins to one my heart
to
one it is but one round left no one
round left she forgot to sheot to heal
but we will take those we will take I
accept it because I will win the next
fight
oh the Sak snap it together
left okay
okay you can you can do it your PE
wait my dearly departed wife this is for
you my she's literally right my wife in
heaven I will Shakira wins she gets to
marry you will not take me as your wife
I will not marry you
we will not be wet you will face trial
for your murders you you murdered no
Raven C I've seen it I have seen it with
my own eyes you killed her child the
chicken that she laid cuz she laid eggs
you've killed her you will not take me
too you I would rather die I was I she
been she will she to she will to
H you will face trial you will go to
trial for empathy I do not want your
title I only want you to to go to trial
you may keep the T of the oranges well
done gathan it is a trial tomorrow where
will the trial be held it will be held
at the Gallows I suppose there's no how
we have the trial the day after tomorrow
day after tomorrow proposal
because I still have many things to do
that I want to do before I go to prison
are you getting are you trying to get
out of this no are you trying to get out
of this you would not have such
knowledge of me not being available on
the last day so um how about tomorrow I
uh get a few more quests done and then
we have the trial the day after the
tomorrow how about you finish your quest
and then we have the
trial have a propos well on the day
after theor of course so we have a tri
right now we shall discuss it on the
bulletin
board get married and have a tri you can
have both
what she she would not marry I I have
one you're going to courts
anyway true but if you're there anyway
might as well get married no true like
who who was she married to to you no no
the I can't my heart belongs to my
dearly departed wife Amber
departed myart run away from I know that
your wife left
you she
did sensitive SP here to I am here for
you admired you I am going to become in
a sensitive spot I will you you are now
single that at this court you can I will
become a nun you can hit two birds with
one stone I will having none of it h
this bird I will your
stone to the Sewer
Dain I offer my love to you and my
internal protection if you can prove
yourself innocent in the trial I no I
will consider I got my memories back and
I still remember my past murder gathan
come here there and I shall give you
your potato salad thank you may you need
a little b a potato salad will you will
you bunk you got five oh five potato
salads that is 1,000 gold 500 gold maen
lless you remember
I'm thank you oh did it happen ah yes no
worries Well Done You Are Victorious a
diamond if you you are a skilled Warrior
thank you appreciate it could be a
knight I am a knight I am the knight to
queen Tam Gander but see we are of the
same morals I also stand for team Gander
you are team Gander all along and we are
both orange don't you think this is
meant to
be I cannot be you're the criminal so
you must prove yourself innocent
criminal trial I am not we were told by
a ghost that you killed
Nissa I have I have not done any such
thing she is still alive she's just not
uh currently with us but she get married
isai or what do an isai yes what but if
you are so innocent then loves each
other very
fast well under one uh condition what is
the condition I feel slow and steady
wins the race I do not know about
you what because she's alive I will have
to see tomorrow it seems when I I have a
right to a lawyer right yes you have a
right to a lawyer night then narissa
ravencraft shall be my lawyer she will
she is the victim of the crime but I
demand her to be my lawyer I think you
will have to contact her the thing is
this is likeing cat or something because
she can my lawyer she's alive right and
if she's alive that means I haven't
killed her so then then is no need
for court thing a glorious symbol I
think we will just have to see tomorrow
and then then I will make my decision on
how I feel of your stat keep an eye if
you see her running around that would
mean I have not killed her and then that
is true thank you so much for joining in
the tournament I appr and I will deeply
consider your
proposition keep in mind she's known to
be a witch and she has she thank you so
much for joining in the tournament you
are Mighty F chicken which she cannot
bth a glorious glorious tourn I take
your evidence into head into my head I
will keep it in mind I would like to see
both sides I do see your side that she
could not have possibly given birth to
an egg but what if she did see my side
that I am orange and that I am team
Gander she is not you are the side of
queen that I serve that is she serves a
different Queen we not holding hands she
is just speaking to me very
closely she is not we are not holding
hands would you trust someone who served
the wrong cream wait before you leave
wait Miss ninoa before you leave I would
like to have a conversation with you and
Tanashi karia Shakira of the what is
it I shall go to the gardens goodbye
thank
you thank you for the arena thank you
thank you for joining it is nice to make
you of the Arena it was good job thank
you thank you very strong Warriors
farewell
[Applause]
for yes what I wanted to speak with you
about we are we all still loyal to Queen
Tam Gander are you yes of course well I
know that you are siblings with one
princess kosaku but I believe that she
is possessed by a
stain it seems that is true I swore hat
to slay her myself have need be oh you
you know then you know of have you seen
the corruption that has beell our our
lands I have I believe that it is her
that is doing this that she is
corrupting our
land I know but what should we do it's a
good feel I must drive her down she I
know this must she cannot suffer like
this yes do we have to put her out of
her Misery we will have we do put her
down I did hear of a magical Golden
Apple that could maybe bring her
back I will rest until tomorrow and I
will shall see you then okay yes fairly
well one Amelia Watson oh thank you
Jonathan with G congratulations on your
win thank you I appreciate it this is so
heartbreaking I will I will see you guys
what is the matter no no it's it's
nothing it's nothing it's nothing I
really wanted
oh all right iy farewell well have a
great great night have a great night I
will see you than for assistance yes
goodbye goodbye fwell
farewell are are you okay joh conon it
hurts this hurt but I respect her I
always knew that this would potentially
be an outcome so I have come to it
doesn't have to be like this she has
forgotten me and it is fine no our she
can remember we have diverged our path
she
is the option that we don't have to kill
her we just have to take off the hat oh
I have considered that but it seems that
the um the stain hat has taken root and
possessed her within she has shown her
head a few times but then she has put it
back on immediately after have you tried
okay have you tried beheading her what I
guess that ends up in killing her it
does end in killing her damn it
well we can behead her and try to put it
back on her head no no no no there there
there's a tail of a magical Golden Apple
that can cure perhaps cure her but she
refuses to consume it I don't it's
because she knows she is possessed is
The Possession on her head feed her I
don't know we must try how will we try
what what do you propose we do I'm not
sure where to get this magical golden
apple as well I I I know I can get a
normal Golden Apple but this seems to be
a more special magical Golden Apple
maybe we can hide the golden apple in an
apple pie yes yes we hide it and we
blend it with another meal that she eat
oh yeah like a smoothie oh that's true a
special movie perhaps maybe if we look
at mayhaps once the library is open we
will find the book the library on how to
attain it your hats the F Mar that I've
heard in t
very large they are girthy
hats yes they're very girthy are very
girthy hats yes they're they it holds my
giant brain a very large Brain full of
empathy our empathy has empathy that is
why we must put her
down
yeah yes yes all right shall we convene
tomorrow maybe I can find a book
tomorrow that will lead us wait so you
want me to help with this and yet you
want to put me on trial
if you help us with this maybe this is
the trial yes this is the trial to prove
your innocence is by doing this for
Queen team by showing empathy yes I
empathy I shall take this because I am a
hero and I like to do things with honor
so I shall help for Queen Gander I will
for the queen I will ask FAA fart if she
has any books that relate to this
possession but be very quiet we do not
know who to trust in this Kingdom that
is true there's many people be safe
everyone yes there very few people to be
trusted there are very few people that
we can trust yes so please please
message me through carer pigeon you mean
Discord I yes the carrier pigeon named
Discord that's weird that's a weird name
for a bird yes because he when he flies
there is quite a bit of dissonance in
his in his
um so that's why he is called Discord oh
I see I see all right that's making it
clear thank you yes yes well we cannot
be seen together too long otherwise
people will know so yes I will go
another way we will split up I will go
this way
split
yes it see was that even though some
terrible things have happened today at
least I have found some allies in whom I
can
trust I was worried that I wouldn't be
able to trust in miss ninoa seeing as
her relationship
with the hot pink one has L her to being
with you
know as well as Princess kishu but seems
we can trust them a little
bit yes yes we can trust we can
believe princess is still working on her
I will also work on this a little bit as
to not tip her
off we must remain
natural oh a r from the dearest Amelia
Watson well I hope that you have a
splendid rest I will see you in Tom
tomorrow yes have a great great great
night I wish you well I hope when you
wake up that your head is clear and that
your memories have returned fully and
you are no longer
suffering thank you voices in dearest
one of Amelia Watson's head and bear the
well veryy well until the next day I
will see you all in in the tomorrow we
ah if I make another batch of nice uh
milkshake and
uh and uh hand it
over to you I would be Delight S I hope
you look forward to I will
it seems that
Miss Miss Nena is beginning her Quest
princess kosaku does seem to to trust in
her this is very good very good news
indeed yes yes very very good Miss
ninoa very
good I am
delighted I am happy to have her as an
ally
very
great let's see do
this
this we do
this yes
yes all right now that we have a moment
a moment of
respit let me
return back to these peaceful musics and
I will read the notes that the voices in
my head have so dearly left me while I
was distracted by all of the happenings
in the
world let me
[Music]
see I'm going to read these
messages so that I may C trip on them
and not leave them thank you for your
support fellows I greatly appreciate
it it is in
here is it in here it's in here yes
where did I leave
off let us
[Music]
see I think over
here thank you
Ritu n voice in my head I do not know
why you said the words pain it was not
painful at all it was not a painful
thing no it was um it is just life it is
life thank you voice in my head Jessica
roone sir Jonathan you must stay strong
I am I am staying as strong as I Poss L
can thank you for keeping me in your
thoughts I greatly appreciate it is very
kind of you to keep a night such as I in
your in your
thoughts Fair thee well yes Fair the
well thank you Shir Yuki stay strong my
Lord voice in my head I will stay strong
thank you thank you thank you dumb ball
voice in my head
thank you for giving me such a sweet
note don't give up on your Pearl sir
Jonathan true love will persevere I'm
sure of it
but if it is true love
then I will have to let her
go I believe that it is wrong of me to
Shackle her to me when she does not want
to she may have some if she were to
remember me she may hold some fondness
she may think of our time dearly but are
we to discredit her previous Memories
the memories that she has built over her
many many years and many many lives and
everything that before
her I am just but a little resting space
a resting
spot I'm happy to have been just a
little moment of her journey so that
when she were if she were to recall this
I hope she thinks of us this moment
fondly I'm happy to have been a part of
her journey at
all there 1 2 3
4 1 2 3 four yes so do not
cry it is okay I am at I am at peace I
am at peace with it it seems that this
is not the correct thing
here up
here thank you voice in my head Juna
stay strong Jonathan G oh there's
another voice in my head it echoes it
sounds like a voice I remember a very
strong wonderful Queen from another
life and she loves me I sent many hearts
back to that voice
onwards
onwards thank you voice in my head dear
scary walus somewhere deep down your
Pearl must still be there don't give up
sir Jonathan you are strong I have spent
some time with my my departed
Pearl I spent some time with her after
she has regained her memories and it
does not seem as it will return there
were some
glimpses a chance that it may
[Music]
recover but I do think it would be rude
of me to tr by and but in to the
memories she already
has I'm sure she has someone waiting for
her a pearl as beautiful as her surely
has someone out there waiting for her
and I cannot take her from them they
must miss her so
dearly and I know how I would feel
if that were to happen to me
so I have I I am strong worry not worry
not I am strong and we will you will
overcome
this thank you voice in my head gome
silliest Prophet just better to have
loved than to have lost sir Jonathan
cherish the memories you had with your
Pearl and feel the joyous day of her
recollection and know that your love
will always be there I will remember I I
will think
fondly it will be a tale that I tell for
years to come mayhaps someone will write
it in a book one day and place it in the
faunal library so that hundreds of years
from now someone will read it and
remember remember our story that is the
most that is the best that I could hope
for that our love does not die here and
that someone may remember it and someone
may honor it in the
future and that would be brilliant it
would be brilliant for when our bones
are in the ground and we are nothing but
dust that someone remembered that she
had a KN that loved her very dearly at
some point in her
[Music]
life thank you dear Voice to my head
James Larry for love is as bleeting as
the Pearl in the ocean blue Noble night
and your Pearl will remain in your
hearts let her and celebrate for her Joy
huzzah huzzah Glory Day glorious day
thank you voice PR technique to love is
like a flame warmth and comfort in the
night upon the morning dawn one may find
it snuffed but may helps New Horizon's
bright that was very beautiful thank you
for sharing such kind words you have a
way you are like a
poet thank you voice in my head are the
voices in your head are at your side
Till The Bitter End oh Noble Jonathan I
appreciate it dearly I appreciate it
greatly I am able to keep my head held
up so very high because I know I have so
many voices of support to me and I
cannot let you or the queen
Down May the queen rain when she returns
and may she see to it that all the
subjects in the land remain loyal to her
and may we user a new age of kindness
and empathy huzzah
huzzah thank you voice Rob my Lord I
Will Follow You into battle even if I
have to give my life for the queen
alongside you for the queen huzzah I
sure hope that we do not have to give
our lives there is no
battle the lands the stains although the
stains are getting a little more active
on the
field there will be no battle I would
soon rather die than see one of my
companions
fall so when we go out into the
battlefield voices just know that I have
your back and I can only hope that you
two have
mine thank you red voice in my headed
tager I appreciate it the support the
unwavering
support thank you dragel be strong s me
tonight Jonathan be strong just Jonathan
the Pearl may have forgotten everything
but your love was real it was
real just because she does not remember
doesn't make our love not real what
matters is that I remember I knew of it
some people in throughout the land know
of it as long as someone remembers as
long as one single person
remembers does not matter who it could
be someone thousands and thousands of
years ago
ago from now thousands of years from now
if they remember our love then it was
real and it was
[Music]
true thank you Sonic Cherry please stay
strong thy Noble KN Jonathan I will I
will stay strong thank you KAG she may
no longer remember thy bonds sir
Jonathan but what you had be it for a
moment or an eternity was real not be
filled by woes of the heart when instead
look towards the light of tomorrow it is
thanks to you I know that I had a moment
of weakness early on and I'm sorry to
show you such a pathetic miserable side
of me it
was very traumatic and crushing
and I I was feeling quite down but
having you all here
having my fellow Companions and knowing
that they still believe in me has given
me the strength to go on to the next day
and the next and we will fight for this
Kingdom
huzzah huzzah glory be blessed
days thank you sha for for the thoughts
and prayers thank you for all the things
you've done for our PE was fun while it
lasted yes it was thank you Suki do not
be led astray Jonathan we love
you your words are giving me such such
great power thank you bum status We
Stand By Your Side good sir Jonathan the
gold-hearted even in these trouble times
S I raised my cup in your name and to
what could have been and what has been
lost huzzah
huzzah thank you Queen te for the
thoughts I can only pray the other
people learn from you to stay loyal if
the son of lust is too great we can only
hope the queen can correct them we can
only hope the queen can show them
empathy and
kindness and if it must be through Force
then so be it that is also empathy it is
a kindness to show
them such compassion
thank you Rin to Jonathan G our hero I
am no hero I am just but a mere Knight I
appreciate it though thank you iguana
for the thoughts best bedtime story ever
it was a brilliant bedtime story I
cannot wait to um donate it to the
library I'm looking forward to filling
the fom March shelves with some
stories thank you the faction for the
thoughts a silly story that touched the
hearts of Millions
Millions might be a stretch I hope that
it could at least touch the hearts of
dozens
[Music]
perhaps if it can touch the heart of
even one person then that would be
enough thank you Frid for the thoughts
I'm not crying you're crying I am not
crying there are no tears to be F here
and you you
may you may cry it is fine what what is
the quote there there was a quote I once
heard I've heard a quote once it was
that tears are not that precious enough
to be kept
inside a quote from I know not where a
theater play in my mind from many many
many ages ago so let them fall let your
tears fall so that we may see tomorrow
even
brighter thank you
thank you Santa for the thoughts why am
I crying it is okay to cry it is fine to
cry what matters is that you make it to
the next
day thank you evil evil earns e not evil
you are not evil you are e EV earns for
the thought the road to Healing is going
to be a long one in the course you will
make it someday
someday what matters is that we are at
least on the the path you're at least on
the
path we have taken one step onto the
path and that is the true thing that
matters thank you thunderchild for the
thoughts good sir Jonathan with a G we
voices in your head will stand strong
with you while today may be a sad day
Thou shalt still be remembered as their
Jonathan a pure the faithful the good
thy Deeds shall be told forever forever
surely you just
[Music]
such Tales to live for so long does not
fit a night as small as I mayhaps if you
tell future
Generations a few Generations from now
may remember me but I will just be a
fleeing memory in their
heads thank you for the thoughts let's
continue to protect her as Knight we
will just because it is over does not
mean I will stop protecting
her we will continue to do our duties
our
duties thank you oh for the thoughts
cheers to this
gentleman go sunflower for dos when you
say huzzah but she says who that huzzah
no it is huzzah you always return huzzah
huzzah on this good day thank you KU for
the thought the tale of Jonathan is
better than the Minecraft movie what is
Minecraft and what is a movie a theater
play What is the what is Minecraft five
stars tomatoes that are rotten what a
Rotten Tomato you throw Rotten Tomatoes
when you are booing someone on a stage
that sounds
terrible thank you desert for the
thought show them the strength of the
Knight that protects the queen good luck
in the tournament sir Jonathan and we
have won that is the strength of a true
Knight it is the strength of I thank you
Bound for the thought thy support truly
is Noble this must be the essence of
Knighthood for thou sacrifices for the
good of the Kingdom three cheers for our
Queen huzzah huzzah to our Queen thank
you Mappy for thought yes stay strong
and for the queen thank you m p for the
thoughts it's time to find the meaning
behind the cryptic message maybe then
Jonathan may find piece or truth about
himself huz what cryptic message we did
receive a cryptic message but will there
be an end to that I know not I know
not thank you Amelia's s for the
thoughts thank you for the absolute
Cinema it was beautiful mayhaps it's not
over yet it's PE fiction best thing I
saw in eons hope Amelia's memories come
back and you both have the deserved
happy
ending did come back what is your what
is your name what is a is a
s of Miss Amelia Watson
my my once my once
pear thank you half and half for the
thoughts and thus Jonathan G let the
detective go in peace the gentle night
holds fast into a new dawn and with with
memories of a glistening Pearl in his
heart yes glistening Pearl in my heart
thank you pink salt for the red message
we will support you to the end Jonathan
we will be as loyal as you are to your
queen I hope that you will be loyal to
my queen as well she has shown me
nothing but kindness so I will not
falter just because we had a story end
today does not mean that our entire
Journey comes to a close
we still remain loyal to the
queen I hold her letter dearly in my
backpack at all times so that I may read
it when I'm feeling
down yes let me see let me gaze upon it
once more from the
[Music]
queen she has
written my good bleach joh
with a G I have left a home for all of
my beloved Guild
mates he cares for us dearly and then
her final words protect our guildmates
until we meet again being Tam
Gander it is only a part of the very
long letter that she has left me but I
see those words and they they fill me
with hope they fill me with hope and I
will will protect our
guildmate and I will see her again one
day I will see the queen again
yes thank you Ray for the thoughts
huzzah huzzah huzzah huzzah huzzah
huzzah thank you crusty for the red
message for so the path of a night is
not easy but is chosen not because it is
easy but because it is noble and it is
no that it is that Noble spirit that
allows their deeds to live on people's
hearts Jonathan your spirit is amongst
the noblest to walk these realms
Kudos thank you for believing in my
spirit I hope to continue to inspire you
for the coming
days thank you also for the thought to
face
Justice she will stand on trial she will
either help us with the princess ordeal
or she will face her crimes as a
murderer I hope she will find it in her
to help us with the
princess or
Oreal thank you Captain yoro for
thoughts congratulations on your win
Jonathan huzzah thank you I could not
let the queen
down I could not let her down thank you
Juna for the thoughts huz officer
Jonathan the
orange Shakira may be orange as well I
do not seek to take her title she Still
Remains the orangest orange to have ever
oranged I am just an orange
Knight huzzah huzzah good day
[Music]
thank you thunder child for the thought
it's a it is 1:00 a.m. I have worked in
6 hours and I have never been more
invested in a live stream what is a live
stream are you speaking of the ordeals
that are happening I hope that you are
able to get some rest there is still
some Journeys to be had in the marrow so
please please get some rest
congratulations on your Victory my Lord
I Thank the thank you Deputy Ninja for
the thoughts huzzah for your great
victory for honor for empathy huzzah
huzzah thank you Knight and Shai for the
thought you are the strongest Knight in
the entire land Jonathan it was proven
today in battle ins sparring so I will
accept that I will accept that title
[Music]
huzzah thank you M for the thoughts
Jonathan with a gene now may have of the
oranges he is The Faded sword of the
queen and the Greatest Warrior of the
Kingdom
huzzah I do not wish to take that orange
title from her
she can remain orange forever I am just
another
[Music]
orange let to see there are some
more thank you Dian Island for the
thoughts sir Jonathan stay strong but
don't bottle up your feelings let them
out as a
night it is very has been a very long
journey a very hard journey
I'm sorry if it seems as if that I keep
my emotions bottled up and I allow
others
to trample over me but they are my
ideals and I hope that the thoughts in
my head and understand that I am doing
my best but I will I will try I will try
to
be a little
more selfish I suppose it will be a long
journey to fight
for no not for myself not for others but
for
[Music]
myself I've always served others that
I've never thought what would happen if
I no longer serve them would I be on my
own would I have to seek things
myself I worry not of that day
those are things that we do not have to
think about before the queen will return
she will return and the kingdom will
return to peace and maybe years from now
we may may think about it we will think
about
[Music]
it yes yes
yes
um thank
you let me
see thank you thank you tincho for the
thoughts it was the most exciting thing
I have ever seen in my life thank you
very much Jonathan I am very proud of
you rest well little man Tam Gander
would be
proud I hope the queen is
proud I hope that she is still watching
over me from wherever she is I will
write to her you know what I think after
our Journeys are done I will write to
her and tell her everything everything
that has happened and then I will make
my loyalty known once
again thank you shutti for the thoughts
Jonathan be not sad that your time with
her has passed but be happy that it has
happened stay strong for your Pearl
would want out of you of course of
course thank you Jimmy for the thoughts
Jonathan with the G purest of heart
truest of Faith the most Valiant of
knights greatest champion of her Royal
Highness Queen Tam may you find new true
love in this harsh and cruel world
huzzah I do not know if I am ready to
find love I am quite taken with the idea
of becoming a
nun mayhaps my journey with love ends
[Music]
here but my loyalty will never end
huzzah to the next day thank youy for
the for the thoughts I have learned a
valuable lesson from the we should hold
our full and vond memories close and be
glad they happened rather than sad it
has ended yes hold your Fondest Memories
close to your heart you may mourn it but
with
time the sad feelings will grow ever
smaller and then you can look back at
the times with great fondness and
happiness and sometimes it will be sad
because the sadness never truly goes
away but it will take a very very very
small amount in your heart that you will
only feel that sadness on the coldest
and harshest of days but remember that
the coldest and harshest of days are
only very little comp compared to the
days that were
bright so worry not worry
not thank you for the thoughts to
Jonathan when your memory returns like
her or when you two meet in another
world or something I wish you two will
be tied together with a new beautiful
Bond
again ah what a grand idea what a grand
dream mayhaps I dream of that tonight
but it is nothing but a dream we know
that it cannot be reality so let us
Rebel in these dreams together as they
are dreams and these dreams cannot be
true thank you Shir Yuki once again for
the thoughts we'll always have your back
and me for there for you sire thank you
corano for the thoughts oh sir Jonathan
will you take me another Squire so I
become an honorable Knight like
you take you in as my
Squire when the queen returns mayhaps I
will take upon a few to
to fight I am still just a humble
growing Knight myself so I do not know
if it is in my place to
teach but in the future when the night
returns mayhaps I will take in a few
disciples thank you sry for the dot T
the Fate for those who carry the will of
G you will surely find the one Pearl yet
again thank
[Music]
you I appreciate your kind words
there's the next
[Music]
one thank you mauchi for the kind kind
thoughts and prayers thank you Nelson
for the thoughts your honorable
treatment of your pearls what brings my
voice to add the course in your mind
Brave Ser Knight keep hope I will huzzah
there's a light shining at the end of
all of our
paths we must keep fighting for it thank
you wato dial for your thoughts sir
Jonathan your tale so far has been
legendary and the GL is carving your
path is masterful in her craft of
forming your journey I am both excited
but also sad to see the
conclusion is not
over just because we may not be
projecting our memories anymore does not
mean that our Journeys are over we
continue to live our days every single
day and we fight and we hope that we
become a better person with every
passing day and mayhaps our
Journeys will we will meet again our
path will meet
again even if we are no longer
projecting our memories for a while
there is always the possibility that we
may once meet again maybe not now maybe
not in years maybe not until we are both
dead but I hope to see you all at the
gates
above and we can sing choirs
together thank you Tamaro for oror sweet
to thought no sword so strong or spell
so devastating could destroy the memory
of your love your faith and heart shall
protect the queen of the Kingdom huzzah
huzzah thank you Cadence for your
thoughts and prayers thank you Pineapple
clock for the thought May the b sing
your tail Noble KN thank you ailia wats
off for your thoughts what is his name
scrawled along a beat and parchment
remember this oh Resolute and faithful
Jonathan may love or the lusterous Pearl
be as wide and deep as the ocean that
once held and nurtured yet so closely
yes may it be huzzah huzzah to
you thank you jesson for your thoughts
it is if it's not tears then what is
this in my eyes wipe them
away a smile is much more fitting for
those as what what is that one quote
that one quote from scriptures from ages
and eons ago that one
quote a smile is better suited for a
hero so chin up chin
up thank you thank you a troll for
fighting for your thoughts and prayers I
remember you Jonathan always it is a
privilege to witness your Noble and
beautiful story seeing the strength your
love has given you was truly a gift hold
fast brave knight huzzah
huzzah thank you night writer for your
thoughts your loyalty is truly something
to behold Rejoice good night for your
Pearl will surely be joyous that she has
the affections of such a night yes
that is all I can hope for that she
thinks of me very
[Music]
fondly that is all that I could ever
wish thank you tager for your red
thoughts thank you for the stream
Jonathan words cannot convey how amazing
today has been your loyalty the queen
will surely be
rewarded I can only hope that the queen
enjoys this statue I have built for her
I hope she sees it and that she likes
it thank you blue Mobius for your
thoughts of mighty whatever thou art
striding on congrats on the victory
nobody light for the queen huzzah huzzah
huzzah good day to
[Music]
all yes yes yes thank you pad puff for
your thoughts even the dear things come
to an end and all we can do is look back
and smile being able to say goodbye is
nothing but the proof you truly loved
and we did we did thank you Dylan for
your thoughts thank you for being an
inspiration sir Jonathan ofor and you're
the lights in the darkness a what kind
sweet words you have for
me and thank you I cannot read your
symbols in your name I am sorry I am not
a very well ver
night I am only barely literate alter
not to Jonathan for this voice feels
fairly certain that more Fortune is yet
to come for you we have trotten far yet
there is far more to experience and
discover thanks for the fun fun
experience you are welcome I hope that
you enjoy
today despite all that has happened oh
thank you
thank you dearest Tim kicks I appreciate
the support your unwavering support I
very much appreciate it huzzah good
voice is in my head huzzah
[Music]
huzzah and thank you ritten for your
thoughts I become completely Smitten by
Jonathan throughout this journey may you
live long and prosperous in this life
and the next into the next thank you
Linkus for your thoughts and
prayers until next time farewell
I will be departing now as well fairy
well we will
continue wait you wait oh seems
that Frieza Frida Frieza Frieza wants
yes she wants to speak with us I wait
yes about what how do you get stained
bones you kill stains in the
forest m the forest mountain path I can
give you some I have
[Music]
plenty where is
she I am just am I just
unlucky they are not dropping is
okay they are the humanoid looking ones
with sword and Shield God to be with you
fair Thee
Well ah yes my
goodness thank
you it is Miss Nino
Ina oh but I am also going to depart
very very soon here I will let everyone
to gaze upon this statue before I leave
we have finished one side of her head
we are working on the back side of her
head and we are also working ah ah this
is why we put this
here and we are working on this side of
her
head we're making great
progress it is very very precarious to
be building on this
side the Magics only go to this boundary
line so I must be very very careful when
I am building over here
here my goodness my
goodness her foot yes her foot shall I
build her
foot the queen protects she protects
always she will always protect let me
see I can build some of her foot right
now I must gaze upon my blueprint to see
how to build her
foot it looks like
to build her foot would be like
this I'm
taking a brief
photo we need some of this do we have
blue
already I think I want to switch this
color we'll switch the color that way it
will be easier to distinguish between
the two
this
[Music]
away like
this oh not there this
goes this goes
here this goes here and then there will
be
two like this like so get rid of this
one is her
heel I do not think I have any more oh
thank goodness some more yellow concrete
such as
this like
this then some white
concrete like
so like this like
this our dearest Queen's foot
and
then what is this
like is it's her
leg her leg would
be not
here is it here is it here is her foot
[Music]
here seems as if she would 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
eight is she too wide 1 2 3 4 5 six 7 no
she is not too wide did I make this foot
too too
little ah my head her foot is Tainted
who what is
[Music]
this who would do such an evil
thing I would not allow it
[Music]
back
back gone with
you we must protect the
[Music]
queen and like
this I will not allow it I will not
allow it seems that me and Miss Nena
have quite the task on our hands
tomorrow yes yes a
very very
very difficult
task all right I will stop here for now
we will build a wall we will build a
fence
mayhaps a fence so that the corruption
may not
spread it looks
like it looks like she has
I fear that it is too late for
her
[Music]
pathetic my
goodness oh no it will be too late it
will be too
late I will see you all this is very
concerning I must depart and I must
speak with the
council I will see everyone in the
tomorrow please take care and be careful
it seems that there is a Darkness
spreading in our
kingdom be the well
Travelers be the well
[Music]