foreign
[Music]
thank you
I am on muting you all yeah you're
unmuted
oh
yeah
I'm nervous you have too much power in
these lands
[Music]
I know I'm nervous ladies
okay I got this I know how to do this
okay
no you're not beautiful
oh you're not muted we're not muted
girls I think I can do it
wrong
wrong one hello
hi everybody and welcome to the
collaboration today I am nervous
but also I am Nina kosaka oh my God hi
everybody Welcome girls thank you for
joining me yeah yeah thank you
thank you for for trying to get us
together again and also doing EU
friendly collabs right yeah high five
you had to wake up so early I'm still
asleep but I'm here
sleep really talking she's so cute all
right ladies would you like to introduce
yourselves and please everybody I am so
bad with my volume so you let me know as
we keep going if the girls are in
adequate volume let's start with
uh oh should we start with seniority
date of debut
I am a senior
[Laughter]
Grandma I mean I really feel like a
senior and I'm so old oh man damn it's
it's crazy how much how fast time passes
isn't it
yeah how long has it been since you're
DB yeah I have a free year anniversary
in like in three months I think oh my
God
we're so years old
how much is three years in like YouTuber
years it's like 20 years right one video
yeah Facebook
basically
[Laughter]
I feel something piercing from my heart
it's our cuteness
[Music]
you should say little [\h__\h]
yes
grannies are so cute yeah yeah but
sometimes they're dancing for you
sometimes the grandmas are smelly help
me but they're cute smelly right who's
the next one in line
who's the other grandma is the second
senior yeah second scene I'm coming 40
I'm going through my midlife crisis
right now
okay and who are you hello oh hello I am
Purple Rain puff of midi Sandy Eaton's
first wave lazulite my Oshi is
[Music]
you know the oldness is making me
emotional
reminding you of the good old days
almost quiet apparently I'm turning her
up a bit
don't silence me I I think it's it's
it's fine I just tune out I don't need
to silence you I just do it out half a
year I'm like a mosquito in your ear
I had that last night the whole night I
heard
foreign
also everybody for Pomo being quiet just
wait till she maulds she'll get a little
loud
today I think I'm too tired
why are we all tired because Except Nina
because because I usually stream at this
time at noon but for them it's like oh
noon our Alaska lab I'm not gonna say
who but somebody was like please can we
move it back I can't wake up so early
was it me I don't remember
um if I can't confirm or did I
I said I could I said I could do it at
that time too I said I prefer it if it
was a leader but
which one was it I think Nina is also
just like generally physically healthier
like I feel like you do the sport and I
think you eat these things you two are
unhealthy she thinks you don't touch
grass she thinks you both drink bubble
tea all day chicken right now yeah yeah
I had I did have bubble tea two days in
a row I didn't have Bubble Tea in a long
time and I'm pretty healthy but I stayed
up late reading a villain last night
[Laughter]
work out at all I do yeah
roseme is roasting me she's strong to me
actually she's the next person would you
like to introduce yourself oh who's this
Chad hi I'm the wolves and I'm turning
40 next month
I'm a DD and I love everyone
baby
that's sweet
with the workout
what do you do to work out oh and you
start like really like I have abs Kiara
you used to what about nowhere oh what
happened okay it's long it's a long
story but basically when stuff got
closed I was like okay I can't go to the
gym anymore so I didn't go to the gym
but now I do like a lot of like Just
Dance oh yeah I do a lot of like yeah
okay
um
but I used to only do weights yeah fun
he's a chat she's not like other girls
she's a chad
dance
also y'all are dances me too but I feel
like the dancing is not maybe I don't
dance enough but I feel like it's not
it's not working as a workout for me I
mean if you dance all day then maybe
good cardio at least
I'm not trying to be buff I'm just
trying to
you know yeah when you say dancing you
girls talking about idle kind of dancing
right
I think you're in love what you're about
to say
wait what kind of dancing are you doing
I kick my legs up sometimes like a
Can-Can yeah
[Music]
I can I can go to the gym I can Spa you
guys at the gym oh let's go
let's go I've only been to like my gym
at my oh wait what what
I see a lot of pole dancing in the chats
uh we're saying we're saying you know
what I heard such a good sport I
actually really would love to try it I
heard it's so good for your core
strength your everything strength yeah
it's really [\h__\h] exhausting though
yeah okay not that kind of experience
wait would you ever try it
I was
[Music]
oceans it's all an illusion
implements Club
it is but it's actually a real workout
like it actually is a real workout and
it's like yeah
yeah yeah yeah I thought you just
twirled around it it's it's tougher than
it looks girl we should take a pole
dancing class no no we should take most
of me to a pole dancing place what and
make her look at it wait like a
gentleman have you guys been I wanted to
go
oh God I'm so sorry what are we still
talking about wait is it bad if I if we
go to
a gentleman's club yeah a little bit we
could dress up and see yeah
very gentleman amazing yeah
[Music]
I just have to ask you
what would happen if you're walking down
the street and you see like accidentally
like a knee play how would you react or
what a nipple like
knee play
oh no I'm just I'm just asking for
myself like what would happen if you
just like saw
a woman's naked body I mean the [\h__\h]
okay you mean peeking out
oh yeah that's very different
you see the color you see the shape you
see the size
wait not not like through like okay okay
but is it like is it out on purpose or
is it like right you know like right
there but I want to let them know if
it's on accident right if they don't
mean for it but if this lady is just
like you know what girls I'm sorry I'm
being a Debbie Downer let's all dress up
in suits and go to the gentleman's club
together
[Music]
if I saw you in public and if it were
around walking somewhere in public and I
saw your nipple I would tell you
you up your nipple is trying
I will tell you because like you can't
do that especially because I feel like
if we were to meet up somewhere it would
be Japan
I don't want you to get arrested lady
what were you gonna say Rosemary I think
I know what you're about to say
Rosie why are you blushing
what are you typing
I'm not sure I feel like
you know
you don't want to talk about
no but it's about Nina scene
it's not about me it's about me
okay I
I don't wear
a bra so usually when I'm with the girls
they'll they're they can see Venus Twin
Peaks she has she has one time we had an
offline collab and I was wearing a
sweater and I took off the sweater are
you okay
well honestly I can't imagine it's way
more comfortable for you without or it's
like wait I mean apparently so at some
point the bigger your boobies get the
less comfortable it is without
um
because they get too heavy but then for
me like I feel more comfortable without
me too
I just have to say one time we were
having an offline color we were we we
had met up offline with some other uh
girls too from the company sorry I'm now
I'm blushing oh my God and one of the
girls was like Nina do you even own a
bra why don't you ever wear a bra and
then Rosie my girl Italy she's like I
don't wear a bra either
she just like jumped to my defense
if you're not wearing them
you wear them most of the times okay no
but you were like you were like it's not
always comfy
yeah and I I it meant a lot you defended
me in that moment thank you
[Music]
all right ladies I think we gotta get a
game in oh yeah
[Music]
unbelievable also hi everybody I'm Nina
kosaka of niji Sanji Ian's third wave
etherea and I must be in luck today to
be here with these cute ladies and all
of you
girls are so mysterious
gentlemen's club welcome I can't wait
roseme for you to experience the
gentleman's club filled with gentlemen
and women
what
I never been to some place like that we
will become gentlemen
only in games
we're going to the farm I guess it's
like one of the unless you want to go to
another one is there another one that no
no exactly
let's go to the farm yeah yeah yeah
oh crap I'm sorry I couldn't stop
jumping
okay
all right my one of my biggest pet
peeves in games is hmm
yeah I forgot how to rotate stuff is it
cute yeah it's cute and cute good
um it's when guys like male characters
when they don't have nipples in games
oh no link yeah
Zelda game and that is Skyward Sword
yeah she distracted us awake
at the time was a factor in this game
[Laughter]
none of us okay thank God okay okay okay
okay so you don't like when there are no
mail yeah cause like it's like you're
free
[Laughter]
[Music]
I feel like this is strategic
well what are you thinking of doing oh
oh oh whoa what just happened doesn't
that make it easier
let's go
oh how do I get out of here
[Music]
I'm a horse you
could I'm a horse
you can't go hey Ken we got this
we have to have not ever So eventually
we'll get like harder and harder things
we have to make people actually lose
I'm usually on the side I try to make it
easier and not more really which is so
wrong I know I should be making more
difficulties yeah that could make it
easier yeah I made it more difficult
okay good good good
[Music]
how about we all agree to make it easy
fried chicken
[Music]
[Laughter]
smells like fried chicken
yum you're also free Prime now
oh my God
she's like a killer
oh not the flower
[Laughter]
punches you in your face
Put the flower up there me
do that
oh
[Music]
I don't think this is possible I
apologize that's ridiculous absolutely
ridiculous
[Applause]
okay okay okay okay okay
wait is it only me what happened to
everyone you have happened to everyone
okay
[Music]
time to get rid of some stuff yeah like
the flower you put up there Kiara I saw
you get to the flower we didn't even get
there we can't we haven't tested it out
yet
we gotta make it easier now okay
yeah I agree yeah I agree I agree
because we'll just fail again what's the
door do
uh yeah you're welcome
too easy probably
oh yeah that's pretty good though salty
oh
my God
[Music]
yeah
it's too easy
also girls give me just one second I
thank you so much for feeding me welcome
I am having a collab with very few girls
gonna make it No One's Gonna no
oh
the top is not inaccessible
oh I think you ate it
I think you ate it
okay children welcome I am having a
collab with Kiana
[Music]
thank you
by the way I'm dead with Palmer yeah
nice punch
high five Rosie your mama's favorite
gamer
oh good
[Music]
yeah you like it though right you liking
it
what did I grab oh
mommy you like it
why won't you add anything there wasn't
me
oh my God it's me
not dead I know I see oh that was a
horse
I don't know how to get over there I'm
just gonna follow what you guys did
before
also
somebody earlier
somebody earlier called us the 4S I
guess so it was fairies box Phoenix and
flower
is
don't you bring money in this household
oh you suck Palmer
you suck
ers
[Music]
don't believe in yourself believe in the
me who believes in you
I don't need to give up
[Music]
oh my God
gave her okay oh my God she did it you
are such an actual gamer
nah that was nothing that was everything
you are so cute and impressive
anyway ladies
that doesn't count restart the Run
yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh yes
[Music]
what would you
sucking videos
I was doing good and then I was not
doing good what is that I was winning
until I lost
like things are really good and then I
just keep getting it what is going on
[Music]
[Laughter]
yourself yeah I thought that was your
spot that's where you always go
I cannot deal with you
okay
I'm as a b word
sure
okay homo you suck
oh
come back
I'm the horse you're the awesomest
ultimate horse
the fact that the Trap is what got you
over the edge
okay
I'm gonna I'm gonna show like how I am
when I honky I'll do it do it
right now right now
[Music]
[Laughter]
right now
what is that what is that spinning thing
yeah I don't know let's find out oh I
think it goes up and down
okay oh
boy oh
[Laughter]
here we go
don't feel bad
[Music]
that's a proof there's two black hole
[Laughter]
all right
what is this
that's so evil who put that there
yes I I thought I can't I I shouldn't
always be trying to help hello
he's helping me
pain pain
I can't put it anywhere oh yeah it's
still too far guys
[Music]
I'm doing it how do you run I don't know
I don't know I just I just I press d
wouldn't run like that you guys I don't
think we can make it the rest I don't
know
[Laughter]
yeah
that was a plus plus plus that was
everything
I could try I loved that I'll give us a
little help yeah yeah
oh yeah in the beginning too please
thank you what's the man
oh thank you for letting the oldest one
go first
[Laughter]
the honeymoon
[Music]
[Laughter]
so happy over there oh I wanna know how
it feels to be in the goal
wait why did you
did
to mess with you
this is a dumb game
I love this game
also I love this game by the way when I
say it's a dumb game I mean it with love
I think yeah I don't think we're gonna
win we're gonna win it's gonna keep
going we got this we got this oh
I used to be so much better
you used to what sorry what'd you say I
used to be so much better at this game
I don't know why I got so bad at it why
would you do that
I'm so
sorry
there's no way we can make it now I
think it's go to the honey
[Music]
how the [\h__\h]
that was so cute you like licked your
lips you're like yeah
how can you
I thought we were honkidasu
no sabotage
it's fun
what is your item Ice Ice Baby okay Ice
Ice Baby what is your sabotage
okay that's nice that's nice
it's the wind on the right
it is not the black hole we need to get
rid of the black hole
oh
[Music]
my God
one shot hold on everybody quiet one
shot one opportunity
Nina please
[Laughter]
like double jumped why
the big green thing is it okay I think
it's gonna shoot
okay you know here here I want to help
us out okay
you're welcome oh no it just explodes
my bad I for real didn't know
no problem no problem we gotta test it
out yeah
um
you're thinking very hard about this I'm
actually trying to help us
[Music]
attached to
catch two of them wait what look at it
look look at the the oh no how's the hey
oh yeah
no
but yes will the my enemies die wouldn't
block you think the whole of silica
can you um can you
um try sorry baby a very high jump at
the very top
sorry that was not very girly of me
you got this kiwawa did you get past the
big ball so cry look at my eyes
wait till you get to the top top
[Music]
[Applause]
points for the coins
[Music]
all right
I'm entering my Joker Arc the straw oh
yeah get rid of it that was good that
was a good destroy
these jokes
oh you're so cute
how did she make it look so easy oh oh
I'm daring I'm a little daring today
yeah a little daring fairy
hello rainbow I'm down
please
die please
oh
[Music]
yeah it's just like Mario party you know
when you play Mario Party and gives you
random Stars
[Laughter]
the game's like well you know you just
need a little bit more
um
[Music]
wait oh to run we have to hold up
wait what happened to you I'm not even
playing the game at this point I wish I
immediately no you got this
I mean uh do what I did and go past the
spiky hey Pomo
do what I did and win a game
when last
time I
watch balls
and now I'm gonna watch you fall before
my very eyes
yeah yeah oh [\h__\h] there's a spiky there
now
Panic raccoon so
oh my God what is the best way to go
[Music]
I was supposed
[Laughter]
I'm gonna I'm gonna try that way too
I think yeah okay
dying them
[Music]
I'm so happy hey you can still come back
three turns kiwawa I don't know it only
gets harder and harder from here no if I
win each one
then yeah
I I have to assist myself here I have I
think we were struggling on the other
like um
oh okay you're really going for the
chance
I need to make it really really easy to
at least get past the beginning okay
okay okay okay okay okay well maybe you
got this watch out for the oh my God
yeah
the wrecking ball Milly Cyrus in the
beginning
Cyrus
[Music]
[Laughter]
in the chat just being really
disappointed
[Laughter]
oh my God
[Music]
I mean come on at least one time I wanna
get to the
Club you got this this time you got this
oh oopsies
oh okay
Lily says I'm sorry
[Music]
okay okay
wait wait for me can you take my hand
yeah yeah yeah come here come here come
here yeah
then on the side
we got this we got this
I got you baby
so be careful be careful you're gonna
need to make a really big jump and
there's ice so just be careful
okay okay
oh make a big jump and then just go
right go right go right yeah yeah good
job good job okay don't panic thank you
don't panic do a small jump small jump
smoke away sorry sorry okay
no no no come back to the left a little
bit and then when the hay comes back try
to jump over the ball
over the ball yeah yeah yeah yeah wait
wait okay like you can jump on the hater
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
you did so good though
[Music]
you did so good
[Laughter]
she go
wait is it a tie oh
God
[Laughter]
I'm back again
coming back
I am the trash raccoon
where is it hold on I need to open a
window
that gave me a workout
oh my God
we're gonna work out where is the Wawa
win
I need a win do we want to go to the
waterfall yeah I guess
emotionally stimulated
oh it sounds hot give me a minute
oh I'm old take your time I can't handle
this much excitement
okay
for balancer
I think oh wait I don't know that I
think it's to make it like more
difficult or more easy for us no
I don't know what this is no it depends
yeah you can choose how much you want
these oh yeah
[Music]
um
who won the first game wait was it
Rosemary or me I forget
no way
did Polo actually win the first game no
way yeah
I don't remember
I don't remember oh you're right um it
just it just it's such an event that
doesn't tend to happen so who could it
have been yeah
oh I love this one I'll win this map you
got this come on Kiara
just sometimes I feel in this game you
gotta like believe in yourself
you know okay you just gotta believe in
yourself we can go for the water I mean
right we have to be able to yeah I don't
think we'll be able to okay we won't you
won't be able to jump yeah if you don't
do the ladder yeah the stairs
but they're still like up to the
mountain I don't think we can jump down
put it up top put it up top it's not
letting me that's not what I want to do
yeah it is it is I did it it I don't
know why oh I bet I thought we started
from the top top whoops
yeah.com
I'm with us
[Music]
little flying horse
you look so cute
foreign
[Music]
I think it's too high yeah
no problem no problem let's go ladies
let's go girls
[Music]
you girls are really alike I love it
off meme oh yeah
but you joined me anyway even though you
don't get it that sweet
[Laughter]
ie
[Music]
I'm just trying to give you girls a
competitive advantage
thank you
[Music]
oh she did it oh wait oh
I'm just trying to make you girls feel
like you have a chance
oh
you are if you're gonna jump up get away
from the honey yeah don't jump good job
okay
[Music]
oh
she left you she abandoned you no I'm
right here
come on Chihuahua you got this oh
if you loved her the horse and the horse
crouches
[Music]
if you loved her you'd give up
wait hello oh it's a little weird if you
loved her you would have given up
clearly your love is false joined me
yeah it's just like pomu and Kiwa wet
okay
well wet yeah
Go In Style hey
you all wet I want to go in style keep
that up it's something
what happens when your feathers
I don't know
I don't I don't currently I only have
feathers in my ears
character
you guys can go through the ferris wheel
by the way oh
[Music]
cold no just go through the bottom go
through the bottom Pomo
I don't trust you
okay keep doing the same thing you're
doing it's gonna work
[Music]
oh
I should have taken that path I made
that easy I told myself wait oh wait I
didn't even know there was ah
okay okay okay
wait I want to go in style Cannon style
yeah
hold B that's the most stylish option
that is pretty stylish oh
[Laughter]
wow Nina what's wrong I'm purposely
throwing so that you girls feel like you
have a chance
oh thank you yeah she nerfed herself on
the scorer modifier
what is that
oh
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
why am I here
might he suffer like literally
how much food
I was so good at this game before who
put the cat in there
that's what you get I put the cannon
that's what you get don't put the kids
we all die yeah yeah we all died
[Music]
wait that's a it blows up right yeah it
blows up like bigger stuff like I think
there's a smaller TNT that will blow up
one thing and then you have the bigger
what is this I actually have no idea
what this is
[Music]
what's that
I blocked the cannon from shooting
okay nice I welcome that to you what you
guys don't like my Cannon come on I hate
you and your cabin
easy football yeah
I need to eat those wings
oh
wait did you hear the little
did you hear that when she fell
no it was my inner voice oh
yeah
[Music]
I'm I'm nodding at you you could do it
you can do it you can do it
yeah jump okay no more
what was the dancing again R uh
[Music]
back down I'm too scared sorry pomu okay
let's do a big jump big jump yeah big
jump big jump big jump big jump
now go down down is the safest
don't go into the cannon though if you
do just just like hang on to the wall if
you do get into the cannon because
that's what I what I wanted to do you
got this
come on
[Music]
yeah
two two let's relax relax
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go
I'm so emotional no don't make it harder
no
[Music]
no oh
no no no
[Laughter]
you gave me dreams just to then
disappoint me oh hey what the [\h__\h] what
what's this we're just like a real
friend group
oh that's evil Chihuahua
okay okay
but how do we jump over it
how the hell
[Music]
oh my God
[Laughter]
oh my God that's right that's so awesome
hello
[Music]
which way are you gonna go oh far away
from you
I think that's a bad way though
use your Mario 64 gems
I don't think I can wait yes you can
maybe I think so you can you can yeah if
anybody
oh my body flopped okay it's okay
if anybody can do it it's you I believe
in you
Nina
[Music]
sorry for my language I wanted to get
back burn it darn it all to hell yeah
okay that that means I still have a
chance to Carnation par Nation maybe the
song is a little difficult
who wants to get rid of it I can get rid
of it please do thank God yeah
that's what I'm talking about
the door
[Music]
let's find out thank you I think you
open with something that's called a
handle
the color of the water is the same as
the ball
I did not put that
who put that there
it was used
[Music]
that's so evil that was I did not see it
it was amazing now we know
[Music]
the cat in front of the ball that way we
won't hit it it's probably put the fan
if you yeah yeah yeah it's gonna stop oh
yeah oh yeah a hook who put the fan was
that poem that was Pomo um
[Laughter]
come on
[Music]
um
well well well oh my God
damn it why do I have to be here with
pomu
I wish I was here with Chihuahua or
Rosie thank you but I would like to be
there with pomu okay I wish I was here
with rose in my dance
[Music]
wow wow
there is an ocean for me to stare at I'm
the one oh wait
what did you you're the what I'm the
horse yeah okay yeah that's what I
thought I said
and the good horse you are
[Music]
you know I have this option of reality
okay
yeah I shall add to the
to the reality but wait yeah okay
whatever I don't care
I don't care okay I don't even care too
quickly you know I'm like Vin Diesel
yeah you love it okay
what now
everybody's waiting oh
oh okay oh okay oh my God
I finally
[Music]
reality
I was pressing right
our reality is to die together it's our
reality together oh
how does Nina keep making it Mina I told
you I was losing on purpose at the start
[Music]
I wanted you girls to feel like I was
bad I wanted you to underestimate me
really I am big brain mental games now
we have to team up against her and make
sure she loses
there's a question mark at the waterfall
one
oh yeah that means I've never been there
okay should we do old mansion yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay
what is up here a monkey we should come
on
I don't think I've ever done we could do
it
okay okay
this one sucks I think question mark
means we're gonna unlock a new map so
I'm gonna try getting it
at this one okay oh okay where do we
start or down here
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
I think I'm dead
it's a dead body I'm dancing over your
dead body
[Music]
people to me I'll take a photo
[Applause]
confidence
all right roseme goodbye um
why am I the only one up there
oh
you think I think we actually have to
destroy that yeah I'm on it I'm on it I
realized my mistake but how do we get up
then
um there's a button here I don't know
what that does that does the elevator
but I don't think it'll come down
because the stairs are in the way oh
okay that is an option it's dangerous
but it is
oh wait how'd you get up there
I deserve that go on this thing right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah like
a bunch of thorns but that's kind of my
thing I think you can come through you
are thorny
oh
you're so immune good job
good job my girl Mama's proud
the solo points stands
are you are you announcing a solo song
with this
yeah
it's called
um I made I made it I made it
I am now showing you guys how much I
love you oh no wow
[Music]
honestly
problem then
I was an eye who did that I don't know
yeah I put it there that will be my
favorite that's a Looney Tunes moment
the Anvil dropped on my head
[Music]
Us close your eyes and kiss me oh I
think I can't close my eyes I think I
have a that's awkward then I don't want
to kiss you oh no what
it's
the black hole it's going
why is someone
oh oh yeah
[Music]
oh no she's not getting stuck
getting sucked
[Music]
oh okay
I don't have Facebook also it's not the
metaverse it's akiverse
I love
you and
wow
you girls just hate
gaming and winning it seems so yeah yeah
I think so oh my God wait actually I
think you guys ate okay I think I think
uh kiwawa if you put it to the right
like between the red thing and the goal
like up there so we can jump on it oh hi
hi yeah yeah like hear it oh yeah yeah
like here
no I think we'll be able to go
[Music]
does that does that make sense
I'll try I'll try bad oh okay
I keep looking at other people's
characters
nice nice
I'm happy when you suffer together noise
yeah I like when we suffer together
right
does somebody want to build something
with me here to get up oh okay
if you do that roseme yeah yeah that's
good because then only a few people can
go and use it oh oh
that is evil right
please
jump first Nina
hold on I did it for you it's all why
did I do it wait I want to see what this
thing does
I don't know what it doesn't do anything
it doesn't do anything what the hell
do it I think I want to go down after
all no
no no no no no no I died I died she's
trying to lure you no she's trying to
lure you into a solo Victory okay
hello
come on I don't know where do we go do
you're gonna have to jump but avoid the
oh okay jump and then duck yeah don't
stop ducking oh
my God
okay okay are you ready we're gonna have
to jump to jump high
oh
Chihuahua listen to me you have to go
left yeah and then right oh my God
everybody
else
[Music]
you got this you got your job yes good
job let's go okay
[Applause]
so close
so close baby
well we know the way to go now yeah I
was the last survivor Elise
it's hard to jump over to the right wall
and why what why oh what just happened
oh hey elevator oh yeah the elevator now
if you make the elevator possible yeah
that's that's oh now you girls are
complaining it's too easy yeah yeah you
will never be satisfied ladies
first
oh my God
[Laughter]
damn girls I thought we were friends
it's a it's a gift like you get a new
effing character or something or
something no yeah
cool if you place the second one I see
it nice
[Music]
wait you don't want me to unlock levels
what do you see huh
you'll get it but at what cost yeah
okay
[Music]
I'm so disappointed with myself I'm
gonna end up here yet I did
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
no I I hate the blue thing
the blue thing with the blue thing the
little spiky blue thing
you know the blue thing
[Music]
this thing
this thing oh the ice yeah
oh it's still evil
what is wrong with us that is so evil
why are we like this
[Music]
good job where's my other
wait how many games do you need for
Underdog I don't know I thought you just
have to be the last one in a suddenly
surprising
okay
um
damn I felt so much adrenaline just from
there
I know isn't it fun pumped up now
oh interesting
this is so troll you guys this is
getting interesting absolutely these
arrows are still evil
okay okay oh
you got things
both of me what the [\h__\h] you thoughts to
everything by one millimeter I swear
oh
I initiated my hacks
let's get the flower oh
he's almost gonna win fine she deserves
how to make it harder she deserves it
why are there so many doors
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's using her big brains
what is the killer cooking it's the new
recipe
[Music]
okay
so evil what the heck is going on
oh my God
oh my God I hate this
oh
I hate this I hate this I love this game
[Music]
the arrows really make it impossible I
know
duck okay
no no
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
fix this I know how to fix it
[Music]
no no I can fix it oh wait it doesn't it
doesn't only temporarily but can someone
else just said Thank you mine is
temporary I think I got you I can fix it
I can fix it
foreign
[Laughter]
I'm the best
a little bit too good
when I saw like a minion what the heck
[Music]
what's his name
I deserve this
the door is open for you oh I deserve a
win
[Music]
Victory oh traps oh
nice finally suffering from my own hands
hey oh my God what a game yeah what's up
talk to me baby
I don't like the way you go I don't like
the way you kill me too I don't like the
way she yeah let's work together all
right yeah
I don't think it's possible
I don't know oh places so you go all the
way above you go all above the building
oh my God I forgot about it oh yeah I
forgot about this
is so evil
wow oh it doesn't go anywhere
wait can you actually
can you oh
how you do that how do you shmoo like
that you know it's called it's moving
all the time
how did she do that wait where did she
go how does she do that she keeps moving
someone tried a cannon yet
[Music]
I don't I don't know
what do I do
oh my God wait I don't even know what's
the best way to go where are you guys go
what the [\h__\h] Nina what the [\h__\h] how
[Music]
um
like that who is Nina kosaka why is she
she's so amazing does Nina kosaka speak
Russian wow
[Music]
the bubble
boy now Nina's gonna win
I gotta do my Tippy yeah in the middle
of the black hole and the bubble
this is all up to you
[Music]
actually bubble you just had to drop
down where the flower was yeah
[Laughter]
purposely tried to sabotage me you think
I'm not gonna try to sabotage you wow
some jeans
[Music]
I just need to use the restroom can I
pee before the pyramids
pyramid
give me a moment okay I'll be right back
they should be behind the pyramid not in
front of it maybe
hey you make sure they behave okay
everybody you have to protect my honor
while I pee all right
they look really cool
in real life or in the game both oh yeah
both yeah me too yeah
I want to go too I want to go I want to
go eat the goo
what what cool the sarcophagus
[Music]
you want to eat the ghoul of dead people
it's like a dead people have glue it's
for like the everlasting life
I think the goop Maybe
formed there eagle
follow your dreams full moon
I'll let you know how it is if it's good
yeah if it's good you can add it to your
menu
[Music]
maybe it has like a chicken nugget sauce
or what oh
do we have lucky sauces yeah yeah
I'm so sorry I would love to do that I
would totally do that but we already
have like 20 sauces on our menu so I am
incapable of adding like a limited time
ones
of sauce like a sauce collab you know
the law of sauces prevents me from doing
that I'm very sorry otherwise I would
totally do it yeah well with the sauce
that like people don't like
you know they don't everybody likes
every sauce oh okay yes except the cool
one no we love we love it and I would do
it but you know the love of the sauces
prevents me I'm sorry I think of a
loophole maybe can you add the glue to
the usual room uh-huh uh yes I would do
that indeed
yeah who makes like the ghoul with like
an existing sauce and then it could make
like a special oh yeah you know oh
Deadpool movie where you got that they
don't know yet from now thanks for
watching
so much I'm laughing so we discovered
with Mommy goop in the mommy mom mommy
sorry Mommy uh in there and people on
the internet to really said they would
drink it yeah yeah
we're drinking who's goop they're all
joking right
um
sorry Mommy I'm sorry sorry Mommy
what's going on here
how do mommies produce goop
well wow the goodness comes out or
something from where
[Music]
um
because we're the pyramids
can we please unlock some of the items
[Music]
oh there's a ton of them oh my goodness
wait I have been the pyramid wait you
have been for real for real okay so many
gifts and this one yeah because I
remember the quicksand
yeah I never have yeah I'm gonna try to
get some of the stuff too what I mean
quickly where's the quicksand on the
other side
I got it
[Applause]
[Music]
there's your kitty oh
you got an outfit
is there still gifts left no no I but
it's the random so we have to jump over
this yeah you have to jump over when
does the cat do you have to jump up yeah
jump up on him yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
or he'll squish you if he lives down
yeah
all right I need to meet you in the in
the quick set I just wasn't sure
oh
maybe I'm doing the wrong decision but
hold on
Oh I thought about that oh ah yeah wrong
position
it's my party yeah who's not dead
actually one of my fears is to drown in
a quicksand or like in a swamp where you
you know like this I don't know if it's
true that swamps do this but like in
Russian there's a word called balota and
it's like swampy water where you slowly
sink I don't know if it's a real thing
or a pulse thing but it's one of my
genuine fears that sounds real it's a
genuine fear of mine
I think if I died I would like to go out
by like a swamp Maybe
by a swamp like you want to slowly
suffocate to death what is wrong with
you that's so weird what's under there
peacefully in your sleep
can somebody please die
okay do it Pomo for Kiara yes I love you
that means so much to me
[Applause]
I am sorry to bring it back but I am
just so
you want to like slowly suffocate to
death
what is under there
like I don't know just if I were to die
like I'm just saying you know but you're
okay with like the excruciating like
asphyxiation or like you're fine with
that
yeah I guess so oh
yeah you're a punk rock that's all baby
oh I'm so excited you are so punk rock
it's the most like rock and roll thing
I've ever heard
metal AF
what is this what I picked what's a
rocket but what happened how does it
work
I don't know
hello okay
we got so quiet all of a sudden
you
you saw nothing I saw your black hole
you jerk
it's silent scares me oh it's part of
the game but me doing that is not part
of the game huh I don't hate the player
hate the game
[Music]
I think I'm alive I don't know how yeah
you are you can jump up the kitty gay
good job
come on Chihuahua you can do it well
even if I make it we get no point that's
good because it means we won't get
points because if you don't make it we
get points
you have to make it
big jump big jump baby you got this
yes yes yes okay you're good you're good
okay yeah yeah don't even stress no just
keep jumping there you go there you go
there you go go go go go go go go yeah
yeah you can touch the cat good job
it's better that we don't get points
than if like we all get it we don't get
further away from me at least
um
running away from you
door
door oh
my God everything's out of there wait a
second yeah
[Music]
um uh
oh God
oh
how did you get up
how did you get up there
oh what the hell did you
how did she make it up there I think she
jumped from here
wow from where oh from the very top yeah
yeah yeah yeah you stinky poopy
here
yeah you can you can do it you just
gotta do it how did you jump so far
we're flexible because we're young yeah
yeah okay
you gotta Sprint how do we Sprint by the
way it says it's like up but is it just
yeah I brought 50 bones trying to do
that job Nina do you really want to yeah
um
run it doesn't work for me either
printing yeah
um
shut up shut up why are you so mean to
me be nice to me
don't be nice to me
I feel I feel like there's so much
distance between us again
[Music]
the distance makes the heart grow fonder
that's true
I mean I would like to have some
chocolate fondue right now but oh that's
so sweet
what kind of fruits are you gonna put in
there
[Music]
what's that what's that really stinky
fruit called again
I've never had green oh me neither I
really want to try it but yeah you know
you gotta flip it around you have it
flipped the wrong way oh
oh like this yeah thank you thank you so
much I really appreciate that what's
going on
oh my God wait I can't I can't stop okay
[Music]
are you kidding me wait what
oh God I initiated mine
in the game this whole time
yeah yeah yeah try touching it try
touching it oh my God how
how jump up on the as high as you can on
the on the you got this yeah
you're killing it
oh my God
good job
[Music]
wrench off when I'm funny oh he's gonna
win she's gonna win I'm not I'm not
Nina's gonna win somehow
rosami Rosemary sweet Rosemary sweep
no I'm scared you got enough block kids
what's the timer thing you want to die
too
what timer
s
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you it was so zoomed out Kiara you
can get the jet pack as well
yeah I get the jetpack get the jetpack
I'm trying to do this really simple jump
right now you got this you got this just
double jump double jump yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah go go go go go go
good job girl good job kiwawa high five
such a cheese cheese man
oh my God oh my God are you hungry
you have to not win
you have to leave I told you guys
[Music]
okay back to skill okay actual skill
let's let's see yeah
[Music]
oh oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway I can't even stand on this house
roasting me I think Peanut's gonna win
again no no we're gonna have the sudden
death remember yeah
Don't Panic come on you got this baby
okay wait did we all make it oh yeah we
all made it yeah oh you became the under
ground oh [\h__\h] my Kelly oh my God
good job
you deserve it Rosie
[Music]
my Golden Child
again again
I'm getting better okay so let's give me
another chance let's try windmill it's
new yeah
I think I'm turning Kiara into the
sweatiest gamer
because you keep going again again
failure like in my heart right now
relatable
oh
oh wait you don't die if you hit that
right I don't think so
you know what
countries I don't think you can make it
wait does this go up and down
no I don't think it's possible and I
think there's no ground to land yeah oh
wait we just uh
really is this not a oh fudge
bye Rosie I love you what do I do here
trust me see if you can jump on it
I don't care can get out of here you got
this I believe
she's a gamer girl
I think trying to get to the ceiling to
try to get this stuff
die
she died in there oh my God the darkness
well
[Music]
um
I think that dying green silos yeah yeah
we found out it's so scary and what in
that green silos it's like people die
from that like a lot of people in a year
die from them Oh I thought I could yeah
we can't make this
there's no way
I think you fall I think there's like a
hole in the silo if you walk too far
oh yeah oh my God nice job I don't know
I don't even know no I think there's a
hole there and we died guys I don't
think I can
suck you
excuse me I don't think it's possible in
here
going to the right and see if there's
yeah hey no you're still alive
what do we die on we don't die right
away oh maybe a certain spot oh no way
good job Rosie good job Rosie you're a
gamer you're a gamer oh my God am I done
wait watch out
good job that was really nice you can
launch yourself from the thing okay
oh no this is the item I hate the most
yeah
I get it Polo just wants to see the
world brain it's true
she admits that she's evil
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
my hacks what on Earth she was ready oh
my God
she did not come to play around
she came to win
money
money money
[Music]
yummy yummy yummy you know money world
um okay what's Happening Here
how the heck are we gonna do this I'm
lost
there's a spike on there there's a spike
at the top I didn't know I'm blind oh no
it was so zoomed out yeah oh nice nice
jumps like a normal horse
join me in the silence
oh
[Laughter]
some people make it out yeah some people
don't some of us can find the hole what
is this thing didn't think this was
possible for us
but you're falling on like hand
huh I have created
it's my path okay you have to pay if you
want to land on my path okay
yeah okay I'll pay the toll is how she
makes her money
did I you want it yeah
when you ready come and get it
[Laughter]
[Music]
when you're ready come and get it
I said I put on the clown nose and I did
I did Nina stop
you said you like watching the world
burn I do I do I do so what's the
problem what's that dog
sorry I watch a lot of take off
[Music]
[Laughter]
gonna stay here I'm having a good time
here
[Music]
I had it I had it I panicked
holy
[Applause]
[Music]
family
oh listen to me my body is
[Laughter]
[Music]
I am so sweaty spaghetti right now
mmm I got you darling
[Music]
blew up the thing that you placed yeah
nice nice
[Music]
oh my gosh
join us home we'll come dance with us
Yeah dance with us
I will I'm just waiting
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
sweet
can you hold my hands I have a half I'm
sorry
I have no fingers I only have one
Evolution why
no I'm sorry
what's the what's the this deal
get punches if you touch the button up
top of it oh
good job
they were just crushed don't don't you
gotta practice this game oh no not again
[Music]
she crumbled
[Laughter]
oh I'm back I roseme yeah I'm sorry I
love you ah I'm sorry Rosalie you need
to learn the hard way the real world
freaking
oh
[Music]
I think there's levels
I put like a
what are we gonna do we want to do
another one
okay you can do a last one
because this game is fun but it's it
overwhelms
[Music]
[Laughter]
I guess that's funny
there's a box up there oh
foreign
you see remember when they were like
let's stop Nina from winning meanwhile
those two are winning yeah they're
trying to pin you against you
they're trying to pin you again
[Music]
here look here I give you this that's an
offering
I got the coin check out the coins
[Music]
[Laughter]
we
and
somebody can get the gift oh yeah yeah
because it's a random drop anyway I'm
gonna go get it
[Music]
okay okay
more stages
[Music]
okay
why does como keep getting all the
outfits homo
[Laughter]
let's go this is so sad
when I wake up
you'll see me tomorrow
when you wake up what do you mean there
is no space on that piece of wood you're
wrong
there's always
yeah
yeah honestly I followed you into the
skies no if you loved her you would have
died for her
I already died he's gonna die for her
huh
when did you die for her I die for her
all the time I die for her already when
are you gonna die I die for her all the
time
no no Zuck
Ah that's literally Mark Zuckerberg
okay I deserve that I deserve that I
deserve that I deserve that
I deserve that
I deserve that and they've still took
people made it and it's still them
making it
damn it okay this is gonna fail every
time now do it I dare you do it oh yeah
this is for you only
um
the black hole though okay here I'll
help you out here's a little Stone
offering for you thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
exactly
[Applause]
[Music]
that's awesome
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
nothing bad ever happens to the coasts
don't worry it's a reference
damn it
hey what what Ah that's water huh
well okay we need a platform to jump on
though uh however this one has the
downside that it oh
okay okay yeah yeah put that okay where
you first wanted to put it like uh yeah
yeah yeah
we don't need it there
quickly quickly
okay
you can you can you can save yourself
you can save safely
I'm a bit clumsy today I don't know okay
you are so cute that like it does not
even matter
sorry that was so loud
no
congratulations
[Music]
Frozen you win
it's a kind of short one do we want to
do one
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I was pretty sore right yeah is there is
there a map that we want to do
uh the pyramid is kind of fun
the pyramid was fun we can also do
random if y'all want
[Music]
um
yeah random
oh wait one of you had like the
chameleon and stuff do you want to try
it on oh
I think uh oh wait okay
[Music]
I think Rosemary had the chameleon no I
don't have it no yeah you do yeah I
think you did yeah does anybody know
where we can change the outfits I don't
think I got anything no you did you did
oh Pomo it's you how do you
nothing
to see anything
she's so cute what did you press as a
button to change I just left click yeah
I don't have anything
oh yeah I only have the raccoon darn you
oh I really
really no you have the chameleon I saw
that you said you bought it huh
you're the owner of the lobby so let me
get all this stuff you press uh right
click sorry no lava chameleon do you
really not
oh wait did I change the mode sorry
sorry is free playing on the right mode
should it be party sorry everybody thank
you
[Music]
Patty potty random
party party matter anyway it does all
right
laughs
let's go
but that's ridiculous
oh no it's not this one
oh well I have fond memories of it yeah
oh yeah yeah this one I think was the
most chaotic one yeah this one's pretty
crazy
oh wait I forgot
yeah
all right we can
you get the pleasure yeah you really
slip
[Applause]
[Music]
how do you say squirrel in Japanese
all right I should have known I love it
it's okay brain horde it's like when I
forgot how to say two and it's my name
is Mina
oh
well I mean that's not that's not like
you know it's a little different yeah
oh
my God
I'm so sorry for laughing I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry for laughing I love you so
much
I used to be a gamer Chihuahua will
continue on I'm so sorry
I love you so much oh [\h__\h] I'm sorry you
gamer girl I want to be a game of girl
you're a cool gamer girl no no no gamer
girls here only refined gentlemen true
true oh at the refined Gentleman's Club
us can I be a a refined Gamer look at
how few babies
wow okay
this is training Arc a little bit late
but it's training Arc
um
what
what what
why would you why would you
thank you
why would you put this up there
the suck oh thank God okay
okay
[Music]
the genius move that saved us all
oh wait give me like a headless chicken
[Music]
what do we do oh
bird baby baby oh more black holes
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
skill issue for us
[Music]
she got this good job easy
you got this Rosie oh I've always
wondered what it's like to be punched by
my own kind
yeah but I want to see what it's like to
get punched by Rosemary okay did it feel
good me too did you like it no no
it all up
hmm
[Music]
I don't understand the traffic stop
thing the what me neither what does it
do it just opens up which trap thing
sorry wait what are your traffic or not
oh yeah
you know what that does right oh it does
it existing thing is yeah maybe maybe
yeah
oh you can cool yeah but the cannon is
gone too no oh
[Music]
thank you
don't even worry I'm having so much fun
yeah I love it okay
I needed so much laughing and this is it
yeah he was so silly
[Music]
okay here we go
it only the glove only punches when you
step on it right back oh
you know
[Applause]
[Music]
she just left
how could you do this
I missed I I did it I'm so sorry Kiana
[Music]
I'm so sorry Kiana
what that was
oh my God
oh I know what this is I know what this
is wait what is that it makes it makes a
little like see the little surfing board
up top and shoots it across the screen
yeah
I didn't realize it was a paper
am I the only one still alive
[Music]
chaos I call it fun
[Laughter]
I have to help myself
okay maybe well I'll tell you don't go
in the paper plane do not go on it yeah
careful of the fire careful there's a
fire here careful okay
okay
yeah
because you're getting a Twist like this
[Music]
look at my dead body
when I was in the paper plane it crashed
I think as you landed on it that's why
[Laughter]
yeah I got squished between the elevator
and the platform
[Laughter]
oh
if you call the elevator and then you
jump on it but not from this side that
you're on from the other side yeah yeah
from the other side careful
and just get in and get it yeah yeah get
in and jump jump yeah
yeah you got this
if you like touch it on the tip maybe
that's when it crumbles it just starts
crumbling if you land on it perfectly
yeah
I think the second you land on it is
when it starts crumbling oh no no no
don't go there don't go there don't go
there
just go open the door oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my gosh
yeah yeah good girl I'm gonna get like a
timeout at some point you can't get over
how Nina died it's so funny
nice nice
girl or what you doing
you're always waiting for you
[Music]
it's so cute it looks so cute
it's so close can I just can I get it
with my tongue touch it
I will
I will survive this time
[Music]
because it's gonna block the elevator
yeah it'll block the elevator no you can
take the paper airplane just take the
airplane
oh pee it's so good okay
I will try yeah try and try it
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm gonna report it
hey guys we're having a meeting
I saw Rosemary and Nina kissing stairs
with with kiwawa with the with the
splashard
it wasn't me oh There She Goes
oh
recreating this whole what
oh my God
suddenly sheep
oh we have three turns left
okay Kiara grab the coin and you have to
win oh no I grabbed oh which coins no no
no that's my I'll put I'll put it Oh I
thought I got the coin okay
yeah
[Music]
let's go girls grab the coin yeah yeah
okay okay okay okay
come this way
okay wait stay there where you are you
can just get on the plane also yeah I
think you should just do the play yes or
the air or like the look look yeah yeah
get in here just stand here stand here
the girls
[Music]
oh
victory
victory is mine I had to die or else you
want to get the point
true true
you're a good girl
I was just excited maybe I want to be
here with my with my chihuahua thank you
you're cute
I can be I can be everybody's whoa
there's enough wallet to go around bye
Rosie
[Music]
our communal Chihuahua we are all the
Bugs Bunny meme
oh my God
[Music]
oh
can you only get the coin once oh man
hmm
here I'm gonna
oh
um
I accidentally pressed that I didn't
mean to
sorry wait wait anywhere sorry sorry
go for it
I saw that
I'll activate the elevator
don't look at my body please it's really
embarrassing no you deserve this you're
cute
[Music]
yeah
you're so fluffy you're using me like a
perfect casket what what as long as I
don't have the mummy good
dab
I'll Come Dance With You yay
last one Chihuahua you gotta Focus this
is the one this is the one
[Music]
don't do it though
you want to know how I got these
feathers
[Music]
thank you
what has she done what are you done are
you okay
[Music]
it's gonna be okay
oh my God you want to know how I got
scars
[Laughter]
I have changed I am not myself anymore
this game has changed
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
wait which one of us is not dead hold on
oh yeah I see someone I saw someone
moving oh there you go it was me no no
there it is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
she does truly mean kfp
I'm sorry everybody I'm moving you from
the chair I'm putting the girls in the
chair
oh no we're at a key party
snacks Wawa would you hire me
is it good money
how much is it per hour it's good money
for me
so do you think I could make a standard
living wage
uh you will make a negative wage wait I
pay you to be kfp
but you give it directly to me oh my God
are you a quote leader paid an exposure
yeah yeah exposure
don't you want an exposure I would love
this offer it's a great offer actually
see right I thought so yeah and like
this is also part of the plan
oh enlightenment
yeah I would like to be enlightened me
too
I'm going to no more no more darkness in
The Silo right yeah
yeah
kfp keep the Phoenix paid have
um by the way like where are the where
was the hole in the silo I don't know I
feel like it was like Schrodinger's hole
you know
consistent it felt like
sometimes it was there sometimes not why
not people get the special seat across
you yeah because I don't want bomo to be
with kiwawa and rosemary I want oh
oopsies sorry ah what did I do no
okay sorry I'm just you know what I'm
just gonna bring you girls back you know
what you're gonna sit on the table
can we sit on top of each other uh I
don't have the vertical like a totem
like a totem because there's like a Fuki
that is vertical
oh wow I got this oh
yes
we're sitting on top of ourselves
[Music]
oh yeah
oh I'll be on the bottom oh
you're you're you're about you I'm a I'm
a boy
oh my God it looks like we're like
cheerleaders you know
oh my God
it's your birthday we're gonna party
like it's your birthday
[Music]
I've moved it away so we can have more
room
[Laughter]
three don't feed us yeah no you get paid
in exposure
[Laughter]
she learned from the best
oh yeah I brought my daughters can you
watch my daughters for today no no no no
no
she talks she cries
so perfect
baby my babies I I I I I have
I don't know I can't handle them alone
in a second yeah
look at us we're a family
are we
we're a family look
[Music]
this looks like Nina playing with like
three cutouts
[Music]
this is Baby Rosie and baby Bobo and I'm
Papa Nina
[Music]
yeah
my gentlemen what what are y'all um what
are you all doing this week what are
y'all streaming talk to me
endless Titan I'm almost done with totk
okay can you can you pitch the game
but I want to like stall because I said
it feels so much to like explore some
stalling now you're getting all the
corrects all 1000.
I love them but no thank you
what other games are you playing after
qtk can you tell us
I'm thinking like GTA San Andreas
you did yeah it's really really good I'm
doing the frick now did you play it on
stream yeah I did
oh oh did you finish it yeah I did
name every character
DJ Big Smoke Ryder big balls
yeah and big boss
I love big boss
Rosie Pomo what are you girls playing
this week
um the seat's a bit hectic for me I'm
thinking about playing some Outlast it
may be GTA four what's like original
Outlast or trials
are so so into GTA whoa
yeah I'm I'm a gangster
[Laughter]
this is why she has a gun yeah do you
like muscle cars
oh cart wait what's a muscle cars
what is the muscle car what is a muscle
car I learned it from playing GTA 5.
yeah it was a good practice the muscle
car isn't like an American car or that
is really wide and it's like all power
goes like yeah wait like what I missed
it why does the low riders or no is that
different it's a wide car and they
mostly are I think in n a Mustang
is a muscle car
yeah yeah
what are you streaming this week
um I don't know my schedule
Minecraft oh my God we're like Monday
what do you mean you don't have your
schedule
yeah so what are you doing this week I
have to look at it
it's tomorrow
something I I
um
oh you're gonna have so much fun
are you crying don't be talk about
cinnamon roll
s and and um
is that how they're gonna connect yeah
spicy spicy
I love how that's the things that you
see cinnamon rolling
what's Nina doing this week hi
what am I doing this week poem
you say I am playing metal gear it's
five or six streams for five or six
creams
she's inheriting the metal gear solids I
have just metal gearing it up
and it's during the day because public
streams at night she'll be able to keep
up
Oklahoma will be back seating oh she's
done she sometimes she's like oh you're
missing this thing go here open that
door
it's her passion I know I understand I I
also I can't stop myself from
backseating people even if we're playing
a game I know in what game I know
sometimes it's really hard yeah we're
getting Chihuahua what game do you
backseat people in I want to see you be
toxic
I I can backseat Sims
[Music]
I I Backstreet with someone in Sims
already and I could backseat uh a lot of
their pictures
it's like the spider maybe maybe I can
maybe a little bit but not really not
confident not as well as Nina could hey
I mean you don't need to be good at the
game or even beat the game in order to
backseat people you know yeah
yeah you're just gonna wanna
do embarrassing no no no no it's they
love to call people out when they have
back seat in there yeah it does feel
good if you backseat then do it with
actual correct knowledge please
do not try to manipulate us
it's because the funniest thing is
sometimes I I will just read someone and
everyone's like oh you got one guide you
believe that yeah and I'm like I guess
sorry for reading my chat
I got one guide every day at school
[Music]
the problem too is like especially if
it's a name that I don't recognize I go
out of my way to read what they wrote to
make them feel welcome in the Stream
right because I'm thinking like oh it
could be their first time and if I'm
like hey how are you let me read what
you write and they're lying
I feel you
[Music]
hi girls I am hungry before before we go
could you give your quick goodbyes and
where people can find you and all that
fun stuff
starting with uh I guess let's Go
reversed order oh yeah
granny Frozen I'll start with you girls
because then like I'll finish talking to
stream so Rosie
okay okay
um meet you in the schoolyard for a fist
fight yeah okay um see um yeah or or my
YouTube channel where's me love luck
youtube.com or whatever she's also on
twitch sometimes yeah
yeah
thank you for watching it was really fun
thank you for inviting me
thank you for waking up
thanks for waking up early
he wasn't that early
so earlier that early 10 a.m next time
early earlier
yeah yeah
oh oh it's my turn oh ARG it's me turd
um
catch me getting a Grimace Shake today
for his birthday
is she a pirate now I don't know all
right
pirate I just felt like a little spin
you know gotta ah
[Music]
Just Go With It
accept it
[Music]
you Barnacle head
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
it's the truth
that a little Barnacles are disgusting
yeah they're like all salty and weird
they're like they attached to the sides
yeah they're sharp and disgusting yeah
[Music]
I
yes I didn't mean it
I guess I'm sorry yeah you have to leave
on a good note you know it's true it's
true
[Music]
okay
hello I am so sorry for the suffering I
put everyone through today it was fun
yeah
where I can do better but I don't know
man today it's a Monday you know it's a
[\h__\h] Monday so it happens to the best
of us
like lasagna
I I
am rich and she hates Monday I think oh
God
don't expose me don't worry
do they know that you're the Garfield
SCP
I am uh I am a phoenix I am maybe orange
but I'm and I love cats but I'm a
phoenix Okay so
I love Garfield I would love to be
Garfield I want to be a cat yeah
[Music]
the video of the a care field video I
think on my Channel that I uploaded a
million years ago where I did A Garfield
meme
okay okay hear me out I hear the QR
field but what about gar Wawa
mom
really does feel like I could not it
could it may not be a reference to
Garfield it may also be a reference to
Seinfeld field oh
[Music]
okay I have a question uh-huh when can
you tell the audience perhaps maybe
if we will ever get another M animal oh
uh what animal would you like me to
impersonate
[Music]
America
it's a meerkat what is a meerkat yeah I
think they sound like a
oh that's so cute easy okay I'll put it
in my suggestion box
oh sorry could you do it again I didn't
hear
I was in the suggestion box with some
the paper Destroyer oh oh simple mistake
simple mistake however I ran out of
paper and I ran out of pens I'll submit
it later
yeah
I'll give you my email it's uh
[Music]
okay writing down writing down right now
at
um
l i g i g m a
dot com
email her promo
seconds
wait a second it was the dot a t a t for
Austria oh ATM
foreign
I'll I'll look into it okay
okay yeah thank you thank you for your
valuable time you're so welcome no thank
you for getting us together again
and and uh lastly just in case uh
everybody didn't know I just want to say
Kiara I know you're so busy because
you're preparing for your
you're a busy busy girl thank you for
making time for us despite your busy
busy schedule
[Music]
I'm sorry
computers we're like last night when I
was so confused with my schedule
everybody was like can you can you make
sure I think you is this time are you
sure yeah yeah yeah yeah
you stressed me out with the times you
yeah and then I was like oh I'm sorry
koala I know can you check again please
that's me every days I wasn't even
phased by it I was like oh
I was even sure I was like did we change
the time I was like okay I'm done with
it
for you you really made me doubt myself
because I fixed my schedule two times
and re-uploaded it two times and then it
was still wrong and the time that you
guys were looking at the EST was still
wrong
and I thought it was right I was so like
confused like what do you want I already
fixed it five times
everything's good well here we are just
just just believe believe in the
I I up until this morning I'm like I
don't know you said there's like hours
between us but it says 11 A.M Eastern
and this starts at noon Easter yeah I
doubted you until the very end my love
not only EST was wrong even on on the
Monday and I also had the everything
plus one yeah because it was supposed to
be plus two everything is so hard it is
everything I think my brain cells are
just burning away these past few days
feeling it so you're working hard
[Music]
to use somebody else can you donate
brain cells uh I don't have enough to
give yeah
I have I share it with lots of lines I
got barely any we take in ethereum we
take turns on the on the brain cell
oh okay I'll ask somewhere else then
I don't know if you I don't know if
Macbeth was like really big for you guys
where it's like you know the witches
they share I think it's like an eye and
stuff like that oh yeah that's us yeah
they like give an eye to each other or
maybe it wasn't from maybe I'm
misremembering I know that's in Hercules
oh that's the one it's the fates from
Hercules sorry
uh
uh did they yeah they did it many years
since I watched that
um
oh Macbeth also has the same story
though that's what I thought oh
we can have a communal it's like The
Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants but
it's like The Sisterhood of the
Traveling
take turns
uh
[Music]
me ladies it is time
yeah time for what for me to kick you
out bye-bye
thank you for having me you're welcome
Rosie I'm hungry oh okay bye bye
me too you know now that you mentioned
that I'm also very hungry how hungry
very hungry
how tempted
how tempting
[Music]
meme
how hungry I did not know
huh
yeah yeah yeah yeah we will teach you
all the memes
[Music]
bye everybody thank you so much
[Laughter]
yes okay