[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing about so emotion
it R feel me
[Music]
your
feel it R
me feel it me
[Music]
Kik hello
hello
y
I have [\h__\h] up the latency so chat is
not going to be the most helpful today
which is okay I mean the stream is not
going to be too long and the game is I
mean no DVR I turned that off if you
refresh it will be
gone uh but yeah it's probably be
fine oh my God so late the Kik the key
oh m m Mia
oh that's like DVR I can still turn off
once the stream is started but the
latency I
can't that's like once I press Start
stream it's over it's so
over so it's okay it's okay
no
problem four to five hours no for real
not honestly I'm aiming for two hours
today I don't even think I'll read Super
Chat sorry I wanted to but I realized I
have to get up uh really early
tomorrow maybe I can do like a 30 minute
speed reading uh at least if I yeah I
think I can do that I can do that
probably if the gaming part does not
take more than two
hours yeah yeah yeah yeah that would be
ideal and I heard I heard it doesn't
take that long this game and I honestly
don't know anything about it I don't
know what to expect it's probably just
one of those dorky funny games uh I
didn't watch anything about it I just
saw maybe one or two pictures or
so so we're going to have fun with this
I I like these kind of like stupid games
I like them I'm expecting it to be
stupid so yeah um in terms of health
health
update once again since yesterday my ear
is free I'm happy that my ear is
empty and my throat
is yeah my throat is I would say
healed
yeah we are back on track
all is fine I hope you guys are doing
fine too I hope you guys are taking care
of yourselves not getting
sick depending on where you are here and
there there's I feel like people always
say this though but like there's
something going around but there's
always something going
around but when I went to the doctor uh
yesterday he was I was like yeah I got
some like some virus and he was like
yeah something's going around right now
and I'm just thinking there's always
something going around don't you always
say say that don't you always say
that there's always
something oh my God the chat reaction is
so slow
today sorry man sorry for [\h__\h] it
up going the
going ah it's so
unusual Sor I I'll put up a pin comment
sorry today the chat latency is super
late
oops deal with it
[Music]
no yeah that's
fine two times the video hey you can't
do that can
you nothing that does nothing I
think you have 7 second no way you don't
have only 7 Seconds delay do you I say A
you say B go one 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 n oh oh
that I mean 8 n seconds is not
crazy that's not that's not the worst of
the
[Music]
world huh it just feel feels really
long doesn't
it okay I'm going to start the
game I am a part time
work I would like to remind you guys of
my
lore officially I am part-time Warrior
and part-time
Idol I
think
yeah no part-time Warrior and part-time
fast food worker no part-time Warrior at
part-time Idol with the dream of having
a fast food
restaurant oh starting starting tweet
[\h__\h] forgot
it that's it I think that was it but
it's not accurate anymore because I'm
I'm I have a fast food restaurant we
need to update my lore kfp is real okay
you can't tell me otherwise
okay starting
now what you got a problem with my
thumnail what what's with my
thumnail it's normal when you're like
part time working it gets stressful so
sometimes you sweat a little
bit I can't control my sweat I can't
unsweat myself excuse me for having
bodily
functions hm I'm working
hard okay why is this
Japanese I thought I thought there's
English too right English Korean Chinese
Chinese don't know I don't know I can't
read
English ah what oh my God
stressful I don't even hear anything am
I supposed to hear something yet is this
am I is this am I supposed to hear
something at this
point no I like how it says no
sir how did they translate this like
when I do like
epic yes or no
sir I love
that I love that
[Music]
yeah
oh I like seeing how some things are uh
capitalized and some things are not I
like
that
okay operation what does that
mean back to main menu so wait am I
supposed to hear something
I feel like I should be hearing
something no motion
blur
okay
okay okay for you just for you just for
you because I love
you
ah hauh yeah okay I hear it now
it was routed wrongly I knew there was
something
off
prologue IU his name
ISU that means in Japanese that means
like doing something first try for
example or or just the first first
attempt for
example my name is I I'm just an
ordinary civilian I recently moved to
this city iig
gyu it
that's uh that's also funny Ichi is also
funny interesting choices I heard that
it is generally unsafe and that many
residents are a little bit
confrontational I like that I like a
confrontational
environment then we all just speak our
mind let's go today is my first day of
part-time work B B I have to go now so I
won't be late the job location is just
past the downtown
core oh let's go to work this is like y
Yakuza this looks like
Yakuza shift run it's not working what
is it because of my keyboard being in
Japanese where's my mouse
h ah it takes a while until he starts
running it's it's not a horror game
right you guys said it's not a horror
game
this is why young people these days damn
it shut up oh he's being scolded yeah
those shitty young people [\h__\h] drunk
people [\h__\h]
off what's going on here oh man more
aloh this is not good guys don't drink
alcohol ever
ever you don't say anything oh okay
okay yay I work at the convenience
store this is the convenience store
where I will start working part time I
have to go to say hello to the manager
first manager son imagine if it's just I
am the I am the
manager maybe I am first
time here and I become the
manager uh hello wait that t just now
was a reference to F mommy ma I think
family Mar Melody when you enter the oh
my God you scare me like the way you
walk towards me with that
smile oh it's you I'm looking forward to
working with you uh yeah I'll do my best
no customers are here yet so you can
take a look inside the convenience store
before you start your work when you're
ready take your
position okay where's my position sir
over there okay let me let me look at
what you guys
offer yeah yeah yeah yeah that's the
that's the usual lineup although hair so
much hair dye that's a bit
unusual cute plushies I mean of this
size with oh with lucky bags that's
these kind of huge Plushies are rather
rare oh yeah spicy
magazines and some normal
magazines who who's that cute girl who's
that twin tail
girl what's her
name oh we got some
manga are these real ones love mine buin
say what over
roll can I crouch no
[Music]
oh
what oh I opened it w what a square ass
toilet the cat magazine is interesting
too who okay we have Yaki Sila
Jamba spring rolls KAG
chicken some uh uh pork with uh uh uh
bell pepper stuff
T
egg
manatu chicken rice sakis SOA hurger
[Music]
hamburger ice
cream more of that
[Music]
stuff oh where's this go
storage okay good good good good I'm
finding out where everything is alcohol
this is the the cause of all evil in the
world is
alcohol as we have seen
outside oh Bento section let's go yummy
yummy yummy yum yum yum yum yum it's all
the same [\h__\h]
Bento or at least they have some
different
sandwiches yeah those look very
classic do you have some hag and DTS
no lame I only eat hugen duts and if I
can get to a a basket Robinson you know
you know the drill potato
chips oh warm drink section I just found
out that in summer in the warm drink
section in the convenience stores in
summer they don't sell the same drinks
the same warm drinks I was like looking
cuz of my throat being
a little bit in pain on the last day I
was looking in three different
conveniences like three different uh
companies Family Mart Lawson and
7-Eleven cuz I thought it was just like
a matter of going to the right store but
nobody had the one that I wanted I
wanted a a hot lemon with honey
drink cuz I remember them always having
it when I needed it which was normally
in Winter and in summer they do have
warm drinks but not that anymore they
only have this like green tea hot and
the H hji hoi cha which is another type
of green tea but not
green yeah and like some
coffees and
maybe maybe another type of green tea
but they don't have the one that I
wanted what is this stuff
um more coffee coffee and tea to make
yourself
sticks we know what those are
Pokey oh oh yeah yeah there's some
famous Brands here but they changed the
name of
them all the package just looks super
familiar yeah yeah chunky chunky chunky
and
chunky those two down there Chun and
chunky normally I think it's cranky or
so what was
it anyway it doesn't matter let's get to
work shall
we
an thank you for your hard
work good night thank you for your hard
work let's go some of this
all right I'll leave you to the cashier
duties actually I've got some important
things to take care of I'm sorry but
you'll have to take care of things on
your own it's my first day it's my first
day you can't you can't trust
me don't worry it's a simple job I'll
give you instructions over the phone so
take it easy over the phone okay if you
can't be on the phone with me then you
could also be here I think but okay all
right wait for the manager to call all
righty well I'm in control of everything
now I shall destroy it all I shall burn
it
[Music]
woohoo I just saw him go around the
corner there how long is it going to
take him to call
me and where is the phone there's a
Wi-Fi
router and a printer and a laptop
guys I need to tell
you I have some some Japan advice for
foreigners
now recently there has been a trend that
more and more Convenience Stores um like
if you buy a bentle or something to warm
up they always used to warm it up for
you if like they ask you should I warm
it up for you and then you have to say
hi if you want it to be warmed up and
they would do it but nowadays more and
more have like a a separate uh section
where you have to warm it up yourself so
it's not a given
anymore which I had to learn depending
on the convenience store more and more
just have you do it yourself so yeah if
they don't offer it to you you can
assume there's probably somewhere around
the entrance there's a a section with
several of these uh
War warming up machines I forgot the
name yeah just keep an eye out if you go
[Music]
microwaves
yeah hey can you hear me first hold the
item scanner in your hand
ah that makes me
think that makes me
think I was going to
oopsie I was going to put something in
my
hands because in the logo they have the
item scanner and they
have um the what's it called the ENA
Bonk
stick here that's the one thing I I I do
have I don't think I have an item
scanner
okay I don't think I have an item
scanner I
can yeah that's the best I can do I mean
I can always come out with this
[Laughter]
one here maybe this one's
nice wait I think I want to put that one
on just to protect myself I'm alone
after all very confrontation exactly we
want confrontation don't
we I'm it's loading in crowbar is better
no no no
no no
no it's just not the right for the right
outfit
but it's
okay ah
ah
okay this does this look okay
looks okay
right don't [\h__\h] with me I'll bunk you
up with my baseball bat my cute golden
baseball bat okay
scan equipped with scanner okay how do I
scan though it says left click
but uhuh ah I equipped the scanner first
and then beep beep okay could somebody
come by and buy
something how do I put it
back what am I supposed to
[Music]
do no not
go oh that's a lot okay
[Music]
breakfast
shampoo some drink and some stuff that I
don't know what it is oh energy
jelly okay wait did you how did you pay
how did you do
that momy
mommy yeah for a moment I thought we
were in a mate
Cafe you do you're doing well working
the cash register adds to the store is
good rating my
stock I mean monitoring work is going
well over here as well okay now let's
deal with the Troublesome customers
equip a weapon oh really I beat him up
[Music]
really where I am anticipating it
come on come
on bring it on who left their coffee
here HH also it's like really disgusting
I see you I see you do you first have to
make trouble or can I already attack
you may I already get to
work let's see what they'll do first ah
no no smoking no [\h__\h] smoking get the
[\h__\h] out of
here I'm per I'm whacker the fact that
you chose to smoke means that you were
ready to die so I shall just kill you
right here right now you're doing well
letting Troublesome customers laer adds
to the store's bad rating customers are
not infector right mhm so beat up the
trouble so much it is my pleasure to do
so I'm done with my work feeling lazy
now let's go out for a drink oh just
kidding I actually have to go because I
got a call from HQ next use your store
scan skill you'll be able to see the
movements of all those Troublesome
customers who are hidden in seconds
uh-huh what you can't use that it's an
essential skill for convenience store
workers store scan okay first I'll
probably need some people to walk in
here wait is that somebody no that's a
plushy oh someone's
coming okay
so oh
oh wait what the [\h__\h] are you
doing well outside smoking I would say
normally would be okay but it l says no
smoking right next to
him you are terribly sorry uh it's too
late now you already [\h__\h] with me [\h__\h]
around and then find
out looks like you've mastered story
scan now you're a full-fledged
Convenience St worker you've got it from
here okay so there's free controls like
free buttons really
nice Assassin's Creed oh is that of like
something you can do in Assassin's Creed
too I never played that
[Music]
before I am a part time
worker what I don't understand
this how do I finish this game do I have
to play all of these
guess let's start with the first
one Ian translation
sucks I mean it's
fine
[Music]
yeah do 60
60 oh I don't have to do all of
them 60 Minutes is like 60 IRL minutes
let's do this one first though cuz I'm
already
[Music]
here please be good oh my God there's a
lot coming ooh I feel like that one's
here to cause trouble the way he's
walking already tells me ah what
what what what are you doing little baby
I feel at home in the corner I'm per
work this is not your home get your own
corner I'm sure your own home as a
corner hey what the [\h__\h] is that PO
supposed to mean I am per time
worker what are you guys doing does
nobody want to buy
something come on please zai I need to
make money thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you bam potato
chips lemon flavor
ah okay goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
seems like no troublemakers right now
okay more breakfast items I feel like
it's night time but maybe you're buying
it for
tomorrow get the the aiming aiming is a
little bit difficult 1,000 wait does it
does it does the two mean there's two
trouble oh my god there might be there
might indeed be troublemakers right now
wait to to to
[Music]
wait is he still there is he outside or
inside wait hey hey hey hey hey hey
heyy [\h__\h] you what the [\h__\h] who gave you
the right to start drinking in my store
you have to pay for it wait what's no
what what what
what is she allowed to sit there I'm not
sure maybe
not I am p no I think she was very much
allowed to sit
[Music]
there wait what is that guy
inside no no no no no no no wait let's
let's just let's just get through this
first cookies
alcohol and the Yi
Silba bro bro bro oh wait I thought
there was somebody here did he disappear
where is he be hey
hey I am parttime worker oh thank God
okay okay okay what this is busy what is
this doing on the ground are you buying
this oh wait was he I I would have
probably nor on the normal circumstances
missed it if I was already standing
here okay that guy is behind the
store he keeps on giving me minus points
okay I'm go I'm going to
[Music]
go you were too close to the
evildoers I am part time you can lean
against your own trash at home okay what
is what is you you want trouble don't
you I
am I didn't even I don't even know what
was like the problem but I mean the fact
that he's wearing a bucket is obviously
like the
problem I don't allow buckets on your
head no you can't just wear whatever
head wear you
want that's not okay okay what was that
H she's [\h__\h]
grilling wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
wait why is it so slow why is it so
slow okay go go go go go go go go go go
bucket guy still there bu is bucket guy
stealing my Stones I amain Walker what
is he
doing he's he's
lifting he's doing a workout I
Amer is that the same one from
before no break dancing in my
convenience store I'm parttime Walker I
am parttime
worker I am part-time worker
[Music]
this is an intense first shift why is
there more [\h__\h] on the floor I should
hit you for throwing it down put it down
more gently next
time do it is for Tik Tok honestly I'm
sure that like maybe in America or so
this is like a common
sight for people who make Tik
[Music]
toks any any evil people H wait AAR
yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait it's
so
wobbly who's okay you are doing
something bad are you trying to steal
money I'm part time wer no you're just
angry that you don't have any money hey
what the [\h__\h] oh you don't have to ask
the fridge you can just open the door
like a normal person hey don't steal
things I am P Time
Walk okay here we go here we go here we
go we got to do some business here okay
uh weird
people what's going on what's going
on this one running is maybe bad stop
running stop running running is not
allowed apparently I think I'm okay okay
okay okay okay okay that was the right
choice but apparently there's one more
one more weirdo what the [\h__\h] there's
SoDo here Pro probably should kill her I
about okay let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's
go wow am I doing well I think I'm doing
well I'm trying my
best okay uh you seem
[Laughter]
no just no what's going on this store
called the manager [\h__\h]
you oh really that was good to do why
are you taking pictures of me is this
just a joke to you is this funny to you
I'm just doing my job here please do not
like make me into a Tik Tok okay I'm P
this is not funny this is serious I'm
suffering what is this car
doing I
am what
what what the hell thanks for the Super
Chat hey hey hey hey where are you going
where are you going this is my back room
don't use not to watch
porn can you not can you not he he hey
hey hey hey hey hey I have a feeling
that your thickness only comes from all
the things you put in your booty there
what are you sneaking up to huh wait
what's going on what's going on oh break
dancing are you angry at the break dance
for me too but it's my job to punish
him it's my job
what are these sounds that
heer what the I'm power wer holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] baseball [\h__\h] baseball I am
parttime
worker what don't B for the Walker don't
B for the
old what the [\h__\h] I'm going to call my
boss you can't do this
you're destroying my convenience store
he's going to blame me for it I don't
want to be blamed I didn't do it boss
are you watching this for the
cameras Oh my God he's going to do
something weird he is going to do
something weird he's going to do
something weird what are you
doing [\h__\h] okay he was not doing
anything we but someone's doing
something weird
you what are you doing
part time worker what there there's one
more weirdo could it be him or the guy
behind him what is he
carrying let me just let me just do my
[\h__\h] job just this
once just this
once what is he doing is he going to
like now I understand
what what what why why would you do that
why would you do that what why you
bringing it to a different convenience
store or why why I'm trying to
understand but I do not
[Music]
understand wait it's just gone now it's
just [\h__\h] gone you you're you're
weird you are weird are you going behind
the
counter he was about to play baseball
with me I got him I got him right before
okay okay okay okay oh no no no okay oh
okay this is a weirdo I am he wasn't but
he was wearing a weird Mask wait there
was somebody running wait and there's
somebody right
there wow okay that's just
impressive I can afforded he says what
are you
doing what I am parttime rer I found him
1 second too
late he I am part time Walker everything
is escalating now is there somebody here
by any chance no
okay oh normal
person well I guess I mean come
on that's fine I guess
but it's it's a little bit harder this
way um penguin but what and
clavia we don't want Street musicians on
the parking lot thank you honestly the
penguin I don't want to hurt the penguin
do I have to hurt the
penguin it's too
cute okay I'll do it I'll do it if I can
get him I can't I can't
what what what is he inside or outside
ah he's
inside now I have a shortcut to go
outside from this side at least hey it's
it's all good it's all good bucket
person bucket person bucket
person I am what is that person do over
there what are you doing do you doing
yoga okay that's beautiful and good for
you but I don't agree with yoga because
yoga doesn't agree with
me what what what what what what what
what what what what what what I don't
know what that giggling was about just
now the P the penguin penguin is
probably probably fine right he just
wants to chill in the in the ice section
maybe okay let's just get this over
with something's happening and I cannot
pay attention to
it what what what what are you doing no
no
no I don't know what he was about to do
but I had a bad
[Music]
feeling
I
exactly you're so cute you're so cute
you're so cute I will allow
it I am I need a bigger range for my Bon
stick what's what's happening
who's is he drinking or smoking in there
I guess the being on the phone is rude
I'm part time Walker are you
stealing I'm perect yeah
probably okay what I hear somebody
sleeping I
think
[Music]
huh is is it this guy is it no wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what
I'm time I don't know I can't find the
sleeping person hello welcome back are
you working
here no probably not
oh how was my shift I think it was
really
good oh he was sleeping in the olden no
way again how could I not see that
no well sorry about that no it was a
tough day
that's why I actually that's why I left
because it's like this every day sorry I
knew it was going to happen sorry I
didn't tell
you uh you can just beat him up take
care of yourself beat him up beat him up
beat him up by the way I'm going on Vaca
I mean business
trip could you take care of the store
for a month for sure I'm counting on you
parttime I am a
part-time oh I am part time rer
okay that solves all our
[Applause]
[Music]
problems this is fun next next next are
you telling me that the 60 Minute one is
just this nonstop for 60 minutes that's
so in
[Music]
intense oopsie that's so intense
can I can
I
okay
[Music]
TT a wait one
second give me give me two seconds
[Music]
turns out my windows were
open and I was screaming
and who knows who heard
me all right all right so 60
Minutes that for full 60 Minutes Kiki
what geki is here in the one second
where I was gone geky showed up in the
chat no
way no way
[Music]
G no why did you guys say
gigy why are you walking so
happily and why you going to the back of
the
store why I can't like usually if they
go to the back of store that can't mean
anything good
right
yeah I am P time yeah I don't think it
ever means anything good what are you
doing let's just kill him I am parttime
walk had a
feeling are you just saying gigg but you
also say
gy sorry for the wait had more important
things to
do you're also important
but troublemakers need to be taken care
of I Am the police of the store and I am
policing okay
ah what do you think you're doing over
there honestly there's not much wrong
with that except for the alcohol I'm
worker
I have a personal bias against
alcohol I got to check
behind the counter and everything and
behind the store got to make sure to
have my eyes everywhere if only I had
some security are you are you leaving
without buying [\h__\h] no if I have
someone evil on the map then it shows me
on the top right I would
assume okay okay pretty good pretty good
pretty good makes me trigger happy no it
makes me experience got it got gave me a
good taste uh-oh we have a
troublemaker but we also have a couple
customers wait that one Troublemaker can
wait a little bit be
faster holy [\h__\h] you're sweet you got a
sweet tooth don't
[Music]
you okay we got one guy grilling and
some people there but I don't think
they're doing anything it's just you I
am part time Ro he's grilling the
chicken rice did you actually buy it I
don't think I remember you buying that
what are you doing kind of sus there
it's just too much peace right now it
should be less
peaceful are you going to steal that
yeah oh no wait wait wait I think
they're buying
it I think they're actually buying it
thank God I
missed I think it's still like pretty
calm right now and it will get less calm
later huh
oh uh that guy that guy that guy is
going to do something weird he's no is
he not he's in his [\h__\h] box of
shorts he's in his [\h__\h] box of shorts
can't be up to any
good
[Music]
okay toilet paper
very important for idle meetings number
one
ingredient what are you
doing are are
you no really I thought it would be bad
to like try to get rid of stones in your
shoe in the middle of my store
no he was just what was he doing then
wasting my
time yeah I I should I should just like
yeah if I don't see any red
Emoji there's no reason to suspect them
of any anything I
guess he's also sus though his hair is
too shiny
ah but when he doesn't do anything bad
yet yeah like I could catch them before
they start doing it
time I I knew it I knew it you're not
supposed to enter the back rooms
[Music]
fancy hair you got there very purple are
you takachi is you know your favorite
YouTuber
understandable
oh okay I guess you're you're normal
there's nothing wrong with you you're
welcome to buy your things and then come
back later and then you're going to
cause some trouble
probably
mhm so if they use those models for
normal normal
customers that then I can never know I'm
W I feel like I just destroyed that by
breaking the glass but apparently we're
[Music]
good no it's not the catcher it's not
the
catcher just um I mean some some guys
wear makeup too but I feel like you can
tell that it's
like uh that they know what they're
doing if they do it like
commonly that just looked like someone
painted his face as a prank or he's
pranking
me we good so far
[Music]
yeah you're also dying your hair good
luck with that I think your gray hair is
beautiful too
you don't need to hide it you don't need
to cover it
up
sauce
[Music]
no might just be a clown yeah maybe
maybe after his shift that would make
sense a clown who was done clowning for
the day and now he's clowning me
every day I'm
clowning every day I'm
clowning oh
what I I I don't I can't imagine you
being here for anything
good W okay maybe I'm too
discriminating it seems to
me I have judged People Too Much by
their looks
and I understand that now I
shall I shall think
over my
actions and perhaps improve myself in
the
[Music]
future sorry I don't want this store to
get a bad reputation or anything
anything I I I will be less
discriminative from now
on there's just some weirdos here like
him but there's nothing wrong with you
sir of course
not oh oh oh
oh what H what what
[Music]
who's who eh wait wait wait wait wait
who who is doing what
y y y ah ah n n n n n wait wait there
must be something
[Music]
outside oh was there someone stealing is
he still stealing are you
stealing oh he's he's stealing I am oh
thank God took me a while to see
that sorry sir thank you so much for
reconsidering your loyalty to the store
and coming back even though I hit you
really hard with my crowbar thank
[Music]
you wait we have we have somebody two
people two
people okay one is here cuddling with
the plushies very cute I would want to
do that too sometimes understandable are
you stealing you
eating you're eating the food right away
in front of my eyes no no no no no no no
no no no no no con man shirt is cute
yeah okay
[Music]
are you testing whever or not oh Oh I
thought it was a mirror I am parttime
rocker wait I saw the finger after I hit
you I feel largely insulted there's
still one Troublemaker but I I I didn't
see anything right
away about there
them out the
we a the grill the
grill he's grilling I want to buy a
grill but I'm not sure how much I want
to invest into a grill do I want to to
buy like the the grillest of the
grills or is just like a a simple Grill
good enough for me I'm not
sure I do want to buy one
though thank you
for the member
message what is that guys what do you
think he's doing can you explain it to
me because I'm not sure wait there's
something wrong there's something
wrong
you I am time Walker
and what
[Music]
look what the
[\h__\h] how did you break that with your
head
Mama M oh sorry I'm looking at the
chat oh my God okay it's getting
stressful now it's getting stressful
now wait was that what was that just
now I'm per a the [\h__\h]
camera wait you you you still have
something what is it in front
of it's all over here ma'am ma'am I
didn't see that because it was on your
side ah
[Music]
n where's that who's that where's
where's the one
Troublemaker it's okay we can wait a
little
bit we have a lot of
points what
what what is it him it's him he's
smoking
no he's not smoking oh wait that that
censorship fell down down
there I
aming what is this why are you doing
that what did I do to you sorry for the
wait I'm I'm the only one here today I
have a solo
shift yeah please pity me I deserve to
be pied I pity
[Music]
myself have fun bye
a nice fashion very nice fashion you got
there
kak
puka I was just holding up my
finger that doesn't fly here that does
not fly I don't allow yoga here so I
also don't allow lifting of fingers the
only lifting of fingers that will be
done is me lifting my own fingers
because I'm working so I am lifting all
my fingures all my
[Music]
fingers no Troublemaker right now it's a
little bit of a
calm SE I should hit you for that quick
I am P wer wait I almost I felt like the
game wanted me to do that cuz that was
rude I I'm I'm okay with that I don't
care I'm okay with that
[Music]
I
personally will take the those
points because oh my God wait what's
happening I thought you were on the
outside
y I wouldn't mind someone breaking the
wall now so that I have a
shortcut
I wait wait wait wait no no no no no no
no no no part time Walker okay okay okay
there what who who whoa who who whoa who
what do you want I am the manager I am
alone therefore I am the manager of the
day I'm managing the situation after all
so I am the manager wouldn't you agree
guys I am literally the only one
managing the
situation so in that way I am the
manager smart smart
[Music]
okay
okay good [\h__\h] morning I am part time
get out of here you can work out
elsewhere go to a have you ever heard
to have have you ever heard of a fitness
center no you don't want to buy the
membership well that's too bad this
convenience store also asks for
memberships
oh what what are you doing you're
showing me a heart thank you thank you I
I deserve some love I need that love I
need
it yes if you have a membership at kfp
then you can work out in the store then
I don't
mind but that's the only way what are
you
doing
what cannot scan him does not work like
that
okay uh wait there's somebody is it is
it him it's him it's him it's him it's
him I'm
[Music]
wer
okay Mama
Mia is it actually uh IRL 60
Minutes it feels like it's IRL timer
I think I might go insane before this
time
ends I feel bad I I it's like I killed
the grandma that might have killed her
why are you running was that bad last
time was that a bad
thing cut I am no was a bad thing okay
okay okay okay running is
indeed looked down upon in some
places I can't relate but okay
be careful guys don't break don't break
any weird rules that you don't know
exist o are you inside or outside
what he looks almost like he's inside ah
yes I am part time Walker yeah she was
just sleeping outside the store but she
should go
home I Walker
wait there's one more right now who who
who who
who who who who who what's wrong what's
wrong what's wrong what's
wrong what what what what what wait wait
wait wait I don't know I don't know I
don't
know guys what's wrong what's wrong
what's wrong ah
ah I'm per I'm Walker okay this is the
solution if you don't have a grill I
could just I could just do a campfire in
my garden why not why not thank you for
inspiring
me I am parttime wer I may be famous but
you still need to ask for permission if
you want
pictures and when you ask I will say no
so go [\h__\h]
yourself he's he's
backflipping you may wonder what's wrong
with backflipping I'm part worker
well well it's because I can't do it and
you're making me feel like an idiot stop
flexing you're so slow you're so
slow what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] stop
chopping my trees this is not Minecraft
this is not Minecraft wait why does he
have like a there was like a container
down there was he chopping the tree to
hey the [\h__\h] Grandpa
I was just going to give you time to do
your
purchases and this is how you betray
me oh my
God people are so ungrateful are you
stealing no
okay so [\h__\h]
ungrateful what have I ever done to you
be nice to convenience store workers
have
some oh we're both of them bad because
normally I think I should have
been punished for hurting someone normal
that was collateral damage but maybe she
was also about to do something
bad M I am Pat time
Walker Double
Trouble Ooh Baby a double
[Music]
I had no
idea but I must I must have it in my
sixth sense it must be my my women's
senses
tingling women
[Music]
yay ah honestly this is so
sick oh W you're running against the
wall you're not even doing like a real
backflip
I wonder if that's easier I I would I
would think that it's easier when you
run against a wall like that but it's
also pretty
impressive that is honestly pretty
impressive what are you
[Music]
doing oh I I didn't get punished for him
though that's nice I
guess how how come I don't get punished
for that now I feel bad that there was
nothing wrong with that guy for sure
[Applause]
that's mean when they're standing so
close
[Music]
together
sorry
[Music]
sorry he's so
determined bam H I knew it I knew it I
knew it I knew it I saw the
determination determination
determination oh is that a
word stop messing around part time
rocker I'll call your mommy and I'll
tell her the evil things that you're
doing hey you're going to activate my
smoke
detector I'm going to get scolded by my
boss oh the penguin the penguin was fine
right I am parttime Walker I don't
remember if something happened with the
penguin he took a Bento but I I wasn't
able to hit him
anyway no matter how many times I
tried I am parttime
worker give me give me give me give me
give me give
me oh
oh ah what how did I not see you
I am part Walker
woohoo
oh I
Amer Piano Guys good wait wait wait wait
what what what what what what what I
didn't even notice I was getting minus
points for that did I get minus
points Piano Guys good oh wait maybe
salak I mean yeah okay wait we were not
going to judge by the model because
sometimes
the weird models they also sometimes buy
something like a normal person I am
parttime worker
[Music]
right I am part yeah he put up a [\h__\h]
Flag I saw it I was like was that there
before apparently it was not there
before thank you for putting up the
[\h__\h]
Flag penguin penguin you have to pay
penguin chunk
oh penguin
John okay we'll just let it go we'll
just let it go we'll close our eyes it
never happened I didn't see
it I didn't see it it didn't
happen the I'm not sure what to
do should
I should I kill her what else is going
on here you doing something weird
stay away stay away don't get
hurt this is like once she enters the
store it's over yeah okay no it's not
over but okay she walked out to the
store and then she was going to do a
spooky
thing be I'm I'm not good with horror
please stay away I want this ship to be
a nice bright shift with only laughter
and
love no horror please than you
back into the TV you go what is that
what is
that n
you I
am [\h__\h] inflatable guy you you you are
there's no way you're going to do
something normal I
am okay we got him early we got him
early this time before he took my
whole okay how was I supposed to stop
that beforehand he was on the
roof
right I don't think you can stop that
your your your story is just like bounc
to look like that at some
[Music]
point can't be helped it is what it is
okay uh there is a troubl maker
oh
ah yes I am so disturbed by what you're
doing stop time
Walker the flexing man your flexibility
is disturbing me what are you doing no
no no no no I am Walker no no no no no
no no no no no no
no hey that guy over there wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wa
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait tissues tissues
could you please
stop y
[Music]
stop you you really must Wonder like if
you work at a store like this where you
have a like really
repetitive Jingles or like the same
music over and over
again like this is already making me
feel like I'm going
insane mommy mmy
mmy what
[Music]
explosion oh they're inside [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] fu [\h__\h] two people in the back room
I
think please please hold a moment oh
no I am part time and one more moment
please there's e where did he go y
okay first
this I snap in less than an
hour wa this ah he's inside I didn't
realize you were inside here that's why
this is empty I am part time work that's
why this was empty to begin with so that
they could people could put people in
there cuz somebody just took a photo of
me that is very rude you didn't get my
chocolate side
I am get my [\h__\h] chocolate sign in
German we say chocolate
sign wait where's the photo
person there
stalker I am part time worker what's
wrong what's
wrong on
it
oh okay okay okay okay is that guy going
to do something
weird
no
wow okay all right normal customer yeah
nothing wrong with
you nothing wrong with you at all no
judgment only Justice
[Music]
thank God there's nothing weird going on
right
now we're halfway
through halfway oh we're halfway there
oh part time
worker beep beep beep oh Inside
Outside
Inside I am parttime Walker
wow
wow living on a
PR if I was here working all alone I I
should be turning on my own music I
should play my own little
radio and then I should just like you
guys remember my 3D
debut early last year my transitions the
way I was dancing with the BR broom in
the back room broom back room wow so
going that's what I would be doing if I
was working alone I just be dancing to
my
music in the back rooms hey
he I am P Walker are you in there no
you're
outside can you wait a minute
hello hello
Su I know what you're up to you want to
watch porn don't you it's my thumbnail
not good enough for
you I'm per
whacker is my thumbnail not satisfying
enough I'm
work what's that car doing the car was
weird right yeah the car
explodes I'm I got early do you get
extra points for earliness cuz I don't
know
the what the what the okay I was not
able to catch that one that was
impossible
impossible I am per time
worker are you going to do
something are you going home oh where
she's fine she's
fine thought you were about to set up to
do something and he's zooming he booked
it but you had to you have to catch him
right
normally but how are you going to catch
him you got to like know that he's
coming just like I know that you are
doing something weird but I don't even
have I'm per
zero zero I am indeed it did not it did
not say that I had a troublemaker on the
lot it did not
say but that's interesting I didn't get
minus it's just a JoJo
pose
a he was like neutral it's like oh if
you're if you're bothered by
[Music]
him bro
oh should have gotten them
early
no
no what are you doing are you trying to
enter through there that's not a normal
entrance
bro this is not an entrance don't
misunderstand are you going to buy
something
[Music]
oh he's going to destroy one of my back
walls I
[Music]
am all right next please I know what
this guy's up to
too I know you too well now you wearing
a mask will not throw me
off you're leaving through there too all
right all right
then you do you do you do
you meta
gaming my
experience is just assisting me in life
now he's he's he's not not good he's not
he's up to no good I'm time
[Music]
Walker if you want to throw some balls
go to the Dodgers game Take Me Out to
the Ball Game take me down to the
Crouch go I am part
time take me down to the ball
game the
[Music]
crowd
all
oh why is he walking so fast why is he
walking so
fast what he's normal he's normal no way
ah okay I have a lot of customers
now I'm
roer if you want something from the Oden
tell me and I'll get it for you this is
not a self-service place
okay oh God oh God
[Music]
please wait a moment I
am I'm so good at this I'm so good at
this I have a good eye
now
Mama what's that what's what's
what's how am I supposed to see this how
am I supposed to take that off of here I
feel like something's going to happen
something's something's going to happen
[Music]
happen is he smoking outside I don't
know nothing weird right now apparently
but sometimes it's too late sometimes
they just [\h__\h] break your walls and
it's too late
wait are you mad because the the line is
too long I'm sorry I'm working alone my
shift is alone right now my manager just
[\h__\h] went on vacation and no I'm not
alone
here what can I do what can I say
[Music]
nothing
okay there's someone snowing yeah but I
killed him um like it's a bug I think
because he's
already he's already done
wait I think it stopped
now yeah no Troublemaker on the launch
and it fell down again pick it up why
you making me walk around the counter oh
no okay he's still
snoring it's a bug though I'm pretty
sure it's a
bug oh thank you thank you thank you I
appreciate it he's supporting me he's
like oh a little bit more come on wa wa
a little bit more you can do it maybe 20
more minutes or something like that and
then you're done I believe in you thank
you I believe in me too holy [\h__\h] the
line is never
ending I wish I could like use this
thing
faster it's really
[Music]
slow nothing happening except people
buying normal [\h__\h] that almost feels
like a
bug doesn't it not
[Music]
anymore it's too calm just busy just
stressed out right
[Music]
now holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
faster faster
[Music]
faster that's rude That is rude but I'll
give you the benefit of the doubt it was
slippery or it's just a game bug you
didn't want to throw it like that right
right
yeah are they are they are is it a bug
that that nothing is or is it the storm
like the storm itself is the thing right
now like that's the
thing isn't a thing maybe because this
person bugged out this is bugging out
too do you know what I
mean cuz the game thinks I still have
this one oh no wait there's a new
Troublemaker H okay then then it's
probably fine I'm
P that was just a rash of people of
normal people I should not be complet
compling about the things that are
actually normal my sense of what's
normal and what's weird is just thrown
off
[Music]
now oh
sure
[Music]
okay m
m I'm constantly like looking out for
people who are about to break my walls
or
[Music]
something but it's really just what he's
he's not going to the store that's weird
he probably wants to lay down behind my
store
probably I'll I'll give him a
moment anybody who just doesn't walk
into to my store I think it's out oh
wait wait wait wait now we have
something oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh you now the that guy the fact that
he's not going inside is also weird I
about okay okay like what what were you
going to steal and do what were you
going to do they were walking so close
to the side that I can't really tell
what they were about to
do what was their plan did they have a
plan
but I just got free trouble makers
before they could even make
trouble
[Music]
oh now the rush is kind of calming down
but they're sending these people again
stop it part time roer I will never let
it happen Dam it it
you you son
[Music]
oh boy Trel yeah they're traveling in
packs wait there's there's another one
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay I I am parttime worker
bnk BK B BK
BK what what ah I'm wer I found you
quickly at least what are you doing time
Walker this is not some kind of bar
where you can stand a up here and do a
sexy dance no no I don't appreciate
that I do not appreciate that thank
you I am part time
worker I am parttime work don't [\h__\h]
with
me get out of
here oh
oh Uno I am part
Walker I am part
Walker press I am part
Walker Oh baby a
triple you missed the dancer you never
had a dancer
before when you played the game and you
missed it in your playthrough or are you
saying you just looked away for a moment
why would you look
away why would you look
away oh what does it say what are you
doing you reading newspaper
time that's a weird position to be
reading newspaper
[Music]
in
oh ah ah two of them I am parttime
Walker turn around I'm parttime
worker I've got everything under control
guys another one another one what you is
you yes eat eating the
chocolate just can't wait to buy it yeah
just buy it and then you can eat it and
then I'm not going to Bonk you and then
we're not going to have any issues hey
I'm per I'm e you crouch too close to my
face too close to my face
nowo wait okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait you but also I think someone
outside oh are you wait how long have I
am how long have you been there that's
not the one that's snoring all this time
I'm pretty sure are you stealing a
bikeit he was planting broccoli what
well he was
broccoli but he was also doing something
weird with the
bike he said something about broccoli
and I think I saw broccoli it was
like monochrome in that moment but what
is going on are you doing fireworks oh I
had time
oh this is not allow
I'm wow oh at least we still got to see
[Music]
that when Japanese bro is saying that's
something that happened in reality I I
think he means the the
broccoli wait that person is outside
I'll go there in a moment ah sorry I
don't want to scan your
crotch ah looking at
chat that be really exact
no no I am Cloud Time Walk why do why
[Music]
whoa what does that say I'm rooing for
you I'm I love
you T it says Tanto live oh that's
speaking to me
personally because I am Dent are you
guarding in here I eating the
soil no no no what what else is
happening oh my God help I'm Walker
help help wait who's
you I am Walker oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God I okay okay
okay clear clear clear clear
[Music]
clear
a oh yeah yeah okay it didn't say tento
it's said tan but that's still speaking
to
me they meant just the worker thems not
the Tanto Tanto is like the
boss
hey that's by the way also the potato
chips flavor I would buy in Japan
usushi lightly salted I've bought that
same package of potato chips a few times
y me boy
got okay slightly calm season again I
see I see I see I see how it
is uh-oh uh-oh
money I think it's outside
yeah I am part time work the snoring is
a bug there somebody slept here but I
already killed them ages ago
[Music]
don't worry if you hear double snoring
that's when you got to be really
[Music]
concerned all
it people walking around the back of my
store what are they
[Music]
doing ah he's dancing he's
dancing he's about to break out in break
dance
I saw you I saw
you I'm parttime
worker I saw
you you cannot escape the eye of the
Phoenix it's the eye of the Phoenix it's
the F of the fight
[Music]
okay how much
longer maybe like 5 to 10 minutes
judging by the
meter my throat hurts from
screaming need to drink water but is
there there's literally no time to drink
water unless I pause the
game
n
where
oh people really I want to be here right
now either either eating the soil or
doing something else weird huh are you
stealing
[Music]
no 8 minutes 5 minutes you
think okay I can do it I can do it cheer
me on cheer me on chat come
the
fight I've missed you
oh I'm going dangerous dangerous go
faster faster faster faster faster I
don't want to hit
you I Walker okay then usually even
though he's not doing anything yet
usually it's good to hit those two and
you're going to do something weird I'm
I if you don't buy anything then don't
even bother getting close to my
convenience store
what are you doing you screwed up you
screwed up by by walking over here and
going through the wrong
entrance oh n why who did I
miss what did I do wrong are you in
there no you're
behind I was so Vigilant is that the
word oh you're doing more
graffiti graffiti is really rare oh it
says
it's again cheering me on graffiti is
really rare in Japan I was going to say
which I honestly appreciate like there's
some cool graffiti out there in the
world but the problem is just they they
spray onto
anything like in Europe there's so many
beautiful historical
buildings and they don't even spray from
that sadly that's the
problem like so many buildings would
just look so much better and structures
if there was no [\h__\h] graffiti on it
what's going on what's
Happening who's doing what what what
what what where where where not even
outside [\h__\h] maybe in the back
rooms maybe in the back
oh I'm part time roer oh no oh do I am
part time
Walker
ah ah are you in the toilet oh I am
on the trains yeah lots of on the trains
it doesn't even bother me although it
depends
like doesn't bother me as much as on the
[Music]
buildings I saw some super cool graffiti
before in some places like in in Brazil
I think I saw some cool graffiti
before but yeah
usually often they put it on the most
beautiful buildings and then it just
looks like [\h__\h] often like was it really
worth it messing up the beauty of this
building was it worth it tell
me I don't think
so like it doesn't even
look like anything
sometimes a lot of the times just some
random scribble Scrabble
looking ugly as
[Music]
hell huh are you
stealing I am parttime
[Music]
Walker
oh oh wait wait wait wait wait I see you
I see you I see you
trust me you don't want to work here I'm
I'm doing you a favor by killing you oh
my God oh my God oh my God okay it's
rush hour it's [\h__\h] rush hour time
walk I'm part time walk robot robot
robot robot
robot oh my God what's happening what's
what's the wow is he looking at where is
he where's that wow guy is you wait no
wait who's
H
here everywhere [\h__\h]
everywhere wa I don't have time for you
right now bro fast boy fast boy cut him
off
I'm what am I hearing a
train on fire
alme I'm
wer okay nothing here
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm sorry sorry sorry is there someone
in here no point Time Walk wa is good
enough focus on the
stream not on the porn my eyes are up
here okay
a oh there's so much going on I am
parttime worker last SP
I'm tick tock tick tock
tick I am part time
worker no no no no no I am parttime
worker no no no no no
no I am don't chop up the
trees tick tock tick tock I wish we
could have gotten to 200,000
M I am P time so close do I get bonus
points for
[Music]
something oh that was a that was a close
hit wait wait wait can I get him get can
I get
him ah
[\h__\h] it's okay he didn't do anything he
was actually just passing by sometimes
those guys really just passed by huh but
you get like extra points I guess so
wait I have nothing to hit
I have nothing to
hit
oh
I'm
H give me those points give me those
points make sure to give me those
[\h__\h] points I'll be watching The
Vault to see if I got those in the
end there was someone in the Shelf [\h__\h]
I
see oh I tried my best though holy
[\h__\h] Mama
Mia I sure that you have to deal with
Troublesome customers but if you don't
like it that's fine you can just beat
them up beat them up beat them up yeah
you said the same thing before you just
keep on going on
vacation what the
hell just you just come here to laugh at
me and then
leave I am proud time wer
time
work kapoo
K
I am definitely quitting this part-time
job and going back to Whole
[Music]
Life y that's so fun
though that is so
fun but one hour of this with no break
I think I think I don't need any more
than that watch the credits list oh no
what what does it say is there something
important
there wait what why did I not get like
this here I finished 60 Minutes do I
need to finish 30 minutes as well what
what do you get here what do you get
[Music]
I'm sure there's like two hours and
maybe endless endless
mode
here the credits show all the different
guys Ah Ah that's okay I think I saw
plenty of
[Music]
them it it unlocks if you don't skip no
way
don't tell me no you can't do that to me
like just because I skip by the the
credits
what
[Music]
no apparently apparently my score was
pretty damn good
out of like compared to others Cho
Sensei had a bit more
though
oh I got a good
score well I'm not going to do another
hour just to see the [\h__\h]
credits I mean whatever I'm going to
unlock is probably just like endless
mode another 15 uh just to check the
credits
[Music]
M that's surely not going to unlock it
is
it okay I'll test it I'll
see I I'll I'll
check I didn't skip the right I didn't
know any other way to skip it
though yeah
[Music]
okay I will not skip this time I didn't
see any other way to skip I had to go to
the main menu
somehow yo it surely registered my high
score in the game right not not that it
matters cuz I'm probably never going to
play this game ever again even though it
was an absolute Delight an absolute
Delight in
it oh
[Music]
I am parttime Walker sorry for being
loud he didn't even do
anything he didn't do anything but I was
right and he had a sense a feeling of
guilt he knew in his mind he was up to
no good and that guy over there m wait
what are you doing I am okay okay I
thought he was doing something
sorry I didn't have I didn't even have a
failure like that in my 1 hour
run that's actually impressive I don't
think I had anything weird like
that n n n I'm per Walker one person
what what is the other one
you I am per Walker Callie also skipped
it like that ah
Takami aam Mori in
it two P of a pod they
say
right I'm pretty sure that's what they
say I am I'm Walker what no don't lie to
me that was not no no she was already
like getting in position to start being
a Karen
he's also
weird what is he
doing I want to hit him but I already
[\h__\h] up several
times now now they're just like T posing
actually a posing I'm getting minus
points for
that what I thought that was the
Troublemaker what are they
doing what are they doing
it's not
normal I'm telling
you I've hit people for doing way less
annoying things
somehow there's another one though wait
I can't
scan I can't scan now oh oh over there
ah
huh what do you mean go for a meme one
I'm per what what what would that mean
what would that
[Music]
entail
ah ah I am they just standing there
menacingly just bonky
anyone I don't know if I would call that
a meme
run just going to get minus points
[Music]
endlessly this whole game is a meme
run okay what's what's
[Music]
happening there's a person smoking here
I think no ah ah he's cheering for me in
his own way VIA graffiti
okay no more of that please I will not
accept
this wer Your Graffiti is nice
but I am not going to be the one
painting over that tomorrow thank
you
n oh there is that is that a robot over
there's a robot coming okay we got to we
got to Bonk him
before gets too close I actually don't
know what he does when you let him go
too
close maybe he will blow up in the
store what does the robot
do does anybody
know I am parttime
Walker okay
[Music]
no nobody
knows what are you
doing
I'm was it worth it losing your ability
to get children one day was this worth
it for
[Music]
you now you'll have to adopt which is
nice too adopt some
Bud make a child happy out
there I'm
adopted says
[Music]
coob I
man that is so rude and like so out of
nowhere like I should really Bonk you
for that
[Music]
H yeah I'm parttime
worker outside no
really there's two more
people
huh okay it's inside it's inside sorry
sorry sorry sorry both of you I'm part
time rocker you came here together
didn't you I'm parttime worker
ah
no not my roof now it's going to rain
inside please don't do
that don't do this to
[Music]
me somebody please clean the rub
Rubble the
stones wait apparently somebody's doing
something y my just run is worse than my
last run what what what what
what I don't know I don't know okay the
Pebbles are gone at
least go Dam it
no it's him he's eating all the apples I
am parttime
worker one apple b don't don't eat five
apples please oh I I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry
but at least it clears my line a little
bit apparently no damage has been
done to my
score hey hey what do you think you're
doing I'm per Walker what do you think
you're doing I work here now and I
prefer to work alone
honestly I like to play the music that I
like I like to Bunk the people that I
hate
I'm wer someone there
[Music]
no oh
[\h__\h] uh-oh are you
[Music]
uh-oh ah sorry
ah I only saw the person behind you some
oh the car the car the car the
car okay okay
what
n hey are you mad at me I'm sorry are
you telling me to hurry the [\h__\h] up
quick March okay okay okay but you
didn't really have to throw it down like
that
what oh oh the fast Bo the
fast I am I got him I got him but it's
not a fast boy but he's different speed
I'm wack I'm
wack
youer I just hit his girlfriend yeah I'm
I do feel actually really bad about
that um what are you here for oh
baseball just because I'm carrying a bad
does not mean that I am up for a ball
game oh S I like the CH po okay I am
part time I know he's
harmless I am part time but I prefer not
to be involved with him okay you're
going to do something weird aren't you
I'm and the piano Guy let's see what he
will do this
time
maybe maybe he's okay
[Music]
cuz last time apparently I hurt him and
he didn't deserve
it Takami desk from tyent me just
arrived O Let's Go the cute one with the
cute
illustrations let's go what are you
doing what are you doing what are you
doing oh okay but now he gets to be
bonked oh or not wait
penguin also here
I'm okay he's making music but we're
forgiving this what are these double
[Music]
standards
N I don't
[Music]
understand it's too calm right now I
must hit this person I am part
okay
okay no minus this was a great Zone and
I killed her in the dark so nobody saw
it nobody can judge what I just
did this kind of beautiful yeah I got to
stay
[Music]
positive maybe he got permission from
the
store could be but normally there's no
piano players in front of convenience
stores what kind of agreement do they
have oh piano gu is
leaving byebye thank you for the
beautiful music
making I appreciate it that was a nice
change of
pace and we're almost done oh
oh Tik Tock Tik
tock tick
[Music]
tock I
Amer are we clear are we in the clear
you want to do something don't you
I am guy
too
I I couldn't save the
microwave
no huh oh oh the Wild guy the Wild
guy get him get him get him get him get
him get
him Walker oopsie you tripped I feel so
bad how come you tripped I'm the floor
be too slippery sorry I cleaned
the the floor out there the parking lot
this
morning and I wax I waxed it yeah so
what oh no I was about to hit his
crotch we got exactly what was it 40,000
points though was a nice
number hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi thank you
this time I will watch the credits no
skiper skip
okay okay I power time
recer I'm definitely quitting this
job happy endo
happy end development kukuro asset store
Unreal Engine Marketplace D 3D
interactive
[Music]
license
oh
a ordinary you call that ordinary and
the catic post okay that's good yoga is
good oh I killed a yoga person before
stra I killed that one too
before oh oh oh oh at least the pengu
and you weren't able
to take down anyway I'll never allow
blance reading in bed campfire idiot
he's just an idiot not just a
fool female ghost kick save oh we have a
save oh that guy's just flexing his
muscles oh my God it's so fast
I one from the other store yeah he's
wearing the the uniform from a lawon and
we have a family Mart I think makes
sense people who were made fun of on the
internet oh yeah they made fun of so
they started to lift uh I see I see I
see I respect the
hustle superhero life shopkeeper a live
live running along a wall cigarette in
the restroom Uncle wall breaker [\h__\h] him
man [\h__\h] him the car I was able to stop
several times
though it only got me like one
time noisy person under the
we oh I think that may have happened
once I wasn't like aware of what was
happening
though sorry music is really loud right
now
[Music]
person who lost the key a Rob that says
the right oh he he
[Music]
talks
uhhuh
earthy he's just
earthy and yeah [\h__\h] my
boss he's
bad so you
yeah the end
Yahoo he I got
everyone eh does that did that mean I
got everyone in this one run or overall
I'm not sure what that means what you
[Music]
mean okay I cleared the game then Ah
that's okay there is
no uh endless
run oh they missed out oh and this
changed it's gone wait is my score from
my 60-minute run in there yeah
okay
n look at that number a we were so close
to 200,000
[Music]
it's a pretty nice number
though a relatively nice number wouldn't
you
[Music]
say picture book and score yeah that's
what we
[Music]
got all these crazy people honestly I'm
not even so surprised because these kind
of people this is what you see in Yakuza
very very common
people in the Yakuza game
series was a good run I think so too the
long one was a good
[Music]
run I think I did a good job at
protecting the convenience store and
then blowing it up after my very first
shift I killed it so this speak yeah oh
yeah those are basically
sujon actually so true just curoo things
mhm that's just a normal day in kamuro
this is basically kamuro like little
mini game like a a side game they could
just take this game and implement it as
a little mini game with vin Yakuza
and then all the weirdos will be
[Music]
sujon wow
wonderful that was
fun this is the kind of like shitty C G
that I enjoy thank you so much thank you
thank you thank you I'm going to read
super chats for like half an hour no
more
okay are you ready for 30 minute
hardcore Super Chat reading yeah let's
go okay this is kind of messed up so
[Music]
hi I mean Co off is kind of nice in it
in
it I think it's
nice but that's not where I'm meant to
be
H oh
[\h__\h]
huh why is this like
this
huh why does my usual button not
work my usual
button
wait ah
okay we're just zoomed in isn't this
weird we're just going to be zoomed in
very zoomed in yeah zoomed in like this
is rare for me anyway isn't
it why
not something's off
it feels like I'm confronting you well I
am still carrying the
bat I am having a confrontational moment
anyway what was the number where we
stopped last time for the super chats
what was
it let me play some meu
[Music]
are any of these
good oh this is perfect
or
oh I mean this is normally to upbeat but
for a 30 minute Super Chat rating this
is not too bad 221 a
211 okay well this is nice
[Music]
okay that was from from the one super
super the the the
the which one 2 from the birthday the
to to much
[Music]
right mm
two
21 from the
to
really oh yeah I stopped that Slavic
fellow did I cute are you calling me
[Music]
cute stop
hey hey don't claim
me I claim
[Music]
you okay let me put
the speed Super Chat
[Music]
reading thumbnail
thumbnail
[Music]
do what are you riding there guys my
boss that is true cutie know you
trome Super Chat reader I have a super
CH stop you guys are cute I like this
this is my kind of
humor you like my hair
you can you can get the same kind of
hair just put it up in the
ponytail free the wahas yes I'm waa
cute orange woman you guys want to know
why why I wrote orange uh channel for
myself okay you probably don't even know
what I'm talking about partially um at
Japan
Expo um I was in control of OBS and I uh
I didn't make the QR codes but I got the
QR codes from the staff and I put them
up on the screen and then I I wanted to
uh name them according to the
member and I think in the end there were
not many people who didn't know us but
just in case that there would be some
like just walking by I wanted to make it
very clear and easy to understand just
assuming that some people wouldn't know
our names right so I wanted to do
something visual visually understandable
so for me I just wrote orange woman
because I'm just orange you know if I
Rite Phoenix or so I am Phoenix but
they're not going to tell by my physical
features that I'm a phoenix I think and
then I was thinking you know blue blue
girl or whatever or so but I I I I I
didn't I didn't know if I like would if
they would feel if the girls would
feel like
like just put how to
say putting it down to just like the the
color maybe they wouldn't like it so I
only did it for myself I am the orange
Channel
woman yeah so I just called them
detective even though that's that wasn't
like very clear either and shark that
wasn't very clear either but gooda at
least like I feel like I feel like you
should know who she is so even if you
don't watch YouTubers you should know
who she
is I don't
know I don't
[Music]
know so I am orange woman very orange
that's just like I feel like you can't
tell that you know I am the things that
I
am you can't tell by just looking at me
that I'm kiata and you can't tell them
I'm a I'm a phoenix and and all those
things so just to make it simple
orange
[Music]
orange yeah I got to put a dare okay
here we go maybe we can finish it if I'm
fast maybe we can finish the super chats
May nah maybe not
[Music]
y y yum yum orange orange yay orange
orange orange orange orange orange
orange that's me that's
me no it's me
yeah thank you you're orange I am orange
we're
orange could make some juice with us
together
okay H Slavic fellow thank you for the
red super chat happy infinity plus 4
birthday waha thank you thank you for
another wonderful year you're amazing My
OC thank you
D yeah already I am four years old wow
so good I wish I wish I was only four
years
old I am unfortunately more than
that my throat
hurts something something
[Music]
there
although 4 years old can't really do
much when you're just four years old
that's also not good thank you slaving
fellow for the red super jat and for
celebrating and counting down to my
birthday with me thank you for
supporting me
me mfin eight thanks for Pinky happy
birthday Tel next two months will be
rough but I'm sure it'll all be worth it
in the end stay safe in the summer
heat looking forward to the birthday
life whenever it happens by the way
Final Fantasy 14 actually added alpacas
in its newest expansion alpacas to ride
or just random
animals but that's interesting not that
that's going to get me to play it but I
thank you guys you can stop pointing at
me
now to ride andt pets
a a how fluffy are they let me look it
up Final
Fantasy
[Music]
ala very
cute oh
very
[Music]
fluffy very sufficiently
fluffy oh do get do do laa Fels get
smaller alpacas because they they seem
to be sized down when a Lala fell is
riding on it from what I can tell from
these
screenshots that's cute not stinky
exactly
[Music]
alpaka lover yes I love
alpacas no brain is not empty brain is
like stressed out brain is like there's
a million things that I need to do in my
head pretty yabby actually I just
realized I have to
record some songs before I go to sleep
because tomorrow I won't be able to and
for the following days I won't be able
to
[Music]
that's not
good that realization just hit me hard
it's okay stressed out yes hardworking
yes thank you thank you oh you guys are
so
sweet a are you guys maybe we should do
closeup more of
[Music]
not a Chihuahua I'm
kiaha needs a good break after this
crazy summer H yeah but I don't think
I'll be getting
one it's okay this this weekend I'm kind
of getting like a small break like some
sort of
break the the remaining days of the week
it's it's a small a couple days break no
streaming no
working so just smaller breaks here and
there
yeah what the f is when I take a little
break things are piling up and the
mountain is looking
and I'm not a good mountain
[Music]
climber GD
Dusty thanks to the pinky happy birthday
K I'm glad that you're in whole life and
that we can all enjoy the time together
with streams projects songs concerts Etc
hope we can all continue to enjoy the
good times for many years to come me too
I hope so too thank you KY I feel like I
haven't heard from you in a while so
it's nice to see your name pop up again
my Australian mate another Australian
mate thank you so much for still being
here for still partying with me every
freaking
[Music]
day motion D soon the quo artist thank
you for the pinky Happ happy birthday
boss what do you call an attractive
Phoenix from Austria and Ada
arasan that's pretty
[Music]
bad that's not that's not a good
one I try better next
time thank you though for the birthday
wishes thank you soon I didn't butcher
the delivery the material was not good
to begin with I'm sorry quo
artist it is what it is I appreciate it
doll I see you're flirting with me
that's the point in the
[Music]
end D doy Mingo Dan peekaboo dun space
wo dun Dar Bobcat Dan Spartan NS 95 tun
and Yin com for the
red Super Chat happy birthday
[Music]
w
s
h
[Music]
h p
oh
[\h__\h]
okay thank you thank you thank you thank
you from Korea all the way to Austria I
am receiving your love and I'm sending
you back a
PO another Korean bro with another red
super chat right after that and his name
is or their name is let's
see
uh
one one one W maybe I
think okay happy birthday potential
kiala has always been my strength as I
was wandering around after losing my
dream oh thank you for sparking my dream
again once again happy birthday my Kami
oi best Idol
[Music]
kiaha M po
poo thank you that what a sweet message
I did I did spark some things here and
there thank you I appreciate it oh yeah
I might be able to finish these actually
yeah it's looking good in these 15
remaining minutes I think I can do
[Music]
it one more month before the sweet
Embrace of the fryer oh I almost jealous
of you
guys feels seems cozy sounds
cozy and Tassimo thank you for the red
super chat cuz I was a little late for
the stream I have a little song for you
hul
[Music]
and wait how does this melody go in this
version is it still the
same must be different at that point I'm
not sure how the melody changes here cuz
the lyrics are um different in this
version I know this version but this is
the first time in many years that I've
seen it thank you for reminding
me let me translate this beautiful
meaning of this beautiful birthday song
okay she shall she shall live happily
and be loved by
many
uh eat good
food and
find only luck in
life happy
birthday that is exactly what that
birthday song means
[Music]
once again happy birthday laa I thank
you from the bottom of my heart for this
last year at kfp I love you thank
you thank you so much it was a pleasure
thank you for being part of
kfp some more German speaking people to
share our passion for this beautiful
language right right than sh m m m a
booy
booy don't make me feel weird about
saying that
chat you want a booy too right from
[Music]
me don't make it
weird B you s
SII it it just means like a a kissy a
little
kiss in
German a choo Cho a small
[Music]
CH be be just soft
be U SS
I just a small
one come on guys give me give me a [\h__\h]
give
me give me a
[Music]
booy oh thank you oh thank
you oh
than thank you thank you okay I'm happy
now
[Music]
stop stop stop
stop thank for the many
[Music]
[Laughter]
booies a troll for Van D yuk Mike D for
the pinky happy birthday K I wish you
the best in these upcoming busy months M
the foreshadowing but you already knew
cuz I warned you guys so many times
thank you for always making us smile and
for always giving it your all for us we
love you and we'll always support you
thank you so much
I love you guys
too I hope I hope you do continue
supporting me because I still got some
stuff to do here and I hope that you
guys will continue to be a part of this
journey thank you so much you got M
D Dance M thank you for the reer chat
happy birthday I haven't sent one of
these in a while so don't spend it all
in one place also I have been feing for
the backstory on the Warhammer painting
you mentioned on Twitter also apparently
this is my 20th Super Chat that
information is disconcerting I don't
think there's anything wrong with
that yeah I I mentioned it I think
yesterday or so maybe or during my
members only stream but I'm really not
sure like it's been so long that I don't
remember any details to be
honest uh when it comes to the
[Music]
Warhammer I just know that I painted
some stuff and I think it was probably
my brother's figures anyway mostly I
didn't have any of my
[Music]
own yeah well thank you so much for your
big Super
Chat thank you soon for the
support very very appreciated moose 66
667 D Philip ho Dan G me D Jello bear
Dan g c k e Dan and Ken Nakashima Dan
fried screw Dan just another kfp Dan and
last but not least David escute thank
you for the red super chat happy
birthday to the best boss with chickens
could have I'm so happy to be able to
send an ala spot is here thank you I'm
happy too
thank you for bringing so much joy to
our lives thank you for inspiring me to
better myself I'm proud to call you my
Koshi
a you guys you guys also inspire me to
better
myself we are forming a
circle of give and take M thank you
David very much appreciate it D I'm glad
I can be your com aie I hope that will
never
change aboy aoy I didn't that wasn't so
bad that wasn't so bad I'm going to eat
this
now
[Music]
um that was my
dinner not very
[Music]
nutritional I'm still
hungry maybe I'll go eat you you guys
[Music]
next should I eat
you I think
[Music]
so no no no no no no just kidding yeah
you you I I need to tell you to the
customers I can't eat you all can't eat
you all what are the customers going to
eat
huh me
next I volunteer of course you
do I am here
mhm are you
[Music]
guys are suspicious suspiciously open to
this I volunteer as a tribute oh Hunger
Games
pose fingers up in the air
[Music]
whistling okay so this was a lot of fun
thank you for joining
in I actually managed it's two and a
half hours I managed to to actually for
once
accurately do what I say I was going to
do accurately stream as long as I said I
was going
to normally I can only do that if I if I
have like a really hard limit for some
reason like a 3D stream that is bound to
be an hour or so oh my God who would
have thought enjoy your weekend thank
you I'm I'm sorry I was only back for a
few days
now I'll be gone for a few days again
but uh I hope these little Refreshers of
Wawa made you
remember my
existence don't forget don't forget
don't
spaget I'm still here I'm just you know
not
streaming yeah I'll be back next week a
on Monday or on Tuesday possibly more
realistically Tuesday but maybe Monday
no probably more realistically
[Music]
Tuesday and next week we have some fun
things I think I'm participating in a
fun collab that hasn't been announced
yet that is not planned by
[Music]
me but I think you guys will like
whatever
happens
yeah
yeah oh yeah EDF is also happening next
week so with that being said thank you
for
watching and in German we say bu Al
gonna go record the things have
dinner and finish my
preparations yeah than sh thanks for
watching love of my life Wow sheesh a
and
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah EDF also EDF on Saturday I
think
H oh one more thing I'm just going to
quickly advertise uh first of all my
merch obviously buy my birthday merch if
you haven't yet please but also I mean
this isn't on sale yet it will go on
sale on July 24th but I think this is
has been making people quite
happy
uh so let me show you
[Music]
H God damn it what am I
doing yeah you remember those little
figurines that you were able to get
before and they were in standard outfits
now look how cute this is now they come
in Halloween attire and this time
they're not random I think they were
random before now you can like um buy
the one that you
want
so you should get all five anyway of
course because we look so cute together
and then you can do myth or treat so
sales I mean uh it's going to be a few
more days but I'm just going to tell you
now so keep your eye out on the H life
collection I retweeted it on Twitter in
case you don't know where to go
yeah and bye my
merch
bye-bye I'm going to go to the loading
screen because it has the merchandise
bye-bye I'm going to miss you I'm I just
want to chill with my cats and
stream but okay I got to
go thank you ch
thank you I had fun
[Music]
oh
honey night is
[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
we am dancing on