foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
music
hello
pineapple juice
good evening good day
[Music]
oh
chunkies
what you doing Junkies
yeah thank you thank you guys for
waiting for me I'm okay
uh
my sweet chickens
um I'm as good as I can be
that is a really relative answer
is this too loud on my side it's too
loud actually you know what that's
because I have it too loud
how is it too quiet actually it might be
too quiet now for you guys
let me raise the roof
whoop whoop a bit more
whoops
oh
okay I think oh this is Maybe
about the right
uh volume what do you think
we're still so quiet
screen is B yeah we're going full screen
today
sounds good a little bit more okay
special
I raised it a tiny bit
maybe a tiny little more
okay okay
well you tell me if it's too loud at
some point
welcome back it's been a while since the
last Sims 4 stream
uh up until now we had a lot of fun
playing the myth family
which was very chaotic now it's too loud
nah I don't believe it
and yeah very chaotic family that we had
there and uh today I felt like doing
something new I felt like starting fresh
so we are doing
Council plus hope
yeah
yeah yeah yeah audio is fine okay okay
everyone's shut up who sang Too Loud
only say too loud if it's really too
loud
doesn't mean that we're giving up on
myth family forever my family my family
my
whoa wow
wow
I'm a view that I will destroy you
wow that that is that's kind of
wholesome
anyway yeah it doesn't mean that we're
giving up on them we might get back to
them at some point
um but today I feel like doing something
fresh we're gonna start off by creating
them it's probably gonna take me 5
million hours
um oh
crony too loud
[Music]
we'll see we'll see
and get when we create her okay so shut
up we're gonna start off with uh Sana
oopsie
Sana
oopsie I switched to Japanese simple
there we go
that's how I write her name right Santa
is big
uh wait I need references I need a
little references wait wait I have
references uh got a tab out
uh
um
I got I got those
I got those
resources
I got those tattoo A's
there she is there she is okay let's see
how close we can uh get her I mean
clothes this is like randomly generated
clothes
and I already feel like this is this
looks like something that she would wear
I mean I don't know her that well but
somehow I can totally imagine her
wearing that
I don't know what about you I feel like
this kind of Suits her
it already has some energy which is why
I decided okay I'm gonna start by making
Santa
needs more beak how do I how
hiker big
um how do I increase the the body size
here
uh oh yeah right wasn't it in Sims 4
that you cannot actually change the the
height
only the width
I think
and in other Sims games I think you can
increase or decrease the body height but
not in
um
yeah it's fixed per age
that is that is something I would like
them to change
we should decide how she walks first how
does Santa look
she walks
she probably walks like that yeah I feel
like she's an energetic bouncy type
who has no worries uh and is just happy
and and spreads happiness Wherever She
Walks that's that's where who she is
oh she has a high voice
can we can you get an Australian accent
though where's my Australian accent girl
oh thank you
not such a b what the hell not such a
Visa you're telling me to not be such a
being uh-huh is a Samba
yeah yeah
there was something close really
[Music]
I believe
hello Santa lights I don't know how to
do a verse eating at the store
that's a baby voice
and I'm prep kid up I don't know
it's very cold you found an Irish voice
what those babies what
I've been nice I'm just gonna do
a lumpy the Ruskin
pomeray Quest I'm gonna do that yeah
that sounded maybe in a different uh
Galaxy it sounded similar
okay and uh what is that
ah
can this Sim use the toilet stand do you
guys think Sana would use the toilet
stand
I think I think she's so big that
everywhere is her toilet like she
couldn't even sit down on the toilet
like she stands on the globe and pees
all over I'm so
sorry
if she would sit down
she's so big I feel like I'm roasting my
like you know those those roasting your
mom jokes
so big
and if she sat down on the Earth
to do her idle meeting
it would break perhaps but she has her
limiter on usually at least on Sims 4.
so we will say she will sit down when
she goes on the toilet
hey I'm just trying to you know she says
she's big so I'm just trying to work
with that
anyway
uh should we do looks first or
personality let's do her looks oh God
okay so can we do yellow or eyes first
of all hell yeah I got some wow
oh
that was yeah those have a good good
like brownish gradation at the top like
she has
uh okay sorry I I tapped out
and she has she has can you change the
the outfit for once because I need to
look at your hair girl
wear this for now okay you need long
luscious blonde hair let me change my
hair
gosh she's she's cute
it's buff
okay so there we go
um there is no hair that is that oh
accurate I think
[Music]
um I did download a lot more packs Like
official packs by the way but no more
custom content unfortunately because I
don't know where to go
I don't know where to find it so I
figure in theory she has two very long
long long
twin tails
oh my God the music is so
Eerie right now if that's the right word
I don't see it two twin tails
two twin Tails ah
yeah but not really
this is the hair color though
can we have like glow twin tails
ah this is braided
oh my God
we're just getting started guys
braided huh
maybe maybe no twin tails
maybe just give her the longest hair
that I can find this is the longest hair
maybe now this is the longest hair I can
find
oh my God she scares me with those eyes
and that skin toning combination
scares me
in Sims we're gonna make it work and
Sims it scares me right now but
[Music]
um
too dark too dark
not not quite the right color oof
what about this one this is too dark
this maybe
[Music]
whatever else do I have
else not too short
I love this pigtail though
yeah she has a very soft look
I don't know how to recreate them we
started off with a difficult one
but I will give her this hair because
she does have some curliness in her hair
at least at the bottom
um so I guess that kind of looks like
that maybe now let's start off with the
face
let's can I just give her a basic ass
face to get off with oh God I haven't
been here in a long time how do I do
this no no I want to do face shape faces
yeah oh my God who are you and what did
you do to Sana
she got
a game oh my God this lady
um went into the tanning booth a little
bit too long or a bit too often
I had something nice here I don't know
was uh oh my God
uh
[Music]
she has a little bit of a yellow
like that
I can make it darker too here
is that yellow
it's not that's not really it is that it
ah
that looks more yellow
somewhere like there
that's a bit more yellow than the others
I
[Music]
think
I mean as in you know some people have a
pink Hue some people have a yellow Hue I
have a
I have a look at myself I think I also
have quite the yellow Hue in my skin
tone
um
wait a second wait a second I'm not done
I'm not done
[Music]
darker
no this is as dark as it can get
what wait but the eye color changed
give me give me give me eye color back
uh
uh oh God I I don't know if I like this
creation interface that much after all
[Music]
right there I had it no give me no eye
color
okay okay we had uh not this one
no
do we have that one
this one
was that the one I think that must be
the one
it doesn't go darker than that but you
will see it I think uh I think this is
pretty close to it but you will see the
the difference if she stands to the
others next to the others
and now I shape I mean Robert's not
gonna recreate those animal eyes so
cool
I don't know
she has actually her eyes are like kind
of how to say this in English Drew Bree
like they they are higher at this point
and lower at this point but right now
it's the opposite way
it's kind of kind of like that actually
kind of like that but just bigger big
how do I make pink
I'm already getting frustrated but the
the Glock sliders and [\h__\h]
what how do I do like how do I pull it
how do I pull it detail edit mode
there it is
oh my god oh I didn't realize you could
do that oh my God
oh my God oh my oh my God help
help
[Music]
oh my God
ah
looks like metal
droopy eyes I mean they are we're
getting there I mean that's that's cute
that's cute and small nose she's a very
small nose
can I turn you yeah
[Music]
mom small small
nose big body wait that looks a little
bit like her
[Music]
cute wait no I heard from your guys's
point of view this perfect looks really
scary
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait no no I
kind of messed it up it was better a few
steps before
wait
ah
somewhere here it looked cute
less cheekbones okay
okay I don't know kind of cute maybe
nose is a little bit too narrow
[Music]
there we go
what do you think it's a little
terrifying what do you mean cute from my
point of view
[Music]
it waited
she's cute
we need to add makeup it'll kind of look
it's gonna look better with makeup trust
me trust me
uh
makeup
makeup edgy makeup okay
night perfume what do you mean the eyes
are perfect I would say
and
oh cute okay
cute lips I mean it's on lashes no those
were not lashes get them out of here get
those out of here
is this also eyes
I don't know I want lashes
does that come with lashes no
eyelashes
all right maybe on their Islander
eyeliner
oh oh
oh oh dear oh my God
she kind of looks like I don't know
she looks like those
those
Instagram girls now
[Laughter]
[Music]
as well now oh
not
what do you say it's a valley girl she's
definitely one of those she looks like
those wannabe influencers
[Laughter]
oh
God she scares me with that makeup look
look to the front oh God the eyes are
too big I made them too big
we need to change the pupils they're
they're uh
scaring me
[Laughter]
oh my God
oh God don't look at me like that don't
look at me
like sorry I'm sorry I'm gonna lower
your Lids a little bit oh
hmm
oh
she looks so surprised
[Music]
okay can your eyes be a little bit more
in the middle of it
[Laughter]
oh it's so difficult are they centered
though I feel like they're they're like
going somewhere else
no this is too small we need animal
anime Vibes what about now
oh that's
these scent
[Music]
from the from fire she looks good and
most of the time we will not be looking
at her in a close-up
oh God no she scares me oh God
ah I don't know how to recreate her
beauty
um
maybe maybe it needs a bit more makeup
we have we have these eyelashes I don't
have any other eyelashes I think maybe
under a face paint
ah yeah yeah okay wait let me let me get
rid of those where are the ones that I
currently have on
uh
makeup
these ones get rid of those go here no
those are eyes a damn it I was
Bamboozled I thought those were
eyelashes didn't I have eyelashes
I know eyelashes
well those are some nice lips
pretty oh you know what that fits better
I feel like she has nude lips I mean
if you think about it we most of us
girls don't really have lipstick on but
for Sana I would definitely say nude
lips the cheekbones make it look scary
yeah my cheekbones are pretty normal
what do you mean maybe more cheeks maybe
fill the cheeks up
oh no here any I mean the no no no no no
this part but then I don't know it looks
kind of chunky chunky
she's very angular what does that mean
nozo nosolabial crease what this pie
does that that should we make it bigger
cute actually kind of cute
actually kind of cute
Am I Wrong Am I Wrong
[Music]
what is that mouth
oh yeah
[Music]
wow
bodox gone wrong
um
ah
this one
I mean it was fine before as well but
edit mode
can I make her smile a bit more
[Music]
much okay I'm going right to
retail
this is gonna take me five hours at this
point
oh I'm gonna move the chat a little bit
somewhere else
not the duck lips what's your what's
your problem she looks good now she
looks good
uh but but wait now she has no lashes
should we bring back those those lashes
that she had before what do you guys
think does it look worse or or better
are there any lashes here
[Music]
remember lashes are here
oh God
[Music]
it doesn't give me Santa Vibes if she
wears too much makeup I think because
then then she just looks like one of
those Instagram girls oh no oh no I
don't think we can give her
um that the lashes no
[Laughter]
um
but you know what um she is gonna get a
choker because she has
um that little ribbon on her neck
it's a blue ribbon
I think this one is fitting
or even that one all cute
blue blue yeah ah
okay I'm gonna move on to the clothes I
think but you guys still don't like the
cheekbones what
oh the cheekbones Loa oh oopsie and
something something weird
okay
how about how about now well that makes
it worse
more cheek Fuller flatter
Fuller one person says Fuller one person
says flatter
um
wait this this part
now it's now it's Fuller before after
but it like changes the job not really
the cheeks oh wait a second
maybe I grabbed this part but maybe I
should grab but that's the cheekbones at
the same time
like this
[Music]
before
after
which one lower her eyes oh I can do
that probably wait a second
I don't want to destroy the eye shape
ah
ah there we go
lowered it
I think that was better before
not maybe not that much maybe just a
little bit
uh there you go
okay ah that might be good that uh
[Music]
so much detail we're never gonna get to
play the game today
what about now
is that looking good yes
she looks middle aged
really
I mean I think that's maybe a little bit
of the skin texture this is like a
this is a skin tone that I downloaded
the texture is like she has like kind of
like freckles well not everyone has
Perfect Skin okay yes she got abs that
is also part of the skin texture
they got abs in the skin texture texture
oh yeah so oh my God I need to do her
boing boing
no no no no no no no no
go
boy oh
yes
also big Big Boing Boing here yes
[Music]
no no no no
no no no no no
what the hell I'm clicking here
okay there we go
uh I don't know what the Flies are
looking like right now let me
put her in some panties right now so we
see her
wow wow badonkas
yes
[Music]
uh
more more and maximum you tell me that's
the mess the maximum well oh okay okay
it didn't look like it changed much from
the side okay no not that much
like this yes yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
happily is big in a good way shoulders
maybe a bit less there you go oh oh okay
time to dress her up
um
we will not be getting anything that
looks perfectly like her clothes but
let's try to get the color theme
uh of white and blue and perhaps gold
do we have something that shows side
boobs yes we do
[Laughter]
oh God are you okay
um
[Music]
what's what's this t-shirt
ah Sana I think she's a kind of a girly
girl like she would go for some girly
clothes but like still comfy but really
comfy really comfy
um
[Music]
turns out the end of my eyes are on the
shirt yeah just look there look there
oh I feel like she would wear something
like that but it's bugging out because
the boobs are too big and the hair is
like uh vlogging into the boobs
damn it
let me look at the addresses maybe dress
dress full body let's see what we have
here
oh
my oh the boobs are too big
[Music]
I see
cute I I downloaded a few more packs I
bought like so many kits and I think two
big expansion packs and I was missing
and a lot of other stuff
so there is some more stuff here
thankfully than before
[Music]
hey what would she wear like if we if we
gave her casual clothes
uh we could put her in a spacesuit the
game probably has that
[Music]
uh
oh wait your face scares me oh my God no
I can't what happened to your face what
happened to your face
I need to fix it I need to fix it
[Music]
oh God did I do what did I do
look front look front
the nose the no it's the nose it's the
nose it's her skin no it's her nose and
her skin maybe the texture is a bit
weird I know
um but it will it looks a bit more
realistic than this The Sims skin tones
they're like plastic it's the entire
face
I try no it's it's okay just sometimes
she looks weird when uh when she looks
to the side she looks a bit weird but
when she looks front
oh God
like since they when they smile they
pull apart their mouth so far that they
look like Joker
[Music]
I can't help it
mmm
[Laughter]
damn oh oh by the way
uh
uh is she is she a buff or not
how buff would Santa be there's a lot of
Bubba there
um
I think this is okay
uh okay let's go back to the dresses
just just don't look don't look at the
face just don't look there
we could also just put her in that and
then no one has to worry about it
oh
spacesuit or something like that
oh my God is that Sana
that demos that looks a bit summerish
[Music]
um so many choices that's cute baby
um there's too much choice
oh
wow what
wow what that's hourglass shape though
[Music]
um
it's a lot of formal stuff in here oh
wonderful perfect wow wow that really
emphasizes her body shape again oh look
at that booty it's so shy
oh my
what the hell is that what is that
oh dear
um
wasting too much time
what am I doing
oh here are some of the
uh downloaded clothes that I had from
before anything here that could be
fitting yeah
[Music]
I wore that
not very flattering on her okay back to
the top and
I'm gonna try
[Music]
what
why the space suit no space suit is
no I want to try at least to do her
justice a little bit
[Music]
uh
you know what this
this kind of low-key only low-key gives
me Sana Vibes only a little bit
wait does this have other colors
I'm looking for white blue gold
[Music]
the jumper which jumper jumper
because it's not helping space
the one next to it this one
it has a blue color
all right
all right this is her all right okay
this is okay
this one you want this one or is there a
time delay and you don't mean this one
I think you mean this one
okay
okay then we don't have to worry about
shoes and stuff either
[Laughter]
let's still just all the other outfits
we're gonna have to at some point do a
like redo it but for now we'll just
throw in something anything
[Music]
don't think too hard about it
don't think too hard I think she would
be wearing a somewhat longer dress but
[Music]
um
wait a second
colors
blue but wait let me give you let me
give you your choker again
let me give you that hole
choker
uh Rings bracelets
I did the Joker go
fingernails no no wait toenails though
yes yes oh she has blue blue blue
there we go
detail that's correct
uh I can't find it the chocolate
[Music]
I want to gloves she has long white
gloves in her main outfit should we do
that here
[Music]
this looks more like sound and the main
outfit now
is there something I can put on her head
by the way
like
uh
[Music]
maybe for the Casual one
how do I
got it
is there accessories on the head no
there must be
no no no no no extra detail mode
hats
like a limiter that I can put on here
I need a limiter oh that's that's maybe
that's a limiter
pink
to close your limiter is Pink
or or not
cute
laughs no
is there here are the chokers by the way
good to know
wrestler Santa let's go
she does have some some not earrings I
think but there's like some dingles
dangles dangling
on one side of her ear I love something
similar
tool
bulk I kind of like this one
but that's the Snowman
I we don't even see it even if we put it
on there
okay
okay then and I want to go here and give
hair give her the Joker
[Music]
choker of her dreams there we go see
this looks more like her now outfit wise
also Barefoot barefoot
Barefoot she's barefoot no matter where
she goes can we give her that ankle ring
can we give her the ankle ring
accessories
toenails
oh
what shoes
leggings socks toenails fingernails
Rings gloves bracelets is there any
bracelets on on the leg I want to give
her a bracelet on the leg
I don't know how to do that maybe I
don't have any
that's okay
okay sportswear uh quick
uh what the hell that's not that's not
sportswear
let's give her that no shoes she's no
shoes gang
we're at the painted
painted toes
[Music]
blue there we go
do I have to do this every time wasn't
there a way to like
uh
send it over to all the other outfits
this is her sleeping mode girly are you
sure
how does I think she would wear pants
like that yes pink I think she likes
pink and blue
um did someone ever say what her
favorite colors are
we are wearing with beanie to bed is a
weird thing
oh wait you know what a NASA t-shirt
would be perfect like for the casual
outfit even
and I feel like the game would have
something like that
wait
take off the beanie
yeah
wait do we have a I know you all of this
but if we find the NASA t-shirt
I don't know if I can keep this one NASA
t-shirt not a t-shirt something that
looks like a NASA t-shirt
Sana t-shirt doko
ah so many pet related outfits
NASA
huge
I didn't even properly properly look for
this one yet I think
[Music]
um
Deadbeats
now so
I don't see anything right now but that
would definitely be something that
someone made as like a custom content
could download for later and change your
outfit later alright guys if someone
wants to find me that NASA t-shirt go
ahead and get me that what is that party
outfit
party outfit
party party
that's not party but it's cute I would
wear that looks really comfy Kawaii
it's really rare that something looks
good that's randomly created
[Music]
oh
what what would you wear
what would she wear
what would you wear Sana
come on give me a sign
oh that's cute that's also cute that's
cute
hello dorps
uh do we have this in blue no
we have this in blue
I want a dark blue
everything must be dark blue didn't we
already do something uh formal okay so
this doesn't really have to be that
formal
oh party party party party
[Music]
you know what just just wear this this
is blue and then go to the party
Barefoot I know it's a little bit
dangerous or blue boots no barefoot's
Barefoot it is
and toenails
blue it's the details it's in the
details guys
trust me can we put something on their
head for party time
um
[Music]
I don't like these hats
what is that
oh that actually works with the custom
content I'm surprised
oh bee cats beaks be cat for Big Summer
wait a minute
wait that actually looks kind of cool
haha
I mean the fact that she's always
Barefoot is a little bit worrying
but it's okay next up
I don't care just I guess we can't go
with that now we don't go
we don't go with that we gotta go Blue
and this one
so sorry Sana
you're gonna wear those because you're
dorky and I like that
uh toenails blue
[Laughter]
perfect little bit uh buggy in that area
but what can we do
hot weather
first of all time to take off your shoes
and put on some toenail color yeah
and then we want you to wear
some nice booty pants some Santa hell
yeah oh yeah oh yeah
what's top actually you know we had that
before
but no I don't think that's her style
um
[Music]
hot weather
difficult too many things to choose from
that's cute and simple no pants
foreign
[Music]
actually you know that shirt is really
cute the one that we just had and we
could do this one
[Music]
okay I think uh
for that one
no we'll do this one but do we have any
white because that looks a little bit
like her uh outfit with a lot of fantasy
[Music]
cold weather
no
um
[Music]
blue
well funky cute pattern oh cute pattern
blow
wow big size I feel like Santa is even
though her main outfit is so
um
you know emphasizing her body I feel
like she normally would wear clothes
that are just comfy and chill right
[Music]
not that though no no
I don't know I don't know about warm
clothes yeah
this is like for going skiing though
I can totally see that yeah right so
let's give her leggings
yeah yeah yeah bug Barefoot even in cold
weather Sana knows no pain when it comes
to coldness or hotness or whatever her
feet
her feet are like what how do you call
what do you say uh how do you say uh
Juan house
in English
probably has so much horn hat on her uh
feet that she feels nothing anymore
calluses
hallucis
is that it
[Music]
wait I wanna give her that beanie that
she was wearing before for the cold
weather or like something like that girl
[Music]
that's right
yes let's go virus and Santa outfit
later
[Music]
blown we have blue and pink maybe no
would have been too nice
okay let's go with that
kind of cute
okay wait are we done uh with outfits I
think we're done
uh okay was there anything else here
okay what kind
of this took us this took us almost an
hour what kind of personality do we have
um what's your aspiration creativity
[Music]
seems like her
creative one she's the inner of a myth
of cancel because she's gonna be making
all that money for my family by drawing
every day
I'm gonna exploit her
[Music]
okay painter extraordinaires same wants
her life to be all about iron painting
uh hell yeah okay pick likes and
dislikes
uh okay do you guys
she ever say
where the Santa lights at
lights
[Music]
blue did she really say that yellow
yellow she likes pink
well let's say she likes yellow
she likes blue
wait oh can I only do one color no I
think Ninja
[Music]
she likes pink
um
and what music genre did she ever say
what music genre she likes I don't think
we have to even do these like we don't
have to go that much into detail
Ahoy what
well Ahoy did you just say Ahoy
classic jazz
metal she said
metal oh my God uh where's metal
um spoopy
metal metal metal
am I blind I don't see any metal music
new age
this is discrimination
there's no match
what she was in a metal band
oh
what I can't use I can do metals it
doesn't say medley anyway Rock instead
where's Rock
Rock why don't you rock on it I'll throw
it in blue is classic
Electronica Island hip-hop am I blind am
I blind
classic
what you know what we're just we're just
not gonna do it but that's very
interesting info to me oh does she like
baking she likes baking I mean at least
in Minecraft
ninja
and definitely video gaming rocket
science
huh
um
bread
[Music]
yeah so far so good
painting was there painting did I miss
painting ah there it is
okay the core
yes I don't know oh yeah
[Music]
I think she's a genius
yes but also she's cheerful though oh
there's so many trades to choose from
no she's definitely cheerful
[Music]
I want to give her a dog lover but it
makes me sad
should we do it anyway
oh no maybe not
[Music]
astrology was their astrology
astrology
[Music]
do you guys see astrology
what else would fit her
um
you mean here
uh was it a knowledge
academic spell craft and sorcery and
that's new I got I got the the magic
pack I think huh astronomy
where would that be
Chuck
I'm blind
oh wait no
it's in science
foreign
am I blind I don't see science
animal athletic created creativity food
family Divine deviants Divine Fortune
knowledge is cute
location love nature populated Wellness
we're just gonna keep that
[Music]
foreign
outgoing
she's outgoing
would you say say Sana is outgoing
Fortune
oh as here what Fortune Fortune Fortune
Fortune Fortune
watching Fortune now
outgoing okay
the first one oh my God it only took us
a million years
ah
class one
add a new sim
uh let me see Let's do let's do Bales oh
God bails is gonna be difficult
okay one one
fart today hello Bales nice to meet you
uh I need I need to change
a lot about you
[Music]
um all right
slow Vegeta hello
that's her yes
walking
gotta be efficient guys
oh I feel like Bales would would kind of
walk like that
oh
she actually shook me the other way
around How can I
can I um uh what's that oh
[Music]
my God I have an idea
in in Minecraft there's this one name
that you can put on pets with a name tag
or anything really
um was it something with bone I think
I should I should pull a prank on her
but
naming unnamed uh Foxes or whatever in
her apartment dinnerbone yes all of them
turn them around because you know
Australia
or or just the confident one
bouncy or confident
[Music]
chaotic walk
which one is chaotic
there's no chaotic walk
okay oh this this is maybe chaotic
now we're gonna do the bouncy I guess
that was the most requested okay yes
just look at you let's look at you first
of all
oh my God
I mean this would be this would be the
normal uh
uh skin tones from Sims these are the
the ones that I got
um
should I use those
pale as can be she is really pale
oh God that's that's so yellow
but that's
um too pink
who's Akashi you know what I'm I'm gonna
go over that we're gonna make it we're
gonna work or this one
[Music]
or this one this one okay okay trust me
trust me trust me trust me first of all
let's try to find a hairstyle that
somehow
that's that's the Kiara hairstyle wait
oh this one one I don't have anything
better than that
those are some weak ass twin tails you
got their veils what happened did you
run out of Hairspray
I feel like it has to be this one though
wait I don't like your face I don't want
to change I want to change your face
faces
I started off with a crazy face again no
mind would you change that
[Music]
they changed the skin tone again okay
okay hey that already looks like her
don't you think
do we have a
do we have a spiky collar for her by the
way
Spike spiky dark color color color color
color color I don't know how to
pronounce that word
apparently not on it
how did I get to the chokers before hmm
we'll find it eventually
[Music]
they must have one right
let's hide that is unfortunately not
possible in this game unless we make her
a child
okay actually her face is
um
not that difficult I mean let's do the
eyes let's make uh
beak and then
uh no actually a bit more higher and
then pink
[Music]
okay
that's a bit sharp she has quite a sharp
chin
[Music]
but the whole uh height of the chin
should be like that oh yes that's
do you agree with me or not
uh when I want the fancy eye colors
where do I have the fancy eye colors on
it
this isn't makeup yes I think it was
one second
but she looks cute
what's the problem
she has blue eyes with some red accent
in it but I don't think I can recreate
that
I don't like those eyes
blue blue blue
oh dear
it's not quite the blue that I want
[Music]
those are those are the best I have I
guess
what did I have
um
cute
actually actually she looks cute
but a bit brighter like this
what is that
isn't that what you
okay those those don't really do
anything unfortunately
oh well give her whiskers ah but she's a
rat with two rats have whiskers okay I
should look more like a cat though
but okay okay cheeks I think it was in
cheeks yeah ah
you want this
is this what you want is this what you
desire
I I want to give her those crazy lashes
though those
those lower lashes I know
yeah
I want to give her where are they
where are they
choker would be I think
spiky choker collar thingy
she has it in black with some cheese on
it unfortunately no cheese here oh my
God look at her oh that is that is
pretty accurate I would say by the way I
have to go back one on to her because
why is she wearing this right now you
should be wearing this okay thank you
okay bae
all right
uh one thing I didn't do with Santa is
your eyebrows oh well they they you
can't even see them because she has that
long hair covering up all of her
eyebrows
her eyebrows are shaped upwards
I don't know if you guys have noticed
this before
um
so I need some more yeah like like this
yeah
like inside this angry rat she's more of
a happy rat yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay
we also do this one I
think oh yeah
oh Sullivan I stay with that cute
hamster indeed
looking better than the Santa one
I have to revamp her at some point all
right we're already done with the face I
feel like or maybe wait
um oh I'm happy
I'm happy with that
can I give her ears like Mouse ears
I want to give her a mouse ears
[Music]
there's no Mouse ears I'm sad
uh well we could put something else on
her head
when Downs no no why
why yeah
I want the hats and the twin Tails I
want The Best of Both Worlds please
no oh my God why would you do that okay
then no no then not I guess
uh okay okay close come on we gotta
speed up a little bit I'm now gonna get
to play the game today
actually her outfit is a little bit
easier to recreate because I want to
give her like a crop top uh that's a
little bit like
um
flowy not super skin tight
[Music]
and I think I've seen something like
that before
something like that but that's not the
one I wanted I think
that actually is
that works
not exactly
I was a different one there was a
different one that I wanted
[Music]
that's beige wait a second I'm gonna go
with that
yep I'm I'm going with that the colors
are also pretty perfect
and you can still see her color all good
okay and skirt oh perfect she looks like
a cheerleader though
[Music]
or this one oh this is cute oh my God
oh
oh she's hella cute she has a pleated
skirt with a kind of some kind of belt
in her actual outfit so this is pretty
close
in theory I know I don't have a tail for
her sorry
okay and then shoes
um
she wears those like kind of like
a school shoes
oh but those those would look
it doesn't look good
oh
[Music]
hmm
front I mean yeah you could say the belt
is a that kind of rat tail yeah yeah
if you want to say like that you're
welcome to do so
um
[Music]
I want those Japanese style uh
those are cute though those are so cute
you know what we're just gonna go for
these oh my God I I would wear this yo
hello
adorable like oh my God like cute
I still want to give her those crazy
lashes though I can't find them anymore
[Music]
where are you [\h__\h]
oh what's that is that icon
oh no those are more lashes oh yeah all
right you know what I'll give you lashes
you look cute with those
cute why does she look so much better
for
I feel ashamed
I am ashamed
I'm sorry
belly doggle yeah
no belly and sacrifice for a cute outfit
don't you think that's fair
wait where were those uh skirts there
like this one would show a bit more of a
belly but I don't really like the shape
that much
wow
what do you think this one number one or
number two number one or number two
number one number two number one number
two number one number two
number two number two number one most
people say number ah wait let's do a
poll
one and one and two
dirty
this is two this is one
two one two one two one two
one two
one two oh two is winning
sadly two is cuter yeah from like the
whole the way it's like created it looks
cuter this is custom content by the way
not from Sims
both would work honestly but this one
makes her look a little bit too much
like a cheerleader in my opinion yeah
okay two it's a close battle but two is
winning thank you for participating
oops
[Music]
okay next outfit
formal
a formal rat how would a rats dress if
she wants to be formal
like this this is this is exactly it
I wish it would be more red instead of
pink though
rat rat rat rat
it's black
uh the pink one or the fully black one
foreign this one looks nice though
black and white
pink wow wait you mean this one actually
those are both pink hot pink or soft
pink hot pink maybe okay let's go with
the hot pink
hot pink
[Music]
shoes
what are those socks girl what are those
socks
[Music]
oh where are those socks
there we go
although she does have
I wonder wait can we give her yellow
socks here because she has one yellow
sock
oh wait she has there's little socks too
oh wait wait wait wait wait she has one
normal yellow sock and one loose sock
kind of look kind of like a chunky
oh no those bugs oh no it was overlapped
with the shoes so that's a No-No
mm-hmm
how cute
oh my
okay
this is maybe the best Sim I've ever
created except for the hair I want a
better twin tail hairstyle I'm gonna get
a better one until the next stream I'm
gonna get a custom content twin tail
hairstyle because the game just has
these shitty childish ones okay oh my
god oh
oh
[Music]
Chuck E cheese bell
we don't have chocolate cheese in in my
country but I've heard of that mm-hmm
oh by the way
you know small small
weak rat
[Music]
okay
come on give me some speed uh that's
okay uh
oh God uh
work out
workout are you a freak are you a freak
wait
[Music]
take this
uh no that's actually not like her no no
no no that's not like her no no no no no
no no
oh
[Music]
um
no
yeah
oh okay
all right all right all right all right
okay whatever I don't care I don't care
about the other outfits
vans
I'm not trying I'm not sponsored by them
guys
this is sleepy time
I think Santa was wearing that one
with a lot of fantasy this is a wrap
okay okay
[Music]
why she do be looking cute though
okay
[Music]
there we go perfect
Falling in Love
this is party party
time can we get something crazier than
the formal wear
um
he's down to party that's for sure Hmm
this also looks like something maybe
oh no
no no no no okay
[Music]
um
oh oops no we're going for this I guess
party party
[Music]
shoes
clown clown juice what do you think
about clown shoes I mean she's chaotic
we gotta make her more chaotic
where is the chaos in all of this
oh no never mind you don't see that
chaos I mean chaos here chaos wow chaos
oh my God so chaotic oh my that this is
chaos
hahaha
oh I think I ruined her
let's hope she never goes to party
[Music]
this is a cute one
everything's red
oh
not so far off I would say not so far
off
mmm hot weather it is
this was the one that I was looking for
first
we could do it in white
although red is almost better but and
then we can give her this skirt instead
it also looks very close to
a good outfit hell yeah
hell yeah I feel inspired
yes
[Music]
okay okay
can we give her
um
[Music]
some socks
oh
how come there's only these socks now
because of the hot weather
do these work now they don't really
almost almost
yeah you get socks in summer
yes
oh sunglasses I want sunglasses
sunglasses sunglasses sunglasses
that looks like cheese that looks like
cheese
and sunglasses what is that ugly
necklace
no no can we have that necklace
okay
uh chaotic sunglasses
that's okay this is maybe the most
chaotic we can get
yes okay good but I want those cheese uh
earrings here as well
I need them and maybe a piercing
[Music]
leaves
cheese where's the cheese where did the
cheese go
oh streamer headset
skull
cheese
ah here it is cheese
leaves
we can do that we can do that if I if I
really remember
okay hot weather done cold weather
if we're done with that then we almost
made her now in half an hour still gotta
do her traits though okay a cold water
cold water
chaotic
so let's just make her chaotic
[Music]
hello my name is
bales
her aspiration I think
could be this
chief of mischief
yeah yeah I am
and color
red
yellow
white black blue brown orange green
purple pink Gray
[Music]
activities
what does she like to do help me out
guys miss Chief yes
uh video gaming
favorite color yes
dance dance dance dance dance dance
dance dance dancing dancing rat comedy
is a company ah
she likes violin really
what really are you sure can people
confirm that
she read last night wow wow
that doesn't necessarily prove anything
not much of a gamer really
but it's it's kind of our job
Mixology Grant who really
she likes phone
[Music]
oh wait where's the phone
uh she craves violence with praise crap
where's craving violence here
coffee where do you see coffee coffee
coffee coffee are you are you kidding me
guys
let's see coffee
you guys are saying things that aren't
even on here
stop effing around with me with me all
right so
um
no she's not evil she's chaotic
is there a chaotic one here and a
creative genius gummy goofball
goofball
um childish
[Music]
dance machine oh she's a dance machine
erratic
talk to themselves and have
unpredictable emotions is she erratic
[Music]
uh
not really okay
but it would be chaotic it would be fun
I'll do that because yes look at that
can't wait what the hell why are you
even still wearing that come on
okay okay okay I'm done I'm done I'm
done
I can do occult Sims now by the way who
are we doing next let's do
let's do crony
we could do a cold alien spell cast a
mermaid no I guess it's just a normal
one
mesoplim sarpava Mesa plums a papa
exactly all right so your name is
crowny
odor
did I write that correctly I think I did
first of all she walks
how does she walk
we will never know until she becomes 3D
but uh-huh
I think she would walk like huh
confidently and like
a little bit like that
I'm sorry but
I feel like that suits her
yep okay good you guys are great and I
don't feel bad about it
and a low voice
[Music]
oh wait that actually sounds like come
on Genie Luray you hear that guys
holy night mokosa holy night makosa
okay done
we're fast here okay
crony look at me look at me I need a
reference there it is she is also
extremely pale if not even paler than
bales
are sure
wait let me first give you a little
random ass space
and give you the Payless oh God that's
that's true
all right I want to start with your hair
actually
she has dark blue hair
[Music]
oh and it's actually not that
difficult just short hair
which is longer in the front a little
bit but
hmm
oh crony where are you crony
crony
[Music]
crowny oh maybe things
Ah that's supposed to be dark blue
I see a tiny difference here okay
uh I would like it to be a bit more blue
though
I'm getting the red color is gonna be a
pain in the ass
anything that the game provides Me Maybe
This
oh this has a lot of colors
oh this is the darkest blue that they
have
hmm
otherwise we have
no
this only comes in mixed colors
[Music]
ah I need more hairstyles I need more
choices
crony what do I do with you I said it
would be easy but I was wrong
[Music]
ing
it's blue it's like that's the with
basic hairstyles I think that's gonna be
the only blue that we can get though
that's a really ugly blue
intense
[Music]
in Sims 3 you were actually able to
really adjust the color completely to
what you want
which was nice but we don't have that
luxury here all right I don't know man
use gray it is almost grayish yeah
but I don't know
feels wrong
it needs to be a navy color what do we
have here this or this is too long
though the hair is too long
this is not the right hairstyle
this is this is pretty much black
[Music]
I don't really see much blue there
apparently it's supposed to be the kind
of blue
I mean this gray could be okay
oh
that's
I'm looking at it side to side and
that's maybe the closest I've seen so
far from hair color wise
yeah yeah oh you guys agree okay
nice nice okay
in that case we'll go with that
unfortunately no fringe
maybe we can give her a cool hat instead
of a fringe
if that doesn't
um mess up the the hairstyle
crony
[Music]
ah
crony I don't I don't know what's what
clothing style she would generally go
for like I really I can barely tell a
helicopter head
we have something like that no
maybe without feminine
[Music]
now that gets rid of the hair
oh
helicopter
no
this is almost like a helicopter oh this
is
from far away
this looks exactly like her
I think I think that's the best I can do
what the [\h__\h] is that
is that an is that an insult to me
Electronic Arts what are you trying to
tell me where did my helicopter hair go
where is it where is it where is your
local dog on here
we can even make it dark blue perfect it
Blends in it Blends it perfectly ha
what do you mean they added Kiara to
Sims 4 where where I didn't see her
oh Ollie hello oh this is crony we're in
the middle of creating her so ignore the
cloves and all that violation she is
um like sofin
but she has these these
badonkas you don't even see it with
those clothes one second
[Music]
okay let's just put on just suit full
ones
uh yes
she needs to be
she's really uh not very broad shoulders
she's so thin
her legs are like so long
[Music]
this is
this is pretty close to her body shape
wait a little bit like that yeah yeah
[Laughter]
she has literally toothpick legs this is
accurate
from all legs for days
doesn't get bigger than this
I can make lower it though
come on here is it too low
there you go ah it's a bit too low
okay
okay okay
[Music]
right right
I like ribbon ribbon earrings
she has blue ribbon earrings I'm sure
there's something like that
ribbon Blue Ribbon earrings that's it
that's all the earrings
Blue Ribbon
that's it
um
anything like that looks like a clock
and clock then maybe I don't know Blue
Ribbon
maybe maybe this one
blue ribbons
[Music]
I can't find any Blue Ribbon earrings
pick a blue one okay
these ones yes okay crony looking good
ice battle it we're gonna go for Custom
Eyes again
and some
nice eyeliner oh hell yeah
uh
[Music]
some pretty whips oh crony edgy
that's some oh oh she's oh who did I
just create she's hot
what did I do oh look at what a girl
crush oh my God
oh
my God hold it down
[Music]
oh my those fake eyebrows look so good
on her too her eyebrows are more shaped
like
not quite wait chill chill a little bit
nah
they're a bit more like
angled so not not not like this but
oh yeah maybe yeah they're a bit thicker
in the front though to be honest if we
want to be accurate here
oh wow don't be so angry though
oh my
God what a girl crush
my heart goes doggy doggy for you
um eyelashes
oh my God
[Music]
very very sharp chin
although it goes through the eyelashes
go for her hair no but it doesn't really
stand out that much like I think
I think no only if you look very close
yeah why does it even go through like if
I look from here it doesn't go through
weird
oh no she's hot
oh no
oh not
hmm
wait a second I need to go into detail
mode
she has
oh I might mess it up now but I try I'm
gonna try a little bit
[Music]
oh my God
oh
my
she has big ears though have you guys
noticed
her ears wow I just it's the first time
I noticed her ears are pretty big and
they stand off like like elephants ears
it's so cute oh my God her ears are so
cute
[Music]
marry me
oh God she's hot
crony
we're done with your face like look at
you girl
okay we're going for a close now
can we do it in half an hour
um
oh
[Music]
my God wait a second it kind of looks
with some fantasy wait if we have like a
if we add them
a blue skirt and a black skirt
no
we got a lucky made up why the hell a
main outfit
what what happened Dad you guys
associate her with a maid outfit
jeans no no no no no she wears a skirt
but we will actually she wears something
like that but much shorter
she she has a clean cleaning Obsession
cleaning chest box
and watch the I watched a tiny bit of a
stream yesterday that's the first time I
really got a good look at her bunker
and I was
um shocked
is is this what you call uh
uh OCD
oh my God
[Music]
that's um
I want her to clean my apartment and
organize my apartment please I need some
help cronie
that's uh I was shocked oh oh no it bugs
out
sad
sad life
oh God her legs scare me no well I have
to do something about this or maybe it
looks better with uh
the socks that I'm about to give her
you know what you're gonna get leggings
oh oh I can combine I don't wanna though
yeah black tights improve it a little
bit oh I should give those to Sana
oh anyway this for now
and
I'm not happy with the pants necessarily
but it works all good
do we have a striped skirt somewhere
I think
just
if you squint really hard
then this is crony hundred percent oh by
the way she needs a black gloves
foreign
[Music]
and some funny boots
maybe something that stands out
that that's all I was going to say about
it my English that flops flops off from
the side would be good but
um
I mean that's pretty good
side stop
hello
oh hello
[Music]
I think oh wait actually
yeah no
it should be blue actually
but those big flip-flops around it I
don't think I can do that oh wait those
those look like it
those are Uggs actually aren't those
like the like a special type of Uggs
but it it looks it looks uh accurate
pretty accurate
color wise as well like ins on the
outside it's blue and it's inside it's
uh White
okay
I think
that's the best
oh my god look look at her her outfit is
kind of weird but if you're squint it
looks like her
okay we can go on to
actually wait one second do we have a
ribbon for her neck that's that's the
one one more thing I want to do
ribbon
a ribbon she has a big Sailor Moon
ribbon on her neck
uh and it's light blue so like this oh
cute
cute groaning
all right formal time
one more time
for formal
um
oh look at that cleavage
yes Chrono yes
[Music]
oh wow
the boobs just look so weird when
they're in maximum size
you don't like the skirt
yeah
well you want me to put there instead oh
what about this
no not really nice colors
the skirt is good skirt was fine
[Music]
take off the hat no [\h__\h] way that is
the last thing I'm going to do taking
off her hat skirt was okay okay wait
wait wait wait okay Skype was okay good
good good good
this is fine
and oh
you can keep those pants I think I think
that's okay
and
um
that looks like the big ribbon she has
on her chest
actually
[Music]
um
oh grill grill Crush vibes
oh
[Music]
jacket
oh the jacket it looks okay from the not
honestly her waist is ridiculous at this
point
oh
you're gonna wear this I do not care
uh sleeping sleepy time
[Music]
this is her yes
a party time
nice hat you got there looks like a
helicopter
[Music]
oh
let's look at dresses oh cronies
crony is this you
party party
[Music]
oh my God
she looks stylish
even the shoes are fine with me to be
honest but let's see
let's see what we can do
oh oh instagrammer
um
swimsuit you know what you can keep that
we're trying to save some time here
oh my God what is that what is that
shirt is that like the Matrix shirt
what is that hot weather
hot
I mean
you know what this looks good on you
[Music]
I wonder if she's the type of person who
would wear like really colorful clothes
privately or if she goes more like
chilling probably more like that no
it is hot out here
oh god oh oh oh my God oh my God you
wear this because I don't want to see
your legs
I'm so sorry but I can't I can't look at
it
actually looks kind of cool
flip-flops yeah
yeah flip-flops
not bad okay and then we got the cold
weather
cold weather
[Music]
I feel like she would be the type of
person if it's cold she wanna she really
wants to wear clothes that really really
warm her up she doesn't really give a
[\h__\h] about what they look like
even if it's uh not not so flattering
[Music]
you don't know
kind of kind of edgy though at the same
time she's chill but still like edgy
like f effortlessly edgy
sounds accurate yeah like if I look at
her bunker it's just the the most
efficient way to
always is it really efficient I mean
she's at least like
um how to describe that she's taking
good care of herself
she has everything she needs
more than enough of it
so if I think about that if I think
about her clothes
then I don't know she seems like the
type of person who just wants to warm
herself up in winter
[Music]
so I'm drinking my pineapple juice
and
oh yeah oh yeah she would definitely
love some Pockets she wants those
pockets but we need to give her a hat
Hat Time
[Music]
hmm
actually that would be so cute just a
simple yes
I like those kind of hats in winter time
hmm besides berets
okay
wait a second are your eyes her eyes
change somewhere at some point why
how
wait does that did that happen for the
others as well every time I changed the
outfit
yes it did that's so annoying wait how
do I apply to I think there was a way to
apply it to all the other outfits
right
[Music]
how do I does anyone know where are my
Sims gurus
[Music]
we're at my Sims gurus
ah
yeah I thought there was
makeup doesn't carry that's so annoying
oh my God because how the hell am I ever
gonna find all those things again
Oh no you're not gonna make me do that
huh are you gonna
oh that's triggering
that triggers me
real oh my God
oh God
I don't have it oh cheese
nah I'm not gonna do this for every
single no I'm not gonna do that I'm not
gonna do that I'm not gonna do that I'm
not gonna do that but here you can have
this while I'm here
where are the eyes though here
those those are not the correct eyes are
these are these might be them
um nope those are by their eyes okay
whatever you're looking like this now
that is unfortunate I might do that
Upstream yeah I mean those dye color is
pretty accurate anyway even with this
basic look from Sims
okay I think
we're done look at her
oh
okay cronies aspiration is what you guys
gotta help me there I don't know her
that well
what's her aspiration here
oh
be happy
[Music]
Perfection dude it's that's just not a
choice You Gotta Give me something
that's here a choice be happy
but
why is why is there a be happy Choice
what do you mean
to be happy what what is it why
haha
Fortune
popularity
popular
really
think so
[Music]
um
wait if she would want to be that
popular I don't think she would want to
um
make a bunker like that and hide herself
honestly no
talk about it think about it nature
Destroyer
is that a thing
outdoor enthusiast hmm
she just wants to be happy is that
something she says all the time or why
why is that and then maybe I don't know
love
is she romantic
kind of feels like she's secretly a
romantic
story nature
all because of fun oh come on
she loves herself oh she wants to be
happy
family there's no just being happy
that's isn't that every human being's
aspiration being happy
Wellness works best really
self-care specialist system wants to
make it big with monetizing Wellness
activities Oh no inner peace the sinless
on a quest to achieve inner peace
although true Harmony is sometimes a
fufumeral what what's important is
developing tools to mitigate negative
that actually sounds good I guess that
sounds the most like being happy
okay okay okay you guys agreeing good
um I don't care about these that much
except for activity
[Music]
um
what do you guys say about activities
for her
Gaming Minecraft every day
silly Yips barter inbox
there's the Minecraft book we chose
video gaming cleaning is there cleaning
cleaning
cleaning I see gardening but no cleaning
handiness
oh that makes sense interesting we're
getting some really interesting Sims
here
singing
gaming mixing comedy comedy really
comedy
really
all right I'll be rowie Miss Chief silly
yep okay
okay then let's do trains
[Music]
mmm neat
she is
considering the bunkeroni
is she a loner
she alone
[Music]
yeah okay
okay what else
um
we have Art Level Pokemon geek musical
perfectionist okay yeah yeah we got it
neat Lola and perfectionists
she calls herself a villain
self-absorbed real oh [\h__\h] I I don't
wanna
should we change one of these herself
absorbed
to say selfish
on here
these Sims are all about themselves they
can fish for compliments
no keep it switch out Lona
[Music]
when receiving a present it may become
tense when they haven't gotten enough
attention the celebrity Spotlight is
something that generally relish after
all everyone else should love them as
much as they choose
I mean we're trying to I guess
exaggerate all of the girls and stuff
personality and you guys seem to agree I
don't know her that well I don't know
that much at all so I'm gonna I'm Gonna
Leave it to you guys you see your
comments come and stay Perfect all right
okay if you say it I'm okay okay
um
now we're done with her we are now doing
let's do fauna Divas
mokosa fauna
saris
oh we're getting closer I feel like this
like this event two hours now
okay
I have my reference a soft voice
how do I
Betis yes
such a b these don't sound like her at
all
and a prep kid up
if it's a man if winner is this maybe
the closest but she's just two yeah
too energetic
little works aurorba
it's just too energetic what does this
Halloween music
and then
it should be a gentle look
gentle gentle gentle I say there's no
gentle
okay
[Music]
you can do this then okay cute girl and
let's go follow series
we start off with a basic face again
we give her
pale as fox skin
[Music]
and let's do heart hair again first oh
my God wait a second what if we do this
what if we do this
oh I can't get like a light green
but I can I can do this
well they're all on top of a hair full
of flowers is perfect I mean Hello
doesn't get any better than that
that's actually actually so sorry I
think so okay okay
all right then we'll go down I guess
[Music]
okay
um
uh well that was fast and let's go to
the face
let's give
uh
eye color and a leaf
actually she does have earrings and
they're not leaves guys
her earrings actually
are like a sparkle a spark stream Sparks
and a drop like a lot of drop below it
we could try to go super accurate there
hmm
actually The Sims one gets pretty close
see it anyway never mind you don't see
it at all with that hairstyle
unfortunate but okay wait I wanted to
give her the eye color right
uh you can get lashes too pretty lashes
yes
and
oh she also has yellow eyes
all right those are oh that's something
else ah you know what you can keep that
where are the eye colors again
[Music]
not here
oh should we add this too
wait why does it not show up
um
[Music]
ah because maybe because I'm wearing
something else from that category
weird okay
[Music]
where are the eye colors again
makeup makeup must be it
here's some soft soft pretty lips well
she has a beauty mark yeah yeah yeah
yeah true
one second I'll give her the right eye
color
oh
oh I love that that looks beautiful
there's more a little bit more yellow
that's a bit too brown maybe
so pretty
I'm trying to work on your eyes
you know what I'm gonna keep those eyes
because she has a little bit of a great
color graduation in her eyes as well so
how do we do beauty marks is it a makeup
where's it here
cheek scars is skin details
[Music]
what the hell red nose
oh here are some more skin tones we can
oh wait those are those are so much
prettier I didn't realize I had those
oh that was gonna make her green now
it's just [\h__\h] around
oh my God automatically makes it so much
prettier okay Sana come here come here
I'm gonna try to help you I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry for everything
let's see what I can do for you
oh cute but they're so they're so pale
oh I don't have anything
darker than that I think
oh my God
[Music]
ah
I can download some darker ones
later on
because this one's that's the darkest I
got
I think no
what is this
that's also very pale what does that
change
not much
what about this
no
[Music]
oh
nope
I think we have to go back to that
other skin tone for now
where is it
that's that's how much the skin tone
influences the whole look oh my God
oh God
laughs
looks like a freaking yellow but you
know what we can give the others that
that skin tone for now and I'll find I
think I can find the same maker he
probably had more skin tones
[Music]
um tattoos
oh
interesting I didn't even know they had
tattoos here
wait where is the
where did I get that from
it
face ah there it is
skin tones no face no skin details
to get back the let's that's cute
actually no I feel like she almost
looked better before but that's probably
because of all the makeup and all that
[Music]
[Applause]
does that get rid of the
the the whiskers
[Music]
she looks better without that did she
look better before
Kyoto
I mean she I don't know she looked kind
of
um teeth
wait
you want to give her a sharp teeth oh
yeah right let's although they might
have them oh my God
[Music]
oh my God
please do some motions please I need
some motions for me
they're too low
okay you give us some purple left oh
sure oh my God
sorry
do that again
[Music]
oh my God
it's not too bad you think so
I wanted everything more emotions give
me more emotions
oh my gosh and you know what with crony
she already looks so fabulous we don't
have to change that hairstyle uh skin
tone I mean okay anyway continuing fauna
you look beautiful
beauty mark Dell
um here can we combine those
no we can't
[Music]
oh
we can't
we can't combine that skin tone go
around
here
squirrel squirrel squirrel squirrel
squirrel squirrel squirrel squirrel ah
there she is
gummy what what a gummy
and what's better that skin tone or
giving her the beauty mark that we're
never gonna ever notice ever again
because we're gonna be scrolled out huh
what do we want I got a smile okay
skin tone beauty mark beauty mark
skin tone
beauty mark skin tone skin tone
[Music]
really much
oh do I need to do another poll
and what's
more what what should we
prioritize
the beauty mark
or the skin tone
go
go go go
go look at look at her though that looks
so good custom content makes seems so
beautiful
sometimes not always
[Music]
and how's it going 50 50 so far oh dear
she has a small small cute mouth
[Music]
and she always says ooh doesn't she
okay it's 50 50. I don't know what to do
four percent beauty mark one by four
percent
okay okay okay yeah
maybe I can do a scar instead
well
yeah that's not gonna work oh my God
freaking teeth wait but you can combine
freckles
and and this beauty mark I can combine
but this one I can't
oh
yeah that's not fair well what if I what
if I What if I
[Music]
but she still looks cute though
that's okay
what about this one oh
what about this one this one
[Music]
um
well I want to get rid of the
this I added too many things
this
oh
you know what the first time I saw that
it scared me but now I kind of like it
but it just looks too too perfect like
makeup and all that like fauna is more
natural than that right
okay
okay okay
wait where did it go where did the
beauty mark go here it is all right uh
she looks so
she looks very
um
Asian
she's Mother Nature
that you that's very noticeable by the
noticeable butter the flowers on her
head
she turned into an Asian
yeah she's an Asian beauty oh my God
what a beautiful girl
[Music]
um
let me see
[Music]
eye shape she also has kind of droopy
eyes
and soft gentle looking eyes
let me change that
droopy
oh
[Music]
this is this is yandere mode
you you plucked out one piece of grass
from the ground I will destroy you
by their nature does not forget and not
forgive anyone who hurts any green
leaves wherever they are
yummy yummy
[Music]
you're so cute but you don't look like
yourself
you're so cute maybe maybe the eyebrows
is something about the eyebrows perhaps
uh eyebrows don't go there
she has extremely thin eyebrows I just
realized
uh pretty much like that I think she
needs more lashes though she has really
really long lashes
makeup
[Music]
we can make her even more green
oh no that gets rid of the eyes I don't
want that I don't want it then no
no wear eyelashes again those are not
lash those are eyes
oh here
no those are the wrong lashes never mind
[Music]
it
this is so confusing
where did I get those nice eyelashes
before
[Music]
ah was it here here here
yes
we've got some green some green in it
oh the guys raise eyebrow higher yeah
yeah she has them very up high and also
angled differently like that gentle she
looks so
oh my
her haircut was her forehead I know but
I can't do that with a hairstyle there's
not that much Freedom smaller nose
bigger eyes okay she looks so cute huge
small enough
small
also the angle of her mouth should be
more like that
oh
uh how low are her eyes
alone
your eyes
okay what about now
don't make those weird faces just look
normal cute the gentle smile
okay okay
she looks like a cute deer yeah that's
kind of what she is perfect more yellow
and I can't change the color that green
is like this is the only uh green I have
um
sadly
maybe for next time I can get more
custom content though
kind of clothes yeah
yo chill holy cute right
did you see my other ones crony looks
fabulous she looks like a helicopter
[Laughter]
fails so far I need a better hairstyle
because that's the only twin tail
hairstyle wait that's not her actual
outfit
special outfit is this yes
don't you like it it's so cute
and then we have um
[Music]
but also they wanted the space suit I
was I was trying to get her something
proper but they wanted the space suit
now the bay one is pretty perfect
but but I don't know they wanted the
space suit and also it it emphasizes her
nice boing blings
yes
I had a galaxy leggings yeah but I can't
combine the galaxy leggings with that
outfit we would have to change
the whole outfit
I can't do that we can we can try it up
to actually you know what we can do a
second daily outfit
and then we can have the best of both
worlds yo
wait do you do you want to do that
we can try to quickly do uh
uh a second outfit one second
all right
where are the leggings here
um
[Music]
down here space leggings
I wear them oh ah I can't see them
there it is okay
and then what top
can we combine that with unfortunately
there's no NASA shirt why not
anything that looks Spacey
face space
I need space
I need the universe sometimes they have
they have some like completely different
patterns in the extra options
but I would have to go for literally
everything although this yo
haha
it's that's kind of funky very colorful
yes that is Sana
that sun okay
[Music]
you like it it's very funky very
colorful
um
it's good work really
wait but no shoes what the hell why are
you wearing shoes why would you do that
you're barefoot you're one with the
Earth
and but we're gonna call in your little
toenails once again there you go
I love the color palette yeah it
actually works well okay back to fauna
oh cute oh my God actually that outfit
is also cute
she's fashionable from the get-go
okay
where's my reference
uh there it is
okay
what are we gonna give her to wear a
nice nice dress a pretty dress
a nice
pretty dress actually something like
that fits because the dress is very
bright and sparkly
we can do this chill or pink
or
green cloves yeah
some nice flowy green dress
oh what about this
oh
oh wait now now we have that ugly
necklace
this leaves
leaves everywhere more leaves
leaves leaves leaves leaves but I don't
what is that what is that huh
bracelets rings
that thing that I'm looking at
that's I have to click here again and
then here and then go down
necklaces there it is you can make it
can we make it green
no
there's more chaotic than bales
we can also I mean nature is not only
leaves and all that it's also ocean
so we can do that
that's a pretty necklace that fits her
you know what we're going for that yep
yep yep and we're keeping that dress
we're gonna keep that dress she has a
bow tie I know but I want to go for the
bow tie
he Barefoot she is actually she actually
is barefoot
you know what
she will be barefoot and I'm also gonna
paint her toenails each goddamn time
green
actually it's like light blue
is your life boy has this one there we
go
ah by the way we didn't change badonkas
here
I don't know about her booty though I've
never really seen her booty
[Music]
okay
I love it
yeah like a turquoise color are you
looking very closely at her feetsies now
guys
this is the only time you're allowed to
do that
okay we're going for formal formal
formal
yes
a nice pastel
green or a nice pastel pink she has a
lot of pink in her dress
well I guess we'll go with that the more
green the better but what about those
others part of the other no
there we go oh that's better
do we have an apple green apple
somewhere no
she actually has also those nails
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
turquoise
no turquoise green
oh wait that's pretty oh my oh my
God we're doing it guys I guess I'm
gonna paint her nails in the main outfit
too
[Music]
scary a little bit scary what are those
uh-huh those are kind of like too long
[Music]
those are okay oh oh
or more blue I don't know should we go
for more blue
green
I'm gonna go for green
she's one with the nature
okay so we got that now we're going for
sporty
[Music]
what would she wear if she would do
Sports hmm
[Music]
it's fun it's as good as the real thing
I'm glad you think so
[Music]
Jim fauna
good I think oh my God she looks cute
cute in those in those leggings oh my
God
[Music]
oh
this is fun
yoga pants
you gotta give her a yoga as a hobby if
we can do that
um sleepy time I think fauna nature
sleeps naked to be honest
um let's give her a bath rope to imply
she's naked or a bath towel
[Music]
she likes pajamas she said that
really
damn it
how contradicting
[Music]
well I'll give her the bathroom though
she's naked underneath
imagine don't imagine don't
and she she will be one of the things
I'm not gonna paint your toenails every
time after all sorry
and now party time
party
God
[Music]
this is not going that bad actually
we've got some good cloth choices yo
clothing choices
no wait
no shoes nah
you're gonna she's gonna wear shoes yeah
yeah
okay oh
interesting so interesting uh swimsuit I
don't even dislike it
oh wait a second is there a fitting
color for that
we could do green
oh
she could be mermaid
uh green there we go
yeah for this one I am going to paint
your toenails
stand still please
there you go did I do blue buffer
oh did we just call it I think we did
this color
and then hot water
hot sweater
[Music]
what do we have let's go to chops
we did do light blue okie dokie there we
go
mmm
[Music]
I feel like she would just wear one
simple
flowy dress but I didn't really see
something nice so I'm gonna go for
something like
this again green
or maybe just turquoise no I want
something more pink though for once
I like that top for her the previous one
but
I don't like the colors that much
the green is still ugh I want some
softer green tones you know you know
what I'm gonna go maybe for that or what
about this
[Music]
she looks bad what do you mean everyone
was so happy with her now there's people
who said she looks so good are you
trying to do a better job go install
Sims 4 right now I'm not sponsored but
do it
do it better then
sometimes it's pretty difficult to make
Sims look good
[Music]
I think she looks cute I don't know what
your issue is
on the pants yeah
oh that's kind of cute
in the hot weather she can wear no shoes
again
foreign
[Music]
sport has been around for a long time
but they have yet to add antlers I'm
sorry don't complain to me about them
and what I was gonna do a toenails
Santa and phone are toenail Buddies
and naked feet buddies what is that
that's actually
that's that's for cold weather and it's
actually kind of cute I don't know it's
funky but it's cute
it looks good on her
I don't know why
[Music]
hmm
keep it
looks good that's a weird outfit yeah
looks cute isn't it
[Music]
uh shoes though shoes is a difficult
thing here
[Music]
keep it oh maybe these they're a good
shape and oh there's a green color oh
she's so green
so great for red
rat green green green
blue turquoise green green blue green
[Music]
good job let's go on and let's move on
wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh no sorry I think I don't know that's
her main outfit okay okay Okay so
nature obviously
freelance botanist oh this thing wants
to grow plants and become an expert
gardener
potions out there enthusiasts and uh
fishing okay so either I would say
outdoor Enthusiast or freelance botanist
what do you think
oh yeah their eyes they change with the
other outfits and it's a pain in the ass
to adjust so we're gonna go with this
for now
botanist yeah it sounds like fun
and colors green
blue
pink white I would say but Laura Colora
yes Colora
um
gardening
probably fishing
does she like cooking
help me
hello Fitness good
Ness Juana is into sports
really I didn't know that at all
did she work out
fauna works out
[Music]
no sports fitness getting raped
she's actually healthy what she's into
the gym what she wants a gym in
Minecraft what she's ripped
goes to the gym
that is impressive I feel like she would
be into Wellness I don't know why oh
Laura
doesn't she like painting I feel like so
many of the council members are into the
painting
am I wrong
phone is buff wow okay
bafana
she's vegan wait really
or are you guys just I don't know adding
that to her character
I think there's like a like a like an
option like that actually somewhere here
I think in the traits
um I think I saw it with a vegetarian
she actually is vegan what what a
[\h__\h] coincidence are you kidding me
[Music]
oh yum yum Apple wait do that again
yummy
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
um next one is loved outdoors I would
say
what do we have she's very very sweet
IE oh wait workout
active
tend to be energized can pump up other
Sims may become upset if they don't
exercise for a period of time
that's I think the one
uh yeah I think so
yeah okay
oh cat lover I can only do three she
does love her cats a lot though should
we get rid of Outdoors because she
already has the freelance botanist
button
and then do cats instead
make your modeling I don't know how to
do that
unless you know what I could give it a
family-oriented trait but she's gonna be
so sad if I don't let her make a family
and then we gotta like get her someone
to make babies with and that's gonna
break everyone's Hearts like that's
going to break the saplings Heights
and
cats over outdoors I know I know I agree
I definitely agree I just don't wanna
put my own personality too much into
funness
remove fishing fishing from the interest
oh this one is not that important I
think but okay
she doesn't like fishing I don't even
know she doesn't like fishing oh we're
not in the dreams be indifferent to it
no we still
get movement is on the way
yeah
I guess let's do
cats instead of Outdoors
[Music]
what else
Doki Doki damn
who's that collector oh
Galactus can find rare Collectibles more
often cool okay
okay oh my God it's been two and a half
hours
oh yeah Hello nice to meet you
[Music]
uh
uh roommate wait I forgot her last name
um
no name
[Music]
mom
hello I'm leaving the chat this is you
now we're gonna try to recreate you here
there's a there's a bird's Voice already
yeah
does that sound like you come before you
cherelle
[Music]
berries
come on Genie larae so baby oh
Delroy the gnarla oh no
that's the voice I think that I gave
Bales but it also fits move me she has a
very high voice
[Music]
he he crowned me have some berries
oh female no the voices don't change uh
like uh doesn't matter
still the same voice
that hairstyle is the same that summer
has that face though you look like
you're so done with this [\h__\h] already
let me let me edit you
get off of a bear face
uh which we have here there we go
we could also give her one of those
um let me get my reference there she is
oh brown hair thank God it's gonna be
easy in Sims
brown hair is so easy
I want to give her that's one of those
nice skin tones that we had baby
hello
um
[Music]
this one this one
oh hard to choose
[Music]
lighter paler
um this this this this one that's tail
very pale
okay I think we'll go with that
oh
I don't think I want to give her lashes
it's gonna make her look too too edgy
she's gonna look like she doesn't wear
much makeup I think
so by the way take off those uh glasses
good
all right I want to do her hair first
hair is oh wait that's the perfect
hairstyle
ta-da
[Music]
way
wonderful and the color is a bit lighter
than that
that's actually maybe the most accurate
[Music]
yep I think that's the most accurate
it's it's a little bit too blonde but
these ones are too dark maybe that one
even this one or that one
or
that one is too bright
this one number one or number two
number one or number two I think number
one
first one
darker two
two really a lot of twos
oh that looks pretty even in the chat
okay we'll go with that then
moment what do you think oh my are you
still here let's let's move it decide
Lemay one or two are you still here one
two one
two one two
I think one mom is still here okay yeah
I think so I think the other one is a
little bit too dark but this one is a
little bit too bright but I think it's
better
yeah yeah okay
I was right with my first uh idea
unfortunately we don't have any feathers
to stick on your head I think
we have this
wait we should have put that on fauna
but she has the flower her hair it
doesn't work together damn
um yeah but oh you know what maybe this
one
[Music]
that ah that stands off so much nah it
could have been so nice
oh well okay
now uh
[Music]
oh see I think these ones actually stay
when I go to the other outfits as well
so that's pretty good so she has brown
eyes
um now these are too basic
oh
this is a little bit too bright in my
opinion
no
I want them a little bit darker
that's so basic
actually these look cute too
and Amber gold
yeah on the bottom like but generally
her eyes are pretty dark on the in the
in the top area
mmm
these work
but those are the basic ones
[Music]
bottom red these ones
that's a bit too yellow no
mm-hmm
[Music]
by the way wait wait wait feather
earrings I put them on myself before I
think but we can give them to her oh
yeah all these ones these ones
these ones are nice do we have them in
Brown now we have these in brown yes we
do ah so in exchange for it I'm not
putting them on your head we can put
them on your ears now face shape should
be
um
the earrings are nice right
so your eyes are not so droopy as the
others those are your big eyes
ink
um
[Music]
it's more nice
she has a pretty pretty childish face
it's difficult to recreate
cute
what
wider cheeks
why their cheeks
face is already cute right face looks
pretty cute wait no no no the cheekbones
uh yeah bye
[Music]
it
well here
we go
what cute I don't know if she
knows she's like mermaid though but she
looks cute I want to give her a lower
lashes at least though where were those
lower lashes
um
was it in skin details oh can I combine
yes
simple not too much
very subtle
and I want
um let's see what we can do with the
lips not too much
we don't want to do too much oh
Mommy
adorable
a bit rounder yeah I know what you mean
that like the in order to make it look a
little bit more childish I feel like she
needs to look a little bit more rounder
um
oh I think I did it
[Music]
look before after
before after
um
okay I'm happy what they're laughing I
think because we're lacking time we
already should go into clothes
oh
no
can we find something that evil looks
like her actual outfit or something that
she would casually wear now we have the
actual movement with us in the chat so
she could she could choose herself
whoa what
that looks like a long version of her
outfit
oh my God
or this one
hey I want Kiara to be my stylist oh
leave it to me
if I just follow that one oh I want a
short average
version I don't think there is a shorter
version
this one would look so cute on her
though I don't know do we want to go for
like you know recreating the OG outfit
or do we want to go for casual
because this one looks
like
right
the long dress okay let's do a poll and
um
which one
and OG outfit Recreation or
um casual mummy
go help me out here chat
oh it looks so cute oh she looks so cute
she looks so cute so cute
so this would be the the Casual one
maybe
because I'm in love or or even this one
also oh my God oh my God or even this
one or that one
ah
the Paul is looking
yeah we could use that dress and maybe
in the party
um
we can do both yeah that is right okay
let's try to do both
then this is one outfit and then the
second one is
this one oh my mine done
Paul is over
different shoes though
mermaid shoes
cute cute cute
do you want some socks mommy oops do you
want some socks
socks socks
[Music]
songs oh those are different oh oh oh
oh what do you think guys
socks are no socks
[Music]
they could be red I should like that
yes yes sucks okay
I got you I got you okay I'm happy I'm
ready
okay next one is the formal attire
[Music]
for my mermaid
what do we do oh man you would look so
nice with that
foreign
do you even lift
oh
clever I think she doesn't lift much
elegant yeah alligators oh
you're looking fabulous
looking like Taylor Swift at the Grammys
I think I won I lift Spirits oh I don't
think they're very heavy though that
sounds really lightweighted
I think I think we we need this one yes
yes yes
this is the Grammys who is this
I wish they would carry over the
accessories for everything but at least
just keeping the eyes this time
that's something okay sporty sporty
attire I feel like mummy would just
really wear a simple t-shirt or
or a Parker or something like that but
probably just a simple t-shirt not even
not even crap
nah I think mommy keeps it simple
a simple
[Music]
they don't really have what I'm looking
for
even though I'm just looking for a
simple t-shirt you know what you can
wear
um
yeah
yes
what kind of pants though this movie
wear yoga pants
or short pants like that whoa
[Music]
put some pants on my asses
it was her choice to go out pant less
before
[Music]
yoga No Pants
Ben 10 no
she must wear pants she's say so Bob
that actually
is like the same color and you know what
I don't dislike it we're going nude here
if you squint then she's naked and then
you dream of no pants has come true
congratulations hope you're happy
super brown so like fauna was just too
much green the movement is gonna be very
much Brown
but I think I think we can try to mix in
some other colors here and there all
right sleep well mommy do you sleep
naked or do you wear something
this would be cute so simple I think
Mommy goes like simple
[Music]
wait did Mommy say something that I
missed
up
oh she's looking respectfully
or she's trying to squint no naked yeah
no no no just nude clothes no no no not
squinty she doesn't allow squinting
do you mean you don't sleep naked
okay
this this I think roommate likes cute
slippers women likes cute stuff probably
definitely you know what I've kept her
too simple
okay for for sports attire that's fine
but now we gotta go a bit more cute
mommy likes cute stuff this is party
outfit party party
[Music]
I look cute
cute ume outfit
[Music]
a cute dress
Metal Head Metal stuff it's really all
right she's a she has a very conflicting
uh list of interests
oh
man what happened to your what happened
what happened what happened
I did not allow you to do that also what
happened with your lashes what what
[Music]
I don't want to remove everything but
what did you do
hmm
where did you get those lashes from
[Music]
oh she didn't I just didn't hit the same
here no
oh
[Music]
no
oh you can't keep those earrings but
where did those come from
how do I get rid of them
[Music]
I don't know your eyes
no I don't know where that comes from
all right we're probably won't see much
of that anyway
move
I should join baby metal Louie do you
know baby metal I really recommend it to
you
I uh she has way too broad shoulders to
go
Babymetal big recommend from my side
you know what this dress said I I gave
my sim before
would look cute on mermaid too but I
don't know if that's a party dress
not really huh
[Music]
cute cute woman edgy mermaid
metal mermaid not really that's more a
Gothic Lemay
me
[Music]
We're Cute here we get some pastel
colors
well my culture did nobody say she knows
squirrel squirrel squirrel squirrel ah
say yes
oh
what happened to the music oh I tapped
out
color do we choose
and green blue this this blue Maybe
maybe black
black or white
I think I'll go for white
[Music]
I have a feeling like I'm completely
getting her wrong right now her style
what she would normally go for black
okay
um
what what do what shoes do we give her
those are cute those are cute those are
cute
hmm
maybe maybe oops no under maybe
stockings
[Music]
ripped stockings yeah just normal ones
that's not a party outfit though is it
um oh well
who knows who knows how mummy goes to
party
[Music]
ripped
a nurse nurse
kind of works gives Taylor Swift vibes
striped socks for the previous one
uh wait a second do we have strep
stripes
you know what these are cute I know you
probably meant straps the other way
around but I like this
[Music]
um
The Ripped stockings
nah they don't look good
[Music]
I'm still wearing those socks by the way
I could also do this no I don't know
yeah she has feather earrings earlier
but then I don't know add those to every
goddamn single outfit
change the top I don't know this is an
outfit that like only comes together
you know what we're gonna do this
version of moving have a multi version
of myself too but now this is this is
Mumbai when she went through that face
and she told her mom mama
face
believe me Mommy
this is cute this is cute
this is cute
[Music]
oh
I like this one
this is a cute swimsuit
I like it
one of those fancy bracelets you have
that you can keep them but I don't know
about the I don't know about those
glasses sorry you look cute without them
so I recommend you taking them off you
want those feather earrings back
that's okay I'll give them to you one
second at the earrings there you go
foreign
[Music]
here as well
okie dokie back to hot weather
this is cute mommy looks cute and
everything she wears she can literally
Rock anything
Twitter
hot weather now that's too warm
um mummy you want to wear a swimsuit
outside when it's hot
honestly she would probably when it's
too hot maybe she's like I I just wanna
I just don't want to sweat so she goes
outside with no clothes at all or she
forgets to put on clothes I forgot to
put on clothes that's
maybe she forgot
maybe we'll cope with that that will be
muma's weird thing in Sims whenever it's
hot she's just naked almost
okay no choice for mermaid
and now warm clothes warm clothes for
cold weather
and this time she definitely don't
forgot because the moment she steps out
and she's naked she would be freezing
her ass off
we don't want that to happen
um
that's kind of
[Music]
wait
what are those pants I don't like them I
want her to wear
even in winter time I want her to wear a
cute skirt with some nice warm stockings
yes yes yes
I understand everything don't worry
I get you
let's get her a cute looking skirt
hmm
I love that script but I don't know is
is it clashing with the other patterns
is it clashing where my fashionistas at
in the chat
this Plus
some warm and cozy even more patterns
nah not too many patterns it's too much
that's too much is it clashing
are those those tights are cute
[Music]
oh my God she can be like Christmas
themed
wait that's kind of dorky I love it
oh that's what the skirt looks like huh
ah
oh my God you're a Christmas elf
[Music]
you know what that's I don't know I like
movie like this
if she would show up in front of me like
this I would be like well maybe you're
looking hella cute
you're looking extremely adorable owl
elf girl nerdy Christmas Malay yeah
and those bootsies they're tiny boots
[Music]
women do you like Uggs I'm not gonna
judge you because I do like Uggs
wait I could I call you I could give you
some Uggs if you wanted
you're Uggs
comfy like Uggs are so comfy
she's she's a mistletoe oh yeah she's
gonna be in partner look with Iris
because I'm gonna give Iris a Christmas
Santa outfit
she can rock anything yeah I agree
you know what she's gonna wear UGGs
because it's comfy
you want some gloves
gotta keep mermaid warm those gloves
look like they're literally painted onto
your skin
what what the hell was that
um I don't like those gloves
no gloves it is okay but we're done with
the cloves she looks so cute I'm in love
look
we're that outfit
oh
traveler mode
casual mode
adorable Okay so
knowledge
dad
is supposedly what she's all about
but she doesn't know a lot does she
[Music]
but if we go lower wise then she should
be knowledge we have a academic we have
Renaissance the Sim wants to be good at
many things at once
computer with no brain
um
attend University and learn
spell craft and sorcery
academic
learn she wants to learn
I she probably does really want to learn
renaissance renaissance
Renaissance him
which one
no Berry aspiration sad oh there's a
food aspiration
close enough
she forgets a lot she wants to remember
oh okay I I think there's not much
difference we're just gonna go with this
one and colors brown pink
Orange
I don't know what's your favorite color
movie
oh rochi let me know what your favorite
color is
black black and red
chat says black
[Music]
oh she forgets her favorite
um Berry red
good
oh
beautiful maybe she's gone
[Music]
tell tell me if I miss uh if I missed a
reply but I think she's gone okay so
traitsu
umiz traits I need your help guys
this is difficult to choose
geek book one our odd level she likes
drawing a lot
she also likes burps and animals
goofball
forgetful is there a trait to be
forgetful musician clumsy clumsy
music
yeah there's clumsy
they're forgetful
no
I don't see anything that says she's
forgetful
Outdoors
absent-minded was their absent-minded
[Music]
um
I guess the game forgot to end it haha
clumsy and these ah wait this one
these Sims tend to fail more often than
physical activities and tend to laugh at
failure instead of becoming upset
hmm that doesn't say it's forgetful but
it's good enough
lazy Maniac slop neat squeamish
shallow the ocean ambitious adventurous
[Music]
she's not evil no woman is not evil
maniac
these Sims don't mind borrowing things
from others with a simple swipe but look
at tens when they have not swiped
anything in a while
quite seemed like her she is evil she's
not
mom
you you guys only say that now because
she's gone if she was still here you
wouldn't have the courage to say that in
front of her
[Music]
she's been more evil recently
in their streams she did steal in
Minecraft
adventurous
that last creative though she is
creative
she draws a lot we haven't oh no we gave
her out leather
this but this is more like about viewing
works of art and admire art and discuss
art
should we exchange that for creative
and give her
another one
[Music]
because I think that one is a bit more
Broad and I like that
geek music music
[Music]
I don't know about the live stream I'm
gonna give it Adventures whatever
I guess it suits her I guess it suits
her whole lore and all that okay that's
that's uh all of uh cancel
we got one more oh you know what we
could make the we could make Iris into a
to a cultist but we only have alien
mermaid and spell costume
should we make Iris into a spell costume
[Music]
oh I've never made a spell castle before
I don't even know how they work
spell because let's do it because it
might be fun yeah she can mess around
with Council try to kill them or
something
okay Iris what's your voice like what
the shoes
[Music]
Samba
quiver reginu
the real robot the news a Canad
pomerate Quest
a lava that's a drawing wait that's not
like her that's not exactly her okay
Iris wait does Iris have a last name
he doesn't does she I already are you
why are you ready
I can't write her name again
like this was it like this
Iris Iris Iris Hope oh we can give a
last name hope
good idea thank you
and I think this is correct yeah okay
and now now you walk
like
oh Dad
I think the first one was fine
because those hands look like the way
her hands are always positioned
okay
starting up as always with a basic face
let me get my reference to
super super glue
Iris
[Music]
okay that shall be your name
is this makeup something I can take off
or does that belong to occult Sims
Islander
[Music]
oh wait no no we're looking for skin
tones here
[Music]
oh you know what I think this skin tone
suits her a lot because of the art style
that she's drawn in
hmm
what's the darkest one I got because
she's also
a little bit tan
that one maybe
she's a little bit too pale yeah we got
that problem
we got that problem
I mean in that case we can do um
get rid of that again
skin tones you can choose from here
uh maybe this
a bit too red
that one maybe
and then eyes oh she has two different
eyes wait can I even do that in Sims
[Music]
is that even a thing
uh
[Music]
I think that's
not possible
is it my accessories no
makeup
face
scars faces skin
skin details
head over chromium
only with CC yeah oof I'm gonna have to
do that with CC later on then
who's done oh I like eyelashes oh she
has she has pretty eyelashes let's give
her some nice ones
yeah yeah
that works I guess
okay then for now should we give her the
the blue eyes or the pinkish eyes
[Music]
ooh for now
she has kind of like purple pink
[Music]
pink the pink ones
I have a good color here this one maybe
that's a bit purple
or just one maybe these ones
they are they're a bit too bright
perhaps but okay
so hairstyle let's get that out of the
way
long long long long long long long long
long long
messy hair
it's all tangled up we have that nope we
don't uh oh just gonna do so much Magic
all the time oh this one this one is the
longest I got I think but uh color
yeah she doesn't
her hair doesn't get brighter at the
bottom but
[Music]
um
ah we have them in one color as well
okay
um
color might be good looks a little bit
too red but I think it's the closest
[Music]
she has like
purple or reddish hair one second let's
put it against some different cloves
because
yeah yeah if I look at it like
that I think it seems okay works good
it's getting there the hair does
actually have has a degree what do you
mean
red wine color yeah yeah okay
now let's work on her face and her
eyebrows match hair yes can we even do
that nope apparently not but that color
matches
Finn
and small eyebrows
and they're very up high actually
good like that
but that doesn't mean that it's gonna
look good if I recreate that in Sims so
I want to change the angle
I think the hair is in the way I can't
move it properly there we go maybe here
no
no no
really
[Music]
that's weird
I don't like the shape of this
maybe with different eyebrows it looks
better
I was staring in at my soul
don't let her look for too long she's
gonna take over your soul
and snatch it and then eat it
[Music]
I where did the eyebrows go there
oh God
you know what I think this is not even
make up the Yellow Part around their
eyes I think that's
uh part of being in a cult Sim
it looks it looks very freaky right now
maybe we should let her be a normal Sim
after all hmm
[Music]
what about this one
detail edit
uh
oh very difficult to recreate her it is
makeup really let me see I want to get
rid of it
make up here
up here eyeliner
no
[Music]
nope
spark wait that kind of
matches the stuff the sparkles on top of
her head
she looks like a crazy lady that will
tell you about your future though
it looks cute though doesn't it
skin detail
oh
it doesn't
look
like it
um
[Music]
is it here no is it here
no
is it here
no oh I wonder if we can change the
shape of your ears probably not
because I don't even see them
[Music]
and I don't know how to change that
yellow [\h__\h] at
see that I changed it that was what it
was okay okay okay
holy [\h__\h] those eyes are too bright
though
they freaked me out
okay her her normal face shape is a
little bit like
always pouting or like unsure she has a
very unsure look
if you know what I mean at least at the
basic art that I'm looking at right now
her concept art she looks very unsure
not quite like that
um
her mouth normally it would always be
open
hmm
at least according to the concept art
[Music]
Iris needs elf ears yeah but they're
getting covered up by the hair so you
wouldn't even notice but I want to give
her a Santa hat
there we go
how you like that hat um
oh baby now we can change it can we
change the ears oh
[\h__\h]
yo now you can see them but can I make
them stick out on the side like more
like nope no they just go there okay
oh
perfect
watch out
you're just gonna kill us all
hope has
descended
she needs a very small and pointy nose
by the way
small pointy small pointy thank you
and
um
oh actually she has a kind of wide face
not only change
with the wideness of the face oh
well that's not what I wanted to do but
actually that's nice too thank you
when I'm at it I'm gonna change the eyes
a bit bigger
okay
scary but she's looking kind of cute
what do you think guys
it's not that bad
she has very big guys
but but
thanks oh yeah right she has fangs I
forgot that
because this is the most fangy we can
get unless we do this and we don't want
that because Bae has that
these is that really
is that really the only [\h__\h] option
huh
the eyes are actually freaking me out a
little bit
they are pretty far apart so I adjusted
down a little bit and now on the eyes
the pupils will be a bit smaller after a
while let me change that
I can't change it there we go
okay
[Music]
whoa I think that looks pretty pretty
good oh look that that was a that was a
nice smile can you give her
heterochromia not only with custom
content and I wasn't prepared for that
um but next time next time
I will go get her hello chromia
eyes
not those teeth and they look so fun I
think
they don't stand out that much they're
like based teeth stand out a lot though
her cheeks look odd
yeah well I think her face shape looks
okay
she needs some pretty lips
yeah oh pretty okay I think we can go
and give her
uh some clothes now
[Music]
wait wait we can give our sexy look at
least
it's a bit better than before she's very
buff what the hell oh
um so this one or that one
huh
sometimes
the other one for winter that's a good
idea okay so this one for normal for
normal days and the other one for winter
good idea okay
I'm watching the Stream
[Music]
s forgive me
do any any other uh
options
I don't know it didn't let me also by
the way this would look beautiful I
guess
I guess that that is probably the best
it kind of reminds me a little bit a
tiny bit over the outfit
what are those shoes though I mean I
don't dislike them
what are those
kind of give you different ones though
at least for the formal wear I'm sorry
Iris
this one's okay oh she looks like a elf
like a Christmas elf perhaps
oh again the Christmas Vibe somehow they
they follow me I can't do anything about
it it's not my choice
it just happens like this
sporty wear by the way
oh iris is um
I think she would wear a top like that I
always did uh ringford Adventure before
didn't she
think
am I remembering that world I think she
did
she kind of is very active I think on
that regard
yeah and I still haven't but that's
because not because I don't like working
out and I do not like working out that
is true but I don't want to do it
because it feels awkward
I I want to do it maybe if I have like a
like maybe in VR
oh wait a second
I was thinking of doing oh my God
I was thinking of doing karaoke with my
wealthy model but what about doing
ringfit adventure with my wealthy model
oh
[Music]
come I didn't think of this before
see that would make so much more sense
then just doing it with this Avatar that
can only move the head basically
free is that possible I mean it should
be I mean
uh I I guess I could maybe like if I
would have to use VR chat I could be in
a green screen room basically and then
green screen myself out and overlap the
the screens and OBS and that should work
if there's no other way then that's at
least the the one way I can think of if
there's no easier way
hmm
the gadgets
um I'm
at money
but ah because like for that VR stuff
you have to wear those you have to carry
those things in your hands right so for
ring for the adventure
I wouldn't really be able to carry uh
the the ring
um that's difficult unless I
somehow attach the hand thingies
in a different way or maybe there's
different trackers for the ends that you
can literally put on your wrists instead
of carrying it with your hands the whole
time
but then I wouldn't be able to like
select anything but I guess while I'm
playing Ringfield Adventure it doesn't
matter
because I'm done selecting stuff
let's definitely something to think
about
sounds like a like a good idea
okay
uh oh wait this is uh sleepy sleepy time
oh wait she's wearing that makeup again
she's been weighing it the whole time
except for this time why why must I
remove it every time girl
why you keep on putting those that
makeup on
why
it is that that's there you go
this one
and there
she really likes makeup
I can't judge her
she looks good I mean even with that
crazy yellow makeup she looks she looks
uh acceptable
wait it's bugging up look at that
okay that was what was happening with
lemay's
why is it bugging out here and when it
wasn't bugging out here what is that
looks like an eyeball is bugging around
that area
what is that
[Music]
maybe some custom content that's like
making issues creating issues
oh well oh my God
that look on Iris
[Music]
um
that's Iris when she lost all [\h__\h]
nasty
[Music]
Iris
this is party look by the way
I don't know what to give you those
pants are kind of cool though
are those
boxer shorts underneath
really up high
shoes
whoops radius oh yeah hopefully when she
last saw her help exactly
[Music]
oh
cute booty pants but not exactly
[Music]
what I think would fit
no I don't like those either
[Music]
I do want to give her shorts with that
though but maybe maybe uh jeans shorts
main outfit
that's about
that's about the same size
if she
bends down
I think you're gonna see her panty color
whoa
wait oh my I don't know if Iris would
wear something like that
what else kind of
damn good like I feel like this is so
hard to pull up like jeans pants like
that are so hard to pull off and realize
but for some reason looks really good of
Iris
stylish
okay swimsuit Iris
before we just spend so much time so I
don't really care that much anymore
[Music]
I'll give you a red swimsuit
flip flops whippy floppy
and then we have Hotwire
Hardware
do we have an even even skimpier uh
Santa outfit
[Music]
wait a second case
like this was even skimpier
[Music]
you know what we're just gonna give her
the same for that nice hat by the way
nice hat
I'm gonna help you out we're gonna give
you this one
but wait oh no this is the look that's
bugging out with the eyes
iris is gonna kill me if she sees the
stream please no one shower
don't watch this your Senpai says don't
watch the stream close your eyes oh
that's so cute
Oh wait we're trying to do a hot weather
um okay you know what I'm gonna keep
that and
then we know already what she's gonna
wear for the
cold weather
we are ready now
okay
[Music]
she's like so mad at me she keeps on
trying to kill me with her magic help me
Lord help me
I'm scared mommy
one more Santa hat uh how about that one
with the
with them although I think that's gonna
mess up the hairstyle the one that I'm
thinking of this one oh no it works we
also have this one oh
oh
I don't know which one which one do you
like guys
oh they're both good
[Music]
hope is about to devour you no
rescue me hope is coming and you should
run away
the the reindeer you know it's range oh
yeah that's enough reindeer oh you're
right
reindeer okay I'll kill we're done I'm
sorry Iris I I'm kind of messed up mess
around with you but I mean look at this
group of people
[Music]
oh my God you scared me Sana
Bales crony
fauna cute
mermaid cute
Irish
okay okay okay wait that's the let me
change too
okay
[Laughter]
um so what will be here aspiration
that's a good question
singing
is that something here uh musical genius
wants to be an expert musician and
songwriter
Maybe
I think that's
the most music
trait okay
music genre she thinks J-pop wears
where's j-pump let's do pump
okay
with the holiday music she loves that
stuff I'm telling you trust me
color red
pepper I think black
huh and activity
where's Christmas
okay now what activities should we
choose for that she likes the most
singing obviously
and
um does she play the piano but I think
it would just even if she doesn't really
play the piano it would just suit her so
let's do it
baking oh
also DJ Iris
we're gonna use our our fantasy here
mischief
really huh I don't know
there's no drinking soda here
but Mixology
very interesting character this iris is
[Music]
okay
okay I think that's good uh oh fishing
doesn't she like fishing at least in
Minecraft
oh my she has a lot of interest
okay traits
[Music]
um anything from here or you guys want
to make her evil don't you you want me
to make her evil probably
foreign
[Music]
yes no yes yes yes
goofball
creative genius romantic is she romantic
[Music]
Cody
hates children
does she has she ever expressed that
before
[Music]
she can she be evil and good at the same
time that's a good question nope she
can't conflicts with evil
I'm trying to be uh as accurate as
possible
and a bit more exaggerated
crazy
why
she needed a baby oh my God I mean come
on
you the baby doesn't mean she hates
children forever
she does it really okay
well then let's take away evil then
because that's already evil in itself
and then we could give her we could give
her bro
um but the music lover we can give her
death
and one more one more
she's addicted to soda I can't do that
here
[Music]
um
clumsy goofball I guess so
she's a little bit of a goofball
[Music]
show you the people yeah well maybe
maybe just it was just in the game she
doesn't hate children in general I'm
pretty sure she doesn't hate children in
general
okay she hits dogs in Minecraft what on
purpose for fun
oh my God the more you guys tell me
about about her the more I am scared
[Music]
evil is better better than hating
children okay oh my God what a character
what character we have created
yep Iris be like
right
so
your name you got it right Iris okay I
think we're done finally it only took me
three and a half hours I don't even know
if I should
maybe I need part two for this series
we're done so far though hello
look at this group of people
oh Father and Iris are being called
together
uh-huh uh-huh
can you give me some more funny poses
what is that
oh all the Australians together in the
middle
like a nice nice uh pairing out here
okay I'll take that wait what no no no
God damn it I need to change that later
on
all right we're gonna choose a place for
them to live in
and the season to start off with I guess
we'll start with fall because we're in
fall right now at least where I live
think is it officially fall already
this family oh my God they look even
crazy I didn't miss when you put them
together like that
and neighbors with myth oh is that even
possible
I kind of want them to live in a
different area though because like I'm
sick of this area
maybe I'll let myth move to a different
house later
um to get them closer
we got some newer areas too by the way
we got a like a vacation spot now and we
got some I think these are all new no
this one is not new
um is this new
oh that looks new there's not much space
here though
what how many bedrooms does that have
and tell me
no no no what
[Music]
you're the best fishing spots in all of
glimmerbrook not to mention the gorgeous
Instagram photos that can be taken from
the nearby Bridge wow okay now I
actually I decided I don't wanna really
give them like a huge ass super amazing
Mansion
um I want to give them a one floor
simple uh apartment house
and will work us ourselves up from there
I don't want to go too crazy on the
cheats
go
Magnolia Promenade windenburg windenburg
is pretty
yeah let's go to Wittenberg
really nice area
do we have like
I think I am
I downloaded them
[Music]
a free bedroom house where did it go
my library
ah I think it's just one
[Music]
this one but this one apparently has no
kitchen so I just wanted to like uh add
that
but wait can I not do it because I'm
missing this one but they actually only
have some plants they only have like
four different plants of that expansion
pack of that stuff pack
damn it
[Music]
um
I want a free bedroom house that doesn't
have like a million stuff in it that I
don't own
you first need to place the household ah
is
that real good and what about we choose
this
uh wait are they
go here and then we place the house
[Music]
10 bucks for four plans no no you get
more from that so that's what's used in
that lot that I downloaded
a lot of nothing congratulations
uh oh God I forgot how to play this game
so how do I place that lot
there goes a belt build
oh my or do I have to get uh go outside
once completely I think maybe
um manage worlds
save and go to manage rolls
[Music]
let's see if I can place it
oh we are in Wittenberg
huh the tiny home residential is now
available in build mode open the lot
info panel and select select a tiny home
residential under Lots type to build a
tiny home yeah you can make like really
really really really tiny homes guys
um I bought this one new as well
oh I don't want to place it right now no
no
so I wanna put a
uh how do I do this build more
[Music]
do I have to place it somewhere else and
then let them move
oh
I wanna place it here I can't now I
don't have enough money today
all right let's uh place it here instead
no
here
on it how does it work
oh
now I can't place anymore am I currently
yes I am currently placing it but
there's no lot that's big enough how
about here ah I can replace it
well then you know what let's live in
the city
get rid of
this one
furnished yes
and then we move over there
we probably need money for that though
yeah gotta cheat it first
building Lots
Hammer Hammer hammer drill drill drill
ding ding ding ding it's done wait
wrapping Mouse one eight one three four
five
okay and now can we like move them or is
that no that's so expensive
120k okay
how do I cheat again
was that well how do I open a cheat
console again
uh chat help I forgot how to open it
it's not shift Ctrl C is it no that's
not an Ava
[Music]
shift ctlc
it's not it's not working
Ctrl shift C
Daryl shift see that's what I'm pushing
that's weird
wait my my chat broke as well Ctrl shift
C
J that wasn't that's literally what I'm
doing
wait really
how to cheat in Sims 4
sit down shift C
eh
what
solve hard problems
it
it's broken enabling options
[Music]
where would that be one second let me
hide the screen for one moment
gameplay
a loud cheek somewhere
I don't see the option anywhere nope
don't wait last time it just worked out
easily
no don't even in in live mode it doesn't
work either
nope Ctrl shift C
oh they're gonna attack oh the first
interactions
greeting itself themselves with kisses
oh sure
I don't even have to do anything look
how cute mommy looks
yeah
we nailed her oh my
now she's like why are you talking to my
moment stop destiny
[Music]
oh so cute I'm getting along fine it
looks like
a joke
[Music]
okay what do I do about you guys money
though
oh how come there's the this not working
uh
Sims 4 cheat box not opening
try using Ctrl and she share it on the
other side of the keyboard or try
pressing Ctrl and Windows button plus c
uh-huh
tutorial Windows button and see that's
not it but on the other side feature
shift and see that doesn't work either
by the way that it shouldn't matter if
I'm in live mode or not nope it
shouldn't
uh CDL shift and ALT or Ctrl alt shift
and seal why the hell would there be so
many options Ctrl alt shift and C that's
not it Ctrl
alt and see nope that's not it
are you using any monsters to see in
your game try to remove them and see if
the game works better
up okay maybe something's bugging right
now
awkward well maybe we can get a cheap
house on this lot
can I do that right now probably not
shall we build a house
[Music]
hold house
instead of placing a room can I place a
whole house please
[Music]
build a house it's gonna take another
million years
keyboard is keyboard correct ah good
question
I changed it no it still doesn't still
doesn't work
nope I I had the language on like a
Japanese keyboard but English but now I
have it on German keyboard and it still
doesn't work
[Music]
quick restart
okay one second
and
nice music
what is this
fancy
oh and open again
normally the custom content shouldn't
like influence the
like the game like that it should not
cause any issues normally
[Music]
okay I'm I'm building it back up
okay yes and load game
and sukuma
we think have you tried turning vsync
off
doesn't the cheat box also work in the
Overworld though because now it's uh on
the overall at least it's not working
there is the game
okay going back in let's see come on
turn off the shaders have you tried
turning it off and on again
no no no no
[Music]
no ah nope nope it's not working no no
maybe we should steal money from the
myth family
[Laughter]
steal money from my family
[Music]
there there was no such option though
about like cheats
okay let's see if we can get a free
bedroom apartment that's cheap enough
for us
uh
well how much money do we have did we
spend already lose money because of
buying this lot
and let me can I move them how do I move
them into a panel
twenty seven thousand a free bedroom
apartment for twenty seven thousand
uh
uh how do I move them
move out household
okay forty thousand well what can we
afford this one two bedrooms
foreign
I want to live on one floor though does
this have one floor
whatever for now we're moving in here
we gotta settle for what we can get I
guess we're playing this for real now
what happened no no no no I have my
family
[Music]
no
huh there they are okay
hard mode
real life vote oh no okay this is what
we're working with elastic residents
okay well I said I wanted it to be not
so easy anymore and this is what I get
for asking for that okay we need at
least more beds
um 13 000 simoleons left
okay
we need a
more beds we can get bunk beds
that also saves space because that's a
current problem bunk double bed
they gotta be friends though in order to
um
sleep in a in a double bed so
okay I can't go for the most expensive
one
energy six this one is decent
okay so we get another bed here that's
one two three four
five
and uh we're gonna bring in one more
here
six
six people can sleep now maybe a second
shower would be nice though
because otherwise we might have issues
in this household
and very experienced when it comes to
Sims 4. it's just been a long time but I
know that with six girls we're gonna
need more than one shower probably and
maybe even one more than one toilet but
we would have to get a separate room for
that because they're not gonna use it
together
pretty sure also we have no TV so
they're gonna get bored probably very
soon
oh
[Music]
we're gonna need to find a way to make
money guys quickly
uh wait where are the TVs there
one TV one cheap ass TV come on fun two
[Music]
fun eight seven
two thousand five hundred
outdoor movie screen
[Music]
wow that's actually pretty cheap for
that
oh my okay fun five fun five fun six
seven
oh that needs to
get the stand oh wait never mind give me
that coffee table
gotta save money okay
we have a TV we have no seating though
in case we wanna sit somewhere and maybe
we can sit by these aisles
uh here bar stools
and they're probably gonna eat on the
sofa too because Sims are like that you
prepare a proper table for them what do
they do they they sit on the sofa or on
the ground to eat
okay there you go
oh my God I already spent half of my
money
ah
oh dear
Bookshop do we have a bookshelf no
we need a bookshelf
there's a bookshelf here
now here a small one is okay eighty
dollars there you go this is enough
and maybe an aisle to make quick money
or art genius Sana Sana can make money
for us quickly
is this the cheapest aisle
easel Isle easel easel easel not aisle
what am I saying
I guess so we're gonna place it outside
though
so she can be inspired
yeah I think all of those six girls they
need to apply for whole life because
they all have no job
problematic cauldron of Excellency every
spell class is dream we do have one
spellcaster
is there a cheaper version of that here
800 Paramount cold I'm excited to see
what you can do with that
yes
okay five thousand we need to leave some
money for our food
we can't get rid of that because we
already have one there and let's get a
PC in here
important things guys priorities
that's the cheapest
and yeah
[Music]
Comfort level one
even this is only comfort level one
it's only about the looks here huh
ridiculous
okay here there you go oops no I didn't
want to buy that
so expensive
I'm struggling with money okay I can't I
can't buy these fancy chairs one day one
day I swear I will be able to provide
for you hope and counsel I'll work hard
for you guys
I'll work hard to provide for you like
my family
I'll do my best
immersive Bend cool what's the cheapest
PC oh God look at that
get the good old days with being
nostalgic here okay I I it's it's my
it's my choice I do this on purpose I
like the Nostalgia about it broke life
good life
okay four thousand five hundred anything
else that could be important
um
oh we can get bikes Transportation oh
what a skis
bikes no
chip a canoe
that's cool
is there anything else we need to
anything else we need to get to make
these people happy we can get Ducks
apparently what
we can spawn ducks and stuff oh my God
that's like the outdoor stuff tadpoles
are they gonna become frogs
oh I need to make a pond
Berry Sushi Berry somewhere a bear is
for Mommy okay
um I can get you berries
a berries
is that is that no oh that's a beautiful
tree
[Music]
you know what
I like this I like it this way we're
gonna start with this shitty apartment
and
we're gonna improve it we're gonna work
hard
and we're gonna Die Hard
berry bushes
with some fantasy oh this one looks like
a berry bush
foreign
I'm getting you a bush
sunflower
okay this is mermaid bush
here
you better make
[Music]
oh this doesn't even cost money wow
totally oh
oh berries on the floor oh wait there
were bushes here
oh well
can we get a pond oh let's get a pond
here's terrain manipulation tools but
okay wait wow what there's no Pond yeah
I want to make a pond
fell too high lower water raise water
wait oh wait ah lower terrain oh
can I put water in there
[Music]
oh how does that look like oh
I made a pond
wait
I'm not done uh
we can put frogs in there oh froggiana
is gonna be part of this wait it's a bit
too deep yeah people gonna die in here
there's gonna be way more monsters in
there than just frogs uh
uh Latin flattened point you know what
race terrain race
oops
somewhere here
I don't know where I am I think now this
way it says okay
only like small brush in the middle
School
oh
get down there
[Music]
how does that look
oh not a hold on oops
are interesting what did I do here
come on
wait I can flatten it too
Latin flatten flat and flat flat
yeah
okay okay okay that should look better
and then around it we can put like
stones
dreaming of water ponds gun
this dark water is filled with Decay and
rot
Mossy water I like the mossy water
leafy water well if you want it
oh
okay
oh my God
watching water
decaying rut
doesn't even look that bad
not bad though
uh fish Fountain decorations
flowers
[Music]
oh
this yay
Lily pants
I'll get your clump
allow fishing wait I can fish here
no way
I need some stones
tackles oh my God oh my God
Mr duck swerve mallard ducks
crocodile
says this is the swamp this is the gator
country
and the wind blows hard and the sky is
black back swimming
he's too big
you're too big I need to make my point
bigger
[Music]
everything for Mr Duck's well also maybe
uh that thing should shouldn't have been
there maybe it's in the way
I can't put my
stuff crocodile no
uh
[Music]
I'm surprised this doesn't cost money
okay
how about this now
what's in this part
[Music]
okay
is it big enough for my duck now
[Music]
no
wait what if I
um
go
I don't see it anymore didn't I place
like a big
tree inside
this thing here it disappeared
[Music]
actually you know what no I wanna I
wanna get the mother my large ducks that
sounds like I'm getting more than one
duck
crocodile
could put a crocodile there
do you think the crocodile will eat the
duck
we need to move the Ducks Maybe
[Music]
but it seems like they have their own
territory oh my God
crocodile versus Superman stand by who's
gonna win didn't show down
oh my God
what else can I put country fish
how much space do you need
a country fish oh
unidentified submerged object what's
that mesmerizing light it seems alien in
nature what
[Music]
oh my God this is exciting
well I want to see how it looks like now
[Music]
it was almost don't even they're not
real they're fit are they supposed to be
real where's my crocodile
blurry where's my crocodile
ducks I see the fish though
where are my tadpoles are they gonna
become frogs
where's the crocodile have the Ducks
already eaten the crocodile
[Laughter]
anyway okay
well oh oh they all go to the TV
immediately okay we need to get Sana to
draw though because we need money
immediately as as fast as possible here
figure painting no way that's too
expensive
uh classic painting oh but they're all
expensive let's start with a small one
then go go go go go go Sana what's corny
doing
she's gone
yeah she's gonna fight the alligator
alive
I'm so powerful
don't overestimate yourself lady
it's gonna kill you it's gonna come for
you hahaha
I was having fun so
yeah
I'm not scared nothing scares crony
[Laughter]
oh my God it's coming for the Subarus
oh oh it's going down
this is so stupidly unrealistic
okay she had her fun she made the
crocodile come out thanks to her we saw
it uh-huh okay we need someone to learn
how to cook was there anyone who can
cook
like who has cooking as their interests
we'll wait has no skills although you
have any interest Renaissance ah she
wants to read books anyway so you're
gonna learn how to cook
and read we have a cooking book no oh
dear
uh purchase books
uh skills
baking ah Sana will wanna try to bake at
some point but that's good cooking one
and that's gonna be good enough for now
we don't want to start today
we're finally playing the game by the
way
I don't think it's gonna be much longer
though uh maybe one more half hour uh
weren't you about to buy a book oh yeah
but did you uh you have it in your
inventory
open
go move it
I rely on youth
how's the painting going
nice nice nice nice nice
crony is playing Minecraft
she immediately leaves the whole party
uh after angering an alligator and is
now playing Minecraft
[Music]
and what is she actually doing
browsing web I know what you're doing
you can't fool me Sana
nice drawing like that's instantly
looking so good
sell that [\h__\h] sell it
it's gorgeous now
um it might be a little bit intimidating
to draw when there's an alligator
looking at you
but do your best fighter
draw another one never stop
so what are we doing here um Waffa tub
fauna can you do anything that will help
us
you can collect stuff
wait oh wait wait crony crony no not
chronic Iris Iris was the the magical
one oh she looked back in Jesus
even vegetarian safe oh yeah right we
gotta be careful because fauna is
vegetarian if we cook something we gotta
make something vegetarian too
[Music]
much
she wants to read while standing okay
she could even sit on the bed if she
wanted to
um I guess we'll cook mac and cheese for
later if anyone wants to eat
go Iris I hope she can't start a fire in
The Cauldron when she cooks mac and
cheese oh dear father
defense skill by literally just standing
up from the couch
that's a lot of mac and cheese
I want to see what she can do with her
magical Pals though
um
how about fun I'll just some exercises
here do push-ups go go find out
mmm yum yum yum yum
oh mommy is done reading excuse me did
you learn how to cook yet
she did is that all you can learn from
this one
can you get up to level two with that
one
what a spoon man
oh I don't think she's learning anymore
oh well
better read over it before you forget
about it again mummy don't forget how to
cook don't start a fireplace
a song
finally do another one
do sit-ups come on
no TV
how's the mac and cheese going
uh how's the art going oh she stopped oh
she throws something
[Music]
she's actually being social
uh let's
draw another one oh no no wait wait I'm
fine I'm on fauna I'm on fauna I don't
want to be on fauna
and oh she's inspired
that's so large one
oh
geez everyone can grab a serving if they
wanted to wait toilet toilet wait we
don't have a toilet okay okay
then number one prank toilet oh she can
do a toilet
oh no
uh anyone hungry yet no okay then the
mac and cheese will have to wait
who are those people they brought free
food oh yeah fruitcake fruitcake we
shall take that Bae please take The
Fruitcake off of this lady don't invite
them in the how do we do this
I think will they eventually just leave
it on the ground also who left just now
crocodiles
always hate the crocodile yeah
she's she's so cute I I want to marry
her
Sims fauna I will marry you
[Music]
[Applause]
tribal dorms she's not hurting nature
hopefully
what just happened
maybe next time
give me The Fruitcake
Lucas yeah
they look so good together so they could
be besties
foreign
get out of here
[Music]
felt crony
how's Minecraft going
play a game blink block
it's the block game wait what does it
look like
what does the block game look like in
Sims
oh
can we get based on privacy oh this is
Minecraft is looking a little bit
different here is this Minecraft on on
not Java Edition
is this what it looks like when you're
not playing Java Edition or what kind of
shaders are those
weird stuff never seen that before
she's trying nature because she's
looking at fauna
wow that's what she sees when she looks
at froggy
look at those two beautiful girls oh my
God
one second I want to test something
oh yeah
okay
never mind just wanted to check
something out
um
please this is a happy household no
Sunny you broke fauna's height
you don't like the sun oh god oh mermaid
don't look at that
I wanna take your cute pictures of them
see what
is
how do I get rid of the interface again
I forgot
civilization versus natural debate who's
gonna win place your bets now
oh my God she's so pretty I can't stop
looking at her
any motion sickness oh God I'm sorry
nature goes to the toilet I thought you
were just gonna go in the pond fauna
is the pot that good enough
anyone hungry for mac and cheese go Iris
go eat some of that mac and cheese
grab serving
grab all servings
what
grab another one
I guess everyone can grab a serving okay
you're not gonna give me that fruitcake
I am
[Music]
not you oh she's gonna also take that
mac and cheese
okay we're gonna Exchange
holy [\h__\h] she grabbed a big serving
there
all right then
oh goodness that's kind of rude
and as I told you they're all gonna sit
on the couch fauna this is just choose
to not sit at all even though there's
one space here
funny what's wrong
oh
would you like to put that down
what's up what's happening
[Laughter]
that's kind of awkward
also everyone was called to eat but
crony
crony you're forgetting to eat you
playing too much of the block game
oh cranny you need to eat
your legs are already done it's getting
yolks
not addicted at all we we I think we
nailed them they're all very accurate in
their actions are you done eating back
to work done
[Music]
wow beautiful
nice good job Bales is feeling flirty
and playful whoa while talking to fauna
that's the ship I never thought of
before
slap him silly was that mean
was that mean where's going from
you gotta slap her silly are you gonna
slap him
is that flirty how's that flirty
slapping someone crazy I mean except
oh that smell like
I found that little pink you like flirty
yes well she didn't dislike it
okay then well I'm gonna pay her back on
that Evan Evangel Evangelion vegetarian
benefits
tell her about being vegetarian she
sure
nice seeing I said I don't know if I can
help you with that nope I like my meat
says Bales she likes salads those
chicken nuggets from
already
who's the most handy who can we trust
with that um
yeah maybe maybe she wants to learn
things right
mama you can do
you can do super glue
that's right oh my God she turned bald
for a moment why are you not drawing
you should be drawing uh you can do so
much more now landscape painting why not
uh did everyone eat by the way also she
needs to go on the toilet soon oh
her thingy looks very different neat
nail fight
feet
that sounds funnily similar to uh what's
it called
nephil film
cool
what did you just pay for after the
painting okay well can we like put that
into the fridge
because I wanna
ah wait maybe we've grabbed all servings
she grabs like a whole huge plate and I
can put it in the fridge definitely
that's it that's a word I didn't know
until uh Iris W that I never heard of
that word before
um well may still repairing toilet okay
there we go
is it in your inventory yes okay I'm
gonna put that in here can you make some
magic now I want to see some magic girl
glimmer still wants down by the way
travel to oh she can go to the magic
Realm
oh
is she gonna make a blow up or what
Go bomb
oh
make a big boom come on
what quite ahead is mermaids acquiring
knowledge nice
some screenshots here yeah
oh neighbor yeah boy don't barf all over
it nope
oh crony
do you need to go to the toilet flinging
fixes movie was born to wield a hat
should she finally Embrace that she
likes handiness
hmm I mean why the hell not I guess she
always liked it she was just forgot
about it
now she remembered
remember I'm so proud of you you
remember it oh you want to go to the
toilet okay maybe if fauna gets out of
here this phone need to pee
oh no okay then then you can go go go go
go go quick before someone else goes in
here sure
is Santa gonna use it Asana has to pee
as well okay yeah we're gonna need a
second toilet eventually go faster Santa
it didn't even go there we go okay
do you guys flush the toilet before you
go in a toilet is that a thing that
humans do
[Music]
maybe someone left something there a
present
[Music]
Michelle
okay are you done can can we get Muma in
here she's gonna pee herself
now she must go
how's it going oh my God
I got everyone
Santa you need to draw you finished
another one oh I wonder whose house that
is she just blocks someone from her
audience
who is that
don't worry I'm selling it so at least
the stream won't see it anymore
selling it so that even more people will
see it
Minecraft house
[Laughter]
let's do a pop art painting large Popeye
okay go go Sana
how much money did you already make for
us well
how fun is that what you doing
yeah
you're not doing anything bad to Nature
no this is just magic nothing bad going
on here trust me it's nubara I'm just
borrowing some of your mushrooms and
some of your leaves
magical herbs and all that putting it
all together throwing in some kfb
chickens what there's KFC chickens in
there
what was your voice it's too late for
these friends it's too late for those
chickens oh bay is an earliest sleep
early sleeper it seems okay we need to
get someone so friendly with another
though that they can sleep in the same
bed
maybe let's try to improve the this this
uh
this relationship here oops let's talk
about fishing zubatube love a zoo oh
because tigers that always gets stuck
yeah it's game strategy that would be
good too it always gets the relationship
up High pretty fast
also gonna go to sleep
it's a bit early but okay final slips
naked as we see
just with a bath rope
oh we're done here apparently I don't
know what she got out of that but I
think like she has this like magical
energy that she has to level up
and then we can buy it
skills and stuff it's like an RPG game
guys
what can you do
I even have any I don't have any but
there's like spell spells that we can
learn
so we gotta get to this level first
whoa Adept Master
virtuoso is the max level
we are about to descend no accent yeah
we're currently descended we gotta go up
there
oh
no
uh I hope they can sleep together
I wonder like because they're not
related they're just in the same
household is that
me
okay we're gonna keep this one almost
oh
well movie will think of it she's
sleeping isn't she
oh Ash is here oh
[Music]
he's a narrow and I did a camera work
again man
I don't remember how this does a fancy
camera stuff
no that's not it
yeah
I'm bonding looking at the stars I wish
I could look at them
I don't see [\h__\h]
tab
I
oh
I don't get lower again
anyone else got some screenshots
oh we're dying of that beautiful should
we keep it or how much is it worth
250. we kind of need the money
yeah but let's frame it
let's put it somewhere
there we go it's movie we have to keep
it so it's a precious precious memory
looks so cute
okay Sana you're done for the day maybe
well you still have energy though oh
impressive
timono pause
reveal Brilliant Invention talk about
space tell her about space
[Music]
who are you talking to
him
mommy you need to learn things let's buy
some more books for you purchase
all the skill books
um
baking charisma
comedy
let's get another cooking book fishing
Fitness
flower oh [\h__\h] she's gonna love
arranging flowers Garden oh we can make
it into a gardener too that would be so
sweet she can like pull her berries
in the in the garden yeah
guitar
handiness
or maybe handiness too would be smarter
because we're already level one
not sure how that works herbalism
logic
okay for now let's get those books
there's already one thousand oh my God
knowledge is expensive it seems
uh let's learn let's start with the
flower arranging what is a flower let's
see if the book can tell you what a
flower is if not then just ask crony
ain't that the truth yeah no it's
freaking expensive man
we should share knowledge for free why
are we keeping knowledge Behind Bars and
behind money huh
what preach it preach attack
well said well said
[Music]
based but okay
it's nice that we made this new family I
think I think was a good choice myth
family is great too but I I also really
like here starting from zero and you
know not being too overpowered because
of the cheats so thank you Game for not
working properly I guess for not letting
me cheat but even if I would have
cheated I wouldn't have um gotten myself
like a mansion or anything I just wanted
a basic three bedroom house nothing more
and nothing more than that
okay you still don't want to sit down
will me sit down
there you go
isn't that comfy huh she forgot to sit
down probably I had to I had to remind
her to sit down dear God this this child
needs so much care
crowny and Sana staying up late looking
at stars beautiful but now they finally
decide to sleep
okay Sana you don't want to sleep she's
actually not even a tire you can draw
another
which drum another painting
a quick one
landscape go
go go
go
is logging out for today
it's fun on coronian mummy
that's a combination I like to see sweet
dreams everyone Sana is working hard to
provide for this family
by themselves I can't imagine like once
you know those skills you would be
pretty op yeah
I think sanas oh
she's reading a flower book
huh
wait a second you want to sell that
okay now testing out if you can sleep
there
oh no she can't oh
iris is pretty much done sleeping though
you can she can't nap on there okay well
you'll deserve to sleep now you work so
hard you're gonna get the big bad
because you worked so hard and you are
big Santa so you need a big bed look at
that butt and those Bubbas you need that
big bed
you deserve it for so many reasons oh
mac and cheese at half past three A.M
that's right eat that mac and cheese
no no
mood what a mood
I don't think I've actually ever eaten
mac and cheese though to be honest like
similar things yes but mac and cheese
like the typical American lion no never
I you guys are shook aren't you
common here right where am I is there
any like Germans and Australians here in
the chat Australians
who can confirm that is really not
common you're not really living yet
mac and cheese is the best
lasagna is so pretty yeah baby
oh wait um well if you're awake then
make some magic show us what you got oh
she wanted to go to the toilet I'm sorry
I'm sorry you can you can go to the
toilet
yes yes
no
uh not really common here yeah yeah yeah
she didn't eat those Foods
Kiara field what happened to the mac and
cheese I I did not eat those Foods no
though I I I'll give it a try someday if
I ever have the opportunity
all right what spooky magic is she gonna
do this time it's going up and up and up
and up here behind me you don't see him
ah this is this is oh good morning
they're early rat catches the mac and
cheese
Iris I literally just like woke up right
now so I have no idea what you're
talking about but with with my rat's
teeth I'm gonna enjoy that mac and
cheese
wait we don't have a sink oh we don't
have a sink here they're gonna use the
bathroom sink all the time you know what
we have earned a little bit of money and
also lost a lot of money so
we can buy a sink
which they're probably not gonna end up
using because they're gonna keep on
going to the bathroom as far as I know
Sims
oh wait that's a bathroom
I want to put that on there
um I can put it here I can I can't put
it why can I not ah wait is that a
washing machine
[Music]
what was that ah
contemporary content it's just a normal
counter why can I not put that on here
hold it
um
oh come I can't put it on there
[Music]
if there's something above
ah that thing
thank you good idea
okay now we can put like a normal sink
on here nice
nice okay
well there you go nice broken again ew
it's disgusting
um
wake up
you're a little you're the plumber of
this family now you're decided that you
like happiness now have you forgotten
already
and see see where she washes the plates
this is typical Sims
um
[Music]
you wanna get up and uh fix the toilet
please
we need someone to fix the toilet
okay
oh wait bails wants to repair it
polishable fashion
it's also broken so
a teamwork oh she moved out of the way
though
oh now fauna is trying to polish it
that's not gonna help ya
need to repair it okay at least it looks
prettier
[Music]
I'm counting on yeah
what was that evil left troll temp
forums you see that on the bottom forums
we all know where she is right now
Iris be trolling oh my God my
notification was full even less than
wait a lot to read that
it sounded funny damn it
damn it
what was the evil lesson what did we
learn
okay how's everyone else doing uh crony
is about to wake up soon and eat
uh Bales used to use the toilet but
instead just because the toilet isn't
working he's playing in the pond you're
you're welcome to um
use this as your toilet I mean I don't
mind no one's looking
Sana worked hard so she's still sleeping
uh fun I would also like to use the
toilet it's
fans
nice
use toilet click oh
I was no get out of here get out of here
check dust level what
we'll make it out of here
privacy please
check check dust level then
oh finally this floor is clean
yeah so there's a there's like a stuff
pack or something like that or like an
expansion where you can
okay where you can have the house become
dirty and all that and also there's a
laundry expansion where you can do
laundry and you have like clothes pile
up everywhere if you buy I think if you
buy a washing machine or something like
that that will Auto automatically happen
or like a a clothing basket or something
like that
um
fit nature yeah
let's learn gardening with May
yes
fauna is waiting for the toilet it's
it's ready now
it is yours to use
Iris you're not busy make magic
you almost level up
um
Papa
[Music]
you ran out here just to talk about the
weather in the iris it's like okay so
what what about it's sunny okay so what
what what are you trying to tell me so
what yeah
flowers can grow
so wonderful
fails what did you do with the toilet
what happened here
oh sentiment gained yeah
you around I really enjoy spending time
with you and I hope you feel that way
about me too
[Music]
she's not that evil Christmas elf look
s
really pure like oh my God
I wish I wish I was as cute as fauna oh
my God she's so cute
love
beautiful
oh
oh she leveled up didn't she huh she got
no Talent point but she is back to the
start of that oh
what's happening
oh
it's like available now but I can't get
it yet
knowledge is Magic Sim reads faster and
does computer research at a faster rate
these interactions also provide magical
experience over time
blender arm potion crafting speed
significantly increased
discharge this SIM can now cause the
discharge which empties spell causes
charge on home incredible forager this
Sim now receives more items when
harvesting magical ingredients in the
magical Realm experiment that when
experimenting and practicing Sim games
experience faster with less failures
cool oh
nice interesting so she's just gonna
keep on doing magic with her little
cauldron
and eventually she'll be like super oval
powered
a good morning crony stayed up all night
playing Minecraft huh good morning
you're gonna eat that mac and cheese all
right you go go enjoy that mac and
cheese that Iris made for all of us
we may already forgot that she was
actually able to cook because she
learned it the other day she forgot
because the mac and cheese was just so
yummy there was no need for it what
did you just do ah you were playing with
the fire down there I thought you were
looking at fauna's panties
oh I see what you're doing now
cabinet
uh Sana is still sleeping I think now
she can get up yeah she was about to get
up
do we have more
mac and cheese
open no more
about the last can we like make some
breakfast have breakfast eggs on toast
mmm
wow that booty Santa doesn't know how to
cook but
you gave up so fast
[Music]
so fast don't let your eggs on toast be
dreams
oh that's cute
mermaid's like
you've got flowers on your head whoa
I demise
ah dear koi oh this is such a great
household I love this oh
Bales is streaming right now oh Bales is
done streaming thank you Bales for the
stream that was wonderful
I enjoyed it a lot
that's a nice voice that radio voice
oh she's done talking mommy don't cry
don't cry we all love you
don't be sad she looks so sad she's like
oh
I forgot where are my berries
fairies are I want to get you some
berries
is there any way I can get berries wait
maybe I can uh can I buy it can I buy
berries
no
I wanna buy berries why is this game
lacking berries
oh yeah
now that she knows how to garden how do
I make use of that skill
Garden origin
outdoor activities
um
well I was done oh
that's for a wedding that's beautiful
wow
bee box the bees
also by the way there is there's like a
you can get a chicken coop
um I think I got the
um fruits vegetables we have berries
I think I got the expansion backpack for
that like I could get a chicken coop but
I don't think I'm mentally ready for
that yet because that's just too
exciting
chickens
I don't see anything for gardening
water Decor outdoor cooking
hmm
ah computer
mainly
can we buy berries on the computer order
[Music]
facial masks crystals
holiday correct okay maybe some berries
seeds
no there's just vegetables we can't
pretend that it's berries catnip herb
pack and oh
interesting let's let's get some more of
those magical plants is that for the
potions I wonder oh wait fruits there
are fruits what the hell I didn't see
okay don't I don't eat those veggies
we gotta save money
fruit
s can be found in an imagery oh
[Music]
wait what inventory don't go here
place in world
oh
well how do I open a seed packet
grapes are grapes grapes called berries
are grapes berries
if you can plant it plant it but it's
grayed out I wonder why do I not have
enough skill
yes they do
a glass
wait what about what about the gardening
book
where did it go there it is
we need to learn gardening probably a
bit more yeah we're not done we still
are on level zero with that one yeah
we'll have a nice day
you paint something money please
yeah
we're so broke guys grape strawberries
all right then we got open
she's learning fast
learning fast why are you learning base
bales
[Music]
why did you just look because she's
clumsy that's so cute
you're not done learning about gardening
though where did that go
where did that go
did she leave it on the ground it's not
in her inventory
what is that
it's showing it
what what is level one now
at what level do I need to be in order
to plant that maybe do I need to place
it in the world and then plant it
sometimes
I like how it stands up like that oh but
maybe
let me put it somewhere else then let me
put it
ah
let me put it back here
and we're gonna plant that
Sparks brainwashing very strong indeed
plant
bae's voice is really similar to her
it's so confusing really
you think so okay let's see what she
does here
berries
oh that didn't last very long that
moment of when you have to water it take
care of your berries mummy you plant
them everywhere and then you just leave
them there to hurt people who run into
them
you can't do that
gotta plant more berries we have berries
everywhere
plants
plant nice plant
s
[Music]
foreign
you see this you see this little owl
planting berries in the ground
this is fascinating David Attenborough
where are you
what it wrong
do you have proof fauna approves I
approve
you're doing that wonderfully moment
I'm so flirty what the hell
is flirty
oh my God doing something good for
nature is turning her on
how about fauna you water those berries
hmm
nope no need mume is on it
oh
how you like that how you like that Bono
yes yes yes more yes what on my feet yes
I will become a big big tree
water me more yes yes
what does uproot plans even mean I don't
know what that means
in season by the way wow this is so cool
there's so many things you can do and
I'm what
why is that broken again
it's broken again
[Music]
what
she gave up it no repair it move me oh
because of Iris oh I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry Iris do we have to shower right
now
[Music]
okay I'm gonna make a separate bathroom
this is otherwise not gonna work out
these ladies are too embarrassed about
being in the same room
[Music]
maybe we can add a finished room how do
we do that again
uh here can we get a toilet only
nice
that proper bathrooms hmm
I'll just uh
wait is this gonna be too expensive
[Music]
okay I think I have to uh how do I make
wall
how do I build in this game again
[Music]
here okay
so let's just add it
here here
and
um
gotta put it on the outside
and I'll pick this color put it here
pick let's see how much this will cost
us
put that there
and now we need a door but uh so we have
two entrances
[Music]
um
why can I not put that there because of
the puddle
um
no
uh let's put the toilets here though
I need the door here it works here okay
nice
and then we could move this
over here
and this and this and now we're missing
some light source I'm gonna put that
here as well
I'm running on the money no no no no no
no this is still doing
fine
we didn't spend that much a window
wonderful
window behind the toilet maybe look here
okay okay okay okay
so we got two showers in here which
actually
ah I guess that doesn't work that well
either because they also can't use those
at the same time huh
if they're so embarrassed about each
other well we'll just have to get them
be
um close up with one another
repeat yourself
hey use that knowledge
baby please get out of here
I know we all need to pee I know I know
no no no
I just prepared that
okay I guess iris is going first because
she has the Senpai privilege she's a
senpai to oh crony excuse me oh well I
mean I mean crony what did you expect
cranny I was gonna
miss about that
privacy invaded Sims don't like having
someone walk in on them she's she's ours
plus one now
oh
I put that there look get out of here
check this level or something like that
mermaid will never be able to go in the
toilet oh no no was embarrassed probably
really has to pee
what now she's embarrassed yep she got
the embarrassed straight
um
yes get out of here go go go go go go go
pee pee like it's been like it's not the
last time in your life that you will pee
yes and now maybe take a shower Iris
sleep please you can you can uh oh [\h__\h]
is that making
hmm
okay movement has been relieved uh
anyone else who needed to pee crony
Maybe
and everyone else's
okay I know I didn't look at the right
trait that was Hunger oh well
[Music]
it's gonna scavengeful Parts but nope
um I I guess I
I don't know Bales well enough
foreign
not at the moment apparently
uh
who did I get that making cheese with I
hear
okay experiment go
wait what oh my God I wanted to play
until 1am but for some reason it's
already 1 20 free how did that happen
the time passed so fast
okay okay we're ending it here
isn't that house a bit too small um
we're being realistic here okay I'm not
I'm not cheating money this is all
all hard worked hard earned money
that looks something uh like I I've seen
before in enough streams in her pose
studies noise
we're saving the game now and I'm gonna
take a I think a three minute two minute
break and then we're gonna read the
super chats uh I hope you enjoyed Sims 4
today I had a lot of fun I think we
spent a lot of time on character
creation today so next time we want to
play a bit more and I don't know when
the next time is going to be but um
leave for another day
um
no it's okay I'll I'll think I'll just
read them now it's okay it's okay
yes yes stop safe
thank you guys for watching
um
I'll be back in two minutes yeah see you
my dear chickens
for everyone who's not staying with a
super chat reading I'll be dancing see
you tomorrow maybe for Wario where I
would gladly have you there thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh
spoby
did I surprise you did I startle you
I'm not sorry
this movie looks kind of small actually
is crying somewhere and I'm not crying
but meowing in the back now
ah thank you for waiting master
you let me make myself smaller I know I
was I was so big you guys were shocked
shook
okay don't cry
so that was fun I had fun I mean I felt
a little bit time pressure during the
character creation but I I wanted to do
um them justice so
I ended up spending so much time on them
oh dear
what's this one
yes okay
bgm there we go this is so quiet maybe a
bit more here
how about no this is the quiet
it happens a lot honestly if I were
playing privately I would have probably
spent even more time
but I need to correct a lot of things I
probably need to find a better skin tone
and I need to find
um
foreign
two different eye color thingy for
custom content for Iris
and a better hairstyle for bang would be
nice the better one I don't think I'll
find one that is just as
amazing as the one that she has but I'll
try and maybe I can find even Mouse ears
oh
[Music]
red is Hector real chromia I'll go
heterochromia character creation is fun
to watch really was it fun for you guys
to watch
I I thought that
I wouldn't take that long so I thought
maybe maximum two hours but it took me
three years and a half hours
I was thinking maybe four hours of
gameplay today but
it took me so long oh man now it has
been five hours
oh well
next time we'll have more proper gaming
and less character creating but
um I think it was a good choice to go
with uh like a shitty apartment we're
gonna keep on improving it from there
and by having a shitty apartment this is
also one of the things that I was
looking forward to
um since we don't have enough toilets or
enough showers and all that uh there's
gonna be like problems like just now
toilets breaking or not enough toilets
to have everyone go in the toilet we're
not enough bed so I gotta buy more beds
but then no money blah blah blah so yeah
grinding your way up this is basically
what Sims is about anyway so it's kind
of boring to start off with a huge ass
mansion
yeah it was a bit too easy last time
like if you have no if you have endless
money in Sims then it makes no sense to
go to work either and and yeah then
where the hell are you playing Sims to
begin with
it's kind of boring
pretty impressed it was that much
customization in the character creation
there used to be in some way they used
to be more character customization and
like Sims 3 for it for example because
you were able to change the color and
the pattern of any clothing piece of
clothing or of the hair of each Strand
and all that uh to your liking like you
had a palette to like not not just like
five colors to choose from but you could
choose any any color
I don't know why the nerfed it
um well it's just it's just a too too
much to implement I guess
um
foreign
I think there was probably also another
reason there's a bunch of things that
they dropped with Sims 4 like in Sims 3
wasn't it also in Sims 3 where it was
kind of like
kind of like open world that wasn't Sims
3 right
like open world as in like you could
um was that in Sims 3
that was Sims 3 right
yeah it was open the world
well with Sims 4
it's wait where's the difference I feel
like in Sims 4 you can also
kind of just
immediately leave you a lot by just
zooming out and going somewhere else no
I'm confused now it's been too long
there there is some difference though
Sims 3 had the best exploration
expansion
walking around visiting the houses
seamlessly yeah that was pretty cool
from Sims 3.
um there's there's
um a lot of things that I didn't like
about Sims 3 where I would always choose
Sims 2 over it but Sims 3 did have some
amazing customization and that open
World stuff that was really really cool
yeah
but it had its issues yeah
um
Sims 4 chose to leave those features out
for a reason I suppose
it is what it is
technical issues is an excuse well I'm
sure they had their reasons
I had I heard rumors since what was
originally supposed to be a multiplayer
RPG but what was changed mid-development
it multiplayer RPG what the [\h__\h] you
mean an mmrpg well I'm glad it wasn't
but who knows I mean I'm sure they're
creating Sims 5 right now maybe that
will be an MMORPG oh no that's literally
just what we talked about the other day
like you didn't say multiplayer right
did you say multiplayer because if Sims
4 Sims if Sims becomes multiplayer we're
all gonna be [\h__\h]
the world the way that we've known it
before will not exist anymore like this
there will be an apocalypse
calling it now
[Music]
we will all suffer and be tortured
imagine imagine Sims becoming an mmrpg
and then whole life members picking up
on it so far so good fun
but then then we're gonna have whole
life members making babies
um with one another and then we're gonna
have them cheating on one another with
others and it's gonna be a huge drama
okay you know what that sounds like fun
that sounds like the drama all around
that would be very interesting from a
streaming point of view
okay that would be fun but then don't
give it to Children if you make Sims
into the ml RPG you're not allowed to
give it to children that's
dangerous
The Real Housewives of Halloween by the
way I started finally yesterday I
started finally uh re-watching
Desperate Housewives for the first time
in a million years and I think this is
also the first time I'm watching it in
the original language English
um
yeah it's been a long time why because I
like I liked it back then and I was like
I wanna watch something new but there's
nothing new that interests me right now
so I want to re-watch something old
and Desperate Housewives I've never
re-watched before so yeah
Singapore Yes actually it's a classic
yes
um
taste continues to be questionable wait
what
[Music]
you guys just
you got it maybe I don't know maybe you
need to consider that I'm a girl okay
Desperate Housewives is not bad okay
it's not bad
it's actually a good shot I would I
would say that it's not even just like
considered from a point of view of a of
a girl that's good but I think from the
point of view of a guy it will also be
good if you give it a chance and I I
mean it might just not be your thing but
it doesn't mean that my chain my taste
is questionable
a bachelor is better than that what the
hell are you talking about I did not
watch The Bachelor but that is for a
reason
you're telling me that the bachelor is
better than Desperate Housewives which
has an actual proper story
and is quite immersive and dope and cool
huh
thank you and intricated intricated
intricated
[Music]
what the hell
you do YouTube
[Music]
I've watched worst shows than Desperate
Housewives so
intricate
[Music]
how is Seinfeld was great too but I
wanted something on the side that's
maybe a little bit more that has a
little bit more depth depth to it
maybe watch new shows well there's stuff
I just said there's nothing that
interests me that catches my interest
right now
like Dawson Creek Dawson's Creek I've
heard of that and that I was like Cena
like like like
um in the like I I know that it was like
around before but I never was interested
in it
and I don't think I will watch that ever
I think when Dawson's Creek was popular
I was too young for it and now I'm too
old for it
[Music]
did you watch Avatar yet well which one
this seems like a familiar question but
which one
yeah Gilmore Girls was amazing I'll
re-watch that maybe next year again
the blue one
not what you mean
you mean cartoon you mean the anime
no I didn't watch that no and I didn't
watch any of them okay so they were the
blue one no no they're not a blue one
it's a cartoon okay okay
chill
cartoonime
imagine watching anything 3D are you
saying you will not watch me when I have
my free DW
y
[Music]
that's that's what your hate against 3D
stuff must stop and take an end
that goes too far
you're not gonna do me the honor and
watch that special super special moment
of me becoming 3D one day
wanna see how management handles my
skirt
um management better not be handling my
skirt the only person who will be
handling my skirt is myself or maybe in
the other myth girls
no one else is handling my script
hands off of me
I got you I knew it you weren't thinking
about that huh
no spots on a guy oh
but what if I am actually wearing spats
underneath that you just don't see it
because I am 2D
what if that's accurate
[Music]
I can see the skirt getting longer I'm
gonna ride it if that happens you guys
eop's new outfit today I tweeted about
it
if his outfit was cute I'm actually now
I'm confused because it doesn't seem
like
it's following any specific theme like I
was thinking because of the silhouette
from uh Lisa that's gonna be like
costume slash Halloween themed but
looking at eovie it just looks like
I don't know a cute outfit but nothing
like a costume
um
foreign
costume is lore related she sent her
outfit wasn't going to be in the same
mood at Muna or as munas or Asus
ah
[Music]
they all just got to choose what they
wanted yeah maybe they just have like no
common theme but just like they all just
did whatever they wanted because at
least
said that she Drew and designed her
outfit herself and then her main artist
like took that design and and recreated
that like she not only got to give ideas
and suggestions no she completely
completely drew it herself like the
whole design
like when when we in myth when we get a
new outfit
we are able to give like ideas
and and like inspiration but we're not
able to completely design the whole
thing
so yeah that is really cool but I think
for like they have this this formal
outfit that's kind of like traditional
inspired right if I remember correctly
for dad as well they had
either an insane amount of input or they
also kind of designed it themselves I
think EFI also designed that one herself
so yeah um I think whole life Indonesia
is just like handling things very
differently
if it did didn't she
yeah she did right and I think well if
you don't have the the
talent or the interest in doing the
whole thing by yourself then probably
like Muna probably just let gave gave
some ideas I'm guessing
and then let the artist do their thing
but I'm having it as an option to design
the whole thing yourself that's pretty
dope
oh yes yes I saw three Disney outfit as
well
super adorable but we've already talked
about it yesterday
[Music]
would you want to design an outfit for
you from zero attention
[Music]
I think
um
I think like for if I were to ever get a
dandel outfit kind of yes
I would like to have as much as con as
much control over that as possible
um for other outfits I think like I'm
mostly fine giving just directions and
hoping that the outcome will be good
um
yeah
yeah for the devil I just wanted to be
authentic and
um yeah just follow certain guidelines
um yeah cause I know how it's supposed
to look and I would I would want to have
full creative control over that but for
other outfits I don't know I think I
think in some way it would be cool but
I I don't really
I feel you know for a god-like okay Papa
it would almost be disrespectful I think
from if I were to say here I drew this
design I want you to turn that into a
life today for me
like almost almost disrespectful
from from like a professional point of
view as well like he's been doing this
job for like a million years it's like
saying yo you you can't you're my papa
but I'm taking this job away from you
now I'm gonna design myself by myself so
your job is done here you just look at
what I designed and you draw that and
put it into an actual form I don't know
I don't know it just feels wrong
um
[Music]
I mean like if I were to really 100
percent
design the whole thing you know but yeah
yeah giving ideas and all that that's
that's how it usually works so all good
all good
way
anyway we're gonna Read Super chats
because it's already freaking late and I
don't want this to
take too long it's like almost 2 A.M
[Music]
by the way tomorrow or today
today I'm going to the doctor
what am I doing today
doctor and gonna do hollow top questions
putting those together and then play
WarioWare
busy day
but today I recorded my my harmonies and
something else for
something secret coming up I think
that's secret yeah is this little secret
I think it's still a secret
with that today
before the Stream
harmonies for the upcoming song cover
and something else secret just small
things though
busy baby
I still didn't fix the thing
I'll try to fix it when I got time
foreign
[Music]
not looking for the verification thank
you thank you
gotta say I respect your decision to not
get verified on Twitter the same way you
uh resisted activating windows for a
long time railroad find the power
yeah yeah yes that's a that's exactly
the reason why I'm not getting verified
on Twitter because I don't want to
yes it's my way of showing resistance
obviously no but that has been happening
uh
uh in a way that I barely noticed it
like out of nowhere like I didn't even
sign up for it
um apparently management has been
signing up for it uh we didn't even have
to do anything
and
whenever it gets declined they sign us
up for it again so I didn't even realize
that I was signed up for it to begin
with
yeah yeah so then suddenly the other
girl started getting verified and I was
like okay that's cool that's cool what
do I have to do and the management was
like no no we already took care of that
where we have you signed up just gotta
wait for it
um and then apparently I didn't even see
the the message but apparently I got
turned down
and meanwhile all of the other myth
Girls by now have the verification mark
on Twitter
just I don't have it
which I I really have to say it's been
happening in the background and I barely
paid attention to it and I I really
didn't care about it
but I think it's funny now that I'm the
only one who doesn't have it
hahaha
that's because I got beef with Twitter
that's the real reason that stupid blue
bird thinks he's something better than I
am he thinks he's been me
always those birds who think they're
cooler than me
I saw her reapplying so many times
yeah I mean I really don't care like
it's just funny now I I didn't realize
for the longest amount of time that this
was even happening
foreign
[Music]
blueberry also wants to be a YouTuber
well you can't beat one there you can't
I also have to have beef with the with
the green bird with the Green Owl
[Music]
um
Netflix already did it ah there was
something like that
burp boys let's go but I feel like
Twitter would team up with Duolingo
so I'm gonna team up with mume but she's
probably gonna forget about the
appointment when we go to war and she's
going to stay at home and be like
was I supposed to do something today and
I'm just gonna stand there alone and
then I'll call kfb like yo I was gonna
do this with mume but I need backup
after all so Carefree where you at
[Music]
hey
um
[Music]
oh thank you for the pinky I got
released from the you are finally free
yeah really
[Music]
huh are you sure you're allowed outside
again
it feels so good to be able to see your
beautiful face again
but question are you slacking on your
regard you seem more fake than usual
haha that's no problem though love you
as you are chubby Joel
[Music]
send me
and before after picture and show me
where exactly I gained weight I couldn't
show me show me where I
changed in appearance
and wait
where do I look like I gain like I
gained some weight show me show me huh I
wanna see
[Music]
yeah
it cuts off there your name is too long
cats
he has really fit body Danke Schoen
what are you guys trying to tell me huh
9 plus 320 Duncan
oh
see I don't I don't like it when people
say goodbye send goodbye super chance
what the hell
good luck I guess
[Music]
why are you guys send good bicep chats
I don't like it
Tiana's unfit body
fit Kiana's Danke Schoen what the hell
enjoy your what the [\h__\h] is
here enjoy our chubby fake unfit girls
Danke Schoen
[Music]
Sarah Dean
you mean extension
and Donna campus Duncan you should go to
the gym Duncan
you guys you guys are
you guys are um
how many people are sending these super
chats it's probably just one or two
people
but it's um
trigger something inside of me
I the person who's telling me to go to
the gym are you even going to the gym
huh you wanna fight
catch me outside how about that huh
use it all thank you for the red super
chat
use another bubbling me
[Music]
punch them use it all please for me do
it for me do it for her
thank you for the red one I appreciate
it thank you thank you thank you thank
you mate
nice that you are here today supporting
me hope you enjoyed the stream thank you
good day went back into the usual room
it seems so well how about you just
freaking stay
then don't come out to bully me
Randall dungeon unit 14.
oh dear time
you had a doctor's appointment are you
done
was it Dr nice
do I need to have a talk with him I'm
very aggressive today it seems jackets
monkey donkey
no I did not accidentally eat a pancake
with maple syrup
no no no
no no no I just uh felt uh
off
Miguel and Lopez
and Ben the hero thank you donkey soon
I'm actually
thank you
whatever Oracle baction
hello all I want to say is I wish I
could make it to everyone's dreams but
me being me being me my ADHD brain can
sit still during them oh that's gonna be
an issue if I stream so long always
sorry but take your time no need to like
stress yourself out about it just say
hello every once in a while and I would
be happy about that hmm
YouTube died for a moment when I said
that really
duck
and this look around thank you for that
huge red Super Chat thank you
oh you enjoy is getting ready to fight
noise
says Kiana care Carefree dying from
toxoplasmosis let's go on
why is kfb dying from it
for this movie and changa's wedding
registry
finally someone who supports me thank
you didn't think you could top your
previous cats related content but this
is glorious by the way Jolly loves the
content concept but sadly she's very
busy and can't do wedding art
commissions oh no
no I'm not gonna do it anytime soon
though um
if any if if I'm gonna do it then I'm
gonna do it maybe in like spring
or like very late very late winter
[Music]
there's a lot of time I'm not stressing
myself about it and and I don't know why
you guys were so much against it but
I think you guys are being a little bit
too dramatic again just let me have fun
for God's sake
you can't manage thank you thank you I
support you supporting me
no you
no you support section
I love that idea catwinning let's go I
love you too I love you loving my idea
I support the cat marriage I support you
supporting me
thank you
yeah it's just something different for
once yeah I just wanna just want to play
around honestly I just see it as a
chance to [\h__\h] around with we are again
no they're not gonna look like catboys
from Neko para no
laughs
I don't know I don't want I don't want
to marry a cat boy also they're girls if
anything they would be cat girls and
that would be cute but no
so yeah this look around thank you
thank you thank you hope you enjoyed the
stream today no cats today unfortunately
uh what was the maximum of family
members eight
I could still add cats to that household
I suppose he
do like if I get a chicken Koopa or like
a like you can also get horses and
llamas and all that stuff there now in
in Sims but that doesn't add to the
household so you can get like endless
chickens oh
I should get like a million chicken
coops with a million chickens
okay now we're talking
[Music]
perps JL thank you for the rest of the
chat
hey kenshaw I recently heard a rimler
about camping members whose punishment
exceeds the usual room by being thrown
into a warm style last month's Last Man
Standing Gladiator battle forced to
battle for your amusement and
entertainment any comments on this rumor
by chance
[Music]
I've never heard of it I do not recall
any such thing
there is no proof and therefore it is
not a thing it does not exist
and who knows how much longer you exist
but that's a different story
I appreciate it thank you so much
I need my translator translator
translator translator
Korean translation
there you go
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah I could give her a suit for formal
that's a good idea
would look very very handsome in that
yeah
um good idea silent blue Danke Schoen
then the hero Duncan
when you're done with the first outfit
you can copy it onto all the other
outfits this will transfer all the
makeup I knew it I knew there was a way
to do it I thought so
[Music]
I see I see
okay now it's too late our 9 000
Channel
hope you're having good neighbors in
addition to recently hitting one year in
your membership this stream has made it
a fun birthday for me
question since you liked Fire Emblem
have you ever heard of Valkyrie
Chronicles or XCOM as I've heard of
valkyria Chronicles I guess
but the x-com one no happy birthday to
you
I hope you enjoyed your birthday by
watching my stream and I hope you ate
some nice food and were able to spend it
with your friends maybe or are going to
spend it with your friends sometime soon
please stay healthy and stay happy
is amazing
Expo
XCOM would be
10 16.
ah by the way I did a members only poll
yesterday the members have probably
already seen it
um
about what series we're gonna play next
the choice
uh
[Music]
uh the choices were
um Ori
and Yakuza 0
and that Zelda game the the the cute one
that has been
remastered on switch remade on switch
now I will eventually make all of them
I can't I don't know what I'm talking
about anymore today I will eventually
play all of them on my channel I think
Link's Awakening yeah that's the one
the waking I I compared the the game
time from that that Google tells me uh
to Skyward Sword and it's so much
shorter I was surprised
so I would I would look forward to that
I want to play it especially because
it's shorter thankfully it's shorter
Yakuza zero is incredibly long again so
yeah
Ori is really really short though but
for Ori and there's a a sequel as well
so even if we finish Ori very quickly we
can always play the sequel
and yeah leave Yakuza for last yeah I
might do that I didn't expect to play a
Zelda game again anytime soon but
um
I was thinking yesterday like what else
there is that I currently really want to
play as a series and
couldn't think of anything else that I
really felt
would be good now
that I also have permissions for you
know
uh
yeah I still don't have FF permissions
only Final Fantasy 14.
and all near games
but I kind of decided to probably to not
play
uh replicant at least not for now
that's Square Enix as well right so yeah
no
the only Square index permissions that
we have currently are ff14 and
the near games
um
so yeah
mosquito
[Music]
ES
uh Nintendo 64 switch online games I
only know those still the ones from like
Mario
which one are you gonna do first Oreo
Zelda I think probably
yeah because
um right now we're taking a little bit
of a break so next week we're also not
gonna start yet
we're probably gonna start in the week
after Halloween
um
yeah
but depending on how well the Alice
uh stream does maybe I will continue
that one as well because we're
definitely not going to finish it in one
stream I suppose
um and for little nightmares we're gonna
play one I suppose and I heard there's
the second part right little nightmares
one two
so we might continue little nightmares
as well
that might be turned into a series as
well I think maybe I don't know how long
it is
but that also depends on I guess the the
feedback from you guys if you like it
who is even scarier is it that scary
it's really short okay
then we might squeeze that in as well
so instead of immediately jumping into
another super long
jrpg I gotta say I'm a little bit
um
not burnt out on it but I do see
currently I see more charm in
in a charmand and
um
merits in playing shorter stealth yeah
and trying out a lot of new things
because because I I really like those
games those long games but right now
there's nothing that I'm like all I want
to play this right away anyway and
um I know that a lot of people
don't like those long series because
it's hard to get into and if you miss
something then blah or if you want to
play the game but you haven't yet then
you don't want to get spoiled or if you
have already played it then it's boring
to you because you already know it and
if you decide if you decide to never
play it because you're just not
interested in a game that you're
probably not going to watch your stream
either
so it really filters out a lot of people
um which is very unfortunate so I'm
gonna try for a little while not forever
but for a little while I'm gonna try to
do some shorter games
and try out some some new things
I will still definitely go back to
playing on jrpg once I see something
that I want to play now
um
yeah
hope you guys are okay with it
but judging from the comments I got
yesterday on that poll you guys seem
very supportive of going for a shorter
game now
[Music]
yes yes okie dokie
I also gotta play Diablo again sometime
soon
yeah
continue and give me your donation
[Music]
Iris said she likes the Santa costume
she just doesn't like the old man
himself so you can put her you can put
her in the Santa costume wow okay
Jesus the Gonza thank you for the red
super chat
hey just wanted to let you know that
you're freaking great thanks for being
you boss
[Music]
thank you Jesus that's very sweet of you
thank you
okay
I needed that
today thank you I appreciate it
[Music]
Zachary gorinsurance
loading
hey
[Music]
did I say your name correctly
I hope I don't trigger you
Jackson FB thank you for the pinky
and hi Kiana sorry I can't superchat as
often as usual but congrats on the new
Sims chapter yeah I'm looking forward to
watching The Hard Mode Shenanigans with
you and his this family big love as
always thank you yeah I think it already
started out great so this family is
really really interesting
um and living on on a really like small
house small area small flat a small lot
makes it a lot easier too to see like
what everyone is doing what's going on
everywhere
um and yeah they have a really original
character so it's been fun
and uh
what was I going to say
I forgot I forgot
[Music]
who all the vlogger please play me oh
don't worry um I I've been thinking
about you you've been on my mind
now there can be a milestone like moving
to a bigger place exactly yeah yeah and
like for for Iris we want to get her and
to be a master of magic yeah
and and Mumbai will be the gardener and
the toilet repairer the plumber
Santa will keep on making that money
with the art and one day she'll have a
gallery or something like that and an
observer top we should buy her the the
thingy which you can use to look into
space what's it called again
uh
I forgot
[Music]
telescope yeah yeah
and wasn't there a rocket that's what I
think there's a rocket in the game as
well like you can build on the rocket
and then fly to space which nothing
happens in the game you just fly out of
the screen and you come back after a
while
that's it but still it's fun I guess
and and fauna can be helping mume with
with the garden and the flowers
and what else can we use fauna for
sweet she's just gorgeous to look at
she's like eye candy
and
Bales I don't know what the hell she's
doing right now she's just jumping
around and in the pond and on trash and
all that
she'll find her summoning soon
oh yes fauna needs to get buffed
yeah and crony keeps on playing the
block game
chaos noises
modeling carrier for fauna
she's doing her best yeah Bales is doing
her best
they're all just doing their best
gym equipment for fun oh yeah we need a
gym equipment it's pretty expensive
though so
one day we'll have a whole gym private
gym for fauna
good morning hello welcome and can't be
shovel show for shove shovel Robot
action sweep dankisha and Benjamin Eng
thank you for the pinky everyone uses
Netflix except Iris uses Ned fill in
aha those Irish jokes
it did make me laugh but I guess it's a
good one
yeah thanks for tuning in today
[Music]
you can almost say Sana is this
households Breadwinner oh my God okay
that's funny that is actually funny for
many reasons
that is a good one sappy copy by that
[Music]
amazing
I should give you another an award for
that
I'm crazy dangashion salubrious beats
thank you thank you
yeah a few minutes of gameplay
no surprise that you made open shelves
given the tweets of couples
James
Blades of this shell thank you nothing
wrong with Desperate Housewives I'm just
glad you aren't watching reality TV yeah
reality TV is not my thing I've never
never tuned into that uh Kardashian
thingy stuff
yeah I don't know
um cool if you're like an enjoyer of
that
but I I don't think I like it
[Music]
foreign when I was younger
um and I was still actively watching TV
when watching TV was still a thing
um I watched big brother every now and
then and I kind of fantasized about
being in that house one day and how I
would do if I'm wearing a Big Brother
house
um but like I kind of liked it back then
it was kind of interesting to see them
live but it was also at the same time
absolutely ridiculous and the people who
were in those big brother houses were
always freaking
stupid annoying obnoxious shallow
not interesting people
yeah and they all seemed fake most of
the time so
uh I don't know I watched it with some a
little amount of interest but I I don't
think I would like it anymore nowadays
I think this big brother even still
exist
[Music]
does that still exist
yeah I always wanted back then that they
were really like random people or if
they're all paid actors it still exists
it still does oh
oh wow I haven't seen that in a million
years
you ever see the real world no
[Music]
it's all a setup
do they didn't even get the money the
actors or is the money reward also fake
foreign
[Music]
here in like German TV they had like
normal Big Brother with Randalls and
also a little big brother left like
famous people as well celebrities
or like they would do it with random
people and then mix in uh a celebrity I
think that was a thing too
yeah
anyway
weird show weird stuff but it just shows
that
as as uh human beings I mean I'm a
phoenix but still I'm just gonna talk
for you guys
are interested in the weirdest things
like there is obviously a demand for
that
and I can totally see how it is
interesting to see other people live
like that's why that's why the
Kardashians are popular although I mean
is that why they are popular I don't
know I guess not I mean but but still
like in some way you're enjoying
watching them because you enjoy watching
other people that's why YouTube is
popular
because we like seeing how other people
live so it makes sense like I I see why
people like big brother I I was
interested in it before too
it just makes sense we want to see how
other people leave live in order to like
validate our our own way of living to be
like okay I've been living life somewhat
okay-ish until now and maybe
validate yourself on uh I I lived my
life maybe even better than that person
until now or I can improve my own life
in some way
by doing that thing that they did oh oh
oh I didn't know that that was a thing
you know stuff like that
sense so I can't judge it at all
this is how this is how Humanity
functions
wow we're getting really deep here
remember remember in the Stone Age when
there were only a few humans living they
had to they had to learn from one
another they had override me and first
of all they had to learn from nothing
but yeah Generations learn from
Generations by looking at them and and
then becoming more knowledgeable
philosophical Phoenix
welcome to Kiara's Ted talk thank you
I was I was I was so much I am but I was
chilling somewhere else I didn't want to
hang with those
humans back down because they acted
really stupid
ridiculous
they were like bonking each other's
heads at one another
and we're like
well I was already like speaking
languages
[Music]
how primitive of them right oh
we still do that though why would you do
it my chickens don't do that
kids don't do that
if anything
foreign
yes I I trust in your intelligence
mume was slacking
[Music]
back to the caves everyone no my my
chickens don't live in caves
no they live in the usual room or in a
coop
[Music]
and where was I
where was I
ah here GD dankishan boohoo723 Duncan
I'm almost done I think I'm refreshing
now in my coaching
[Music]
reality TV
Sunni
foreign
[Music]
was also extremely popular in Japan when
that when that when that happened
holy [\h__\h] that was the most popular
thing ever
[Music]
I think before Tara's house maybe there
was not that much reality TV content in
Japan before so it was like a huge thing
there
[Music]
and watch that evil by the way
foreign
[Music]
an anime recreating like big brother or
something like that acting as if it's
reality TV
foreign
already exists Maybe
feels like something that someone must
have thought of before but maybe it was
not worth actually making it
eh Baron man spanking him thank you for
the rates of a chat I thought big cat
was the only one who wanted to be held
we can't spend the day at the dentist
and small cat wants to be held all day
cat knowledge plus one you cats
are you talking about your own pants
[Music]
what your big cat wasn't a dentist
there's a cat dentist what are you
talking about
who are you talking to there's a cat
dentist
or you just mean a vet
who does well they do everything I guess
I guess that's to him
[Laughter]
are you a cat's tooth all right
foreign
like
um
I uh I had a friend who um
has a family cat and that cat was really
really old
and like you know you know how cats
don't really show that they're in pain
like they could be sick for years and
you don't notice and then one day it
gets really really bad and then it's
probably already too late or or you can
barely fix it but yeah they their cat
like had like really bad teeth
apparently and it caused a lot of pain
over a long time and they they finally
found out about it but it was like
it was it was not too late but it was
like so late to notice it so I think
I wanna
even if I like I hold my cats at home
only I don't let them outside and all
that and they seem healthy and all that
I think a lot of cat owners or pet
owners
um don't go to the vet that much after
going there like like once they are
adults once they're grown up they don't
they don't go to the vet anymore
especially because they they don't show
their pain so you you as the owner
you're like oh my cat must be fun fine
but you should still go to a yearly
checkup I guess so I'm gonna try of
course I'm going to do my best to do
that too to not forget once a year I
mean anyone should be able to do that
bring your pet to the vet once per year
to do like a checkup
[Music]
thank you
movie was already at the Vets this year
for that thing with her ear
yeah and I think yeah they were both
there last year to get vaccinations but
I should go there again actually soon
yeah I gotta do yearly checkups the
finger in the bleach stream yeah yeah
exactly exactly
I should bring chonkers over though I'm
kind of way chonkers chunkers might be
overweight I always try to defend her
and I think I think she's fine like she
was she's always been a little bit more
on the chunky side and the vet never
said anything
she's just pretty chunky but what she
just looks like it she
had a bit of a stomach that you can
pinch and squeeze and grab
a little bit the rest is all this
fluffiness
they look much fitter because they're
long hair and she has a very thick coat
like a layered coat once movies coat is
a bit different actually
primordial pouch what is that maybe that
is that prep what's the prime more than
you do I have that too do humans have
that to Prime more
primordial pouch ones up foreign
cats
whoa
why do cats have belly pouches
fat cats are cute but not every cat that
looks like it has a big belly is
overweight there you go
you heard that although the part of a
cat's Underside that swings when it
walks may look like a dad thing
it's actually not tummy at all so what
is it that bit of skin fur and fat is a
protective layer called the primordial
pouch
is positioned along the
shut up
okay advertisements on this website
and
where was that position along the length
of a cat's belly these patches are
perfectly normal and healthy
all cats have primary pouches but
they're very greatly in size ah
some are almost undetectable yeah I
didn't really notice that with smoothie
to be honest
there are three main for you is why they
have it
they allow cats to move faster it
stretches as the felines run oh or
extra space for storing food
not a little interesting
yeah
well maybe that is that I don't know
I see I see well chonkers might that's
that's just another way of saying that
the cat is fat though if the primordial
pouch is for storing food afterwards
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
well there you go yeah now we know more
uh thank you second time for
making that tangent happen
ing
for the pinky pinky love you just the
way you are hot wings
I love you also but when you are TV
thank you
you are too kind I love you
thank you for the pinky it's more like
when someone loses a lot of weight and
they have extra skin
but chunkers never lost weight
the pinky the the big Pinky the XL Pinky
all right time to throw fish cleanse
your teeth guys
so who decided to five years ago or did
you all right run away were you scared
once you saw use it all I would be
scared
look at that chicken in those boxing
gloves I would be scared too
we're protecting my honor
oh well I mean it was uh pretty close to
a red one so I guess you can get a kiss
diamonds foundation for the pinky to
Mom's membership I am a chicken now oh
you hatched
[Music]
congratulations you look so cute with a
cute little chick
[Music]
was it nice being under my butt for two
months
um
now you can enjoy the Free World
no you're not allowed to come back once
you're out of there you're you're gonna
not allowed to get under my butt anymore
motion
[Music]
it's like you're a moving anime PNG or
something crazy
s17 b32 Duncan
[Music]
the hell
um
oh that was a crazy dream what the hell
delicious pancakes
for the red super chat
a while since I sent a rexable chat and
I felt the need to correct that mistake
it's not a mistake don't don't feel like
obligated please thanks for all the
entertainment you've given us and for
keeping me entertained at my job also
saying that you like Zelda games why not
give Okami a try isn't that another one
of those Square Enix games
I would love to I have it on my switch I
literally bought it you saw it on my
switch before maybe
it's on there it's just waiting to be
played oh that's Capcom
[Music]
wait how do we stand with Capcom I don't
remember
[Music]
Monster Hunter DMC Resident Evil on
Capcom 2.
no streaming the endings ah
really
well I guess I'll check it out
[Music]
thank you for reminding me image singing
yeah we've talked about Okami a bunch of
times before and every time I mention it
you guys are like oh okay
yeah well
I'll have to talk to uh Miu Senpai if
she's okay with doing that collaboration
okie dokie
thank you thank you well the broker
please play me donation
foreign
[Music]
with two people
I feel like I've seen like two two
wolves running around
in-game footage before
I think but maybe it's only local I
single player oh girl okay
[Music]
there's two games
foreign
wanted to collab with Ian but didn't
have the courage to ask you know what
she's so early that she's gonna be asked
by me to join the whole talk so
we're almost done guys
[Music]
I spent all night watching your
broadcast oh dear maybe because I've
been a lake so far I'm slowly having a
headache oh don't worry we're ending now
thank you for watching tonkers the unfit
chunky buddy
is so you guys have no idea
chonkers is so like fluffy and and and
soft if you like grab her and pick her
up she's like this huge daki makura
um
she's so huggable
[Music]
she's my angel
I just stupid baby doll
she's like she keeps on running away
from things that she knows she wants
like today I had this this um
fight with her
in the morning
recently chonkers has finally started
demanding that she also gets something
special for breakfast because smoothie
gets wet food every morning and tonkers
never showed interest in it she just was
always fine with just eating the the
Kibbles every morning or all day
um but recently she has been demanding
something as well she's like meow meow
meow and I'm like okay what what now
usually you were always fine so I
started giving her treat those every
morning
not not everyone but like I I tried
every quite often recently because she's
very very demanding now suddenly
yeah and so I gave her these these like
these long sticks that are like salami
sticks thin sticks
they're pretty soft
um I gave her like one stick of that
and I I took I like
um
um rip off those pieces and make it into
small pieces and then give those snacks
to her yeah so
she she does kind of eat it out of my
hand but sometimes she gets so weird
about it she'll like uh take it out of
my hand with her mouth and then go away
two meters to a different place and eat
it there but like dropping it out of her
mouth dropping it on the floor which
usually has cat hair on it and then she
tries to pick it up again but she's too
stupid to pick it up again with her
mouth so she well while trying to catch
it with her mouth she keeps on rolling
it over the floor and the more she rolls
it around the floor the more like dust
and dirt and Cat hairs
gets stuck on the on the tree but she
doesn't care she still eats it like
eventually eventually she finally makes
it and eats it and then she then she
comes back to my hand does the same
thing again
if she doesn't eat it out of my hand
completely sometimes she does that too
she always like switches sometimes she's
like I don't trust you I'm gonna eat it
two meters away from you I'm gonna come
back to get the next one and sometimes
she just eats it directly
so anyway
it's really not much it's really a small
snack and she can easily eat that and
she obviously wants it because she gets
really crazy about it
um but today
she left two tiny pieces in my hand and
ran away and she was like I'm done and
I'm like you're not done I know you're
not done I know you want more so I ran
after her and I chased her around the
apartment she was like
she kept on running away from me and
hiding and I was like eat this eat this
now you left it over I know you wanted
you begged for it and now you leave
leave two pieces I know you want it so I
I chased her around the apartment for a
while and eventually she finally
[Music]
aided when I just placed it on the floor
and and she thought about it for a
moment and she was like ah oh snacks
and then she immediately ate it
not like she has a problem with my hand
though because often she eats it out of
my hand and she loves me okay
so weird about some things
and she loves being chased and like
she has to be proven about certain
things that she wants them
such a weird girl
she's she's so weird
instead of eating it out of my clean
hands she will just carry it around and
eat it from the floor and like rolling
around the floor with her tongue
what a freaking weirdo
so silly yeah
[Music]
so silly she does that a lot
Chase is like she lets me Chase her
around the apartment alone
[Music]
six hours now but oopsie
we're done we're done we're done Quinn
mile thank you for the Super Chat
thank you sir and thank you for enjoying
Sparks my throat hurts so much right now
I wanna stop talking please
thank you thank you you saw me a miracle
Orlando
oh thank you Captain it really hurts I
need to go I love your background thank
you credits to Eden he did a great job I
need to go not easy thank you I'll see
you tomorrow for Wario wear
[Music]
coconut oil
I don't know
and in Germany doesn't bye bye love you
[Music]
us moving
she's meowing you don't hear it
bit me
[Music]
hi
baby yes I'm done I'm done
I'm done
you heard it
hey baby oh yeah
a baby
[Music]
thank you